Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
Flourish in Time
Episode 18
Study for Family Peace
Class will be over in five minutes.
Class 10, Grade 1
It’s the last five minutes
for our class.
Next semester,
you’ll go to different classes.
Some will be in the same class,
while others
will go to new classes.
I’ll remember every one of you,
for you’re the first students of mine.
I hope you can remember
the classmates around you.
Remember Class 10, Grade 1.
Because we used to be together.
Yes!
Okay.
Dismiss.
I don’t want to leave you.
I don’t want to leave you, either.
Stop.
Don’t be sentimental.
It’s fine.
We can still meet. Right?
Ziye.
You are my best friend.
I know.
In the vacation, let’s hold
a farewell ceremony for Ziye.
No. Don’t.
I told you. Don’t make it sentimental.
You don’t know.
It’s great for me
to get away from you.
I can finally take a breath.
No need to explain your questions.
No annoying clubs.
No need to play basketball with you.
No need to listen
to your childish ideas.
No need to think of bad ideas
in the stadium.
I’m a quasi-genius, alright?
How could I fool around with you guys
this year?
What do you mean by fooling around?
The senior excluded.
It’s my honor
to know you.
In my first year, I really had
a great time.
We’ll be friends of a lifetime.
Don’t ignore me
for I study science.
We won’t.
I’ll still chat with you about gossips.
Stupid.
Have we arrived?
Yes.
Have a look for me.
How many subjects did I fail?
Two.
Where?
Here.
I’m doomed.
Half as many students
chose liberal arts as before,
but my place is even lower than before.
If my mom knows this...
How many subjects did you fail?
My name isn’t on it.
I can’t
let my dad know about this.
Shi Che.
Your dad called you to his office.
“Wind blows above the cold Yishui Water.
Hero...”
Good luck.
Son.
In the high school, I can obviously feel
that you’ve made great progress.
Feelings may not be true.
In junior high school, you said
you wanted to be an athlete.
I said it even in primary school.
Yeah.
You said it in primary school.
But you know,
in our country,
the growth of athletes are different
from ordinary people.
You’re already a sophomore.
You’ll soon prepare for gaokao.
You should have a goal in mind.
Your mom and I prepared you these files
about medicine,
politics and laws.
I have a goal.
I’ll go to a sports university.
My dream is basketball.
Even if I can’t be a player,
I’ll do a relevant job.
Son.
Your hobby
isn’t necessarily to be your job.
A hobby
will change.
Yes,
sometimes, adolescents are stubborn.
What’s your dream when you were little?
I grew up
in the countryside.
I knew little about the outside world.
I admired my teacher the most.
So I dreamed to be a teacher.
Mom has told me your stories.
I know you can understand me.
Son.
I know you all the time.
But this test...
The test is no big deal.
I just need to be top 500 in the grade.
Top 500?
That’s not even enough
for a sports university.
This is a top university.
Which place should I be?
Liberal arts.
Top 200.
Then I’ll get into
the top 200 in liberal arts.
Okay.
If you fail,
listen to your mom
and study these files.
Okay. What if I succeed?
Then I’ll
write my name “Shi” reversely.
Okay. Deal.
Don’t go back on your word.
Deal.
No change.
A big bundle was 2 yuan.
Now a small bundle is 2.2 yuan.
We can buy other vegetables.
Other vegetables are expensive, too.
And even more expensive.
All vegetables are expensive.
We also have to support that Jiang Yi.
Alright.
I know you work hard every day.
I’ll cook dinner
tonight.
I’ll take a business call.
Sister.
Lin.
How is it?
You asked me to find you a job.
The employer replied.
He’s very satisfied with you.
Really?
He’d like to meet you.
That’s great.
Great.
He’d like to know
if you are good at WeChat business
and new media.
It’s all about online work,
e-commerce, official account business.
Those are very popular.
So, he wants someone
who knows traditional marketing
and also new media technology.
Can you do it?
I...
I’ll learn about it.
Okay. Thanks.
Yes.
Mr. Wen.
Please go ahead.
Okay.
Work is the most important.
I’ll go however busy I am.
Okay.
Okay. Mr. Wen.
Goodbye.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
What’s it?
A parents’ meeting tomorrow?
No.
He wants to talk with us
about Miao’s major option.
I need to go to school tomorrow.
Major option?
I’ll go for this.
Someone wise should go.
Won’t you work tomorrow?
Children’s future is the top priority.
You are good.
I’ll explain it to my client.
See the teacher tomorrow...
Have some tea.
Thanks.
Sit.
Thanks for taking care of Lu Miao.
You’re welcome. My job.
I suppose you know her result
in this test.
What test?
Assessment test.
Haven’t you signed on it?
Those things happen again.
Sorry.
Please wait for a moment. Alright?
Sure.
No.
Mrs. Lu. Hold on.
How to solve this question?
Are you studying for TOEFL?
It won’t be in the recommendation.
Help me with this question.
It’s the senior year.
How can you be so idle?
So can you.
I can’t.
The National Chemistry Olympiad
is coming.
I didn’t make it to the final last year,
thanks to you.
Don’t worry.
I choose physics this year.
That won’t make any difference.
I must at least get into final.
Only the top 20 of Gold Prize
can be nominated.
Why do you want to be nominated?
My family are all first places
in competitions
and nominated into college.
I got the second place.
I’ve broken one family tradition.
I can’t break another, can I?
Here.
“2” is missing.
Aunt Fang.
NBA season is about to begin.
My battle report
records the birth of kings.
I know.
This is the same as
Ziye’s analysis book.
Yes.
What is it to do with her?
They even speak
in the same way.
“What is it to do with her?”
Well.
I’m gonna buy snacks. What do you want?
Chocolate.
Chocolate?
You don’t eat.
I want the big ones.
- Big ones?
- Hazelnut flavor.
Lu Miao!
Come here!
Mom…
What brings you here?
Come here!
Mrs. Lu.
Wait here!
No wonder Lu Miao is good at sports.
She runs every day.
Stop looking. Go to study.
Lu Miao always surprises me.
We all have tough parents.
Mom. Stop chasing me!
Stop there!
I can’t.
Next time...!
My shoes!
You!
Stop there!
Mom, stop chasing!
Can’t I catch up with you?
Help!
You!
Look at you!
Are you even so bad
at imitating my signature?
That’s the best I can do!
How dare you...?
Auntie. So many people here.
It’s not appropriate, is it?
Go home after school.
I’ll cook roasted pork
with bamboo shoots for you.
Be sure to take her home.
I finally got away with it.
Got away with it?
I doubt it.
Just a summer vacation.
Did you forget so quickly?
I didn’t have time to review
for the sudden test.
That’s just a test.
Why are you so serious?
Grade 2 is very important.
Teachers will speak fast
and won’t repeat.
Take it to heart.
I swear
I’ll work hard.
How?
Do more exercises.
You need to learn tactics.
Let me ask you.
What’s the universal formula
of dislocation subtraction?
Sn plus a...
Wait for me after school.
I’ll teach you again.
No need.
You can teach me
before the monthly exam.
My priority now
is how to survive from my mom.
Jiang.
When you get home,
you must say something good
to my mom.
I know.
What would you like for dinner?
My treat.
Before your mom left,
she said she’d cook pork for you.
Don’t forget that.
Perfume
Hello.
This is our latest color.
Come in and have a look.
Is there a discount today?
Yes.
Hello, have a look inside.
Are you Mrs. Lin?
Yes.
Hello.
We’ve reviewed your resume.
We don’t think the job suits you.
Hope you can find a right job.
Okay. I’m hanging up.
Hello. Do you have children?
Learn about it.
Famous Teachers Tutoring
Hello.
I got your flyer.
I’d like to consult.
Okay. I’m arriving soon.
You’re back so early.
Why don’t you turn the lights on?
What’s wrong?
What is it?
Where is the money in this card?
I spent it.
Spent on what?
What did you buy?
Furniture.
Where is it?
Is this what you bought?
Is this newly bought?
Well, the rent.
The water and electricity bills
this month.
These were all paid by me.
Well.
The car was broken down.
Go on.
Keep lying.
I didn’t lie.
Look, the daily necessities
all cost money.
No money is left every month
in the salary card.
Miao is a sophomore now.
In another year, she’ll be a senior
and have gaokao.
Aren’t you anxious?
I went to school today.
The teacher suggested her
to have cram classes.
Yes. Cram classes are costly,
but we must spend money on them.
It concerns her future.
I didn’t know it until I went to pay.
Where is the money?
She’s just a sophomore.
Why bother to have cram classes?
She’s already pressured.
That won’t help.
Don’t make a fuss.
You always follow suit.
Jiang is already a senior.
Has he ever had cram classes?
If she was half as good as him,
I wouldn’t be so worried!
Don’t say these useless things.
Where is the money?
You won.
I won’t talk.
You keep silent again.
Why are you silent?
Tell me.
If I talk,
you’ll argue with me.
How can I talk?
Fine. I’ll stop.
Go ahead.
Tell me. Where is the money?
How come you’ve changed like this?
You must have menopause in advance.
Have I changed?
How have I changed?
Are you loathing me?
Because I’m worried about her study!
Dad.
How could you say that?
You’re gonna make mom cry.
I don’t do well at study.
You shouldn’t waste money
on cram classes.
Please stop arguing.
I don’t need that.
No. You are a sophomore now.
What to do
if you fail in gaokao?
You must have cram classes.
Listen, Lu Yongfei.
She must have the classes!
It’s not about you.
Go to do your homework.
Go ahead.
Leave us alone.
Lu Yongfei.
Explain it.
How did you spend her tuition?
She doesn’t need cram classes now.
Why?
That’s useless.
Is it useless
or you can’t afford the tuition?
Money again.
I’ll get the money. Okay?
Is it helpful for her study?
Is she happy?
Fine. You’ll get the money.
Jiang.
You left something here.
I’m gonna bring it to you.
Should I put in a good word for you?
Don’t.
No need.
What’s going on?
Did your mom scold you?
Did I push you? How did I push you?
No.
Tell me! Did I push you?
Let’s talk in school tomorrow.
Good night.
Miao. Would you go
for the basketball game?
No.
I’m going to the reading room.
Why are you going there?
To study with Jiang Haoyue.
Hey.
Where are you going?
I’m going to study.
Go to practice alone.
Hey, are you going to study?
Are you mad?
Are you ditching me for a girl?
Am I?
Yes, you are.
I promised my dad
to get in top 200 in this monthly exam.
What?
Top 200?
Do you know your place
in the last exam?
What is it?
567th place.
You should pray
for getting into top 500.
Do you want to get in top 200?
Am I that bad?
You’ve always been that bad.
At a glance of your ranking,
I’ll know how many students
there are in the grade.
One more reason to study.
Sit.
Your goal is way too high.
Moreover,
will Jiang Haoyue help you?
In quantum mechanics,
the particles that make up matter
are the wave function.
Wave function is negative.
What brings you here?
Study.
There are many empty seats.
Yes, there are many.
I mean you can take another seat.
What on earth are you doing here?
I really come to study.
The modulus of a complex number
may not be a positive real number.
Why?
Aren’t they all positive real numbers?
Do you want me to help you?
Do you want to study as well?
Yes, this monthly exam
is very important to me.
I made a deal with my dad.
If I get into top 200 in liberal arts,
he’ll no longer stop me
from learning sports.
I can help you.
But finish these papers of six subjects.
Give them to me tomorrow.
Six subjects one night?
Are you kidding me?
Even an exam takes two days.
One night?
Impossible.
Don’t come to me until you finish.
Wait and see.
These are my papers!
I had time today
and checked the banking transfers.
In last April,
there was an expense of 30,000.
If I remember correctly,
Jiang Haoyue’s artificial leg
was replaced in last April. Right?
You checked my banking transfers.
Will you check my phone records later?
It depends on how many secrets you have.
Lu Yongfei, since I married you,
we’ve been living a peaceful life.
Since we had Miao,
I’ve been frugal,
giving all the best things
to you two.
For so many years,
I seldom buy new clothes.
Have you noticed it?
I shared the burden with you,
didn’t I?
Okay.
Since Jiang Haoyue’s incident,
I’ve never complained.
We’ve been
facing everything together,
haven’t we?
Am I selfish?
Okay. From now on,
I’ll be a selfish person.
Let me ask you, Lu Yongfei.
Had it not been
for Jiang Haoyue’s incident,
Miao
would have had more care from us
and our life would’ve been better.
Had it not been
for Jiang Haoyue’s incident,
I wouldn’t have had to work so hard
and bear
so much pressure
and Miao could
have had better cram classes!
Her study wouldn’t have been so poor!
I’m wondering,
you spent all the money
on others’ child.
Isn’t Miao your daughter?
Money!
Money again!
We can make money!
We have jobs, don’t we?
I lost my job long ago.
Sorry.
I don’t know.
Don’t touch me!
You’ve never been with me at all.
You’ve never seen what I did.
I am selfish!
I should leave you!
Fine.
Yes, I promised you.
We’ll look after Jiang Haoyue until 18.
Then I won’t pay a penny for him!
We’ll divorce!
Mom.
Wenfang.
What to do?
Your dad is ill.
Come here now!
Why are you here at this hour?
I don’t want to go home.
My parents are quarrelling.
Would you want some?
I bought two.
Is it good?
Hurry and eat up.
It’s cold here.
Don’t catch a cold.
It’s my fault.
They quarreled
because I don’t study well.
If I had worked harder,
mom wouldn’t have been worried.
Jiang Haoyue.
I must get into top 100 this time.
I’ll help you.
Dad.
You are back.
Where is mom?
Your grandpa is ill.
She needs to look after him.
What disease? Is it serious?
Your mom is looking after him.
He’s supposed to be fine.
During this period,
only you and I will be at home.
Dad, haven’t you had dinner?
No, I’m not hungry.
It’s sweet.
We can talk.
Math
Six subjects.
All here.
No need to write the composition.
Why didn’t you tell me earlier?
It took me hours.
Never mind.
See you at the self-study class.
Three of six subjects are failed.
The composition is good, though.
Of course.
I’m good at it.
Stop bragging.
Keep your word.
One hour at noon break.
One hour before evening classes.
But I’ll only explain for you once.
Stop pretending.
Only once?
Isn’t it enough?
Right. You are not that smart.
You must be kidding.
If I get serious,
I won’t need your help.
If you get serious,
that’ll be really terrifying.
How many times do you explain to her?
Until she understands.
Meng.
You hear that?
He looks down on you
that you can’t understand once.
Anyway, we, the two underachievers,
count on you in study.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Fail.
You failed.
You didn’t write your name.
You both failed.
Suddenly so serious.
Are they turning over a new leaf?
They are forced by life.
Does it result in
alternating day and night
or alternating seasons?
Are you listening?
Why did you hit me?
This monthly exam was hard,
yet some students’ results
really amazed me.
Feng Kaiqiang rose from 450th to 300th.
Next student also made great progress.
I’m surprised.
It’s
Xiang Weiyao
who rose to 220th place.
Another surprise.
Shi Che rose from 578th place
to 189th place.
He made the biggest progress
in the grade.
At last, we had another classmate
in the top 50.
Lu Miao, the 43rd place.
Great job.
I broke the record!
43rd!
In the pH=1 solution
which contains magnesium ion,
ferrous ion and chloride ion,
the possible anions are...
Many students will choose A.
We’ve got the results!
Because they ignored the stem,
or if ions can coexist
in large quantities...
Guess what my place is!
In the acidic solution.
It should be analyzed from two aspects.
On the one hand,
if the same group of ions
had metathesis reaction
and oxidation-reduction reaction.
On the other,
look at the color of the solution,
namely, the pH.
Well, turn to
page 27.
Analyze the stem.
I’m gonna ask you questions.
Is she so happy for being 43rd place?
It’s easy for underachievers to be happy.
I knew you were not made for basketball.
You aren’t gifted at it,
but you are gifted at study.
Stop.
You promised you wouldn’t interfere
if I got into top 200.
A man
should keep his word.
Gaokao wouldn’t be so easy.
Are you going back on your word?
It’s for your own good.
I’m considering for you.
I know.
I know it’s for me.
But this is my life.
It’s up to me to decide.
I know.
I have no talent for basketball.
But my love for basketball
is more than anyone.
I’ve honored my word.
Will you break your promise?
You chose this path.
You should be responsible for it.
Can I carry on my basketball dream?
You should go to a top sports college.
Don’t fall behind in study.
I know.
Mom.
Guess my place
in this monthly exam.
Sounds like you did well.
Very well.
Within 70th place?
43rd place.
Let me show you a photo.
Okay.
You made great progress.
It’s skyrocketing.
Mom. Are you happy?
Yes.
I can’t be happier.
When will you come back?
I miss you so much.
I miss you, too.
But I have to look after your grandpa.
Dad and I can go to see you
at weekend.
Miao.
If...
Would you like
to live with me?
Yes.
I mean,
with me alone.
I knew you’d be here.
Don’t expose my place.
Why are you hiding here?
Mom and dad only like you.
They don’t like me.
How so?
They praise you that
you are good at everything,
but I’m not good at anything.
They don’t like me.
But when you had a fever,
your mom ran three blocks
to buy chicken feet for you.
Uncle Lu also secretly
gives you pocket money.
Well.
Can you have bad grades in exams?
Don’t listen to teachers.
Try to offend them.
Run around after class.
Don’t be polite to adults.
Rest after dinner.
Don’t wash or dry your clothes yourself.
Don’t tidy up your room.
Don’t have dinner.
Buy snacks instead.
Do you want me to be like you?
Yes.
Do as I said.
Or I’ll hit you!
I won’t!
Will you?
You are so cute, like Congcong.
I won’t!
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪