Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
Flourish in Time
Episode 11
Shi Che’s Romance Theory
Jiang Haoyue.
I’m so jealous.
When can I get snacks, too?
Here you go.
I don’t want yours.
Maybe from some
adorable junior girls.
For me?
Please
take good care of Haoyue!
Am I your attendant?
Haoyue,
please take good care of yourself.
I’ll just have to throw them away.
Why?
Someone may get upset about it.
Who knows who that is?
What are you so excited about?
After the New Year’s Eve Party,
I’ve been getting more and more popular.
Really?
Congratulations.
I received a love letter today!
Who’s it from?
Some guy from the next class.
But don’t worry,
since we’ve signed the
No-Relationship-In-Highschool Contract,
I won’t respond to the letter.
Don’t read it.
It’s embarrassing.
What does it say?
Is it touchy-feely?
Dear Lu Miao...
Stop.
Stop reading.
It’s embarrassing for me.
I can get shy sometimes.
Dear Lu Miao,
at the New Year’s Eve Party,
I saw your back flip
and split on the stage.
I admire you so much.
My dream of childhood was
to become an outstanding acrobat.
I wonder
if I’m honored enough
to be your apprentice.
Hopefully you can help me
to realize my dream.
Sincerely yours.
What a genuine letter.
I think you should say yes.
Stop kidding.
How come Su Daifei hasn’t
come to you that often lately?
We haven’t been in touch
since the party.
We weren’t close anyway.
Not only Su Daifei,
there are less girls sending you gifts.
That’s odd.
Even I’ve become more popular,
how come you’re going backwards?
Unlike someone,
I don’t accept other’s love letter
after signing the contract.
This is not a love letter.
It’s a letter asking me
to be his teacher.
Then who was it that bragged
about receiving a love letter?
It’s my first time receiving
this kind of thing.
Can’t I just be excited?
Plus,
signing the contract means
that I won’t be in a relationship
with anybody.
What?
Really?
I do have
the spirit of contract, okay?
I hope so.
How dare you force Meng
to sign the stupid contract!
What’s the matter?
Do we have a problem?
Kind of.
If so, just tell me.
Can you stop getting in the way
of me and her?
Are you sure
that I’m getting in your way?
Isn’t that the case?
Since I know Lu Miao,
you’ve been placing obstacles for us.
From the Drum Battle,
to bike riding,
and then to the New Year’s Eve Party.
As a senior student,
why do you always pick on me?
Do you...
like Lu Miao as well?
I’m her brother.
You’re not blood-related.
Even if you are her brother,
don’t try to make everything
your own business.
Why did you sigh?
I didn’t expect Su Daifei to be the one
who ruined our performance.
My fantasy about her has been ruined.
That’s right.
Guoguo, how can I
be depressed about
meeting a strong opponent?
That doesn’t sound like what I mean.
When I asked Jiang Haoyue
if he liked Lu Miao,
I found his face expression weird.
I think,
Jiang Haoyue must have
some feelings for her.
But probably he haven’t
thought it through.
Since he’s not clear about it,
I should seize the chance
to stop it from happening.
Che, did you listen
to me carefully at all?
I have to go back and make a plan.
Thank you for your advice.
I’m paying again.
How much is it over there?
78 yuan.
One cup of milky green tea.
I can’t be fooled
by her appearance anymore.
Wait, no.
Extra sugar. Extra pearls,
coconut jelly,
mashed taro and puddings.
These many ingredients
can make you full.
Why do you care?
She’s indeed an evil woman.
I want a cup of milky green tea,
without milk.
What’s with all this trouble?
Why don’t you just order
a cup of green tea?
Alright, I’ll just have
a cup of green tea.
Okay.
Here’s your tea.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Aren’t you afraid of getting cut?
Hello, can I have two bowls
of porridge, please?
We only have the last bowl.
It’s alright.
We can share it using two spoons.
Sure.
What a coincidence, Meng.
Morning, Miao.
Morning.
Morning, Scholar-tyrant.
You are having porridge.
I’ll have the same.
The staff said that it’s
the last bowl here.
Why don’t you have something else?
I don’t want soybean milk
and fried bread stick.
How about...
I share the porridge with my brother.
You share it?
What’s wrong?
This is the last bowl.
Meng,
you need to be clear
that you are siblings.
Your spoons stirring
in the porridge together
is inappropriate.
I’m thinking for your sake.
The school’s been very strict
with students having a relationship.
What if other students see you two?
It’s easy for those
who don’t know the situation
to misunderstand.
Meng doesn’t know it.
Haoyue,
as the elder brother,
you should know it, right?
It’s fine.
I’ll get another bowl
so we can split it.
You talk too much.
I didn’t quite understand
the geometry part in the class.
Can you help me? This question.
This one?
I’m cold.
It feels so warm here.
Meng, you are asking your brother
questions again?
Yeah, why are you here?
It’s getting cold.
I can only get warm by exercising.
I don’t have a brother.
The break is too short.
I’ll help you after we go back home.
Sure.
What’s wrong?
Why do you always focus
on me and my brother?
You two are so obvious out here.
Why didn’t you mention it before?
I didn’t notice his hidden intention
back then.
What?
Anyway,
you two should be more careful.
What’s up?
Shi Che
has been following me and my brother.
It’s so annoying.
He said something
about hidden attention.
Isn’t it annoying?
Hidden attention?
Lu Miao, you mean hidden intention?
Yeah.
But that’s not the point.
The point is
I don’t know why he’s
always following us.
He makes it look like we’ve done
something wrong.
Well,
since Shi Che thinks your
brother has hidden intention,
does that mean...
Lu Miao,
do you feel that lately your brother
doesn’t want to be your brother anymore?
That’s not for us to decide.
Since the first day
he showed up in my home,
he’s been my brother.
However,
Jiang Haoyue has been disapproving
of me to call him brother.
Why?
My ranking went down in the recent exam.
Do you think he’s shamed of my
terrible studying?
That must be it.
Well, I have to study harder.
You do have a strange logic.
Have you ever thought
that the reason
why Jiang Haoyue is like this,
is because he has feelings for you?
What?
That’s impossible.
We both signed the
No-Relationship-In-Highschool Contract.
A simple-minded girl like you
will never understand
Jiang Haoyue’s care and thought.
It’s true that
I don’t know him very well,
especially as we’re growing
older and older.
It’s just a random thought.
Don’t be so serious.
It makes me feel like I misspoke.
No, you didn’t.
It’s just what you said is true.
Though I grew up with Jiang Haoyue,
he always lives in his own world.
A world
which he never tells me about.
I don’t know it at all.
Actually, everybody has its own space.
Plus, there are a lot of times
that we don’t even see
through ourselves,
let alone others.
Alright, let’s go.
What are you thinking about?
I’m working on this question.
Come on.
You’ve done it many times.
Tell me,
what’s bothering you so much?
How should a brother
treat his sister?
There’s no gender difference
between brothers and sisters, I guess.
Well,
what is it like when you fall
for someone?
You’d want to kiss her.
What? You disagree?
There’s another solution
to that question.
Try to work it out.
Time Book
Jiang Haoyue made a cunning move
of secretly signing the
No-Relationship-In-Highschool Contract
with Meng.
It stops Meng from sensing my charm.
Che,
excuse me for being honest,
you’re basically helpless.
Guoguo,
don’t ever say unlucky words
like this anymore.
No, that’s not what I mean.
I mean,
what’s your next plan?
It can only be
using the advantage of the internet.
What do you mean?
I have a friend,
the girl he likes signed the
No-Relationship-In-Highschool Contract
with another guy.
What kind of situation is that?
Is the so-called “friend”
actually yourself?
What a pity.
The net friends are pretty good at this.
Say what you want, don’t be ambiguous.
What the contract really means is
they’ll be in a relationship
once they graduate.
This is a declaration of their love,
stupid!
However, there are ways to solve this.
What do you mean?
To see it from another angle,
she cannot date with anyone,
not only you.
If you don’t have a chance,
it’s the same for others.
This is a unique angle.
Yeah.
Please tell me more.
Find something that she’s interested in
and you’re good at
to leave her a favorable impression.
Let her see a different version of you.
But remember, in this contract,
time means possibility.
Good luck.
The thing which Meng’s interested in
and I’m also good at?
I got it.
Meng,
there is a new batch
of comic books in the store.
Do you want to go and check together?
I’ll skip that.
I promised my brother to study together.
Aren’t you tried of going back home
with him every day?
Occasionally reading comic books
won’t hold you from studying.
Let’s go.
The bookstore isn’t disappearing.
I’ll go with you next time.
When’s the next time?
We’ll see. Bye.
“Luxuriant reeds growing by the river,
the dew of the morning
hasn’t dried out.”
Is there anything wrong
with this sentence?
What happened to you?
I...
got distracted.
I want to have a popsicle.
Eat slowly.
It’s too cold. It may harm your stomach.
Don’t worry, I’ll enjoy it slowly.
What’s the matter?
What?
The popsicle got stuck on my lip.
Don’t panic. Don’t drag it.
It may break your lip.
Then what should I do?
Don’t move.
What are you doing?
The warm breath
can help accelerate
the popsicle’s melting.
What is it like when you fall
for someone?
You’d want to kiss her.
What’s wrong?
Don’t move.
Well,
the weather is too hot.
Do you want this?
Here.
What?
No.
Mr. Jiang...
Girls can’t eat too much cold food.
It’s just a small bite.
Save me the last bite, please.
You didn’t save me anything,
and it dropped on the ground.
Girls can’t eat cold food.
Whatever.
Mom.
I’m so tired.
What are you doing?
Why are you here?
You look so happy.
I came out after finishing
my homework.
I wasn’t playing all the time.
Let me buy you some snacks.
How about popsicles?
I happen to need something
to cheer me up.
Mom.
That’s okay.
Did you do anything bad?
No.
Then why don’t you want the popsicle?
I’m fine, really.
Congcong,
what should I do
when falling for someone?
Che, you need to relax to score.
Do you have anything on your mind?
My plan failed.
What plan?
At first, after my repeated emphasis,
Jiang Haoyue did start to care about
my relationship with Lu Miao.
However, my actions seemed
to have annoyed her.
She even started to hate me.
Maybe you acted too strongly.
It’s understandable.
Why not change a plan?
You’re right.
I can change my plan.
My opponent is too cunning.
How come I feel
that you’re the only one
who’s taking actions?
I’ve thought it through.
Since Jiang Haoyue won’t let
Lu Miao go to the bookstore,
I can borrow the comic books
and give them to her instead.
There’s no way for Jiang Haoyue
to know better than me
about comic books.
Good idea.
Let’s go to the bookstore now.
Play basketball first.
I won’t stop my dream
because of romance.
I’m very confident about it.
You are very wise.
Do you want
to take a look of the bookstore?
What did you say?
I said we’ve arrived at the bookstore,
do you want to go in there?
I heard new comic books have arrived.
I got it, you’re testing me.
I won’t fall for it.
What’s in your mind exactly?
I think you should combine exertion
and rest.
It’s fine if you don’t want to go.
It’s my fault. I was being suspicious.
I’d really love to read the comics.
Let’s go.
I’m going to read it now.
Are you going to do exercises here
or...?
I...
I’ll read with you.
Really?
I’ll choose for you.
This one!
This one suits straight-A students.
And
this one.
Its main character is very handsome,
just like you.
And,
this one,
it’s very exciting.
You’ll surely like it.
So which one should I start with?
Whichever you want.
Let’s read together.
I’ll start with this one.
Is it good?
Yeah, it’s good.
Isn’t this guy cool?
This one?
It’s so late.
What should I say to my parents?
Don’t worry.
I’ve messaged your parents,
saying that we studied outside tonight.
That’s my brother!
You’re very considerate.
Stop calling me brother.
Why?
Is it because
you think
I’m a shame?
No.
This appellation is limited.
We’re more than that.
We’re also schoolmates,
friends and neighbors.
Anyway, just don’t call me that anymore.
Then
can I call you
Haohao?
Just Jiang would be fine.
Haohao!
Whatever you want.
How about I call you Mr. Jiang?
Well, Mr. Jiang,
I’m really cold now.
Can we hurry to go back home?
You’re cold?
Let’s go.
Open
Mr. Hao,
did you just say Lu Miao
and Jiang Haoyue
stayed here late
to read comic books?
Yeah.
Are you sure it was Jiang Haoyue?
That’s impossible.
Jiang Haoyue wouldn’t come here.
Plus, you don’t know him.
Mr. Hao,
you’re lying.
Here, see for yourself.
Jiang Haoyue...
Shi Che, cheer up.
You won’t lose.
Negative Score, what are you doing here?
Chlorophyll?
What books are you reading here?
Why do you care?
There’s a bug.
Where?
Miss Astrology?
With the Academy of Astrology
as the background,
start the love stories
between Miss Astrology
and twelve charming boys
in their time of youth.
You don’t say.
Some people look pretty serious
but secretly read
romantic novels like this.
I didn’t know you were so hypocritical.
What?
You don’t want others to know?
Just say,
“Shi Che is the most handsome
in the universe.”
Then I’ll keep the secret for you.
I’ve never seen anyone as cheeky as you.
Our Study Representative Xie Ziye
loves romantic novels.
Shi Che is the most handsome
in the universe!
Don’t worry, I won’t tell anyone.
Anyway,
“twelve charming boys”,
isn’t it too much for you?
What do you know?
They represent twelve constellations.
It’s related to astrology,
not just some romantic novel.
What’s...
What’s astrology?
It’s analyzing constellations!
It can not only help you
to better understand yourself,
but also help you to know others better.
It can also tell if you match
with other people.
Isn’t it like fortune-telling?
It’s a science of probability
and psychology.
Then, it’s fortune-telling.
Thank you.
It’s for you.
The Most Accurate Constellation
Matching Guide?
Can I refuse to take it?
No.
This is the winter-vacation gift,
the terminal gift,
the Spring Festival gift as well as
the New Year’s Day gift
which was chosen carefully by me.
Sorry for the things earlier.
See it as a compensation.
Chosen carefully for me?
How come I think it’s a book
you finished but
were not very satisfied with?
That’s not true.
I carefully prepared it for you.
You must finish it.
If...
you’d like to return me anything,
a piece of chocolate
with a card
would be fine with me.
I knew it.
You just want my chocolate.
Why would I want you chocolate?
There’s no need for that.
Here’s five yuan.
Buy one yourself.
Sure.
I’m an Aries.
Don’t forget to check
my constellation matching.
He took my money.
The one and only personality code
implies the essence of love.
Madam, you forgot to take off the label.
Do you need me to cut it for you?
I’m good.
I’ll do it myself.
Alright.
Thank you.
I have to return it.
It’d be a trouble if I cut it.
Hello.
Have a seat.
Okay, right,
here’s my resume.
It has all my working experiences on it.
Your resume says that
you have seven years
of sales experience?
Yeah, I’m very familiar with sales.
I was also the top salesperson.
I was also one of the best
regional salespersons.
What’s more...
I can see it.
Can you drink?
How much can you drink?
How do I say?
As
for beer,
maybe just a little.
What about...
Can you sing?
Your company requires singing skill?
Of course.
As a sales representative,
you have to sing after drinking
to warm up the atmosphere.
Plus, your job must be
very busy.
How come you have
extra energy to have
a part-time job here?
I’m just very energetic
and always keep myself busy.
I can practice singing.
I’ve gathered your
basic information.
Well,
we’ll get in touch with you soon.
Alright.
About singing,
I am good at some songs.
Alright.
See you.
Bye.
Goodbye.
Okay, bye.
Resume
Miao,
both your dad and I are
working late tonight.
So, just warm up the food as dinner.
It’s in the fridge.
You only need to warm it up.
I got it.
Remember to wash the dishes
after you’re done.
I don’t want to wash them when
I get home in the late night.
Don’t worry, Mom.
Am I a kid with no self-management?
Alright, that’s all.
Bye-bye.
My time has finally come!
I’m going to watch television.
I’m coming!
Coming now.
Coming!
I thought you were working late. Why...
It’s you.
Why didn’t you tell me?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Don’t we at least have
some basic sense of trust?
Am I a person with no self-control?
The back of the TV is wet.
Don’t forget to hang up the towel.
Let me check your quiz.
I can never escape from
the fate of being supervised.
When did you start matching?
No.
It’s a book from Shi Che.
She Che said he’s an Aries.
Let me see.
Here.
It does sound like him.
Let me see your star sign, Scorpio.
This book is pretty comprehensive.
It contains constellation matching…
and the couple compatibility scale.
Go hang up the towel.
Alright.
You’re so nagging.
Sagittarius VS Aries -98%
Sagittarius VS Scorpio 99%
What’s with your Politics quiz?
I didn’t know the answers.
Then why are you reading
this kind of book?
Figure out the answers first.
How come you could be my elder brother
just because you’re older?
Or what?
I’m not convinced.
Let’s have a competition.
Whoever wins is the elder brother.
You want to be my elder brother?
No.
If I win, I’m your elder sister.
Do you dare?
Sure. What’s the competition about?
I’m not gonna bully you.
How about
cat’s cradle?
Well?
Okay.
Have you played this before?
Then why are you so good at it?
Isn’t the game
a formation of point, line and plane?
You can solve it as long
as you know the theory.
That simple?
Yes.
Teach me.
Brother.
Alright, Sister.
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪