Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
Flourish in Time
Episode 12
Change the Fate,
the Light of the Moon!
Let’s go home together after school
You go first, I’ll wait for my brother
Guoguo,
do you know your zodiac sign?
I do.
Leo.
What?
You’re a Leo?
I’m an Aries
Meng
is a Sagittarius.
The three of us are fire signs.
Since when did you
start studying horoscope?
This is what girls do.
This is knowledge,
which every man
or woman can learn.
What’s your purpose, then?
You study it so
you won’t fail in exams?
Sure. I’ve done fortune-telling.
Fortune favors me in February.
So I won’t fail in exams.
Why hasn’t she replied?
Did she read the
book on horoscope?
Pass me the ball.
Come on.
Ready.
Nice.
Let me check the match
degree of me and Jiang.
Sagittarius VS Scorpio 99%
You need a miracle.
Your personalities,
the ways of thinking
and action are completely opposite.
These words
don’t sound like
a 99% match.
Is this a pirated book?
Why negative all of a sudden?
And the number is so large.
A perfect match?
Draw to each other like magnets?
-98%?
I’m sure it is a pirated book.
The pirated book is priced at 28?
It’s so easy to swindle Shi Che.
What...
what’s the matter with you?
Shi Che is so childish.
He gave me a book about horoscope
and scribbled on it.
How could he do this?
This is out of line.
Childish.
Come and sit at the table.
Dinner is about to be ready.
I tell you what,
I’m so addicted to
a novel recently...
The one I recommended to you?
Yeah.
Did you read the book?
What do you think?
I think you got swindled.
What?
That was a pirated book.
And it sells for 28 yuan?
Also, it’s so childish of you
to scribble on it.
Look.
Negative 98.
You know well
about your grades.
Sagittarius VS Scorpio 99%
Did you give the book to someone else
after I gave it to you?
Could it be Jiang Haoyue?
What are you talking about?
He wouldn’t do it.
He’s so dumb that
he’s talking gibberish.
Che,
at least you’ve learned the knowledge
about horoscope.
Don’t speak evil of him.
Right.
You!
Oh, Ziye,
what’s your zodiac sign?
Virgin.
Virgin?
I remember...
It’s true.
You and Che are a 100% match.
Look.
Aries VS Virgin 100%
This is a pirated book.
This is rubbish.
I wonder what Su Daifei’s is.
Su Daifei?
Why did you mention her?
Right, why would I?
Do you like her?
No, you...
Don’t slander me.
How can I like her?
Then why did you mention her?
I was thinking
she resembles my favorite idol.
Maybe she isn’t as bad as you think.
Right?
He’s questionable.
What is the meaning of this?
It means that you must curb yourself.
Since horoscope didn’t work,
I’ll have to confront him.
Sinister.
Sly.
Childish.
Did you change the figures in the book?
Yeah.
How about a fair and square competition?
Okay.
The teacher told me that
there will be a debate competition
this Saturday.
Anyone interested can
sign up for it.
I’m now going to write down
the statement of viewpoint
and group up a team
of the best debaters.
Are you interested?
No.
I figured.
You aren’t that eloquent anyway,
so let’s forget it.
What classes do we have
in the afternoon?
Chemistry, I think?
Excuse me.
There will be an event
at the comic bookstore this Saturday.
The prize is one of
the owner’s collections,
Naruto Manga collection
with Masashi Kishimoto’s signature on it.
Are you interested?
Signed by the author himself?
I must win it.
Right.
I know you the best.
Naruto is my favorite, too.
Listen,
I’ve got the best
costumes ready.
We’ll get the prize.
Sure.
Jiang, want to come along?
I’m not interested.
Why would you ask him?
He doesn’t read manga.
Plus, I’ve only prepared the costumes
for us two.
Can you tell me a little bit
about the costumes?
It’s a secret.
A secret.
I’ll go check the costumes.
Won’t you come along?
It’ll be fun.
Come on.
It’ll be awesome.
Not interested,
so no.
I don’t have time,
Doing exercises every day is so boring.
Qu Wei,
can I still sign up
for the debate competition?
What?
You changed your mind?
I want to do it.
The 10th Nanfeng Senior High-schooler
Debate Competition
Debate Competition Application Form
I’m Shi Che from Class 10, Grade 1
Email sent
Darn it,
this is so cool.
What is this?
The present for Meng.
Huh?
Are you sure?
Will Miao be okay with playing a fish?
What fish!
She’ll be a mermaid.
Take a good look.
A mermaid?
This is the most crucial part
of my plan.
We’ll be bound together
by the arrow of Cupid.
All right, enough.
Come on, let’s rehearse.
Take it.
Get closer to me.
Get closer.
Closer.
Stab me with the arrow.
The event will be my stage.
At the event,
Lu Miao and I
will make the best memory.
All right, you’re too heavy.
I can hardly breathe.
Alright, come on.
Help me take off the costume.
I’m so hot.
I don’t know what I’m going to wear.
I don’t know what Shi Che is up to.
Ughh!
He said he’d make elaborate
preparations, didn’t he?
But I still don’t know
what I’m going to wear.
I wonder if he is dependable.
Are you free tomorrow?
I’ve signed for this debate competition.
I don’t know if I can be selected.
You can debate?
Yeah.
I’m ETC.
What ETC?
Beep.
A natural debater.
Meng,
would you like to know how we are
going to surprise everybody
at the event?
I tell you what,
I’m a bit grumpy at the moment.
Say what you want to say.
I said it’s a surprise.
We’ll go there together
and at the event,
you’ll know what it is.
At the event?
Do you think you are
being funny right now?
Don’t worry.
Shi Che, Xie Ziye.
Follow me.
Congratulations, you two are selected
by the debate team of our school.
You’ll participate in the
municipal debate competition
tomorrow afternoon
on behalf of our school.
Him?
Me?
What?
What a surprise! Huh?
Is there a mistake?
I didn’t sign up for the debate.
Yeah, sir,
please check again.
Him? A debate competition?
Shi Che, don’t be a coward.
The professional debate instructor
found you.
Xie Ziye,
you’re the third debater.
Shi Che,
you’re the fourth.
You’ll be presenting the summary.
Practice it well.
Wait,
what’s happening?
Did you make a mistake?
I didn’t sign for a debate competition.
And I have something important to do
tomorrow afternoon.
What can be more important
than honoring our school?
Don’t try to chicken out.
Did you see how your
classmates looked at you?
I don’t care how you signed up,
since you’re selected,
you must go.
Practice hard.
Ridiculous.
Did you hear?
Unbelievable.
What’s wrong with him?
Why would he want to do this?
That’s it.
With Shi Che on the team.
we’ll definitely lose.
That’s it.
Without Shi Che,
I’ll lose.
Class 1, Grade 2
Have you heard that
Shi Che is on our
school debate team?
The thing is, the topic is
“Which is more important,
knowledge or ability?”
Shi Che chose
to be on the knowledge side.
Did you do it?
What?
Don’t act like you know nothing.
I went through the whole thing.
You asked for the link, right?
Did you do something to make
him selected into the debate team?
It seems I’m right.
Jiang Haoyue,
this is a master stratagem.
Since you’re so into inference,
why don’t you be a detective?
I kind of feel sorry for Shi Che.
I just can’t get over it.
Shi Che is such a jackass.
He promised to
help me win the signed manga.
Now he’s telling me he’s going to
this debate competition.
I believe in you.
You can do it on your own.
Right.
After all, that’s my stage.
I can help you
if you need.
Really?
You can’t get impatient, though.
I won’t.
You said you’d help me
research the costumes and roles.
Yet here you are, doing homework!
Let me finish my homework first.
Choose the costumes first.
Homework first.
Costumes first.
Cos...
Okay.
Well,
costumes first, then.
I knew it!
I’ve got several ideas.
Help me choose
the most original one.
This.
How about this?
Isn’t it original?
So short...
No.
It isn’t suitable for you.
Why?
You see,
the theme is originality and creativity.
This, obviously,
is to average.
True.
It feels like everybody would go
for this average anime style.
I’ll change another one.
This.
What about this?
It covers so little...
Is it special enough?
This is so odd.
I don’t think
many people would understand it.
Really?
I think it’s good.
You know nothing.
How about you try that one.
The last one.
This one?
This one...
Seems too conservative.
I think it’s quite nice.
And you can
cos-play a hit woman
of a mysterious organization in this.
You know, those who
use a piece of paper as an edgy knife.
A paper knife?
Good.
This one, then.
Che,
you’re wearing the costume.
I won’t have enough time. Quickly.
Can you ride a bike dressing like this?
I’ll be careful.
Thanks to you,
my bro.
My dad
naively wanted to stop me?
No way.
Uh, I suggest you think twice.
If the principal finds out,
not just you,
I’d also be...
Where are you going?
Dad, I’m in a rush.
I know you’re going to the
debate competition,
and you’re running out of time.
I’ll drive you there.
Come on, get in.
Bye-bye.
Time Book
Everybody has given their best.
Why are you here?
I’m here to accompany you.
But yesterday, you said you
got stuff to do.
That was yesterday.
I changed my plan.
Why didn’t you tell me earlier?
Come on, follow me.
Your clothes...
I’m not a participant.
It’s an anime-themed event.
You should at least have some sort
of anime element on you
or you can’t go in.
Well,
I’ll wait for you at the door.
No, you’re here already.
We’re open.
Wait a second.
Mr. Hao,
is there a way to
let him in?
There are some props in my storage room.
How about
you go and have a look?
Sure.
Thank you, Mr. Hao.
Quickly.
Dad!
At least let me change my clothes.
No time for it.
Make haste!
Get the arrow off you
right now.
This is very expensive.
And I spent a lot of time on it.
If you don’t,
I’ll rip your head off.
I will!
It’s me.
What a jester!
Morning, Principal.
Quickly.
Over there.
Look at his funny outfit.
He’s a weirdo.
Young man, you’re
sitting on the wrong side.
I chose ability.
Shi Che,
in the application form,
your statement says
you’re on the knowledge side.
My application form?
Yes, Shi Che.
Please find your own seat.
He’s so funny.
Is he a student from your school?
Good, Mr. Shi.
He’s pretty unique.
Who did this to me?
Was it you?
The competition begins.
The first debater
on the proposition side can start.
How do I
dress you up?
Make it simple.
But originality is also important.
I got it.
Do you need help?
No, I’m good.
Opposite direction.
Confucius traveled around states,
perfected his philosophies
through practice.
He dedicated his whole life to
embedding knowledge
in governing the state.
Zhan Tianyou pioneered
shaft excavation and
herringbone railway through practice.
Yuan Longping plowed farmlands,
had no fear for loneliness.
Having respect for practice,
he developed hybrid rice
and benefited mankind.
The knowledge of these sages
affects the world profoundly.
And all the knowledge
is the summary of their abilities.
When you are asked later,
stick to your argument,
don’t be led astray.
Don’t move,
I’ll draw your model number.
Don’t move.
Raise your arms.
Your hand.
Go,
T800.
In conclusion,
Debate Competition
the knowledge that you learn in school
is only useful in social practice.
Therefore, we firmly believe that
ability is more important
than knowledge.
We’ll try to defend.
If not, we attack.
Chlorophyll.
What?
Help me out here.
Finish it off.
What’s your opinion?
Are there any attack points?
Attack?
Attack what?
What a waste of time!
She makes perfect sense.
It isn’t a sports competition.
Why do you care so much?
Don’t mind him.
Let’s discuss.
Here.
What?
You’ll be making the summary.
Just read it out.
Okay. The fourth debater
of the proposition side,
please give your summary.
Friends of this debate,
why do we waste time?
Time is priceless.
Why do we talk so much
until this hour?
Why laughing at me?
It is you who kept
babbling about the school, right?
I don’t get it.
Do you think
all you can learn
in school is knowledge?
I’ll be honest with you,
My grades are poor,
I don’t really like studying.
I hate examinations the most.
But is all knowledge from the textbooks?
Absolutely not.
I don’t skip class anymore
and start to learn how to get along
with teachers and classmates,
and how to adapt to the collective life
because I’ve learned not
to escape,
and try to do what others cannot do.
From not doing my homework
to trying to turn in homework timely,
I’ve learned the importance of
execution and responsibility.
I joined the school team
because since little,
I knew that
the honor of the collective comes first.
This is the knowledge that I learned
from school,
and with the knowledge,
I give full play to my abilities.
What’s the point in this lengthy debate?
Sorry.
Passing through.
Let’s welcome T800.
This is original.
This is so cool.
So amazing.
So cool.
The exciting moment has come.
The best cos-player is...
Who do you think it is?
It should be him.
I want the signed manga so much.
T800!
Applause!
Let’s go.
We won!
This is your stage.
Thanks.
Come on.
Look at me.
I’m so happy.
It was fun.
And you’re talented in art.
I told you that
other than study,
I’m good at many stuff.
Shi Che?
Why are you wearing this?
I thought you went to the debate.
And you are the best debater.
Thanks to you!
Way to go.
I didn’t expect you to
have talent for debate.
Let me check the medal.
A debate?
Well, it was easy.
They were no match for me.
Look,
Jiang Haoyue won the best cos-player.
So we got the
signed manga.
What?
This ugly cos-play?
Were the judges blind?
I designed this.
A worthy winner!
An undoubtedly worthy winner!
Your costume, however,
is not that good.
You need two extra snake heads
to up your game.
Let’s go home.
We’re off, Shi Che. Bye-bye.
Best Cos-player
It’s always been you who taught me,
today, you came
and learned more about my hobby.
I’m really happy.
Your hobby itself is fun.
Since we were little,
you’ve always been the model.
You’re perfect in everything.
Although we live together,
the more we grow,
the less I know you.
I feel like we’re
distancing from one another.
Are we?
It’s not too late.
How about we take a walk?
The sea breeze makes me so comfortable.
It’s kind of chilly, though.
Put on my shirt.
Let me show you a picture.
This is the
all-sky image
taken by ESA’s
Planck telescope
on July 5, 2010.
It was synthesized with
120 images.
Look.
The oval
is the galaxy.
The net-like structure
is a system formed by the stars.
The growth of a star
promotes the development
of the entire system.
Like our solar system.
First, the sun,
then the earth,
the moon
and all the other planets.
So
a star is like
an ever-growing child.
It’s like...
As I grow up,
I have more and more friends.
You can say it that way.
But if you’re a star,
then...
You’re the moon.
The moon?
Yes.
Although you look icy,
you’re always the most shining thing
in the night sky.
Yes.
The moon is shiny
but it only reflects the sunlight.
I didn’t know you’re into this.
Don’t you think that
when you look up into the starry sky,
all your trouble goes away?
Do you have a lot of trouble?
We could see
the quadrantids meteor shower tonight,
but not in this weather,
I’m afraid.
Look, here it comes.
It’s so beautiful.
Miss!
You missed it!
Missed!
Miss!
Lu Miao, you’re disappointing.
You hang out with a cripple every day,
so you can’t control your hands.
Shut up! You wait and see!
I’ll hit it!
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
You hit it!
I told you I could!
Awesome!
You hit it!
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪