Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
Flourish in Time
Episode 16
Advancing “Enemy”
Doctor,
could you tell me,
if I could be physically better,
weight more,
and run faster…
I admire that, Jiang.
You adapt well to the artificial limb.
It won’t be hard for you.
You need professional
physical training.
Technically you can make it.
But if I’m right,
you’ve been wearing it for years.
To prevent possible harms,
I suggest you change
a more flexible one.
I see.
Thank you, doctor.
You’re welcome.
Linx Intelligent Bionic
Double-cylinder Knee-joint
What happened to them?
He went to the Draft with his friend.
His friend was out
and he was in.
That was
a friendship-killing test.
Guoguo must feel awkward.
I bet
he’d quit.
Well,
I’ll quit.
No!
Guoguo loves basketball.
He won’t join the school squad
at the price of a friend.
I won’t join the school squad
Well,
will Negative Score agree?
As childish as Che is,
he will.
Fine!
Wanna quit?
Beat me first.
Are you nuts?
Even my father won’t do that.
Show me what you have.
Wow…
That’s why they picked you.
Fight for a place in the squad.
Don’t let me down.
Che,
you brought me to the court.
You talk too much.
You serve.
Come on!
Seems Negative Score isn’t selfish.
Guoguo is his best friend, anyway.
But,
he must be heartbroken
for losing the draft,
though he didn’t complain.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
Class 10, Grade 1
Go home. The garden is nearly barren.
Myself have made my soul
serf to my body:
why have vain regrets and mourn alone?
Fret not over bygones
and the forward journey takes.
Alright. Thank you.
Shi Che.
What’s wrong?
You are the last one.
I’ve learned the past mistakes
can’t be redeemed.
But...
But the future is bright
for me to work on.
Go home. The garden is nearly barren.
Myself have made my soul
serf to my body:
why have vain regrets and mourn alone?
I’ve learned
the past mistakes can’t be...
Can’t be...
Can’t be redeemed.
There’s no way
for you to memorize it like this.
When reciting Classical Chinese,
you need to follow the logic.
What logic?
I think their words have no logic.
Do you know the meaning
of the sentence you recited?
How come you didn’t write
any notes down?
This sentence means
since the soul is dominated by body,
there’s no point of feeling
depressed and lonely.
What’s done in the past is done.
But your future is filled
with possibilities.
It means you haven’t gone astray too far.
Do you get it now?
Yes.
Repeat the meaning
of the sentence.
Well...
This sentence means
since you’ve met difficulties
playing basketball,
you should find a chance
to prove yourself?
What I said in the bookstore
is a little bit mean.
I apologize.
You
apologize to me?
Are you okay?
I just think people
who chase their dreams
deserve to be respected.
You finally know how excellent I am.
Alright.
Don’t be too proud
about a few compliments.
The new head teacher is annoying.
Why do we have to move to another floor?
I think it’s great.
I don’t want to stay in the first floor
for three whole hours.
It’s too heavy.
Excuse me.
Which floor are you moving to?
The second floor.
Let’s go.
What’s happening?
We are moving to the floor of Grade 2.
Let’s go upstairs together.
What are you doing?
I’m getting my things.
Lu Miao took them for you.
Let’s go.
Lu Miao?
Come on. She’s right there.
Did you hear?
Class one of Grade 2 moved
to the second floor.
I know.
But why?
We’re in the middle of this semester.
Why would they move all of a sudden?
For a simple reason.
They had a new head teacher.
A new teacher applying new measures.
He needs to do something
to prove himself.
They are the experimental class.
This semester is vital to them.
Besides.
Many students applied
for No.1 High School
just for their former head teacher, Mr. Chen.
I don’t know
why they changed to a new one.
I’m curious about this gossip.
Mr. Chen
is poached by the high school next to us.
A teacher got poached
by the rival high school.
Your father must be mad.
He’s so mad
that he doesn’t have time for me.
He makes countless calls every day.
He said he has to find
the key to defeat the other high school.
Collection of Guitar Solos
The new teacher must be very good.
I’m not sure.
But his does have a unique name.
What’s his name?
Di Ren.
Enemy?
That’s an aggressive name.
Where’s Guoguo?
Let’s go.
Sorry.
I’m sorry. Did I crumple your book?
It’s fine.
Even if you did, it’s okay.
I’ve already memorized it all.
This book is too easy.
Actually I...
Let’s go.
Actually, I’m good at playing guitar.
I can accompany for you.
Can you play guitar for me?
You heard it all.
Play for me, please?
Forget it. Let’s play basketball.
So humiliating.
Let’s go.
All rise.
Hello, teacher.
Hello, students.
Please sit down.
Is there anyone
in our class who’s been
absent from the gym class?
Sir.
Jiang Haoyue...
Are you sick?
No.
Great.
Then, starting from today,
you have to go to the gym class, too.
Alright.
Turn to the third chapter of the book.
Organic Compounds.
One and two
and three and four.
Two and two
Three and two and...
Jiang Haoyue.
Four and five...
Is he having the gym class?
Seven and eight...
Four and two and three and four.
Five and six and seven...
Let’s drop it.
Jiang Haoyue has never taken
the gym class before.
It was before.
If he’s absent from it again,
I’ll count it as truant.
My enemy.
Mr. Di is outrageous.
Why are you so mad?
Why isn’t Jiang Haoyue mad?
What’s the point of being mad?
If he really doesn’t care,
why doesn’t he insist on it?
If it’s me,
I’d definitely not take the class.
That’s what you think.
But it’s Jiang Haoyue.
He prefers to keep everything to himself.
No.
I have to fight for him.
What are you doing?
Writing to the principle.
Principal’s Office
Principle Shi.
You don’t say.
This student’s style of writing is good.
That is not the point.
I know.
The letter of complaint
says that I aimed at Jiang Haoyue.
Jiang Haoyue
is the seeded student
who’s hopeful to get into
Tsinghua and Peking Universities.
Surely
every teacher
has its own teaching method.
But I still hope that you can
make an exception for Jiang Haoyue.
After all,
his leg is a little inconvenient.
I’ve told you about this
when you first came.
Don’t worry, Principle. I got it.
I’d make exceptions for him
when it’s necessary.
Before I came here,
I consulted a doctor in the hospital.
The morning exercises, gym class,
and walking in the parade.
Jing Haoyue is capable of doing them all.
But the special treatments he got
have driven him away from the class.
I’m worrying
that his future
may be more difficult.
The grades of exams
are just outcomes received
in a period of time.
Making students
learn to find their positions in the class.
Teach them to work with other people
while working on themselves.
That’s the kind of education
that benefits them in long term.
I was right about you.
I’ll fully support your work
in the future.
How long?
Six seconds and seven.
No.
I have to make it in within six seconds.
How long have you practiced?
It’s been a while.
If you’ve started to practice
your physical agility privately.
Why would you refuse
to go to the gym class?
I want to improve my agility
to a certain level first.
I can’t let watch
me embarrassing myself.
That’s your concern.
Then why is it okay for me to watch you?
You’ve done more humiliating things.
I really
should change an artificial leg.
Our school is having a ports meeting.
Class 10, Grade 1
In the unit of class,
every class has to have a square array.
All members need to attend it.
So, starting from today,
we’d use the last self-studying class
to practice for the square array.
But don’t let it delay your studying.
Ziye, are you signing up for anything?
No.
- Ziye, let’s do it.
- No.
Everybody stands in their position
of the gym class.
Eleven students required in a line.
Four lines in total.
We have forty-five students, right?
There’s one missing.
Sir.
I didn’t count Jiang Haoyue in.
Where is he?
He’s in the classroom.
Get him here.
Go.
Okay.
Jiang Haoyue.
Mr. Di is asking you to go down
for the square array.
He said we can only start
once everybody is there.
There’s no need for that.
Alright.
What’s wrong with their class?
Are they being punished?
Left, right, left.
Halt.
Sir.
Jiang Haoyue said...
Said...
Don’t stutter.
Jiang Haoyue said there’s no need
to wait for him.
Go back.
Guys.
I know you’re clear
who we’re waiting for.
As long as he doesn’t come,
today’s school won’t be over.
Jiang Haoyue.
Come down.
Stop wasting our time.
Your grades are good
but we still have homework to do.
Hurry up and come down.
I need to go
to the tutoring class later.
Why doesn’t he come down?
Why do you aim at him?
Why do you think so?
As his head teacher,
don’t you know
his basic information?
I do.
Then why do you ask him to do all this?
So, in your opinion,
you think I need to make an exception
for Jiang Haoyue just
because of his disability?
No...
Mr. Di,
I don’t need a special treatment.
I apologize to you.
Why would you apologize?
Mr. Di.
Sorry.
The student in my class is naughty.
I’ll take her back to discipline her.
Alright.
Mr. Wen.
Lu Miao.
We’ll go first.
Jiang Haoyue...
Lu Miao.
What’s the matter with you?
I got distracted for one minute
and you went to meddle
other class’s business.
I’ll go in the line now.
Now, everybody’s here.
Let’s start the training.
Everyone. Dress right.
Eyes front.
Turn right.
Forward, march.
Left, right, left.
March on the stop.
Forward, march.
Left, right, left.
Turn left.
Upright.
Left, right, left.
Jiang Haoyue, follow up.
Pay attention to the rhythm.
Left, right, left.
Halt.
Turn left.
Dress right.
Eyes front.
At ease.
This time should be okay.
I’m really tired of it.
Jiang Haoyue is in our team.
There’s no way we can walk in line.
I think it’s good enough.
Jiang Haoyue.
Stand in the middle.
Sir.
It would look more in order
if Jiang Haoyue walks on the side.
I’m afraid he can’t catch up walking
in the middle.
The array would be look worse.
Then practice until you walk in order.
How can we practice more?
It’s impossible for us
to be in order anyway.
Now he’s standing in the middle.
If we could walk in order,
we’d be able to walk
in the Olympics opening ceremony.
Sir.
I want to stand in the middle, too.
Jiang Haoyue.
Stand next to Qu Wei.
Let’s have a rest first.
We’ll try later.
Thanks.
I’m good.
Drink some and take a break.
I’ll put it here.
It’s fine.
Meng. Are you still thinking about that?
Jiang Haoyue doesn’t know to fight back.
He only knows to tolerate.
What should we do?
Think about it backwards.
Maybe Jiang Haoyue’s way
of dealing it is more reasonable.
Your sticking up for him
may embarrass him instead.
Do you think he doesn’t need our help?
I don’t think so.
We aren’t happy about this thing, too.
Isn’t it? Che.
Yes.
So, I didn’t think too much.
We can’t indulge evil to foster.
Justice may be late,
but it always comes.
We have to teach them a lesson
for Jiang Haoyue.
Alright.
For Jiang Haoyue!
For justice!
Jiang Yi.
I can’t repay you.
I don’t have money.
Did you borrow money from others again?
It’s you.
What are you doing?
Jiang Yi.
Look at you now.
Fine.
I’m drunk.
I’m not sober.
I won’t remember
anything you say now.
Listen.
Haoyue is almost eighteen now.
His body has grown.
The current artificial leg
isn’t suitable for him anymore.
You have to take him to the factory
to get a new one.
Do you hear me?
What do you mean?
Do you want to get rid of him?
I’m telling you.
I don’t care if he’s eighteen now.
You have to be responsible
for my son the entire life.
Do you understand?
Don’t scream.
I’m begging you.
Don’t scream, alright?
Don’t scream.
I’m telling you.
I didn’t mean to get rid of him.
Jiang Haoyue...
Jiang Haoyue is my son, too.
Keep the receipt of the artificial leg.
I will
give you the money later.
You used to take him to buy new ones.
I’m not familiar with the factory.
Why would you let me take him?
Stop screaming.
Listen to me.
Haoyue probably
won’t let me take him.
I’ve written down
the model number on it.
Get the hydraulic one.
Take it.
Keep it. Don’t lose it.
Keep it well.
Don’t give me the money later.
Just give it to me now.
I don’t have money.
You know it.
I’ve got nothing in my pocket.
Promise me.
Only spend the money
on buying artificial leg.
I’m that kid’s father.
I’ll send you the password later.
Alright.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Why did you transfer me thirty thousand?
Don’t you need a new artificial leg?
I know there’s a hydraulic type.
Check it
and buy it later.
Where did you get the money?
It’s not your business.
Who did you borrow it from?
Is it an usurious loan?
Or did you borrow it from Uncle Lu?
What a bad luck!
Can’t believe it.
I won it.
Is that okay?
Listen.
Don’t ever be so stubborn again.
Are you gonna buy it?
Give back the money if you don’t.
No. 1 High School
It’s confirmed.
That’s Jiang Haoyue’s class.
They are having
the physical examination.
Where’s Jiang Haoyue?
He went to the playground
after the examination.
Now it’s the time.
Let’s hurry up.
Go!
Take the shoes.
They are coming.
Hurry. Let’s hide.
How’s your eye test?
My glasses are so thick.
I don’t think I’ll pass.
My left eye is only 0.2.
Where’s my other shoe?
Mine is gone, too.
Did someone took it wrong?
What happened?
Who is it?
Now you’ve suffered.
Who are you?
We are the Heroic Firearm Alliance.
You felt so bad just because
you lost your shoes.
Have you ever thought
about how you’d feel if one of your leg
is disabled?
Exactly.
Just think about it.
That’s right.
If you ever be sarcastic to Jiang Haoyue
again in the future,
you won’t just lose your shoes.
You’ll lose your socks, too.
Don’t tell them the detail.
It doesn’t sound scary anymore.
Alright.
We are only here to teach you a lesson.
So that you can remember us,
the Heroic Turkey Alliance.
It’s the Heroic Firearm Alliance.
We, the Heroic Firearm Alliance
will keep an eye on you.
Are you finished?
Give us back our shoes.
Let’s go.
Don’t run! Hey.
You’re finally back.
I was getting nervous.
It’s a pity that you missed it.
You have no idea how cool we were.
I designed that pose on purpose.
I wonder if they know who we are.
No way.
We used the magic in Naruto.
You are surprisingly positive.
What do you know?
Do you know magic?
Do you know the Sharingan?
You spit on me.
The Heroic Turkey Alliance.
I think,
they were Lu Miao, Shi Che
and Chen Guoguo.
It must be them.
Who else would be so stupid?
No. I have to inform
our teacher about this.
They have to be punished.
Alright.
Though they were dramatic.
Were they wrong?
Think about it.
The training of the square array
was to help unifying our class.
Jiang Haoyue has won
many honors for our class.
But it’s indeed hard for him
to walk in the array.
We probably need to
stand under the sun longer
and sweat more because of him.
But we are a team.
Shouldn’t we consider
for and care for every classmate?
If we aren’t united,
there’s no way for the square array
to be in order.
Hurry up.
Jiang Haoyue has probably started
his training now.
Why haven’t they come?
Go and take a rest.
Continue your training after they come.
I’m fine.
I came down to practice.
I don’t need a break.
I don’t need
to be taken care of, either.
I’m ready
anytime.
Alright.
Halt.
March on the stop. Go.
Left, right, left.
Left.
Keep up with the pace.
Align on all sides.
Left, right, left.
Show me your spirit.
Upright.
Left, right, left.
Jiang Haoyue needs us
to stick up for him.
Why is he looking at me all the time?
Did he find out what we did?
It’s fine if he did.
We did it for his sake.
Even though what we did wasn’t glorious.
I don’t want him to know.
What if he doesn’t appreciate it?
Then what I did
just pushed him even further.
Lu...
Did he have to chase me?
Wait.
Why did you run?
You chased me. So I ran.
How can you run so fast now?
A few days ago,
my father bought me
a new artificial leg.
A new one?
You...
Why have you been hiding me?
Didn’t you say you don’t want
to see me anymore?
Why would you think so?
I know you had a fight with my dad.
Sorry.
All these years,
I’ve been forcing you
to be friends with me.
I should apologize.
I was too emotional a few days ago.
I even said terrible things to Uncle Lu.
Then I let out my anger to you.
Then why did you say
I have a choice
but you don’t?
I didn’t mean it.
Can you forgive me?
Well...
Are we still friends?
Of course.
We were when we were little.
We are now.
We will in the future.
Be careful.
It hurts.
What’s wrong?
I seemed to sprain my ankle.
Let me carry you on my back.
It’s okay. I’m very heavy.
Don’t worry. I won’t hurt you.
That’s not what I worry about.
Come on.
Are you tired?
No.
You should put me down.
I can walk myself.
I said I’m not tired.
You don’t want to talk to me?
Why not?
Mom.
Why doesn’t Jiang Haoyue want
to talk to me?
He doesn’t know you well.
Would you talk to someone
who you don’t know passionately?
So.
Try to find out what he’s interested in.
I got it now.
You know nothing.
Silly girl.
Do you want to buy Haoyue a present?
The Hardy Tin Soldier
Mom, I want this.
Mom will come to see you soon.
My dear son, does it hurt?
It doesn’t hurt. I’m okay.
Then take good care of yourself.
I’ll go back to work now.
Well? Haoyue.
How do you feel today?
Let me read you a story.
Long long ago.
A man used a tin spoon
to cast 25 tiny tin soldiers.
When it come to the last one,
he ran out of tin.
So the tin soldier only has one leg.
Even so.
he still stands firmly with one leg
just as the other soldiers.
Miao.
Let Haoyue read it himself.
Come and help me.
Alright.
Smell if it’s good.
It’s surely cooked by father.
The sea sedge is cooked by you.
All cooked by your father.
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪