Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
Flourish in Time
Episode 15
The Battle of the Sun and the Moon
Are you all packed?
We’ll leave as soon as
your father finishes the procedure.
Where is Jiang Haoyue?
Probably at home.
He’s so busy with school.
How can he be with you every day?
Didn’t he send me here?
Your fever confused you.
It was Shi Che from your class.
Shi Che?
Yes, make sure you thank him later.
What are you so happy about?
Didn’t Miao get sick?
I sent her to the hospital
the day she had a fever.
It was raining.
I carried her like this.
What do you think?
Am I the hero?
What did Miao say?
Say what?
What did she say to you afterwards?
I left before she woke up.
She didn’t wake up?
Well…
Do you think it’s possible
that she doesn’t know it was you?
I’m just saying.
I mean.
I think,
in my heart the unsung heroes
are more worthy of admiration.
Thank you for taking me to the hospital.
Guoguo, she knows!
She knows it was me!
Okay.
Okay, let me reply to the message.
Let me see.
I can’t see it?
Cheapskate.
A piece of cake.
Besides, you didn’t weigh much.
You just almost crushed me.
Get lost!
Did you
see Jiang Haoyue that day?
It’s done. Here.
How is she?
The doctor said she’ll be fine once
the fever goes down after the IV.
If you’re so worried about her,
why don’t you go in and take a look?
Here are her clothes. Take them back.
No.
Her parents will be here soon.
Don’t tell her I was here.
No, I didn’t.
Okay.
Take your things.
Your dad’s done with the paperwork.
He’ll park the car in front of the door.
We’ll go straight down.
Let’s go.
Nothing is left behind, right?
What’s wrong now?
Why are you suddenly in a bad mood?
It’s so hard to lie to people.
Lie?
What? Who are you lying to?
I don’t wanna talk about it.
It’s annoying.
You just got better.
Stay inside.
Now you care about me.
Tell me.
Why didn’t you text me back?
Why have you been avoiding me?
I have my own business.
That day…
Did you carry me to the hospital?
No.
But...
I clearly remember that it was you.
You had a fever.
You had a dream.
I can tell if it was a dream or not.
I didn’t take you to the hospital.
This is the real situation.
What do you mean?
If you have something to say,
you can say it to me.
Don’t be so emotional.
If you keep being like this,
I won’t talk to you again.
Dreams are all lies.
Miao.
Can I watch the game?
OK!
That’s weird.
Why didn’t you fight me
for the TV today?
Miao?
What’s wrong?
Is there something on your mind?
Come on.
Tell Dad.
Dad.
Do you think Jiang Haoyue
is very strange lately?
What’s wrong with him?
He said something I don’t understand.
Do you know anything?
I don’t know what you’re thinking about.
How am I supposed to know
what’s going on in your heads?
Come on.
But, Miao,
here is the thing.
Haoyue is grown up now.
He has something on his mind.
If he doesn’t want to talk, don’t ask.
Some worries
will pass in time.
But
if he worries about something,
why doesn’t he tell me?
I can take care of it for him.
I know.
You’re a good little girl.
However,
you don’t always
tell everything to
your mom and me, right?
For example,
if you make trouble,
you are afraid
that we will criticize you.
Right?
Or,
you are afraid that
Mom and Dad will worry about you.
I think
Haoyue doesn’t want to tell you.
Maybe
because he’s afraid
you’ll worry about it.
Maybe one day he’ll be fine.
It’s okay.
Nice shot!
Spiking!
After Winter Break
Jiang?
Jiang Haoyue?
That’s weird.
Did he forget that school starts today?
Mr. Jiang.
Are you looking for Jiang Haoyue?
He left early today.
I still can’t do it?
The venue was very big.
I didn’t go anywhere.
I’m told to go every day.
Calligraphy, musical instruments.
I’m exhausted.
Well then, I’m a little better.
I only took one remedial course
in IOMC.
You’re really…
Are you trying to piss me off?
Nanfeng No. 1 High School
Good morning.
We meet again so soon.
Don’t mention it.
Besides writing my winter
vacation homework,
I only had fun for five days.
Why do we need such a long vacation?
I’ve been looking forward to
starting school early.
Why?
Because the beginning of the school year
is the school team tryout day.
I’ve been practicing
for the whole winter break
for this.
I’m sure I can do it this time.
Good luck.
What did she say?
Did she say good luck?
What?
Chlorophyll.
You didn’t even attack me.
Do you have some kind of conspiracy?
What’s wrong with you?
You’ve been practicing all winter break.
So I said good luck.
What’s wrong with that?
Unbelievable.
I’m scared.
I thought she’s possessed.
It’s so funny.
Morning.
Miao.
You don’t look so happy.
It’s the first day of school
and it’s normal for Meng
to look like this.
What’s wrong?
What do you think is the reason for
a person’s sudden change of attitude?
Is it because of some kind of shock?
Or maybe something happened to him.
Or maybe he suddenly figured it out
and wanted to try a different state.
Is there anything wrong
with Jiang Haoyue?
How do you know?
I...
I don’t know.
How can I know?
We don’t know each other well.
Right?
Hey, guys.
Quiet, everyone.
The holiday is over.
I want you all to focus.
This semester, you should
think about whether you want
to study arts or science.
You can discuss it with your parents.
I want everyone to make
the right choice for yourselves.
Okay, let’s continue the lesson.
What’s wrong with Jiang Haoyue?
Let’s open the book.
Suddenly he’s very indifferent to me.
Isn’t indifference his normal behavior?
This time it’s different.
Okay, look at the blackboard.
This time it lasted a lot longer
and he didn’t even go to school
with me anymore.
Jiang Haoyue!
What’s wrong with you?
What?
Why do you keep avoiding me?
Why don’t you wait for me?
I have to prepare
for the national competition.
I can get up early.
Why do we have to go to school together?
We’ve always been together.
Anyway, you must wait for me on the way.
We need to choose our subjects now.
Do you think
I should choose arts or science?
You shouldn’t ask me this kind of thing.
I don’t seem
to have any special talents.
Unlike you and Ziye,
I’m not as good at studying.
And I’m not like Shi Che.
I don’t play basketball.
If I have to say it,
I seem to be better at reading comics.
Why don’t you choose for me?
You always make the right choice.
You shouldn’t ask me about such things.
What?
You should choose
your own path.
Jiang Haoyue.
Why are you doing this?
Didn’t you always help me before?
You think
that was helping you?
What’s wrong with you lately?
My dad says you’re in a bad mood.
He told me to give you more time.
But you’ve been in a bad mood
for too long.
Do I have to accept it?
Can’t I refuse it?
Lu Miao.
I am also a living human being.
Why do you all have a choice,
but I don’t?
Mr. Wen said that
Miao has
average grades in all subjects,
so arts or science is the same.
Yes.
She’s in the middle
of the lower class in all subjects.
The middle. Not the middle of the lower.
What’s the difference?
Fine.
Science then.
Is it
too difficult for girls
to study science?
Difficulties can be overcome.
Choose science for a good job
in the future.
Life is not just about finding jobs.
Let’s take physical geography
as an example.
The topography of each country,
the terrain,
the people, the history and culture,
and all that knowledge
are very important.
You’ll think it’s important later.
But the most important thing now
is employment.
You earn a lot of money.
You can go on a study tour.
The most important thing is to build
a good foundation in high school.
All right, stop arguing.
Everything to you is about money.
It’s tacky.
I’m tacky, and you’re noble?
You live on air?
All these years of hard work
have been in vain?
Do I deserve this?
I’ll go wash the dishes.
That’s a terrible thing to say.
Okay.
I said the wrong thing.
Aren’t we talking about
choosing a subject for Miao?
How come it’s about money?
It’s about the future.
And the future is about money.
Am I wrong?
If you didn’t have...
Fine, I won’t argue with you.
You decide.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Why are you sighing?
Geography, 71.
Politics, 65.
History, 68.
Biology, 66.
Chemistry, 75.
Physics, 63.
These are not bad.
Why are you sighing?
I scored too evenly on the arts
and science exams this time.
I originally wanted to take
whichever subject I scored higher.
I didn’t expect it to be so even.
How can I choose now?
It’s okay. I’m pretty even too.
So, are you going
to choose arts or science?
I’ll choose science.
My parents want me to study medicine.
I’m more interested in it too.
What about you?
I don’t care about arts and science.
I want to go
to the professional basketball team.
National Basketball Association.
To be a professional player.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
What about you, Guoguo?
I...
I didn’t think about it.
What’s going on with you all lately?
She’s got her business.
I have my own business.
I’m leaving.
Here, have a piece of apple.
Miao didn’t finish it.
Enough.
The whole night,
she’s been eating fruit and
not finishing her homework.
What’s going on with her now?
And I haven’t seen her
doing her homework
with Haoyue these days.
You’re acting strange too.
Is there anything you two
are hiding from me?
What could I be hiding from you?
Come on.
You don’t want to tell me?
Then I’ll go find Haoyue.
Why are you trying
to make things more complicated?
I’m just worried about it.
Keep your voice down.
Okay, I’ll tell you.
It’s because of the car accident.
What?
Jiang Yi feels
that the money is not enough?
Not Jiang Yi.
It’s Haoyue.
Haoyue…
Why did he suddenly mention
the car accident?
I think
it’s probably because Miao’s illness
was too much of a shock to Haoyue.
Think about it.
Miao’s illness was so urgent.
Haoyue
must also be very anxious.
But he couldn’t help.
So he felt frustrated.
He blamed himself
for all these mistakes.
He must have
remembered the car accident again.
I don’t blame him.
This kid
is suffering a lot.
Haoyue can’t be blamed for this.
When he’s young,
he didn’t know much.
Now he’s grown up.
We can’t force him to forgive us.
It’s hard for him.
Don’t mention this
in front of Miao again.
You think I’m you?
I’m going to take out the garbage.
Haoyue.
Mr. Lu.
It’s been a long time
since you came to my place for dinner.
I’ve been busy lately.
Last time in the hospital...
Mr. Lu, I have to take out the garbage.
I have to do my homework
after taking out the trash.
I’m going down there.
I can help you with it.
Get back to do your homework.
Go on.
Thank you, Mr. Lu.
Bye.
Come on, everyone gathers.
Okay.
Now according to your basketball skills
and physical fitness test,
we will give you a position.
Of course this is not
the final selection of our school team.
We’ll do a more
thorough evaluation, OK?
Shi Che, you move to this position.
Seriously?
I can’t be that bad.
All right, everyone.
I’d like to ask you all
one last question.
Why do you want to play basketball?
I’m a basketball genius!
I like James!
Playing basketball is cool.
Girls like it.
Alright, be serious this time.
I never got good grades,
but my dad was always
pushing me to study.
He said that study was my only way out.
I had no reason to contradict him.
The more he pushed me,
the more I hated studying,
Until I met basketball.
The basketball spirit
in me was awakened.
I wanted to prove
that studying was not
the only way to measure value.
Anyway, I wanted to play
with Shi Che on all courts.
We are the two best players.
Okay.
Gentlemen.
Thanks again for
trying out for the school team.
No matter what the result is,
I hope it will be a perfect memory
in your high school.
Please continue to love basketball.
- Hear!
Meng.
Where are you going?
I’m in a bad mood. I’m just hanging out.
How did your school team tryouts go?
I think my odds are pretty good.
I missed last time
because I wasn’t prepared.
I’ll be fine this time.
I envy you. You have a clear goal.
What’s wrong?
You look so worried.
I still don’t know whether
to choose arts or science.
Shouldn’t you follow your heart
at this time?
How to follow?
I have no direction at all.
Look.
I have an idea.
What is it?
But there is no free lunch.
You finish these papers,
and I’ll tell you.
It had better work.
Or…
You’ve already made your choice.
Look.
You chose comprehensive liberal arts.
It’s such a child’s play.
Child’s play?
The subconscious choice
is called the inner choice.
It sounds strange,
but it makes sense.
Of course, I’m a wise man.
You know how to choose now.
Why are you still worried?
Do you think Jiang Haoyue
ignored me because
he followed his heart?
Is it really that hard for him
to get along with me?
Am I that annoying?
Let me tell you the truth.
Jiang Haoyue took you
to the hospital the day you had a fever.
He wouldn’t let me tell you.
Why?
I don’t know.
But when I left,
I saw him with your dad.
My dad?
I saw the two of them talking
and it didn’t seem to go well.
It must be because of the car accident.
No wonder he didn’t tell me.
No wonder my dad told me
to give him more time.
Because this is something
we can’t help.
A car accident?
My dad caused Jiang Haoyue’s
leg to become like this.
Your dad?
My dad hit Jiang Haoyue
and Jiang lost half of his leg.
So my dad really
blamed himself and felt guilty
and decided to treat him
like his own child.
He didn’t want him to be traumatized
by the loss of half of his leg.
But it seems
that there is no way to
turn a blind eye to this pain.
In fact, what he said was right.
It was always me who wanted
to be friends with him,
and I never asked him.
Maybe he didn’t want
to be friends with me at all.
That’s it.
That’s why he’s angry.
He feels he has no choice.
I’m just too self-righteous.
Maybe it’s not as complicated
as you think.
I will never force Jiang Haoyue again.
I’ve analyzed your grades
in all subjects.
In addition to Chinese,
Math, and English,
among the other six subjects,
History, Geography, and Biology
have a stable average score
of around 70,
while Politics,
Chemistry have a relatively poor
performance, with an average score
fluctuating around 65.
Physics is the worst.
And whether you can pass
or not depends on luck.
Overall,
your strengths are all in the arts.
Indeed,
liberal arts are easier.
But
I can teach you science,
and the basic scores are easier to get.
Of course, if you want to choose arts,
I can also teach you arts.
Should I give you some privacy?
What are you doing here?
I was just picking up a pen.
How much did you hear?
Probably
all of them.
Jiang Haoyue.
I didn’t expect you to be like this.
It’s not funny.
About the exponential
and logarithmic functions
that Ms. Lei just talked about,
all I heard was nothing about log.
I was so confused.
Can you teach me?
Make it slow.
Why don’t you ask Jiang Haoyue?
I don’t want to bother him anymore.
You can teach me, too.
You haven’t made up with him yet?
You two have been arguing
too long this time.
I’ve always relied on him before.
This time I want
to make my own decision.
Forget about him.
So,
have you decided on your choice
of arts and science?
I have.
Arts.
Math alone is enough for me.
And I think I am still
more interested in the arts.
It seems
she has already made her choice.
Jiang Haoyue.
What?
I told Lu Miao
that you were there that night.
Why did you say that to her?
She was worried about you.
It has nothing to do with her,
understand?
I’ve heard your story.
If you’ve already forgiven them,
why are you still so twisted?
Are you done?
Thank you
for taking her to the hospital that day.
If there’s nothing else,
see you then.
Hey…
No. 1 High School School Team
Spring Tryout Results
No way.
How is this possible?
How come
it doesn’t have your name on it?
Could it be your father?
No, it’s not.
He doesn’t have time for me these days.
Congratulations, Guoguo.
Wait.
Good job, Chen Guoguo.
See you this afternoon.
Try harder next year, Shi Che.
You’re the one who doesn’t see it.
Let’s train together this afternoon.
No, my feet hurt a little.
Go.
Negative Score, are you serious?
Slam Dunk
Serious about what?
You didn’t get in the school team, so?
Guoguo was worried sick about you.
And you came here to read a comic book.
What do you think you know?
I don’t know much.
I really don’t understand
why you’re so obsessed
with something you’re not good at.
Have you ever thought that
you have been practicing for so long,
but the school team did not choose you,
then it may be because
you are not so talented?
Since your innate condition is not good,
then it’s no need to take
the matter of failure too seriously.
Sir, I’d like to return this book.
I also want to rent the 12th volume
of Slum Dunk.
Are you OK?
Wait a minute.
Someone
at the front desk wants
to rent this book.
Give me your card.
You...
You’re crying.
I’m fine.
Thanks.
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with someone
what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Someone is just like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
Congcong.
Today
she didn’t wait for me after school.
She didn’t eat with me.
She chose arts on her own,
and she said
she couldn’t always rely on me.
Isn’t that what I want?
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
I
should be happy.
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
Does...
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
She not need me anymore?
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
Who are you looking for?
Where is Lu Miao?
You got the wrong place.
No!
Phycho.
Lu Miao!
Congcong!
Let’s go.
Lu Miao!
You are…?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
I had the most amazing
experience yesterday.
You want to hear it?
No.
All right, go ahead.
I was doing math yesterday.
I couldn’t figure it out
the whole afternoon.
I still thought about it that evening.
And I got the result in my dream.
I woke up and found out I was right.
I’m surprised you’re still doing math
in your dreams.
Do you think I’m smarter
in my dreams?
Dreams can be deceiving.
How do you know that?
Have you ever been deceived by it?
I often dream
that my leg is still there,
but it’s actually gone.
Are you sad
every time you wake up?
If this dream will make me sad,
I will have another dream that mocks it
to get the sadness out of my head.
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪