Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
Flourish in Time
Episode 17
I Will Catch You
When the square array passes rostrum,
there will be an area
for class presentation.
Let’s use “Study” as
our theme.
How’s that?
It’s so boring.
Boring.
Shi Che. Do you have
any good suggestions?
I think the formation
needs to show the spirit of our class.
Right?
Right.
“Dominating”.
How about that?
Sir.
This word has too many strokes.
It’s too complicated
to be our formation.
How about
we design a formation
in the shape of Neenya Ninja?
Whenever the leaves arrive,
the fire burns endlessly.
Multiple Shadow Avatar Surgery.
Thank you.
Since you don’t have other ideas,
“Study” will be the final choice.
This word represents
my profound hopes on you.
Keep it in your mind.
It’s so boring.
Forward, march!
Left, right, left.
Halt.
Turn right.
You’ve been
working hard these days.
I’ll finish school early today.
Really?
How come we’re the first class
to finish today?
I think Mr. Di is testing us.
Don’t fall into his trap.
Let’s stand still.
Since you don’t want to go,
let’s keep practicing.
We’re joking.
That’s alright.
See you, Sir.
That’s great. Let’s go.
See you.
Take that for me.
Jiang Haoyue,
you’ll be in charge
of formation change.
Go.
Let’s go home.
What are you thinking about?
I’m designing the change of formation.
Let me see.
Come on, let me see.
What’s your class’s idea?
It’s highly classified.
How can I tell you?
It’s the same for me to not tell you.
Suspicious.
Curiosity killed the cat.
But a cat has nine lives.
Jiang. Just let me take a look.
Just a peek.
No.
One peek.
Please?
Just a peek.
- Can’t I just have a look?
- No.
Show me, please.
Where’s it?
In the following pages.
Find it for me.
Is it a drip?
The sea?
So the meaning hidden in it is
the water runs into the sea.
Does it mean drops
of water outwear the stone?
It implies the importance
of perseverance,
isn’t it?
Even though that’s not what I mean,
the way you see it is interesting.
Then what’s the original meaning?
See.
If it’s only a drop,
it dries up pretty fast.
But if it drops in the sea,
it’s given enormous power.
It’s just a simple pattern.
How come you could endow it
with such profound meaning?
I...
Do your exercise.
In the training of the square array,
our class has put
much more efforts
than other classes.
You’ve had
complaints
and doubts.
But you did it
eventually.
I’m proud of our class.
The theme of the formation
designed by Jiang Haoyue
is the sea.
Every one of us
is a drop of water.
We have the possibilities
to become the sea.
We are water when we split up.
We are an ocean once
we are gathered together.
There will be a student
to be lifted at the end
representing the honorable drop
of water in our class.
I want
you guys to choose
the student to represent it.
Think about it carefully.
You can vote
by placing the water bottles
in front of the student.
You are pretty popular.
By the way,
which program did you sign up?
The 400-meter relay race.
I signed you up, too.
What?
Without even noticing me?
Guoguo.
When we win
the first place of the race,
push me to the podium.
That’ll be my chance to tell everyone
I like Meng.
Che. Haven’t you given up yet?
Actually, I think you...
Stop.
I’ve made up my mind.
Guoguo.
Do you know the meaning
of “Fret not over bygones
and the forward journey take”?
It means,
if you failed on chasing
the girl you like before,
there are plenty of other girls
for us to chase.
You’ll never understand.
Anyway.
The moment I stand on the podium
will be the highlight
of my career and personal life.
Xie Ziye.
I need a favor.
That’s rare.
Are you asking me for a favor?
Can I take a look at your diary?
Why?
I want to keep a diary, too.
Tell me the truth.
Don’t you have
the information of other boys in it?
The sports meeting is coming.
I’d like to know my opponents.
Knowing the enemies
helps to win the battles.
Isn’t it right?
Tell me the truth.
I signed up for the relay race
after you encouraged me.
Please help me again.
Xie Ziye.
Stay away from me.
Are you gonna borrow me?
No.
Don’t push me.
What? Are you threatening me now?
Xie Ziye loves reading
romantic fictions!
Are you done now?
It’s been so long.
I don’t care
as long as it still works.
Well?
Just for one night.
Don’t read other things.
Xie Ziye is such a nerd.
Her diary is as tidy
as the experimental form.
That’s crazy.
Where am I? Am I in it?
She only documents
the cute guys in each grade.
Are you in it?
Sure.
Good/Bad Shi Che Cheap-mouthed -5
What’s your score?
My score is alright.
Let me see.
Stop it. That’s not the point.
Let’s do the real business.
Wang Feng.
Sprint record, 13’84’’.
Remember that.
Next one.
Yan Su.
Move to the left for a bit.
Here?
Move further.
Further.
Right here?
Move upwards.
Lower.
Which direction exactly?
Yeah, right here.
I’ll draw here.
Alright.
Miao, you are so good at it.
I’m alright. Top three of the world.
Look at the blackboard.
It looks so nice.
We can probably win a prize
this semester.
Excuse me.
I can’t draw as good.
Thank you.
Her level
can surely win a prize this time.
Don’t stand there watching.
Come and help me.
Go and outline the picture.
Sure.
Good/Bad Shi Che Cheap-mouthed +5
He changed his score.
Narcissist.
Shi Che.
Can you do it right?
It looks good this way.
Trust me.
It’s ugly.
Draw evenly, okay?
This is art.
Can you understand?
It looks better this way.
Lu Miao.
Go to the medical room now.
Jiang Haoyue passed out just now.
Passed out?
He’s fine. He had sunstroke.
Some Huoxiang Zhengqi liquid
will help him.
Sir.
Let’s forget it.
Jiang Haoyue has been working hard
during the practice of the array.
Let’s find someone else
to finish the final lift.
If we cancel it,
the guys will surely understand it.
The official presentation is tomorrow.
The time is limited.
Give me the medicine.
I’ll talk to him.
Jiang.
It’s time for your medicine.
Hurry up and get better.
So you can finish the final lift.
You’re not asking me to quit?
I know you won’t quit.
Actually,
I’m not too sure about it.
What’s your concern?
Do you think
they can catch me?
What are you doing?
Be quiet, Ziye.
Let me ask you something.
You’ve learned so much
from the romantic fictions.
You must be good
at writing love letters, right?
Love letters?
Are you writing Lu Miao a love letter?
Yeah.
When I win the first place
of the relay race,
I’ll tell her my feelings
in front of everybody.
Try and win first.
I am Shi Che.
There’s nothing to worry about.
But,
I’m afraid I’ll have a stage fright
when I stand on the podium.
That will be awkward.
You are her best friend.
Can you help me out?
How about
when it’s done,
I’ll
buy you
a gift pack of diary appliances?
Really?
Really.
I’ll keep my promise.
Alright.
I think
when you profess your love
for her publicly,
your love letter needs to be elegant.
Remember what I’m about to say.
Dirt with its fresh smell.
A generation filled with energy.
Songs lift our spirit.
De...
Desert nourished by the rain.
My words imply strong affections
for you.
That’s the first part.
Finish the rest of it yourself.
I was right to ask you.
Thank you. See you.
Be careful.
Why are we here?
Right here. Stop here.
Where’s this place?
Hurry up.
Come on.
Right here.
I watched your class practice last time.
I found the point of your movement is
to use the strength of your thigh
and straighten your back.
Are you sure?
I’m the master.
Stand still at here.
What are you...?
Look at my movement.
After I count three, two, one,
you come and catch me.
No. It’s too dangerous.
Come down.
Three...
Stop it.
Two...
Let’s change to a lower place,
okay?
One...
Are you okay?
Yes.
I’m fine.
Do you know how dangerous
it is to fall from this high?
What if you get hurt?
The students in your class
will be like you.
Just like you care about me,
they care about you, too.
It’s like I trust myself with you.
As long as you can trust them.
As long as you can do that,
your formation will succeed, too.
The 48th Sports Meeting
Class 1, Grade 2 is coming.
Wide sky and enormous ocean.
Heavy rain falls down.
They are presenting
the formation of ocean.
Halt.
Turn right.
Dress right.
Eyes front.
Waves. Ready.
Change.
Not bad.
Arrow.
Change.
You are the next one.
Water drop.
Change.
Excuse me.
Lift. Ready.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
It’s like I trust myself with you.
As long as you can trust them.
As long as you can do that,
your formation will succeed, too.
Jiang Haoyue.
Come on!
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
Great!
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
Che.
♪The point of growth is♪
Jiang Haoyue was heroic.
Are you still gonna profess to her?
♪We staying together♪
I’ll do something to surpass him.
Come on!
That’s so cool.
Why are you sitting here?
You come at the right time.
Take a look
at your highlight moments that I edited.
Come on!
It’s so weird.
It’s not.
I want to repeat this part even more.
You’re just being dramatic.
No, I’m not.
I’m just really happy for you.
You’ve practiced for so long.
The efforts you spared
were not in vain.
Besides, other people like it, too.
The good students
who normally look aloof
and calm in your class
were shouting excitedly as I did.
This is my first time
seeing them like that, too.
How about you?
How do you feel now?
I...
I feel excited.
It’s my first time
feeling that I belong
to Class 1, Grade 2.
Dirt with its fresh smell.
A generation filled with energy.
Songs lift our spirit.
Desert nourished by the rain.
My words imply strong affections
for you.
Your casual movements and words
took my heart away.
I’d like to give this medal
to my favorite person,
Lu Miao.
My Meng.
Ziye.
My period came.
Do you have extra pads?
Then what should I...?
Thank you.
It’s you.
Do you want it or not?
Thanks.
Don’t get me wrong.
I wouldn’t help you
if it weren’t for Jiang Haoyue.
She just wouldn’t admit
that she’s nice to me.
The next will be the final event
of our sports meeting.
It’s the most popular one as well.
It’s the 400-meter relay race.
The first team competing
is the players of Grade 1.
Come on!
Is Lu Miao running?
Isn’t she...?
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
Come on!
Now, Class 10, Grade 1
is catching up with full speed.
This autumn is filled
with their passions.
Cheer for them if you want to.
Why are you holding it?
I don’t want to cheer for her.
Come on! Lu Miao!
Come on!
Come on! Guoguo!
Here we are at the last take.
Every class is sprinting
with full speed.
Shi Che. Come on!
Shi Che from Class 10, Grade 1
surpassed.
Shi Che. Come on!
Come on!
Final spurt!
Who’s going to win at last?
Come on!
He fell down!
He’s down!
Is he okay?
Wait...
This is...
Let’s congratulate Class 10, Grade 1
for winning the final
of the relay race!
Miao.
Ziye.
Great! That’s great!
So cool.
Great!
Don’t be so excited.
That’s what I expected.
Are you tired?
No.
Guys, listen to me.
Shi Che’s last hurdle
was unbelievable!
I think Shi Che should accept the prize
on behalf of our class.
Sure!
Great!
You read the first part
of this speech,
and I’ll read the second part.
Sure.
Then let’s practice it together.
This speech is my acceptance speech.
Read it for me
when I accept the prize later.
Alright.
Read it in my tone.
Read it with affections
to manifest my demeanor.
Read it in your best condition.
Help me to express the pride
between the lines.
Thanks.
Cheer for me!
Louder!
Dirt...
A generation...
Songs...
Desert...
My words...
Are you sure about reading it?
I’ll read Shi Che’s
speech.
You?
Aren’t you...?
Let’s welcome Principle Shi
to present the prize
for the winner of the 400-meter
relay race.
Shi Che.
Here, come on.
According to the request of Shi Che,
we’re reading his acceptance speech
at this glorious moment.
Dirt with its fresh smell.
A generation filled with energy.
Songs lift our spirit.
Desert nourished by the rain.
What did Shi Che write?
My words imply strong affections
for you.
I’ve given all I have.
Just because you are here.
I have a bad feeling.
You left a smile in my heart.
I don’t ask for much.
As long as there’s a corner
for me to lay my eyes
on you with my deepest love.
A memory which I’ll never
regret for the rest of my life.
I’d like to give this medal
to the person I love.
My dearest father, Principle Shi.
Son.
You are my dearest son.
Is that so funny?
You don’t get it.
He’s really miserable and funny.
I think it’s a good speech.
Good for you.
Lift your arms.
No matter what,
you’ve improved the relationship
between you and your father.
Don’t ever mention this again.
Do you think it was a prank by Ziye?
I think
she may have written
an acrostic poetry by accident.
Alright. It’s definitely a prank.
But Jiang Haoyue was worse.
He’s so annoying.
He’s extremely treacherous.
He replaced your speech.
This act is very
irritating
and shameless.
I’ll get even with him for sure.
Jiang.
Uncle Lu.
Throwing the trash?
Yeah, I am.
I need to throw them first.
Jiang.
Have you had dinner?
Here. Jiang.
Well. Enjoy your food.
Thank you, Sir.
No problem.
Come on. Jiang.
Eat now.
Uncle Lu.
Did you pay for my artificial leg?
Of course not.
What are you thinking about?
Jiang, you should thank
your father for it.
Here comes your food.
Thanks.
My father?
Your father cares about you a lot.
You are
a great kid.
But I have to say sometimes
you’re too suspicious.
When have I ever lied to you?
I’m sorry.
That’s not what I mean.
No, Uncle Lu.
I shouldn’t have been mad at you
that day by the roads.
It’s the past.
Let’s forget it.
Aren’t
you mad at me?
I don’t get mad so easily.
If I was always mad,
I would have been mad
at Miao for millions of times.
Here. Eat some vegetables.
Have a rib.
Is it good?
Not as special as Aunt Fang’s cooking.
The ribs cooked by her
are real cuisine.
Jiang.
I still remember
when you just replaced your leg
and came for dinner for the first time.
I remember, too.
That was
the first time I went to your home.
Lu Miao was sitting next to me.
She was curious about my artificial leg
when I came in.
She wanted
to have a same one as mine.
I was so mad
that I pounded the desk
so hard with the chopstick
in my hand.
Then it occurred
to me that she was just a kid.
Miao was very upset, too.
She asked me later
how come
you could be the RoboCop
but not her.
And if she was ignored by God.
That’s really her style.
Jiang.
You haven’t come to my home
for dinner for long.
Come again someday.
Tell me whatever you want to eat.
Aunt Fang and I will cook for you.
Okay.
Are you still yearning
for ribs cooked by her?
Yes.
Alright.
Here. Uncle Lu.
When the Big Bang happened,
atom was formed
which made the stars.
The atoms which I mentioned
constituted our bodies.
So, the stars are not far away.
Because we are the stars.
We are the stars?
When I look at you,
I’m looking at the stars.
That’s kind of true.
So the stars are so close to me.
The nearest star is yourself.
Really?
Yes.
I’m the star?
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪