Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
Flourish in Time
Episode 14
Eternal Regret
Is it straight?
No, it’s not.
The right side is a bit low.
A little bit.
The right side.
Can’t you differentiate right and left?
This is the right side.
Do it yourself.
I told you it’s too low.
Look at them.
This...
This is straight.
Look at our daughter’s exam ranking.
The number is so auspicious.
Eighty-eight.
It means great fortune.
Okay. I’ll go all out next time.
Yes. Great.
But keep the good work up.
Don’t be too proud.
Mom.
I finally got into top 100.
Can’t you just praise me?
Praise you?
I’d better praise Jiang.
Without him, you can’t achieve this.
But kids shouldn’t
study too hard.
Most importantly,
she needs to balance study and rest.
Right.
Studying hard is
the most important thing.
Miao,
your mom didn’t study diligently
when she was supposed to.
Look how tiring her work is now.
Mom.
You’re mistaken.
It’s him.
You...!
Mom.
It turned out that
you didn’t like study either.
Fine.
It’s rare that we come here.
When we’re here,
Miao
doesn’t need to study.
Hang out with us, okay?
Thank you, Grandpa!
If you’re half as good as Jiang,
I won’t have to worry so much.
Where is Jiang?
I haven’t seen him for a while.
He should be downstairs.
I’ll go get him.
- Be careful.
- Come back soon.
Okay.
Jiang.
This is odd.
Why isn’t he at home
during the Spring Festival?
Sorry, the number you dialed
is out of service.
Out of service?
Go.
Don’t do such dishonest things again.
You’re a father.
You should also act like one.
Go home and spend the Spring Festival
with your son.
Well.
Do you have alcohol?
Alcohol?
You haven’t spent enough time
in jail, right?
No.
Look. That was the only money I had.
You confiscated it as gambling money.
I can’t go home with empty pockets
during the Spring Festival, right?
Yi,
you can’t live like this from now on.
Jiang Haoyue is a kid
with much potential.
Aren’t you afraid that
he might look down on you
in the future?
I’m his father.
I gave him life and raised him up.
If he dares to look down on me...
You...
This is it.
If he dares to look down on me,
do you think I’ll spare him?
Don’t talk big.
Why are you here?
Slow down.
I’m talking to you.
Do you have money in your WeChat wallet?
Transfer 100 yuan to me.
50.
50 will do.
Hurry.
My mom is right.
You’re a jerk.
Who is a jerk?
I mean you are.
Do you want to get beaten?
If I’m a jerk,
how can you grow so tall?
how can you be
the No.1 student at school?
Whether I’m No.1 or not
is none of your business.
Then it’s whose business?
It’s Lu Yongfei’s business?
It’s the business of the bastard
who crippled you, right?
You really wish to be his son, right?
Just go if you want to.
Enjoy being a gambler.
You’re on your own.
What do you understand?
How can I stand a chance
if I don’t gamble?
Your mom, Chen Lu abandoned us
and ran away with some other guy
because I didn’t have money.
Do you understand it?
Leave me alone.
No one will spend
the Spring Festival with you.
Go mind your own business.
Happy New Year.
Why are you home so late?
I...
I went out for shopping.
What are you here for?
I’m waiting for you.
I called you but you didn’t answer.
Today is the Spring Festival.
Why don’t you wear a festive outfit?
Outfit is not enough.
To have a festive look,
I need to put on buns
like yours.
Do you know how hard it is
to make these?
I spent hours to do these buns.
And you find them not pretty?
I didn’t say they’re not pretty.
They’re quite cute.
Come to my home.
We have a feast tonight.
Grandma asked me to invite both
you and Uncle Jiang to dinner.
He...
He won’t come home tonight.
That’s his loss.
Let’s have dinner together.
I even bought sparklers.
We can play with fireworks tonight.
Don’t say I’m childish
for playing with fireworks.
Okay.
Let’s go.
- Where’s the cut?
- Keep watching.
This...
Let me cook the dinner.
What’s going on?
I asked you to cook but you didn’t.
You were slacking off.
Great. Now I’m cut.
Let me treat your wound.
No need.
- Her face is so pale.
- Give her a hand.
She doesn’t have the festive vibe.
- Grandma, Grandpa, Jiang is here.
- It’s fine. It’s fine.
Jiang is here.
Let me take a look.
You’re taller.
You’re more and more handsome.
Come.
Let me.
It’s fine.
You bled a lot.
You seem to be
not so busy this year.
What do you mean?
Well.
Every other year,
during the Spring Festival,
weren’t you always busy
calling your clients?
I did this
intentionally to save this time
to accompany the family.
It’s the Spring Festival.
You still want me to work?
Fine. I need to
call my client now.
You reminded me.
Medicine kit.
Don’t forget to put it back.
Hello.
Happy New Year.
I’m just calling to ask you,
when will the company
pay year-end bonus?
I originally planned to
tell you after the Spring Festival.
You’re an old employee.
But your performance hasn’t
been so good for the past few years.
The company now wishes to
terminate the labor contract with you.
Are you saying that
I’m fired?
I’m really sorry.
I promise I’ll try to
persuade the company
to give you a month’s salary
as compensation.
Dad.
Well.
Is mom a bit gloomy today?
Is she?
I saw her spend the whole day
in the room today.
During every Spring Festival,
your mom will call her old clients.
That’s how she manages her relations.
She might be tired.
She’s taking some rest.
It’s fine, Miao.
Today’s Taiping Swallow
is handmade by your Grandma.
It’s your mom’s favorite.
She will be thrilled tonight
when she sees it.
Dad, don’t stop.
Grandma said you mustn’t stop.
If you stop, the meat won’t be tender.
I can’t stop.
Miao.
This is so fun.
Do you want to try it?
It’s like drumming.
Come. Try it.
Have a try.
Isn’t this fun?
Don’t stop.
Grandma said, if you stop,
the meat won’t be tender.
Don’t stop.
I was talking to you
to distract my attention.
Dad, this is so fun.
Do you want to have a try?
The swing is so fun.
Check me out.
Follow me.
The other side.
Do this.
And this.
Great.
You’re so smart.
You learned it so fast.
Grandma taught me well.
Is your dad at home?
Call him here for dinner tonight, okay?
He’s not at home.
Not home?
Honey.
It’s the Spring Festival.
Have some wine too.
Okay.
What’s going on?
You have a rough time at work?
No.
I got a lot of year-end bonus.
Mom, did you hear that?
She has received bonus.
I told you so.
My wife is the best.
We can definitely
enjoy a good Spring Festival.
Yes.
Here comes Taiping Swallow.
Come. Slow down.
Without Taiping Swallow,
there’s no Spring Festival feast.
Taiping Swallow is necessary
for Spring Festival.
I haven’t eaten
mom’s Taiping Swallow for a while.
Thankfully, Miao and Jiang
were there to help me.
Look.
It looks so good.
Come on. Eat.
Thanks, mom.
How is it?
Is it great?
It’s delicious.
It’s the taste of childhood.
I finally see her smile.
Mom.
You must be happy
during the Spring Festival.
I’m happy.
I’m old now.
I want nothing more.
I just want the family
to be safe and happy.
Right?
Mom is right.
Because of what mom just said,
we need to spend the Spring Festival
safely and happily.
Cheers.
Come.
Happy New Year.
It’s lit.
Jiang, look at the camera.
Let me take photos.
Okay.
Watch out.
Look.
Happy New Year.
What’s your New Year wish?
My New Year wish is that
I hope everyone
can be happy and
we can all be together.
It died out.
Let me take it. Be careful. It’s hot.
Sit down first.
I have something to share with you.
This.
This is the rice wine
I just got from Grandma.
I sneaked a sip on the dinner table.
It’s so good.
It tastes like beverage.
Have a try.
High school students shouldn’t drink.
The ancient sages have said
rice wine is not wine.
High school students can drink it too.
Don’t drink too much.
It’s a call from Ziye.
Happy New Year, Miao.
Happy New Year.
I’m talking with Miao.
What are you here for?
We’re in the same chat group.
We can’t send our New Year wishes?
It’s lively when we’re together.
Right, Che?
Mr. Jiang would like to
send his New Year wishes too.
Happy New Year.
Jiang Haoyue.
Why are you hanging out with Meng?
We’re playing with fireworks
on the rooftop.
Give the phone to Meng.
I want to see her.
Meng.
Haven’t you said
you’ll send New Year wishes?
Happy New Year, Haoyue.
I’m not happy.
Happy New Year.
You...
Come drink rice wine with me.
It’s so delicious.
Jiang Haoyue, you let Meng drink?
What are you drinking?
Miao is one of a kind.
She’s indeed special.
Jiang Haoyue.
Stop shaking me.
You drank too much?
I didn’t shake you.
You seem to be wasted.
You’re so funny.
The way when you’re drunk...
- I’ll go now. She’s drunk.
- Is pretty ugly.
- I’ll send her home.
- Bye-bye.
Stop drinking.
What?
I’m not drunk.
Look.
Be careful.
I can walk.
Watch out. I can!
I can...!
Let me answer a call.
Call?
Is it from that annoying Su Daifei?
It’s Qu Wei.
Qu Wei?
You mustn’t answer his call.
When we were at school,
I saw you two
flirting with your eyes.
Answer me.
You used our relationship
to cover something, right?
What’s the thing
that you like about him?
I see.
Do you like
those who’re good at study?
Can you change your preference?
Studying is too hard.
Be quite. Aunt and Uncle are sleeping.
Do you know?
Actually,
I have a lot of
other virtues.
Yes.
I’m good at playing video games.
Look.
Check me out. A flash.
A slowdown.
A combo.
First blood.
Defend the Nexus.
Where’s the Nexus?
Where’s your key?
Key?
Don’t move.
Come. I’ll take you home.
Jiang Haoyue.
Why
did you
get the moon down?
You’re drunk.
Let me take you home.
You haven’t told me.
Why did you
get the moon down?
To give it to you.
You really like me.
If you like me, then you should say it.
Only if you say it,
can we know
each other’s feelings.
Only if you say it,
can we know each other’s feelings.
Mom
Can you give it to dad later, okay?
Don’t eat sweet things.
Why should a boy eat so many sweet food?
Look. What is it?
Isn’t it pretty?
What is it?
He likes small toy cars.
You’re spoiling him.
Give it to me.
Red.
Black and white.
Come. Let me take a look.
Is it done?
Come. Sit tight.
Sit together.
Men need to support the family.
Do you get it?
Look.
What do we have left
in the fridge?
We need to live and feed ourselves.
This costs money,
doesn’t it?
You despise me now?
Yes, I do.
Listen up. I’m also regretful.
What’s your problem?
You’re the one who has a problem.
Just piss off if you can’t live with me.
Mom.
Come. Give me your hand.
Keep it.
Haoyue.
Remember my words.
Mom will come back.
I’ll definitely come back.
You’re a man. Don’t cry.
Do you know that?
Mom.
Happy New Year.
I wanted to call you last night.
But your brother had an upset stomach
and didn’t feel too well.
When he was feeling better,
it was already past midnight.
I thought you must be sleeping.
So...
It’s fine.
I slept early last night.
How are you doing recently?
I’m doing great.
Jiang Yi didn’t cause
any trouble to you, right?
What are you doing?
You’re stealthily calling
your mom again, right?
Does it have anything to do with you?
Jiang.
Have you been waiting for a while?
Grandpa.
This.
I don’t understand
this youngsters’ gadget.
Let Jiang teach me how to use a phone.
How to use it?
Here.
No one wants your crap.
Jiang.
Red packet. Take it.
I can’t take it.
Miao also has hers.
I didn’t tell her mom and dad.
You’re the same.
You mustn’t let them know.
If they know,
they’ll definitely say this.
Give it to me. Let me keep it for you.
I’ll return it to you when you grow up.
It’s a lie.
Take it.
Remember?
Thank you, Grandpa.
Don’t starve yourself.
Don’t starve yourself at school.
- Okay.
- Miao.
Miao.
Whether you’re good at study or not
isn’t important.
There are many paths in life.
Get in the car.
Grandma, watch your head.
What did your grandpa just tell you?
He told me nothing.
Don’t pull this trick.
Do you remember what I told you?
Yes, I do.
Repeat it for me.
First, keep the windows
and doors closed.
Second, tidy the washed clothes.
Third, check the sockets.
Fourth, beware of water-heater.
I remember it, mom.
We’ll just be away for two days.
Have you finished?
Go. Get in the car. Hurry.
I’ll miss you.
I feel there’s something I forgot.
Hurry and get in the car.
Oh!
Recently, there’s mad cow disease.
Don’t eat spicy hot pot.
I get it.
I definitely won’t eat it.
I spent a long time
looking for my notebook.
Get in the car.
Watch out for your leg.
Right.
If I hadn’t stopped your mom...
What are you whispering about?
Nothing.
I was reminding her again.
Bye-bye.
Have a safe trip.
Remember what I told you.
- Yes, I’ll definitely tell you.
- Tidy the clothes. No spicy hot pot.
Miao.
Bye.
- Have a safe trip. Bye.
- Take care of yourself.
I’m free.
Fang.
She has grown up.
Don’t worry.
He drove off before
I could finish my words.
You.
It’s fine. We’ll only be gone
for a few days.
Miao is a good child.
Don’t worry about her.
Lu.
Weather broadcast said
that it would rain today.
Drive slowly.
Don’t worry, dad.
Sir.
What do you want?
I want
beef sausage, coin sausage,
chicken sausage, bacon, fish tofu,
quail egg, and lettuce each.
You eat that much.
Okay. Wait a second.
It’ll be ready soon.
Sir, put more chili for me.
Okay. Wait a second.
Time Book
We’re playing with fireworks on rooftop.
I want to set off fireworks
with Meng as well.
What’s going on?
You argued with your friend?
No.
Meng
is a lovely nickname.
It’s the name of the girl you like?
Tell me.
What type of boys do girls like?
Of course, those who’re humorous
and have high EQ.
EQ?
Well.
How can I tell the level of my EQ?
Let me give you a test.
If a girl
says goodnight to you,
how will you respond?
I’ll of course say
goodnight.
Wrong.
You should say
let’s sleep together.
I’m tired.
Have a sweet dream.
Amazing.
Tell me more.
I need to improve my EQ.
Sit well.
If a girl tells you that
today’s weather is good,
how will you respond?
You’re right.
The weather is great.
The sun is shining.
Wrong.
You should say
since today’s weather is great,
we should go on a date together.
Great.
Tell me more.
It’s so useful.
I need to take notes.
It’s raining outside.
A girl tells you that
you should remember
to bring the umbrella.
How will you respond?
Thank you for your concern.
I’ll walk you home.
That will do.
But it’s not good enough.
You should say
you’re so sweet.
You seem to be the type that
makes a good wife.
The mentor can only teach you so much.
You need to practice your skills
on your own.
For these questions,
you need to draw inferences
from one instance.
Also, you can find
a friend of the opposite sex
to practice more.
Hello, beauty.
How’s the weather?
Psycho.
I want to return the book.
Chlorophyll.
Why are you here?
I should be the one who asks this.
- Isn’t it normal that I’m in a bookstore?
- Bye.
Ziye.
I have a question for you.
Go on. Which test?
No.
It’s...
Which book...
Which book do you think is the best?
The best?
That’s hard to say.
But, for you, the best book
should be children’s books.
It’s the book with you in it.
You’re so frivolous.
I bought many food.
Who wants to party at my home?
I’m still in my hometown.
I haven’t come back yet.
I want to.
Me too.
But I have tutoring sessions tonight.
Then this is a date for Meng and me.
Such a God-given opportunity.
If you all can’t go
and I won’t go,
how sad will Meng be?
Chlorophyll, return the book for me.
Congcong’s mom
Do you have extra painkillers at home?
Painkiller?
I have a stomachache.
Are you all right?
Wait.
Lu Miao.
Coming.
Are you okay?
My stomach aches.
Come. Let me help you get inside.
Come. Watch out.
Come. Sit down.
Be careful.
You ate all of this on your own?
Hello.
My friend is having a fever.
This is Room 301, Unit 3, Building 5,
Chenguang Apartment Complex,
Hepingnan Road.
Hello.
We’ve recorded your information.
It’s raining heavily now.
And the road is congested.
We’ll be there as soon as possible.
Are you all right?
Come on. Let me carry you on my back.
Watch out.
Where are we going?
Let’s go to the hospital.
Are you all right? Hang in there.
Put me down.
I can walk on my own.
♪How I wish I could be with you♪
♪I wish to be your fortress♪
♪Looking up at the sky and murmuring♪
♪There’s no regret in time♪
♪For you I don’t care about♪
♪The pain when I get hurt♪
♪Tell you♪
♪Don’t be afraid of darkness♪
♪Wish you to be happy and pure♪
♪Wish you to fly freely♪
♪Don’t worry I’ll protect us♪
♪The original beauty♪
♪When you leave♪
Jiang Haoyue.
♪I’ll be brave♪
♪Smiling♪
♪Give you the perfection you wish for♪
What’s going on?
She’s having a fever.
♪Give you the perfection you wish for♪
♪I wish to fly with you♪
Call the ambulance.
It rains heavily.
Ambulance can’t get in.
♪I wish to fly with you♪
♪I’m afraid that things
go contrary to wishes♪
Come. I can run fast.
I’ll take her to the hospital.
♪That’s the experience I can’t give♪
Her fever is so severe.
♪So let you pursue it♪
♪In every direction♪
♪Guard what is precious to us♪
♪Don’t ask time who I’ll be to you♪
♪I’ll stand quietly behind you♪
♪Accompanying you is enough♪
♪Give you the perfection you wish for♪
♪I wish to fly with you♪
♪I forget that beauty never lasts♪
♪Guard what is precious to us♪
Emergency Room
Have you arrived at the hospital now?
Aunt, don’t worry.
We have arrived.
What did the doctor say?
She just has a fever.
She’s now putting on a drip.
She’ll be fine soon.
Okay.
Thank you for doing this
in such a heavy rain.
Did you get wet?
I’m still home.
I wasn’t the one who sent her there.
Shi Che sent her to the hospital.
What are you looking at?
What’s up there?
Nothing.
Why are you here alone?
I’m practicing walking.
Somehow, I end up here.
Which ward are you in?
Let me walk you back.
No, I want to take some rest.
I hid this.
Let me share one with you.
Practice walking?
Is it hard?
I always fall down.
In the beginning, you’ll fall down.
But mom said that
if I keep working hard,
it will grow back again.
Your mom lied to you.
If you lose your leg,
it will never grow back again.
Why did you say this to a kid?
If you don’t tell him now,
he will be sadder in the future.
What’s your problem?
Forget it. Let’s go.
Are you all right?
I’m fine.
Isn’t that Jiang?
Didn’t he say that
he’s at home?
Let me go and take a look.
How about you?
Go and check on Miao first.
Be careful.
Okay.
Mom.
Mom, wait for me.
Kid.
Are you all right?
Kid, are you okay?
Why are you walking in the rain?
You’ll be drenched.
Ten years ago,
I seem to have heard the same words.
If you have something to say,
let’s go home first.
You’ll get ill in this rain.
I have nothing to say.
My leg has become
what it is now.
It’s all because of you.
I’m sorry.
For all these years,
I always want to make it up to you.
Make it up to me?
How can you?
Ten years ago,
my life completely changed overnight.
How can you make it up to me?
Do you have any idea
how I felt when the person
I want to protect passed out before me
and I couldn’t do anything?
How can you make it up to me?
You want to make up for my leg?
What you really want to make up for
is your guilt.
Hit him.
Don’t play with him.
Right.
Move.
If you dare to bully my brother again,
you’ll be dead.
You’ll be doomed.
Are you okay?
I’ll be fine even if you don’t come.
I protected you out of good intentions.
I don’t need your protection.
Then you thought
I stole your show.
Then why?
How can a younger sister
protect a bigger brother?
Although you’re the bigger brother,
I’m taller than you’re.
I should protect you.
I’ll be taller than you in the future.
Then I’ll protect you now.
And you’ll protect me
when we grow up, okay?
Okay. When I grow up, I’ll protect you.
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪