Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
Flourish in Time
Episode 13
A Night at Old Schoolhouse
I didn’t know that
you have such a hobby.
If you’re kidnapped,
just blink.
Actually,
this is quite fun.
It’s because there’s someone you like.
If you’re to gossip, then I’ll go now.
No. Let’s study.
Jiang Haoyue likes someone?
What should you do then?
I’ll of course take actions.
In the past, I thought
he isn’t interested in romance.
Now since someone has opened his heart,
I must grab this chance
and win him over.
Then what do you plan to do?
I’ll become his destiny.
Hello.
Today, Daifei and I will take you
to explore the widely spread
campus myths.
Daifei, take a look at the camera.
Hurry. It’s pretty late.
Come.
What’s going on?
Is Jiang Haoyue your destiny?
Isn’t that Jiang Haoyue?
When did he appear?
He was tutoring me at home that day.
It was impossible for him to show up
at the old schoolhouse.
So this is a ghost story?
Have you heard of Bai Lin’s Blessing?
It’s one of the seven myths
on our campus.
Story has it that
when the old schoolhouse was first built,
there was a blackout.
Someone played a prank
and locked a senior named Bai Lin
in a classroom.
She couldn’t speak.
To save herself,
she used a mirror to reflect moonlight,
hoping to attract others’ attention.
The moonlight reflected
by the mirror shone on
a boy’s face who was
chilling out in the playground.
That was how he rescued her.
Then their romance started.
How romantic!
But can mirrors reflect moonlight?
Those pranksters were so boring.
You really have your attention
on weird things.
Anyway, since then,
words spread on the campus,
saying,
when moonlight shines on
the old schoolhouse’s mirror,
and you come by,
the mirror will show
the person in your destiny.
Both of them will be blessed by Bai Lin.
And they’ll be together forever.
Su Daifei saw Jiang Haoyue
in the mirror.
They received the blessing.
Then they’ll be together forever?
No way.
I don’t believe it either.
This story only verifies
The Suspension Bridge Effect.
What is it?
When a person
crosses a suspension bridge,
his heart will
uncontrollably beat faster.
If at that time,
he happens to meet a person,
then he will mistake
this racing heartbeat
caused by the circumstance
for having a crush on the other person.
Actually, anyone
will have this illusion of romance
in a terrifying and intense environment.
But the real destined romance
needs to be verified
with solid statistics.
Whether we believe it or not,
people on the campus
are all saying that
they’re a match made in heaven.
A match made in heaven?
Su Daifei must be the one behind it.
I’ve made the decision.
I’ll talk to her face to face.
She is the childhood sweetheart
that Jiang Haoyue likes.
As expected, she’s a bad girl.
How many times have I said it?
I’m not a bad girl.
What’s going on with that video?
Don’t ask.
Daifei was so scared that day.
You were scared?
In the middle of the night,
a man suddenly appeared
out of nowhere in the mirror.
It’s pretty scary
even if that person is Jiang Haoyue.
You didn’t play any tricks?
You’re so mean.
Daifei is always
so scared of such things.
If there’s nothing more,
can we get through?
Have you heard of
our school’s campus myths?
You mean the story of destined romance?
No, not that one.
Legend has it that this corridor
is called the corridor of truth.
If those who pass through
this corridor tell lies,
they’ll be haunted by evil ghosts.
Why is Jiang Haoyue
having lunch with Lu Miao?
Isn’t Su Daifei his destined lover?
Well. If Lu Miao and Su Daifei
fall into water at the same time,
who will Jiang Haoyue save?
Lu Miao.
Sit down.
Why are there always
people talking about you?
Just don’t take
their words personally.
Don’t mind it.
But of course I’ll be angry
at what they say about you.
Have you watched the video
they’re talking about
on the campus forum?
No.
Confucius doesn’t talk about
ghosts and mythical spirits.
Confucius doesn’t talk about it.
But Lu Miao can.
Mr. Jiang,
do you believe in
the campus myths?
No, I don’t.
Myths are made up by people.
You’re already a high school student.
Do you still believe in stories
to trick kids?
Of course, I don’t.
69.
70.
This one is new.
Che, are you reading the comics or not?
Before I redeem myself,
I’ll never read comics again.
You get stronger with every setback.
You fail every time.
But your goals are higher and higher.
Cut out the nonsense.
I’ve already come up with a method.
Come.
Tomorrow, I’ll propose that
we go to the old schoolhouse
to find out the truth about the myth.
You’ll hide there in advance.
Pretend to be a ghost and scare Lu Miao.
When she panics,
I can grab her hands
and hold her in my arms.
By then,
I’ll become her hero
who rides on
the seven auspicious clouds.
I get it.
It’s like The Suspension Bridge Effect
Ziye talked about.
Are you sure that
a special girl like Miao
will be afraid of ghosts?
All girls will be afraid, right?
One of the Seven Myths
Are you really studying?
Of course.
Come. Drink milk and take some rest.
It’s still hot.
Mom, when you were in high school,
were there any strange myths
on the campus?
What?
No. Stop.
Mom. No.
There’s nothing.
Are you reading fiction?
Are you reading legends
or reading myths on your phone?
Nothing.
I’m writing homework.
Then why are you asking me
this question?
Are you distracted?
Listen. Don’t you laugh.
You thought I’m not in this room?
Actually, I have my eyes
fixed on you.
Stop listening to
such unimportant stories.
Listen, Lu Miao,
there are many things
that you shouldn’t believe in blindly.
If you listen to too many lies,
you’ll see them as truths.
Lies are lies.
How can they become truths?
Then you’ll lose your ability to
differentiate between right and wrong.
You read too many comics.
Your imagination is too wild.
Do you know?
Forget it. I’ll talk no more.
You’re just like that every day.
Milk?
I’ll get you another one.
Adults are so weird.
To break the rumors about campus myths.
To break free from
the chains of superstition.
To protect the light
of truth and science.
A brave and great mission.
Shatter superstition.
Explore science.
The innocence of Jiang Haoyue
will be protected by me.
Protect Jiang Haoyue’s innocence?
Anyway, go for it.
You’re not coming?
I’m occupied that day.
I can’t go.
Guoguo, are you scared?
You’re not afraid?
Of course not.
I’ve done nothing wrong.
Look how scared he is.
Your fearlessness scares me though.
Guoguo has weak nerves.
Then he won’t go.
Let’s meet tomorrow at 10:00 PM.
See you there.
Daifei, the teacher wants to see you.
Okay.
Let’s go.
Qu Wei, I’ll go now.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
What are you doing?
I plan on going to the old schoolhouse
to capture the mythical energy.
You’re interested in this?
As a scholar,
I need to be curious about everything.
This is the night vision device.
It allows me to
observe every detail clearly
in the darkness.
I plan to explore tonight.
Will you come with me?
I’m not interested.
I’ll go now.
Bye-bye.
Che.
Will I get beaten by Miao later?
No. Just show yourself in the distance.
Make some noise.
Pat her shoulder at most.
Fine. Hurry up.
I’m still logged in on the video game.
Don’t worry.
Follow my command later.
There they are.
I’ll hide now.
Okay. Hurry.
Faster.
Okay.
Che.
You’re pretty early today.
I’m waiting for you.
Who were you talking to?
No, I was alone.
I just...
Both of you!
Don’t create a horrifying atmosphere
in advance.
Open it. Hurry.
Wait. Why is the door locked?
The guide didn’t say
it would be locked.
What should we do now?
The plan can’t keep up
with the changes.
You need to depend on me
at crucial moments.
Chlorophyll, borrow me your hair pin.
Can you do it or not?
Let’s take a rain check if you can’t.
Who said I can’t?
You have to call me Dad.
You wish.
Thank you, lock picking expert.
Hurry. Why are you posing there?
Okay.
Science.
Reason.
It’s fine, Ziye.
There must be someone
who’s playing a prank.
The noise seems to
come from the second floor.
Let’s go upstairs now.
Go.
We’re heading to the second floor. Hide!
Okay. I’ll be there soon.
Buy me some time.
Wait for me.
Che, don’t make strange noises.
What are you doing?
Are we going back?
How about
picking it up when we come back?
This...
Shi Che, after you.
Ladies first. After you.
If you’re both scared,
let me go in first.
- I’m not scared.
I’ll go first.
How about this?
I’ll say one, two, three.
Let’s go inside together.
One. Two. Three.
Who is it?
Your performance is so amazing.
Qu Wei, why are you here?
I’m on an adventure.
How about you?
We’re here to explore science
and get rid of superstition.
When did you come here?
Half an hour ago.
Half an hour?
Then I came here
ten minutes earlier than you did.
You came here earlier?
How did you get in
when the door was locked?
From the backdoor.
The backdoor wasn’t locked.
You didn’t know?
Was the noise made by you?
How’s that possible?
It was from this.
It was made by this radio.
I turned it off when I came in.
Seems that there’s another person here.
Coming.
- Mr. Lu.
- Haoyue.
Miao is still studying?
Yes.
I heard from the weather broadcast that
it will rain heavily tonight.
I need to pick up Aunt Fang.
Listen.
Take the keys.
When Miao is done with studying,
let her go home on her own.
I see.
Close the door.
Where can she be
in the middle of the night?
Look.
Here’s a pair of embroidered shoes.
Made in Putian
These shoes are bought recently.
Seems that someone placed them here
purposefully to scare people.
There must be more.
Let’s search.
Okay.
What?
Do you have tissue?
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Hurry. Clean it.
Guoguo, if you don’t show up soon,
they’ll get used to
the horror atmosphere.
I’m ready.
Guide them to the lecture room.
This is paint.
It’s also new.
It hasn’t even dried yet.
Where’s the mirror in the myth?
We haven’t been to the lecture room yet.
Is it in the lecture room?
Why not take a look?
Let’s take a look. Come.
Come on.
Someone is playing a prank.
I’ll definitely find you.
Don’t touch me. It tickles.
I didn’t touch you.
I’ve been looking for you all night.
You finally showed up.
Freeze.
Don’t run.
Move.
Freeze.
Let’s go.
Where is everyone?
Why have they all disappeared?
Don’t be afraid. I’ll protect you.
You’re so touched
that you can’t even speak?
Actually, Meng,
I think you and I are like
Hanamichi Sakuragi and
Haruko Akagi,
Naruto and Sasuke,
Inuyasha and Kagome,
Yang Guo and his condor.
Anyway, I think we’re a perfect match.
I think we can
take our friendship to the next level.
I know.
You don’t have to answer me in a hurry.
I...
I can...
You got the wrong person.
Chlorophyll.
The first half is fine.
But why Yang Guo and his condor?
I’m totally defeated by you.
You didn’t forget about love confession
when fleeing for your life.
No wonder
you’re an active user of
the forum’s romance section.
How do you know?
You’re Unswayed by Spring Breeze?
Nice to meet you.
So you’re the one
who came up with those bad ideas?
Those ideas are good.
But you’re not the right person.
What else can I do?
I don’t believe you.
Smart kids are so cunning.
I’ll let the whole school know that
the Study Representative likes to
read romance novels.
Then tomorrow everyone will know that
the principal’s son is in love.
And his affection is unreciprocated.
Let’s find out
who’ll be more embarrassed.
Who is it?
Guoguo?
Is that you?
Why is Qu Wei always following me?
It’s so hard to get rid of him.
Su Daifei?
Why is she here?
Fine.
Why are you here?
Ghost!
It’s me.
Freeze.
Don’t get away.
- No way. It’s him again?
- Freeze.
He didn’t catch up, right?
Help.
Don’t run.
Hello.
You’re at the old schoolhouse?
Yes.
Did you see Lu Miao?
She was...
She was right behind me just now.
I don’t know where she went.
Find her for me.
Fine. I’ll go now.
Stop.
Su Daifei.
I knew it was you.
Where did you hide the mirror?
I should have picked up
my phone earlier.
Jiang Haoyue.
Why are you here?
I know this event isn’t so simple.
Where are you going?
In the video,
the light in the mirror is odd.
Did you use mirroring
to process my photo?
You knew I lied
but you didn’t expose me.
Do you...
like me a little bit?
You thought too much.
I just don’t think it’s necessary
to care for the rumors.
Actually, I regret it a lot.
I shouldn’t have lied.
The campus myths are real.
I’m haunted by evil ghosts recently.
Jiang Haoyue.
I’m so scared.
Can you walk me out, please?
Sorry.
I’m here to pick up Lu Miao.
Do me a favor.
I’m on the first floor.
Come here.
Qu Wei will come to pick you up later.
Don’t do such
boring things again.
Jiang Haoyue.
My battery is dead.
Mine too.
Are you still scared?
How about you?
I’m a bit scared, too.
I dare not to make a move.
We can’t just stay here all night.
Let’s be courageous and run out.
I don’t want to see weird things.
Then cover your eyes.
How am I supposed to walk
with my eyes covered?
I can hold your hands.
I don’t want to hear weird noises.
Then cover your ears as well.
Come. I’ll go with you.
Come on.
Can you hear what I’m saying?
What?
I’m saying that
you should say something, too.
I’m scared as well.
What should I say?
Say something to ward off evil spirits.
3.1415926.
It’s a wood stick.
It’s fine. Let’s go.
So weird. Where’s everyone?
Calm down.
Science.
It’s just an average mirror.
How can it tell my destiny?
Jiang Haoyue.
Watch out.
Are you all right?
Jiang Haoyue, are you okay?
I’m fine.
You scared me to death.
I...
You’re scared?
If anything happens to you,
do you have any idea
how worried your parents will be?
Don’t sneak out alone at night again.
Do you hear me?
I get it.
My dad sent you to look for me?
Can you not
tell him that I came here?
No.
They didn’t know.
Hurry and leave.
Okay.
It’s a shame that
Qu Wei doesn’t play basketball.
His stamina is incredible.
Stop.
I’ll definitely catch you today.
Aren’t you escorting me out?
Yes.
On the way out,
we can find out the truth.
Don’t you want to know
the look of the creature
that scared you?
I don’t.
64462 29489.
5493.
How did you memorize
such boring figures?
This is not boring.
Pi is very significant in mathematics.
You can hear me?
Here are the staircases.
Beware of the staircases.
There are two more.
It’s all right. We’re out.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
Without your boring Pi,
I wouldn’t dare to come out.
Look behind you!
Let go of me, Che.
Let go of me.
Fortunately, you went home in time.
It rained so suddenly.
Right.
I experienced too much horror tonight.
I’ll go to bed now, bye.
Okay. See you tomorrow at school.
When your dad and mom ask you later,
don’t accidentally spill the secret.
In case they get worried.
Rest assured.
I’ll do as you told me to.
Listen.
Don’t believe in such rumors
from now on.
Do you hear me?
But I indeed heard weird noises
in the old schoolhouse.
Su Daifei made those noises
on purpose.
That’s the truth?
But Su Daifei’s video...
That video was edited.
How can there be a destined lover?
Even if the video is fake,
I still believe in
the myth of destined lovers.
Why?
Because I’ve met mine.
Let me blow-dry your hair.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
You’ll just give up on Jiang Haoyue?
There’s nothing else I can do.
I was wrong the whole time.
Jiang Haoyue has indeed
opened his heart,
but only to Lu Miao.
Recording of the ghost event
at No. 1 High School.
This is my ring tone.
I placed the embroidered shoes
near the window.
The red hand prints were left by me
when I was wiping my hands.
I left the skeleton lying on the floor.
This was Su Daifei’s crying sound.
That figure with long hair was Guoguo.
It’s me.
You even recorded all of this?
No, I didn’t.
There was someone besides us that day?
That’s impossible.
I searched the whole building
before I left.
There was no one else.
When we left,
we locked the front gate again.
Who recorded this?
Dad, how does this work?
When will it be ready?
I wanna take photos.
Soon.
Let me take a look.
Haoyue, move a bit.
Okay. Go.
Go.
Slow down. Haoyue. Come.
Let me lift you up.
Sit tight.
Okay.
Come.
Don’t be scared. Relax.
Look. Like me.
Haoyue.
Relax. It’s fine.
Come.
Great.
When I was young,
I mistook moon for white plate.
You’re wrong.
It’s white jade plate.
You’re not the only one
who knows a lot.
Let me ask you.
What’s on the moon?
Lunar craters. Argon, Helium,
Natrium, Kalium, and Hydrogen.
You’re wrong.
Then tell me what’s on the moon.
Of course, there’re Chang’e,
Jade Rabbit and Sailor Moon.
Sailor what?
Smile.
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪