Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
=Flourish in Time=
=Episode 9=
=Beauty Daifei and Beast Lu Miao=
For the School New Year Gala,
two hosts will be chosen from liberal
art class and science class each.
Is there any volunteer?
(Class 10, Grade 1)
At the School New Year Gala,
our class must present a performance.
Is there any volunteer
for it?
Sir, I will!
I can eat a watermelon in ten seconds!
I can bring the house down with a dunk!
Sir, I can do everything!
The study is intensive in our class,
but we should play an active role
in the school event.
Sir, choose me!
Ziye.
The New Year Gala!
Don’t you wanna join it?
I’m not good at performance.
What matters is to participate.
We’ll have fun with the rehearsal.
Sir, look here!
Well.
Since you are all so active...
Let’s do it together.
This week,
get your performance ready.
Let’s score the performances
on the class meeting next week
and choose a representative
for our class.
How is it?
Yes!
I’ll place a ballot box on the podium.
You will vote for the candidates.
It’s bad to be chosen.
Our study will be affected.
Put it in when you decide it.
We’ll count votes
at the class meeting next week.
I don’t want to go.
Alright. Silence.
Discuss it after class.
Continue to study.
It’s bad to be chosen.
Our study will be affected.
We four can form a group for the gala.
People will be overwhelmingly amazed
at our courage
and wisdom.
I have only one thought.
I wanna play princess.
(Stop)
Boring.
I’m energetic at any performance.
Do you agree, Meng?
I wanna
play a role
that I’ve ever experienced before,
like
a straight-A student.
Is there any performance
that I can have fun
being a straight-A student?
We have different ideas.
Why don’t we prepare separately?
That won’t do.
It’s more fun
when we prepare for the gala together.
Exactly.
Friendship is the best memory of youth.
I agree with it.
What’s the use of that?
If our group performance
isn’t chosen,
it will be all in vain.
What to do then?
Look at this.
That’s child’s play.
Is this child’s play?
If so,
I have to do something big.
With all due respect,
I can’t believe my eyes.
Hey.
I voted for you to be the host.
I’ll vote for you.
No kidding.
I’m serious.
You aren’t afraid that
your study will be affected.
Are you afraid?
(Qu Wei)
I’m experienced in formation.
This is the stage where we’ll perform.
Guoguo will perform here.
Lu Miao will be here.
This is me.
You and I will perform together.
No.
Lu Miao will be my partner.
You will be
the discarded robots I brought back
from an Arabian desert.
Why is it Arabia?
That’s the plot.
Every show has the plot.
What’s my role?
You will
wear a beautiful uniform
smile by my side,
and walk with the rhythm.
I can do an Arabic basketball show,
with the music and beats.
That will be cool.
Sounds like a good idea.
It can be named
“Western Arabian Basketball”.
This is good.
Isn’t it more awesome?
Since it’s a sci-fi theme,
I’ll play that scientist.
In the end,
you’ll all be modified by me
into super evolutionary robots.
Why will you be the scientist?
Since you are the scientist,
I can be a scientist, too.
Given your IQ,
you can’t be a scientist!
What’s wrong with my IQ?
Your IQ is low.
Alright. Stop.
What’s wrong with my low IQ?
We are a perfect match.
She is my partner.
And she likes comics.
So do I.
We can work together.
You’re a muscle-headed fool.
Don’t you know it?
I...
Performing with Shi Che,
I think that will be a disaster
in my memory.
Shi Che is a nice guy.
Why can’t you get along with him?
He is self-conceit,
with low IQ.
He even dragged you down
at the autumn tour.
Do you forget it?
Never mind.
You two are of the same kind.
We can be friends.
Why can’t you be friends with him?
Give me a break.
Ballot box.
Hello, sir.
Who will you vote to be the host?
Jiang Haoyue.
He has no pressure from study.
We think alike.
Who do you think they will vote?
Jiang Haoyue.
You are surprisingly popular.
At the morning exercise,
I overheard your classmates
that they’d vote for you to be the host.
What?
Aren’t you happy about that?
I’m not interested.
Blockhead.
Youth
is not just about study.
Some other memories are needed.
Did you sign up?
Yes.
Ziye, Shi Che,
Guoguo and I.
The four of us formed a group.
We’ll perform a robot dance.
It’s almost the end of the term.
Don’t get your study affected.
Or Aunt Fang will scold you again.
I know.
But I have you.
The host. Think about it.
Why?
Then we can rehearse
and go home together
after school.
I can wait for you as well.
(Math Test Paper for Grade 1)
Did I do it wrong again?
You’ve never done it right.
(Class 10, Grade 1)
Hello, guys.
I’m a scientist from Arabia.
Lu Miao.
The gala host has been voted.
Is it my brother?
There will be two hosts.
The host of liberal art class
is chosen.
Who?
Su Daifei.
How come it’s her?
(Class 1, Grade 2)
The host of liberal art class
has been voted.
I know.
It’s Su Daifei.
The school belle.
Jiang Haoyue.
If you are selected,
you two will be a good match.
Are you envious?
Why didn’t you go for the host?
Yes.
Yes. Qu Wei.
You can be the host.
Me?
Hosts have to rehearse.
A waste of time.
I’m not that interested.
Are you?
Don’t you wanna beat me once
in popularity?
Yes. You can vie for it
and beat him fair and square.
But the voting...
No worries.
Leave it to me.
Your sister is so passionate about me.
Don’t overthink.
I’m not interested in her.
I like beauties.
Do you mean she’s ugly?
No.
She’s beautiful.
So, are you interested in her?
Do your exercises.
Classmates from Class 1, Grade 2!
Look here!
I’m glad to recommend a host to you,
Qu Wei!
Excuse me.
He is an excellent student,
humorous and handsome!
Lu Miao.
What do you think of him?
We’ve cast the vote.
He’s good,
but we’ve cast votes
for Jiang Haoyue.
What about you?
I haven’t voted.
Please vote for Qu Wei!
He really wants to be the host!
I’ll think about it.
Excuse me.
Think about it.
What’s the fuss?
You’re making it like a debut.
Do it with me.
Smile and wave your hands.
Hey, guys!
Please vote for Qu Wei!
Bow.
Guys!
Qu Wei!
No. I’m going back.
He’s excellent and humorous.
Guys,
please vote for Qu Wei!
Look here, guys!
Stop.
Qu Wei is a perfect host
(Qu Wei)
for the New Year gala!
Look here, guys!
You won’t be disappointed!
Guys!
(Ballot box)
Be sure to vote for Qu Wei!
Guoguo.
Hello.
Where are they?
They went to canvass for Qu Wei.
Qu Wei?
Are they so close already?
No idea.
You come in time.
Let’s practice.
I won’t.
I’m adept at basketball.
I’m gonna buy snacks.
You practice first.
But...
Excuse me. Please vote for Qu Wei!
Let him be the host
and win honor for your class!
But I’ve voted for Jiang Haoyue.
Don’t bother.
21 students have voted for Jiang Haoyue.
Just 21.
How can you give up so easily?
Lu Miao.
He means,
there are 40 students in his class.
21 is already over a half.
Your friend is much smarter than you.
Your brother will be chosen.
Why are you more disappointed than me?
We should find another way.
You can just wait
and expect your brother’s show.
I...
I’m off.
Just accept it.
Jiang Haoyue
is bound to host with Su Daifei
together.
Let’s go for classes.
Come to the Tech building.
Emergency.
He’s fooled away.
Qu Wei.
What are you doing?
Mr. Yang.
This matter has nothing to do
with my student Qu Wei.
Lu Miao. What’s going on?
Yes,
it has nothing to do with him.
Why did you fake votes for him?
I...
It’s not all her fault.
I did want to be the host.
Just to choose a host.
Why bother to vote?
It’s messed up now.
Yes.
Other than Qu Wei,
who else are the candidates?
Jiang Haoyue.
Your class may let him be the host.
We should respect the students’ choice.
Don’t talk.
Go.
(Hosts: Jiang Haoyue, Su Daifei)
I meant to waive at the vote counting.
Your sister has skipped it for you.
Daifei, look. Jiang Haoyue.
Jiang Haoyue.
Glad to be your partner.
See you at the rehearsal.
It’s fine.
Let’s go for classes.
Thanks to your assist,
next week, Su Daifei and your brother
will be in the rehearsal room
as partners.
They’ll write the host script together,
becoming soulmates
when they have a brainstorm.
And even...
Cut it out.
I’m wrong. Okay?
No wonder she helped Qu Wei canvass.
Luckily, she failed.
God bless me.
I’m thinking,
we seldom
rehearsed the dance.
Will it be messed up?
Don’t worry. We work well together.
Rehearsal is unnecessary.
Next group.
Basketball Robot High Show.
Let’s go. It’s our turn.
On your feet!
Come on!
I’ve watched your dance.
There’s no teamwork at all.
But Chen Guoguo, individually,
your performance was good.
So, I decided to
let you go for the gala
on behalf of our class.
Mr. Wen.
I don’t wanna go alone.
Lu Miao, Shi Che, Xie Ziye.
They also did a lot for this dance.
We just didn’t rehearse well.
We’ll rehearse
and it’ll be completely different.
I promise.
Mr. Wen.
They are my best friends.
By this dance,
we wanna leave a wonderful memory
in our youth.
You need to support us.
Also,
Lu Miao and Shi Che will
spend a lot of time on the rehearsal.
You can relax as well.
Mr. Wen.
Okay.
I believe you.
That said,
you must practice harder
before the gala.
Don’t disgrace our class.
Yes, you have my word!
Good luck.
We really screwed it up.
That was expected.
Don’t be so pessimistic.
We’ll have a gala next year.
Guys.
Our dance
was chosen!
What? How is that possible?
Yes. Mr. Wen asked us to practice hard
and win honor for the class.
Are we so lucky?
We made it!
Great!
Is it so-called protagonist privilege?
Go.
Jiang Haoyue, the program list is out.
I wanna discuss with you
about the host script.
Wait for me.
It’s gonna be late.
Go.
I’m going first.
We did well today,
but I think the script should
be revised.
Right?
Okay.
Jiang, do you have any idea
about the costume?
I have a white shirt.
White shirt is good.
How come she’s still with him?
It must look good on you.
A tie is also very important.
Do you have a tie?
No.
It doesn’t matter.
I’m gonna rent costumes
for my classmates.
I can rent some ties for you.
No, thanks.
We should prepare meticulously.
Hey.
You boys never care about these things.
Let me see what kind of ties suit you.
Black ones suit you better.
What do you think?
What is it?
I can rent a tie myself.
Bye.
Miao.
You know.
Your mom is out for business,
while we are idle at home.
It’s not appropriate, right?
You must be hungry.
How about
we go to a restaurant with Jiang?
I won’t.
He might’ve had dinner.
I’m not hungry.
My mom will buy meals back.
I don’t wanna go out.
Are you all right, Miao?
Are you at odds with Jiang?
Nope.
It’s not about him.
Dad.
Our school is gonna
hold the New Year Gala.
I will perform.
What will you perform?
The four of us
will integrate a scientist,
robots, basketball,
these three things
into a dance.
Popping dance?
You got the right person.
What do you mean?
I was nicknamed Popping Dance King
in the school.
Really?
Yes.
Come on.
Dad, teach me.
Let me teach you.
Robot.
Stay still.
Go back.
Dad. Do it slowly.
Wait. Dad.
Your dance
doesn’t feel like popping dance.
It’s more like disco for the elder.
Of course not.
This is the disco for the elder.
Your mom is back early.
Hurry. I’ll tidy the dining table.
You, the coffee table.
Hurry.
Miao. Hurry.
Okay.
Hurry.
Coming.
Uncle Lu.
Jiang.
Come on in.
I’m here for Miao. Is she at home?
Yes.
Miao.
Jiang is here for you.
No!
What’s with her temper?
She’ll be fine after some sleep.
Never mind. I’m going home to rest.
Good night, Uncle Lu.
Take care.
Okay. I’m on my way.
Uncle Lu.
Morning.
Jiang.
Are you waiting for Miao?
She has left.
Didn’t she call you?
No.
Look.
Let me drive you to school.
No. It’s early.
I still have time.
I’m leaving.
What possessed you to do this?
What do you mean?
Studying here so early
isn’t your style.
You come in time.
Check this.
Did I write the equation right?
Doesn’t Jiang Haoyue
usually check it for you?
He’s been very busy.
I don’t wanna bother him.
Your tongue sounds jealous.
Is it because of
his partner Su Daifei?
Don’t mention them.
No need.
Many people like Jiang Haoyue,
but he likes none of them.
This time is different.
Yesterday ,
I saw Su Daifei touched him,
yet he didn’t even refuse.
Touch?
That intimate?
Does he have feelings for her?
Look, Che.
I’ve designed a new move.
Look.
This is good.
How about we rotate the ball?
Like this.
Guoguo, you are amazing!
That’s easy.
I can do it, too.
I’m good.
It’s kung fu.
Save it.
Is that kung fu?
Shame on you.
I practiced when I was little,
I’m out of practice now.
Miao.
Have a try.
Like this?
From below.
Like this.
Jiang Haoyue is incredibly cool.
Daifei. Can you get his autograph
for me?
Why do you want his autograph?
It’s the end of the term.
I want it
to inspire me for the exams.
Okay. I’ll ask him about it.
Daifei, I’m envious that
you can rehearse with him.
Yes. Me too.
Delete his photos you shot secretly!
I didn’t shoot secretly.
You are lying!
Why are you so angry?
Does she like Jiang Haoyue?
But Jiang sees her as his sister.
No.
That’s not true.
He isn’t my brother!
It’s normal that you are anxious.
Don’t worry.
You’ll soon get used to it.
Bye.
Hello, sir.
Hello.
Lu Miao.
What are you doing?
I’m practicing tap dancing.
Hello, sir.
Add a line before this program.
What’s wrong with it?
Good.
This is the time we agreed upon.
Right.
Regain your strength.
We’ll go home late these days.
I don’t eat this.
Hey!
Sorry.
We scheduled to practice here at five.
Really?
My schedule is at five, too.
It’s approved by different teachers.
No wonder the time conflicts.
What to do now?
Let them use it.
Let us?
There’s no need.
Hey.
I have a good idea.
This classroom is big.
We can occupy a half each.
Yes.
Distinguished leaders.
Dear teachers, classmates”.
Happy New Year.
Welcome to
the New Year Gala of
Nanfeng No. 1 High School.
How time flies.
It’s been a wonderful year.
Come.
Meng, let me teach you.
Do it together.
Two, two, three, four.
In an instant,
it’s time to say goodbye...
Five, six, seven, eight.
Three, two, three.
Meng.
I can’t hear the music. Turn it up.
Thanks to Luo Mengjie
from Class 5, Grade 1.
What about now?
OK.
Let me show you again.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two, three, four.
I can’t do it. Show me again.
Let me show you.
Five, six, seven, eight.
The lovers are rowing a boat.
Two, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
It’s like this here.
Three, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Jiang Haoyue, wait for me!
Can you do it now?
Our products
boast a great advantage
on price-performance ratio.
It’s true.
Let me tell you.
Rest assured.
What’s wrong?
We’ll talk about the discount.
Really.
The quality
is exclusive.
The price is...
Wash your hands.
Get ready for dinner.
I cooked the dishes today.
Don’t hesitate.
You may consider it.
Be sure to tell me
before 9 o’clock.
Be sure to tell me then.
Go wash your hands.
This product is very popular now.
Okay.
I’ll call you later.
What are you doing?
Practice Qigong?
Go ahead.
Call Jiang here for dinner.
I won’t call him!
Many girls treat him to dinner.
He won’t come!
Why are you so mad?
What are you angry for?
Isn’t my cooking good?
Mr. Liu.
I’d like to ask you about the price
of math cram classes.
After you.
Childish.
Hope you like the hair pin.
Didn’t your brother tell you?
We bought that hair pin together.
I know.
This girlish thing
doesn’t suit me.
You better keep it.
After all, he bought it for you.
(Class 1, Grade 2)
What’s wrong?
Su Daifei chose it!
I don’t want it!
Take it back.
Is she Jiang Haoyue’s sister?
They are arguing.
Let’s talk at home.
Don’t you go home!
You hear that?
So loud.
She told him not to go home.
Jiang Haoyue ended up like this.
Who could expect that?
What’s their relationship exactly?
I’m not upset!
He can be close to anyone.
What is it got to do with me?
We are just
childhood friends.
Gazing for ten seconds
can’t prove anything!
Just a hair pin.
It’s no big deal.
It’s not worth being upset!
I hate Jiang Haoyue!
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Jiang Haoyue.
My dad said you’d return to school.
Yes.
Great!
We can go to school together now!
What are you reading?
Your hands are dirty.
Alright. They’re clean now.
I’m reading Journey to the West.
And you got it away.
Can you understand it?
Of course.
No, you certainly can’t.
You are in Grade 2.
I’m in Grade 3.
I’m always one grade higher than you.
I can understand it,
but you can’t.
That’s not true!
I know Journey to the West.
I watched it on TV two days ago.
There were White Bone Spirit,
Gold Kid, Silver Kid,
and...
It’s Golden Horn Demon King
and Silver Horn Demon King.
Alright. I didn’t watch it.
I don’t know Journey to the West.
You can ask me about Ultraman Tiga.
The Ultra-Ancient Monster Gorzan.
Rock Monster Gakuma.
Do you know these?
You are in Grade 3,
yet you don’t know them.
Why don’t you
teach me to read?
I don’t know it.
It’s 6 o’clock!
It begins!
Miao, come to eat.
It’s delicious.
I’ll eat after this show.
Hurry. Come to eat.
Hurry up.
It’s getting cold.
I’ll eat them up.
I’m watching
my favorite Journey to the West!
Miao.
Isn’t Ultraman your favorite?
I don’t like that.
I’m watching my favorite
Journey to the West!
You don’t know me!
I don’t know you?
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪