♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
=Flourish in Time=
=Episode 4=
=The Significance of Being No. 1=
Say something.
Jiang Haoyue’s so serious.
He’s a super straight-A student.
I don’t know what to say to him.
You’re a good student. Say something.
Would you like to clean your tableware?
Don’t bother.
We’ll do it ourselves.
We will.
Thank you.
Che,
try the chili sauce. It’s super spicy.
You’ll feel too hot to speak.
Try some.
Miao,
Che is always afraid of spicy food.
Nonsense!
How can a real man
be afraid of spicy food?
Try some, then.
Look, he’s funny.
Have some water.
Aren’t you afraid of inner fever
when eating so much chili sauce?
I won’t have inner fever.
Be careful.
If you get chili stain on your T-shirt,
it can’t be washed away.
Eat more meat.
You should eat less.
Have more vegetables.
She has been holding her phone lately.
At first, I thought
she liked you.
Then I knew you were her brother.
Lu Miao told me about you.
Thank you for helping her
with the application problems.
He doesn’t help a lot.
I’m clever enough.
And you often urge me to study.
Reflect on yourself
why you always keep others worry.
We’re sitting across the table.
What are you whispering?
Tell me about it.
Don’t ask.
Aren’t you coming for food?
Che, this tastes great.
Try some. It’s delicious.
Meng,
do you like any boy in our high school?
No.
Your brother sounds like a parent.
Don’t learn from him.
He looks like a stick-in-the-mud
and he’s always cold.
Che, stop.
Don’t ask for it.
Jiang Haoyue is horrible.
What are you talking about?
He isn’t a stick-in-the-mud.
He isn’t cold, either.
He’s just too cool to reach.
He’s my model for progress.
Ziye,
don’t get choked.
Wipe your mouth.
I’m fine.
The water is just too hot.
Isn’t it cold water?
Shi Che is enthusiastic to you.
Yes.
He and I kind of have similar interests.
But he’s just an outgoing boy.
He’s nice to everyone.
He is?
What about you?
How was your training course?
Not bad.
What happened to your rival?
He lost.
I knew it!
My luck charm must have helped.
It’s because of probability.
What probability?
My luck charm helped.
Where’s it?
Did you lose it?
In my pocket.
The right one.
By the way,
have you maintained
your fifth position to last?
Go. Be quick.
Go back home.
My mother has made cordyceps soup
for three days,
waiting for you.
Let’s go.
(Class 10, Grade 1)
Meng,
let me show you something great.
It’s a magic weapon to pass exams.
What’s it?
With Conan around,
you’ll come through all exams.
Class,
turn off telecommunication facilities.
(Class 1, Grade 2)
If you have any doubt during the exam,
raise your hand and ask me.
No students shall come in
when he’s late for over 15 minutes.
You can’t hand in the paper
until one hour after it starts.
May I come in?
Come in.
Take that seat.
Students in the first row,
pass the papers on.
Jiang Haoyue,
it’s been a while.
I never expected to be
your desk mate.
But you won’t win this time.
When the bell rings,
you must stop immediately.
So, manage your time properly.
(Ranking of the Monthly Test)
The scores came out.
Let’s go have a look.
I wouldn’t like to go.
I’m sure I’m not on the ranking list.
Why don’t you check it for your brother?
I don’t need to.
He must be No. 1 again.
Let’s go have a look.
Jiang Haoyue is No. 2?
Jiang Haoyue?
Then who’s No. 1?
No. 2?
Excuse me.
Who’s Qu Wei?
According to my father,
he’s a top student
we got from No. 5 High School.
My brother was defeated?
He’s at least No. 2.
Do you need to worry so much?
But he was always No. 1.
As a student who failed the exams,
why do you worry about him?
Failed?
Two subjects.
Physics and Biology.
How did you know?
I brought you your report.
Who allowed you?!
You only passed two exams?
It’s already hard, OK?
Let me have a look.
Politics, 39 points.
Qu Wei?
(Ranking of the Monthly Test)
Jiang Haoyue,
did you check the scores?
Yes.
You’ll admit defeat, won’t you?
What?
You’re too scared
to say anything?
What are you doing?
Our group is on duty today.
Wipe the outer side of the windows.
(Teachers’ Office)
Mr. Wen,
what’s wrong?
Nothing.
Scores of the Monthly Test
have been announced.
My class is the last again.
And it’s still one of my students
who has the lowest scores in the grade.
They’re in Grade 1 now.
Why do you panic?
Chen,
when you taught Grade 1,
you were the strictest.
Mr. Wen,
this is when you must panic.
So…
What can I do?
Who’s the class teacher, you or I?
Well,
you must keep rules
for reward and punishment.
Don’t let anything
that is against the rule happen.
You’re softhearted.
If you don’t do something,
you can’t restrain your students.
Remember,
there’re no bad students,
but only poor teachers.
Enough, Ms. Lei.
Could you stop?
Mr. Wen just became a class teacher.
He and his students need time to grow.
Chen,
don’t go too far.
Jiang Haoyue and Qu Wei
in your class
are both candidates for top scorers.
Your work is quite easy.
The tea is so hot.
I’m going to check on my class.
You’ve done the survey so quickly?
I roughly collected the intel
and got some basic information.
But he’s now No. 1 on my ranking list.
What?
My brother isn’t No. 1?
Come on.
It’s just a monthly test.
Why are you also...?
Why did you change so quickly?
I didn’t change.
The recorded students changed.
Tell me.
What makes Qu Wei better
than my brother?
- Expectations.
- Expectations?
Yes.
Jiang Haoyue has always been No. 1.
Everyone is used
to his first place.
Suddenly, a transfer student appeared,
who is as good as Jiang Haoyue
and may even be stronger.
He’s absolutely eye-catching.
You just want something fresh, right?
Wait.
My brother will be No. 1 again.
Let’s wait and see.
For this Chemistry Tryout,
our school has only one quota.
Jiang Haoyue,
you’re better at Physics.
Why don’t you apply for Physics
and give this chance to Qu Wei?
Mr. Chen,
I want to strive for this chance.
I don’t need him to give me the chance.
A great man cannot
brook a rival.
I’ve compiled some files for the tryout.
Take them back to class
and review them
with other contestants.
I’ll leave you alone,
if you want nothing else.
All right.
(Laboratory Building)
In the training camp,
I saw how you operated.
Not bad.
I hear you’re good at Physics.
When you go to the Physics Contest
and I go to the Chemistry Contest,
we can both be No. 1.
But you insist on competing with me?
Are you kidding me?
I don’t know
why you made such an unwise decision.
But I want you to be fully prepared.
The tryout of our school is carried out
according to the provincial contest,
containing the theoretical experiment
and the experimental operation.
Even if you have
as much knowledge as me,
how many Olympic experiments
have you done?
You won’t defeat me.
Thank you for cooperation.
When you leave,
remember to close the door.
That’s Qu Wei?
I heard that
you would knock him out
in the Chemistry Tryout.
I’m not very confident.
I understand how you feel.
But don’t lose confidence for that.
Look.
I failed two exams in the monthly test.
But I didn’t give up on myself.
The failure of the monthly test
can be a minor setback.
Anyway, being No. 2 is already awesome.
Students gossip about you at school.
Don’t care about that.
I always support you.
So...?
So, I’m enlightening you.
I don’t study as well as you.
But you must admit that
I have more experience than you
in psychological construction.
I should thank you then.
Are you confident now?
No.
Then why must you compete with him?
Why don’t you
pick the Physics Contest?
Don’t worry.
(How to help others with Chemistry?)
So many words.
You’re writing a composition?
I’m helping Jiang Haoyue
to look for methods
to improve his Chemistry.
A poor student like you
helps a straight-A student
to improve his study?
Amazing.
You’re sticking your nose
where it doesn’t belong.
Why don’t you improve your own study?
Mom,
helping others may make our own day.
When I’m helping him,
I’m also helping myself.
Good.
Very good.
When you fail an exam again,
I’ll put a password
to your computer.
It hurts!
Mom!
- Let go of me!
- What do you think?
Let go of me!
It hurts, doesn’t it?
Remember how it feels.
Study hard!
I know.
Washing it yourself?
Why didn’t you have it washed?
To save money.
What I told you last time...
I don’t have money.
I’m pushed hard lately.
I’ll pay you back when I have money.
I’ll pay a 3% rate on it,
all right?
I have my own family to raise.
I don’t have spare money!
Don’t try to fool me!
You won’t lend me money, huh?
Lin Wenfang!
What are you doing?
Are you nuts?
Fine.
I’ll keep a hundred for fuel charging.
Who are you disgusting?
You think I’m a beggar?
You…!
(From Dad,
I’m not coming back tonight.)
(Pass All Exams)
(How to help others with Chemistry?)
(Class 1, Grade 2)
You want to defeat me with such stuff?
It’s child’s play in contests.
Besides, the last experimental operation
depends on accumulated experience.
You won’t defeat me.
I underlined the key notes.
I don’t want you
to make mistakes on basic parts.
Don’t lose too badly.
Thanks.
I still won’t show mercy.
We’re rivals.
Rivals!
(Pass All Exams
Chemistry Treasury)
Meng.
You’re eating a lot, aren’t you?
I’m sad.
I’m drowning my sorrow in food.
What makes you sad?
My brother.
Everyone says he’ll lose.
But I don’t believe that.
I support you.
Your brother will win!
Good friend!
Do you always win a bet?
Yes.
How about this?
Let’s make a bet.
You bet on Jiang Haoyue
and I bet on Qu Wei.
You bet on Qu Wei?
No.
Trust me.
I can explain.
What if it doesn’t work after I explain?
Anyway, trust me.
I’m on your side.
I’ll go see you for the review.
I don’t have time.
Go find someone better.
What...?
What are you doing?
You always support him, don’t you?
Since I was born,
I’ve lost all bets.
So, I bet on Qu Wei this time.
He’s very likely to lose.
I have to bear disgrace for the moment.
It’s an awesome idea.
But now that we make a bet,
there should be a stake.
Or what if it doesn’t work?
What stake?
For example,
the loser shall promise something
to the winner.
What do you think?
Are you having some strange idea
to fool me?
How’s that possible?
I’ll never do that.
Besides, you’re likely to win, too.
I want you to win, then.
Don’t worry.
I promise you
your brother will certainly win.
Good friend.
(Teachers’ Office)
(Chemistry)
Xie Kexue (Science)?
Why isn’t it Xie Zhexue (Philosophy)?
It’s me.
Me.
I’ll remove my hand,
but don’t yell.
Why are you here?
You come to steal the paper?
You want to cheat!
Who’s there?
If you go out,
we’ll both be found.
Have a look.
I won’t.
It’s the paper for Grade 2,
instead of Grade 1.
Look.
I promise you
I only review the paper for Grade 2.
Then I’m not cheating.
I didn’t see anything. I didn’t.
I didn’t see anything.
Your father’s name is really Xie Kexue?
Stop nagging.
How annoying!
Let’s leave. Be quick.
What?
Read it before the tryout
and you’ll win.
It’s the answers to the tryout.
Who else knows it?
No one else.
You tore it up?
Do you know how much trouble it took me
to finally get it?
I’ll pretend I didn’t know.
Don’t mention it again.
Then can you win?
Something matters more than victory.
He’s quite proud.
What’s wrong with you two?
You don’t even enjoy the food today.
You’re keeping something from me?
No.
Nothing.
Shi Che, Xie Ziye,
come out.
Mr. Yang.
It can’t be true.
I know
my students.
They wouldn’t have cheated.
Come and take a look.
Look.
Look at this.
Why did you cheat?
I didn’t.
You…!
It was recorded by the monitor.
You still deny?
Xie Ziye,
you’ve been studying hard.
And I’ve trusted you.
But this time,
you really let me down.
She didn’t cheat.
I stole the paper.
She wasn’t involved.
Mr. Wen,
Shi Che stole the paper of Grade 2.
He didn’t cheat.
The paper of Grade 2?
Why did you steal that?
I had planned
to steal the paper of Grade 1.
But I was so nervous
that I took the paper of Grade 2.
Mr. Wen, he didn’t cheat.
When he tried to cheat, he cheated.
It’s a very vile thing!
Write a 3000-word self-criticism
and give it to me.
Come with me.
(Self-criticism)
How to write a self-criticism?
You haven’t written one before?
When writing a self-criticism,
your true feelings
are the most important.
Yes.
True feelings matter most
for the self-criticism.
You should reflect on your fault
from the bottom of your heart
and correct it.
Right.
Let me read mine for you.
Come on.
I will not find any excuse
for my mistake.
It’ll only make me more ashamed.
I’ve realized the importance
of honesty and hard work.
In the next exam,
I’ll get a satisfactory score
with what I can truly do!
I won’t let you down.
From Shi Che,
Class 10, Grade 1.
I’m so moved!
What do you think?
Shall I write one for you?
Pay 50 yuan
for every thousand word.
Stay away from me.
It doesn’t matter.
In fact, you were involved
because of my brother.
Shall I write it for you?
Don’t bother.
It’s not your fault.
I’m sorry
for having you involved.
Don’t do it ever again!
I won’t.
Lithium, sodium and potassium
want to lose an electron
so that outermost electrons
will become saturated.
So, they’re highly reductive.
Lithium, sodium and potassium...
Why is she asleep?
Fluorine, chlorine, bromine and iodine
are eager for an electron
so that outermost electrons
will become saturated.
So, they’re highly oxidative.
Miao,
send the soup to Jiang.
It helps to relieve the pain.
Smells great.
Doesn’t it?
Come on. Don’t rush to go.
Don’t rush.
Put this in it.
What’s this?
I...
I met a magic doctor in the market
and bought the aspidistra from him.
Got it?
I had planned to send it to my client,
but it was too expensive.
I kept some, then.
Let’s give it to Jiang.
Miao,
look at your mother.
She always trusts such stuff.
Aspidistra?
Last time, you bought
some Tonify Powder
for vitality nourishment.
Miao and I suffered from diarrhea
for two days.
But this is different.
I got this from a magic doctor.
You don’t understand at all.
What if it makes Jiang sick?
Come on. It’s for his own good.
You’ll make him sick.
Put it down.
Be quick.
Give it to Jiang.
But, you...
Listen.
Why don’t you let me put one in it?
Just put some in the soup.
He’ll go to the tryout.
What if he gets sick?
It’s raining so hard.
He must be feeling unwell.
How can he go to the tryout?
How I wish to beat you now!
Why don’t you trust me at all?
Let me have a try.
Don’t eat it before it’s cooked!
Are you an idiot?
Tastes like a date.
Bring my gratitude to your father.
Why is your face burning?
Are you having a fever?
I’m fine.
I don’t feel well on rainy days.
Hot water will make me better.
I’ll go buy some antipyretic for you.
Don’t.
What if I take the medicine
and feel sleepy during the tryout?
You make sense.
Here comes the bus. I gotta go.
Be careful on your way back.
Are you alright?
Yes.
(Tryout for Olympic Chemistry)
For today’s experimental operation,
you have 90 minutes
to do the acid-base titration.
Two parts.
Titration for alkali
and titration for acid.
Three parallel experiments
for each part.
You may start.
When doing the acid-base titration,
you’ll be tested
on the pursuit of details.
The difficulty lies in
whether the leakage of burette
is fully inspected,
whether the bubbles
between the turncock and the glass ball
are discharged,
whether the burette is fully wetted
by depending liquid
and whether you’re calm enough
at the end of the experiment.
These are key points
for today’s contest.
Why are you pacing up and down?
You make me flustered.
It’s too much.
Jiang Haoyue defeated Qu Wei?
I can’t wait.
I’m going back to school.
I’ll go see him.
I’m leaving.
Let me drive you.
Don’t bother.
Stay at home for some rest.
Take the umbrella.
It’s raining.
All right.
Jiang Haoyue.
Mr. Bai said that
you were the only one
who made zero error?
I do the acid-base titration every week.
How many times have you done?
Why did you defeat me?
When the experiment started,
you felt so painful
that you couldn’t even hold the burette.
I practiced as many times as you.
Why must you pick Chemistry?
It offers the highest bonus.
Jiang Haoyue!
Now you can take some medicine, right?
How was the tryout?
It’s OK.
You tried your best.
You would have won
if you picked Physics.
And you’re sick today.
I shouldn’t think like that.
The result hasn’t come out yet.
I can’t give up hope.
Let me take you to a place.
God of the Sea, bless him.
Bless him.
What are you doing?
It’s for the God of the Sea.
You can’t eat it!
The God of the Sea doesn’t eat it.
How do you know?
What if he does?
We’re doomed.
Hope’s gone.
Why don’t you eat one, too?
No.
Qu Wei will feel prouder.
In fact, Qu Wei is a nice guy.
Besides,
I may not lose.
So, you won?
Why didn’t you tell me earlier?
I needn’t have worried.
It proves that
I still lose every bet.
You’d better worry about yourself.
Will you eat it or not?
If you don’t, I’ll eat it.
I will. I didn’t decline.
Big number.
Small.
Here.
One more time!
You first.
All right.
Big.
Small!
You won again.
Would you like another try?
Why not?
Big or small?
Big.
Small.
It’s really a small number.
I quit! I quit!
This game doesn’t suit me!
If I knew, I wouldn’t have played.
I’ve lost
all my chocolate.
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪