♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
=Flourish in Time=
=Episode 6=
=Fight, Drum Battle!=
Jiang Haoyue learned cycling skills,
and you only gave him two extra points?
What?
You gave him two points?
You should have given him more points.
Make it four.
No, don’t do it.
Chlorophyll.
I’m with you this time.
No four points.
But it’s harder for him to learn this.
He had to put in more effort than
ordinary people.
So when it comes to cycling,
he should have the highest score.
Indeed.
But if I add four points to him,
Jiang Haoyue will have a perfect score.
Then I’ll have to confess
my love to him.
Then you should give him the points.
Give him two points then.
In fact, it’s not that hard
for a guy like him to finish a job.
Add two points.
I was going to
impress Meng,
but I didn’t expect
Jiang Haoyue could do it.
No way.
I have to think of another way
to get back in the game.
(Time Book)
(Open)
Sir.
Mr. Hao, where do you want me to put it?
Leave it there.
Okay.
Bye then.
OK. See you.
(Battle of the Kings)
The team that wins
the first place in the game
will get a pair of
Hanamichi Sakuragi AJ6 shoes.
Yes! Lucky me!
Are you going to…?
Guoguo.
Do you think it’s cool if a man wins
a pair of AJ6
by strength?
Yes, cool.
Alright!
(Class 1, Grade 2)
7 p.m.
I’ll wait for you.
You go first.
See you then.
What a coincidence, Meng.
Why haven’t you left yet?
I’m waiting for Guoguo.
Where is your brother?
Their class has a quiz today.
It ends at 7 p.m.
I’m going back first.
Oh, bummer.
Let’s go back together then.
We got the same way.
Don’t you want to wait for Guoguo?
It comes to me that his teacher
is running over the lesson time.
Why don’t we go together?
I’ll go with you to get your bike.
Let’s go.
Your brother can ride a bike,
Didn’t you practice for nothing?
Not for nothing.
Let’s race.
Let’s see who can ride faster.
I’ll count to three.
Okay.
Ready?
Three!
You can’t do that.
It’s not against the rule.
You can’t win even if
you play tricks.
Shi Che, you’re riding the wrong way.
That’s not the way home.
It’s the way
I’ve specially prepared for you.
Wait for me!
Shi Che! Wait for me!
You won.
I’ll take you somewhere later.
These shoes seem to be
Sakuragi Hanamichi’s
first pair of basketball shoes.
That’s right.
Haruko Akagi bought them with him.
Yes.
And I remember in the cartoon,
he only spent thirty yen.
In reality, it should be
more than a thousand yuan.
So expensive.
So it’s true that there
are 300 layers of
bulletproof glass between
the reality and the cartoon.
Do you want to shoot through the glass?
Are you
going to
rob the shoes?
How can you think of me like that?
If you team up for the game
and get first place,
you can get this pair of AJ6.
First place isn’t easy to get.
It’s hard for other people,
but not for me.
How come?
Excuse me,
but I rank number one in solo
in this community.
You’re good.
But this game needs a duo.
I need a partner.
Meng, before I dominate
the country in basketball,
help me win a pair of shoes.
What do you think?
OK!
It’s a deal.
Done!
You’re finally here.
Why are you here?
You want to win the shoes, right?
Don’t worry, I won’t hold you back.
I came to practice right after school.
Hurry.
Miao, you’re here too.
You’ve found a partner already?
I… I haven’t.
What?
Aren’t we the best partners?
It’s okay.
Why don’t you two fight it out?
It’s not necessary.
I don’t have to participate in this.
Miao.
You think you can defeat me?
I’ll try.
But I never played this game before.
It’s okay. Use my ID.
Don’t say I’m bullying you.
(READY)
(GO)
Guoguo, excuse me.
This doesn’t make sense.
The most important thing
in athletics is talent.
What is more important
than talent is determination.
I believe that,
with time,
you’ll be very good at
this game.
It’s alright.
I can let Guoguo have this chance.
Let me?
Miao.
That’s a bit too insulting.
You lost.
See you later.
I will definitely come back.
Meng.
Do you see it?
I do.
Guoguo looks
so sad.
Not him.
I’m talking about that pair of AJ6.
It’s already engraved with my name.
Here.
No, thank you. Let’s go.
Seriously?
You just finished your exams
and you’re still reading?
You should know that,
only with a combination of work
and rest can you surpass me.
What’s wrong?
Isn’t that your sister?
Don’t you want to say hello?
It’s not necessary.
Didn’t you just refuse to eat?
I want to eat now.
Alright.
No problem.
Why so angry?
The universal formula includes
trigonometric functions,
inverse trigonometric functions, etc.
The universal formula can
convert all trigonometric functions
into polynomials of tan(a/2),
and convert sinα, cosα, and tanα.
We call it
the universal substitution formula.
Lu Miao.
Now I’ll ask someone to come here
and review the use of this formula.
Stand up!
Class is over?
What are you laughing at?
Can you solve all the questions?
You two go out and sober up.
(Class 10, Grade 1)
I’m afraid we’re both going
to be on Ms. Lei’s blacklist.
Relax.
With our math scores,
we’re already on that list.
Don’t worry about this time now.
Don’t put us together.
I passed math test at least.
The difference between us
is just that
between 50th place and 100th place.
It’s okay.
How’s your game practice going?
Better than before.
Left, right, left.
Right, left, right.
Okay, that’s a progress.
Okay, follow me.
Why is your sister standing outside?
Okay, good.
I felt good today.
I never missed
a three-point shot.
Nice.
Let’s go get some drinks.
Looking for Lu Miao?
I’m looking for you.
Me?
I’ll go buy drinks first.
Wait for me.
I’ll be right there.
What is it?
Let me ask you.
Are you still studying?
No,
I’m not interested in studying.
I prefer to play basketball.
Why do you come to school
if you don’t study?
What does it matter to you
if I come to school or not?
You’re right.
I have nothing to do with it.
But let me remind you.
It’s fine if you don’t study,
but don’t affect Lu Miao.
Such a good student.
Don’t you think that’s lame?
School is a place for you to study,
but for me it’s a place to make friends.
Lu Miao, she has the right to study.
She also has the right
to make friends, right?
Besides,
even if you really are her brother,
you don’t have the right
to control so much, right?
She will withdraw from the competition.
Then we’ll see.
Che, what are you doing?
Do you think Meng will stand me up?
Why are you worried about that
all of a sudden?
Jiang Haoyue is jealous of
my relationship with Meng.
He’s trying to get in the way.
Although I’m not afraid,
you know
those straight-A students
are cunning creatures.
Better an open enemy
than a false friend.
I think you’re overthinking.
Meng.
Miao.
Why are you here?
I came to buy something to drink.
I’m thirsty too.
Then I’ll treat you.
Stop.
Either of you can buy it.
I’d like a coke.
What about you?
Two cans, thanks.
What are you doing?
Such a great opportunity.
Say what you want to say.
Ask whatever you want to ask.
Hurry up. Don’t be a coward!
What are you two muttering about?
Nothing.
Che wants to ask you something.
No.
I haven’t asked yet.
Two cans of coke
and you want to buy me off?
I won’t help you with your homework.
Who asked you for that?
You’re not even better than me.
I might as well do it myself.
Do you despise me?
No.
I admire you,
otherwise I wouldn’t have asked you
to join my team.
It’s nothing.
Meng.
I used our accounts to sign up
for the competition.
If you quit in the middle of the race,
I’ll be done.
Don’t worry, since I promised you,
I will do
my best.
Good friend.
Lu Miao.
I’m coming.
Why is he here?
He’s been waiting
for me to buy the drinks.
I’ll leave now.
Thank you for these.
It’s okay.
Don’t be mad.
Two bottles of drinks. Don’t mind it.
Why don’t we have some spicy hot pot
before we go back?
The owner is having a promotion.
30% off for students.
You don’t want it?
Then we can go next time.
Today Mr. Wen asked me
to answer a question about time zones.
I used the method you taught me.
He even praised me.
What is wrong with you?
Why did you go to
the arcade with Shi Che?
How did you know…?
I’m trying to help Shi Che win the game
to get the basketball shoes.
We’re good friends.
What’s wrong with me helping him out?
Besides…
Is being punished in class
also some kind of help?
You also saw that?
Can you not tell my parents?
You should quit the game.
Don’t waste time on
these meaningless things.
I can’t.
This is not a meaningless matter.
Since I promised Shi Che,
I have to be loyal.
A man’s word is his bond.
Besides, the competition
will be over soon,
so I won’t miss too much studying.
Being punished in class is also loyalty?
Where are you going?
Don’t follow me.
Fine! Whatever.
So cold.
Even if he doesn’t want to see me,
how can he refuse the spicy hot pot?
It’s so good
and 30% off.
It is really a loss not to try it.
Meng.
Why are you eating here alone?
It’s sad.
Spicy hot pot is better
when you eat alone.
If you like the crowd, go eat hot pot.
Why are you so angry?
Why Jiang Haoyue is not with you?
You’re deliberately trying
to piss me off, right?
Why would I?
You...
What is going on?
Jiang Haoyue wanted me to withdraw
from the competition.
He said it would affect my studies.
I’m confused.
He’s not your parent
or your class teacher,
why is he so meddlesome?
That’s right.
If you say yes,
that’s too inferior.
Of course no!
What did you say?
When I was little, I respected him
because he was a good student.
I was so humble
and obedient to him.
Today he got angry with me
only because of this,
so why should I
listen to him on everything?
So you mean,
you
chose me and rejected him?
Yeah!
Didn’t I promise you?
I was right about you!
Meng.
For sake of our friendship,
let’s drink this vinegar.
Cheers!
Don’t you feel sour?
It’s sweet.
So sweet.
Your taste is quite unique.
Now that I think back,
I should not have let Jiang Haoyue
control me so much.
You didn’t see it.
Today, his back to ride away
was really ruthless and decisive.
You can’t always defer to him.
He would get arrogant.
He’s taking it too far.
You can’t say that.
It’s true that we shouldn’t
miss studying because of practice.
But we have to spend time on practice
in order to place in the competition.
Right?
Come to think of it,
Jiang Haoyue’s controlling me
seems to be for my own good.
Just think about his cold back
when he left.
Yeah.
He learned to ride a bike
so he could go to school with me.
Meng.
You don’t have to push yourself so hard.
I don’t.
He must have put up with more every time
he taught me how to do my homework.
Meng, I…
I think you’re the cutest
when you’re angry.
Nonsense.
I’m always cute.
Bye. I’m going home.
I’ll walk you home.
No need, my home is just around here.
This restaurant is offering
30% off today.
Eat before you leave.
Let me eat spicy hot pot alone?
It’s sad.
Spicy hot pot is better
when you eat alone.
Bye.
I…
Can you turn off
the sound effects for me?
Turn off the sound effects, right?
Yes.
Thank you.
Done.
Ziye.
In class today,
Ms. Lei talked about
the universal formula.
What does it mean?
What’s with your sudden enthusiasm
for learning?
When I was punished for standing
in math class today,
Jiang Haoyue saw it.
He’s mad.
He still hasn’t spoken to me.
What are you gonna do?
I gotta go. My mom is here.
Were you talking to Haoyue on the phone?
He’s not home, right?
I wanted to bring him some fruit.
I knocked and no one answered the door.
He’s not back yet?
(When are you coming back?)
(Jiang)
Where are you?
Why aren’t you back yet?
My mom is worried sick.
I’ll be right back.
Don’t worry.
Well…
Are you still mad at me?
No, I’m not.
I’ll be home soon.
Okay.
When you get back, tell me.
I’ll bring you some fruit.
Okay.
The universal formula.
What are you calculating here?
Which question is to
determine the combos?
I see.
You are trying to help Lu Miao again.
Instead of studying me,
why don’t you do a few more questions?
You lost the weekly test again.
It’s still a B.
You were a D before,
so you’re much better than before.
But if I am a B,
I can’t help you win the shoes.
Actually,
winning the shoes is not that important.
What did you say?
Jiang Haoyue?
Why are you here?
You can’t win the championship with B.
What’s wrong with a B?
It means Meng has a lot of
room for improvement.
Thanks.
I’ll replace you.
Replace me?
No.
I don’t agree.
This is the most effective way
to improve performance
in a short period of time.
Jiang Haoyue.
This is a video arcade,
not a school.
This is a game,
not a test paper.
I’ve never seen you play
Drum Battle before.
Dare to try it?
Fine.
Haoyue.
What?
When did you
get so good at Drum Battle?
Recently.
I thought I only couldn’t beat you
in study.
Now I can’t even beat you
in video games.
I’m depressed.
I’m jealous.
I am unhappy.
Are you still a normal person?
I’m not as good as you think.
If you’re still modest at this point,
you seem overly proud.
I mean it.
I’m not as fast as Shi Che.
Then how did you beat him?
Whether it’s learning or playing,
there are methods and laws.
Through the laws of
mathematical algorithms,
combined with Drum Battle’s
even and odd techniques,
I was able to compensate for
my speed disadvantage.
However,
he didn’t lose to me
because of his speed.
Because of what then?
Because…
Because of his mentality.
I’ve been looking for you.
Why are you in the reading room?
Come on.
Let’s go practice the game.
I’d better finish my homework first.
Besides, my brother has
already replaced me.
How about
you two go practice?
It’s too boring here.
I’ll wait for you
at the basketball court.
Che.
Are you really going to team up
with Jiang Haoyue?
Is he good?
I feel like he’s not as good as me.
That’s the most annoying thing.
He’s good.
Why would he always
get between me and Meng?
Is he…?
What?
Is he Akagi Takenori?
Why Akagi Takenori?
If Sakuragi wants to
get close to Haruko,
isn’t her brother the first person
he has to deal with?
In that case,
I’m still the hero of this play.
If you have to say so,
I have nothing to say.
Che. Let’s go.
Good luck, hero.
Hold these for me.
Okay.
We don’t have the same hand speed.
I have to listen to the music.
The sound is too low.
Come on.
Given the way you two are playing,
they would think
you’re playing a rivalry game.
I have to listen to the music.
I have to calculate.
Then why don’t you try
each other’s
way first?
Well...
How about
we go home now?
Cool down ourselves.
Fine.
What are you listening to?
English.
It’s really boring when they read it.
English needs to be sung to sound good.
DJ Lu Miao is tuned for you.
♪You♪
♪Give me feeling♪
♪I say Yes It’s you♪
♪Make me smile♪
How is it?
♪It’s you♪
♪I will be there♪
I knew you’d like this.
It seems you can listen to music.
Your formula is really hard
for average people to understand.
Maybe
you could try listening to music?
I can try.
Jiang Haoyue, you’re so nice.
Instead of letting others change,
why not change myself?
Shi Che won’t say it,
but he really appreciates
your help.
And
you two are both double S types.
As long as you work together,
you’ll be godlike.
Why
do you have to help him win the shoes?
In fact, at the beginning,
I did go with the goal
of helping him win the shoes.
But after practicing for a few days,
I found that every time I got rated,
the score was a little higher
than last time.
My sense of accomplishment was strong.
Besides, you’re in this one.
A lot of people
in the school are concerned
about this matter.
One of you
is my brother
and the other is my buddy.
If you guys lose face, I lose face.
I can’t lose my face.
So you must do your best.
Understand?
I’ll try.
How can you be so cool?
So handsome!
How can someone be so cool?
What did you say?
I said…
Are the noodles ready?
I’m so hungry.
I want to eat them.
Let me see.
OK.
You can eat now.
Here are your chopsticks.
Let’s eat together.
Cheers!
You finished your homework fast today.
You two have a competition coming up.
I can’t delay your practice.
Guoguo.
Where is Shi Che?
He’s
in the bell tower.
He said he found some
kind of winning formula.
Let’s go.
Bye-bye.
Come on.
Do not change hands at even numbers.
That means…
Where did you get them?
I borrowed them from the honor guard.
From a friend.
There are some left and
right hands exchange sequences
and some accent structures,
which should help you understand.
Use these.
They’re lighter.
This way our hands should be
at the same speed.
Give me one.
You can listen to music now?
Still getting used to it.
Let’s go.
♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
Thank you.
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Fingertips press the button♪
♪To frame her and him♪
♪I want to go into his heart♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪Let the dreams continue together♪
♪Walk side by side♪
That was great.
♪The point of growth is♪
The score is good.
♪We staying together♪
My AJ6.
See you at the top tomorrow.
Let’s go.
I didn’t expect you
to improve so quickly today.
I take credit for that too!
Right.
You’ve made great progress too.
Without your great performance,
how could we have come this far?
Here’s a piece of duck blood.
Who wants it?
Give it to me.
Give it to him.
You must be tired after
playing for so long today.
It’s much more tiring than studying.
Not as tired as you are with your brain.
Why does it sound so weird?
Forget it, I’ll eat it myself.
Why are you looking at me?
I worked hard too.
No, wait.
Shouldn’t you take us to eat hot pot?
Didn’t you say so yourself?
Hot pot should be eaten together.
Spicy hot pot is only good
when eating alone.
Don’t talk nonsense here!
When did I ever say that?
So didn’t you think it was good enough
when we ate spicy hot pot together?
No!
He’s talking nonsense.
Every time I had spicy hot pot with you,
I felt happy
from
the inside.
You must eat spicy hot pot
with your friends, so it would
taste better, and bring you
more happiness
and more joy.
Right?
Meng, you…
Eat your food.
Enjoy it.
(The Top Drum Battle)
The two are really full of
fighting spirit
and keep hitting combos.
Another combo,
and another series of combos.
Very good.
It’s about to be our turn.
Are you nervous?
They’re going to
place very well.
A little bit.
Listen to me.
You pretend that no one else exists.
And then say in your mind,
what keeps me going
is the belief that I’ll never give up.
Not the shoes?
Let’s invite
the next group of challengers.
They are
Mr. Arrogance
and A Sapling.
OK, applause!
Okay, the two players are in position.
The last group is ready
to start the competition.
Here we go.
Go, Shi Che!
The battle is very intense.
They are not missing a single beat.
Go, Jiang Haoyue!
This group is amazing!
Another combo!
Combo, combo, combo.
Go for it!
These two are really good.
That’s great!
It’s the last part.
Come on!
Let’s give them
a little more applause, okay?
Come on!
All combos and all perfect.
This is the highest score so far.
So great!
We’ve got the highest score in the game.
Is that the highest score?
That’s great!
The highest score!
Jiang Haoyue, the highest score!
Great!
I’m the top drummer!
Top drummer!
I am the King!
The King!
I’m a genius!
Be careful.
It’s okay. Just stand up there.
I’m a genius!
The world is ours!
It’s ours!
Two idiots.
You won?
You’re wearing them.
Do I look cool?
Impressive!
You guys really won?
Yes, we did.
Do you think we’re really good?
Do you have any admiration for us?
No, not really.
You’ll have to give me
extra points this time.
Not even a single point.
You’re too stingy.
What’s the use of knowing
how to play games?
These shoes are 1,600 yuan.
I won them on my own.
You tell me that
playing games is useless?
I’m kind enough to give you
the title of Game Master.
Besides,
you got help from
Lu Miao and Jiang Haoyue.
Why are you here alone?
It’s less crowded
and quieter here.
You’re here to get the drums
for the honor guard, right?
I’ll come with you.
Nice shoes.
Thank you for your help.
You’re my friend now.
No need to be so polite.
It’s all for Lu Miao.
For Lu Miao?
Give me that little castle.
Here.
Thank you!
Jiang Haoyue!
Come down and play sand together.
He can’t play,
so why did you ask him?
Who says he can’t play?
I will let him play to show you.
Jiang Haoyue.
Look what I’ve brought you.
Give me your hands.
It’s dirty.
Okay, now we’re the same.
We’re going to make one
even better than theirs.
How about a giant chocolate?
It’s just a square.
What’s so difficult about it?
So what do you want to make?
I’ll help you.
This is worse than the chocolate.
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪