♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
=Flourish in Time=
=Episode 2=
=Fight Back If Got Bullied=
Uncle Lu.
Jiang.
Waiting for Miao to go to school?
Miao, hurry up.
Jiang is waiting for you.
I’m coming.
See you then.
Uncle Lu.
My artificial leg...
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
If anything comes up
in the future, just let me know.
This kind of thing can’t be held up.
It’s bad for your body.
Take care of yourself.
(Own Uncle Lu 1,000 yuan
for repairing my artificial leg)
I saw the ambulance.
It’s said that Jiang Haoyue
got beaten badly.
It’s reliable source.
Jiang Haoyue
had an excessive loss of blood,
he’s still in rescue.
Lu Miao was so violent.
How come she was there, too?
Their relationship is suspicious.
I heard they’re dating each other.
These rumors are outrageous.
What’s up?
What were you looking at?
Nothing.
I’m here alone
with snow falling down...
The bus’s here, let’s go.
Do you know
that Lu Miao from Class 10 of Grade 1
is Jiang Haoyue’s sister?
Sister?
How come they are siblings
but one’s last name is Lu,
the other is Jiang?
What a complicated relationship.
What happened to their family?
Yeah,
how could she be his sister?
It shouldn’t be this dramatic, right?
What kind of family is that?
She’s his half-sister.
Why does he like Lu Miao?
Have you heard...?
Lu Miao in our class
is the child bride of Jiang Haoyue.
Really?
However,
since Lu’s family
has declined afterwards.
So,
Jiang’s family wants
to abolish this marriage.
Enemies and lovers are destined to meet.
Where did you hear that from?
Don’t ask about where
the gossip comes from.
This is a golden rule, got it?
Anyway,
these two families are family feud.
Really?
Our families are enemies?
How come I don’t know that?
Well...
Is it true about the child bride?
What do you think?
It must be true.
It’s true.
She’s coming.
Excuse me, please.
Jiang Haoyue’s sister.
Here you are.
Take it.
Here.
This is my gift for you.
By the way,
I’m from Class 3 in the neighborhood.
Please pass this letter
to Jiang Haoyue for me.
What are you doing?
Here.
I want to be friend with you.
I’m just curious
about your childhood stories
with Jiang Haoyue.
Please don’t mind.
We only meant to be friends with you.
You are new
and unfamiliar with the school.
We can show you around.
Let’s go. Yeah.
Give somebody else a chance.
Give us some chances, too.
You stepped on my stuff.
Alright, sorry.
Miao,
what does your brother normally do?
What’s his preferences
on food and drinks?
When’s his birthday?
What’s his blood type?
If you want to talk about
Jiang Haoyue, go outside.
Don’t crowd here.
Her name is Lu Miao.
Her last name is not Jiang.
Let’s go.
Why’s she being so mean?
I know, right?
Thank you.
Feng Wanwan.
Yan Su.
Yan Su got so many votes.
Xie Ziye.
I voted for you.
Can you stop causing me trouble?
Who said that I want to
join the class committee?
But you pay attention to class
and you obey all the rules.
You are careful, your grades
are top-notch, too.
It’s obvious that the teachers like you.
What does it have anything to do
with me joining the class committee?
The mentioned students
are recommended by every one of you
after spending time with them.
As the head teacher,
I’ll choose the committee members
from them.
Class President,
Yan Su.
Vice Class President,
Feng Wanwan.
Study Representative,
Xie Ziye.
I voted for my deskmate for her
to be the class committee members.
It turned out that she doesn’t
want to do it.
How come anyone would refuse to do it?
Maybe she’s afraid of all the troubles.
What troubles would it bring to her?
Joining the committee
will have many duties.
They are all plain easy jobs which
would take up a lot of time.
It’s hard to tell
that Jiang Haoyue’s leg is artificial.
You can flip it and find out.
It may be a machine gun,
or a flamethrower.
Aren’t you guys finished yet?
Just focus on your snacks.
Let’s go.
Wait, who on earth are you?
Is it your business to mind?
He’s my brother.
Gossiping about him is my business.
Try and point again.
Let’s go.
Unreasonable.
Be careful, don’t hurt yourself.
Can we be a team?
Stretch your hand.
It’d be fine soon.
It won’t hurt if
you’ve stretched well.
I’m sorry about the
class committee that day.
I should’ve asked you about it.
I’m just afraid of all the troubles.
I know.
Being the committee member
means all kinds of duties.
They take you much time
and can’t exercise you.
You good students
aren’t fond of these things.
But I think you have strong ability,
you can help
students who fall behind like us.
It’d be nice.
A bug!
Don’t move.
It’d be fine now.
I’m always afraid of bugs.
Of course, because
your name represents leaf.
Thank you.
Ziye, let me add on QQ.
Let me scan your code.
Alright.
Okay.
I’ve sent you a friend request.
Okay, I’ve added you.
What’s this notebook for?
I keep scores on it.
For every guy I meet,
I’d evaluate them by rating.
Evaluate them?
Screening them by Big Data,
then choose the one who
got the highest overall score
as my Mr. Right,
then I’ll confess to him.
It works?
Sure.
This can keep me from dating
the wrong guy.
Very rational and scientific.
Well, who got the highest
score until now?
Jiang Haoyue.
How could it be him?
Great height.
High IQ.
Good-looking.
Though he’s a bit aloof,
giving others a sense of distance.
It makes me want to challenge more.
Plus,
he’s a bit of a sister-con.
Stop there, Miss Xie.
Clear your horrible imaginations.
These are not imaginations.
These are reasonable
speculations based on the facts.
With so many rules and restrains,
you’re just like a robot.
You’re full of energy every day,
you’re just like
a long endurance lithium battery.
We two can make a good match.
These are all for you.
They’re all yours now.
All mine?
How can I take them?
To Jiang Haoyue,
ever since we met
at the math competition,
I couldn’t forget
your elegant demeanor.
Hopefully to meet you
at the podium next time.
From Qu Qianqian,
Class 5 of Grade 2.
Can you quiet down?
These gifts represent
their regards for you.
I’ve taken the gifts.
I should bring them to you.
To Jiang Haoyue,
my name is Zhou Xiuyan
from Class 3 of Grade 1.
I’ve always admired you.
I’ve read all of your articles.
You are the most out-standing
person I’ve ever met.
I hope to know you better.
Zhou Xiuyan?
I heard she’s the prettiest girl
of the next class.
Not bad.
Boring.
You are the broken angel
fallen from heaven.
Icy eyes.
Fragile lashes.
Pale face.
Your tears run down silently.
A kiss from god on your forehead.
If you bear from any sufferings,
I’m willing to be your
most loyal listener.
If you can’t walk properly,
I’d be your walking stick by your side.
From Class 6 of Grade 1,
Zhang...
Zhang Xin?
Isn’t that a guy?
You are always alone.
But you are pretty popular
in the school.
I wrote the analysis
of the mistakes aside.
Correct them yourself
and finish the rest of the paper.
You are so strict.
(Disability is infectious.
Stay away from us!!)
I’ll go back first.
Take these with you.
I don’t want them.
Throw up in there,
not outside.
Are these from your classmates?
They are no use.
Throw them away.
When you were in kindergarten,
your teacher said to me
that,
as for your personality,
you need strict discipline,
or you may have troubles
in the future.
Then, I saw you
playing games with other kids,
he fell down and cried,
but you,
you ignored him standing right there.
I immediately understood .
Your personality
won’t cause you any trouble.
You are always like this.
No matter how nicely others treat you.
You’ll always stick to your minds,
isn’t it?
You won’t remember
anything others did for you.
It’s just like your mother.
A heart as cold as rock.
Then don’t trouble Uncle Lu anymore.
Tell me,
is it you?
Who are you?
Jiang Haoyue wouldn’t
stand out for himself
but crying behind your back.
Well?
Are you defending
your brother again?
What did you say?
Lu Miao!
I’ve been looking for you.
Let’s go.
Don’t stop me.
They went too far.
I’m giving them a lesson.
Come here.
There are two of them.
Can you handle them?
I’m not afraid of them at all.
Even if you are not,
what if this gets big and
the parents come over?
What if the school punish you?
But,
should I just
let them do whatever they want?
These losers will be punished one day.
I heard Wang Xinwen is
sort of a coward.
A new Switch?
Thanks to your help of cheating
in the last exam for me.
My parents are satisfied
with my results this time.
I’ll let you borrow it for a few days.
Really?
Look.
Mr. Lame is here.
A coward protected by a girl.
Handsome!
I’ll see you after school
in the Biology Classroom.
I want to talk to you.
Your biggest fan.
(Biology Specimen Room)
Why are you here, too?
I got a letter.
So did I.
Are we tricked?
Have you realized your fault?
I’m sorry.
Why are you sorry?
What are you sorry for?
I cheated in the exam.
Don’t tell that.
Come out, don’t be mysterious.
What else?
I shouldn’t read
Zhang Cheng’s love letter.
Isn’t there anything else?
Think about the things you said,
the words you wrote.
I shouldn’t mock Jiang Haoyue.
I warn you,
stop gossiping about Jiang Haoyue.
Otherwise,
you’ll be just like this.
So, it was you.
I tell you,
I’ll go to the teachers.
Hey, it hurts.
Are you going to the teachers?
No!
You win.
Stop looking at me.
Don’t worry, we won’t
tell the teachers.
Let’s go.
Look at their faces just now.
It feels so good.
I didn’t know you could
break an apple in half by hand.
I cut it in advance.
What a brilliant idea!
I thought you are only good
at studying.
You underestimated me.
(Time Book)
A lame
and a loser.
Jiang Haoyue and Lu Miao
no wonder are siblings.
Cheng,
just cut it off.
I don’t want to have anything
to do with Lu Miao.
How could you take it being bullied
by a girl?
I warn you, don’t mess with Lu Miao.
Or the whole school would know
that you cheated in the exam.
Who told you about that?
Yeah.
How dare you to accuse us of that?
A new Switch?
Thanks to your help of cheating
in the last exam for me.
My parents are satisfied
with my results this times.
I’ll let you borrow it for a few days.
Seriously.
Earlier,
it was our fault.
Please don’t tell others.
Yeah.
It was all our fault.
We apologize.
As long as you delete
the recording in your phone.
We’ll do everything you say
in the future.
What do you say?
Twenty sets of examination papers,
I’ll delete it right after you finish.
Twenty sets?
Let’s just do them.
We’ve scared them alright.
Wang Xinwen even confessed
about the love letter thing.
Me and Ziye decorated
the Biology Specimen Room
to a horrifying setting.
There were a lot of traps, too.
Like the spider web,
there’s a scary
panda mask, too.
Wang Xinwen wasn’t convinced earlier,
I grasped him down on the floor
right after.
He then apologized to me.
But I’ll not forgive him.
Lu Miao,
it’s not necessary.
You think you were incredible
being the hero out there.
I don’t need it.
I can’t stand them
talking about you like that.
Why would be angry?
Why bother revenging on them?
I surely know
what they’d say about me.
Mr. Lame.
A coward.
A loser.
All of these are facts.
Don’t say that!
You are not like that.
Then what am I like?
Do you remember when we were young?
We hung out together.
There was a boy
who threw a pine cone on you.
You threw back precisely at him
without thinking.
Ever since,
no kids in the neighborhood
would bully you again.
You are never timid.
You are neither a coward.
The disability of your body
won’t get in your way of being brave.
I didn’t know better when I was a kid.
You are killing me.
Lu Miao.
Can you stop stepping on my shadow?
It will stop me from growing tall.
There’s a place for spicy hot pot there.
Let’s go.
I’m good.
I heard it’s a newly opened store.
The taste is especially fresh and spicy.
Two squids for free
if you buy three shashliks.
Let’s go then.
Lu Miao.
Can you
stop causing yourself troubles
for protecting me?
That’s not trouble.
There’s a saying
as “When the sky collapses,
it falls on the tall guys.”
You are short.
Stop troubling yourself.
Promise me.
Don’t ever say those
demoralizing things again.
Let’s go.
Uncle Hao.
I’m here to return the books.
Alright.
Do you still have the
ninth episode of Naruto?
Someone called Mr. Arrogance
borrowed it a few days ago.
How about the tenth episode
of Slamdunk?
Borrowed by him as well.
And the nineteenth episode of One Piece?
Let me see.
Also borrowed by Mr. Arrogance.
Mr. Arrogance!
What’s the matter?
A guy called Mr. Arrogance
borrowed all the comic books
I want to read.
You sure have very similar tastes.
Here.
Jiang.
I cooked some vegetables for you.
Look.
Broad beans.
Fried shrimp with greens.
You know?
I cooked this pork
and lucid ganoderma myself.
My friend gave me
a cup of ganoderma powders.
I used it all.
I heard it’s good for your brain.
It’s beneficial to you all.
Come and taste it.
Eat some.
Try.
It’s so good.
Did you wash your hands?
Sure I did.
You can’t use your hands.
Here.
Dip it in the oyster sauce
It must be good.
Must be so fresh.
Here.
Try it.
Dip it in it,
here.
Have a try.
Thank you, Aunt.
Try it.
Well?
Isn’t it good?
It’s so good.
I knew it.
Miao.
Have one, too.
It’s good for your brain.
Eat.
If you like it,
I’ll cook some soup for you next week.
Some cordyceps flower soup.
Her grandparents brought me
a lot of cordyceps flowers.
We’ll use them to make soup next week.
You know, the pesticide effect
of cordyceps flower
is as effective
as the cordyceps sinensis.
Aunt,
I’m going away for training next week.
You want to escape from it?
I’ll save some for you
to eat when you’re back.
You must try it.
Yeah, she’ll save you some.
Not cool, man.
Your aunt is so nice to you.
What’s the training for?
It’s for the chemistry competition.
Aren’t you good at physics?
The chemistry competition
offers higher bonus.
OK.
Miao,
when can you attend a competition, too?
Win a reward or something
to cheer me up.
I’ve won places in the
swimming competition, okay?
Did I mean sport competition?
Don’t interrupt.
What’s wrong with sport competition?
Look at Liu Xiang and
Yao Ming.
They are stars,
aren’t they?
Right.
My dad knows me better.
Eat.
Eating cannot stop you from talking.
Jiang,
please pay more attention
to Miao’s studying.
Keep an eye on her for me.
She’s too careless.
Here.
Eat some pork.
Nothing for her.
All yours.
Eat some more.
You are leaving next week.
Then, my math,
English,
chemistry
and physics
have the possibility
of failing completely.
Your grades
can’t get any worse.
What’s the difference between
the last one
and the fifth-worst?
Don’t look down on me.
This time,
I’ll keep my place of the fifth-worst.
However,
which subject should I start
to work on first?
I got it.
I’ll ask Cong.
Cong who’s got hidden mysterious power.
Show me your true power.
Tell Lu Miao
which subject to start first.
Which one?
Math.
Cong who’s got hidden
mysterious power...
Alright.
I think it’s pretty accurate.
You think so?
How about I
let Cong to tell your fortune?
Why do I need it?
Why not?
Aren’t you going out next week?
Just do it to know
if it’ll be good or ill luck.
I’m good.
Just try.
Hurry and take it.
Just throw them into it.
Just, like this.
Cong who’s got hidden mysterious power.
Where did you get the tokens?
When you were not around,
Cong has made many vital
decisions in my life.
Cong who’s got hidden mysterious power.
Show me your true power.
Tell me
if Jiang could
defeat his opponents this time.
Do we have it?
Show me.
A changing world,
a critical opponent coming.
It’s an unlucky token.
Oh, no,
you’ll meet a rival.
You’ve received higher education.
Why do you believe in this?
Well,
Einstein said
that the end of science is metaphysics.
Einstein never said that.
I’m going back.
Wait for me.
Take this.
This can bless you with good fortune.
(Koi Fish By Side)
It’s not necessary.
Keep it yourself
to bless you a satisfying math grade.
I mean it,
it can bless you for sure.
Take it.
You keep it.
This really works!
Haoyue.
Pay attention to the details
during exam.
Read the paper carefully.
I’m going.
Alright.
Good luck.
She’s really determined.
Guys.
A new student came to our class today,
let me introduce him.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, guys.
My name is Shi Che.
Che, you finally came.
He’s kind of cute.
Naruto!
It’s you.
Do we know each other?
Sit over there.
Alright.
Here, let’s begin the class.
Alright, guys.
Turn to page 10 of your book.
Look at the blackboard.
What’s her name?
Lu Miao.
Why?
Are you interested in her?
Nonsense.
Jiang Haoyue,
look what I got.
Look at this.
Isn’t it pretty?
Lu Miao.
I have it, too.
Very pretty, right?
It took me so long to get this.
Take it, Jiang Haoyue!
What are you doing?
Sorry.
I didn’t know he’d miss it.
Sit further next time you’re out.
Don’t get hit by anything again.
Why can’t you dodge from it
though you missed it?
Save it.
You did it deliberately!
How could you know?
Do you have proof?
You...
You are a bully!
Jiang Haoyue, what are you doing?
Sorry.
Didn’t mean it.
You loser!
You are a loser.
Got hit by a disabled person.
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪