♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
=Flourish in Time=
=Episode 3=
=Predestined Rival=
What are you talking about?
Club recruitment.
One for each.
Fill it and give it to me.
Give me one.
One for each.
Fill it and give it to me.
All right.
The old man is the murderer.
How annoying you are!
Meng,
you really don’t recognize me?
Meng?
What do you think?
It’s the new nickname I gave you.
Do you like it?
I don’t.
Why?
Lu Miao is abbreviated to LM.
Lu Meng is also abbreviated to LM.
It suits you a lot.
Lu Meng sounds much powerful.
Lu Meng.
It doesn’t suit me at all!
All right, then.
Before I come up with a new name,
use it now.
Miao,
do you have some tissues?
Yes.
You know each other?
No.
Miao?
Don’t call me like that.
We’re not friends.
You really don’t know me?
Stop!
You’re the weird guy
who rode a bicycle!
What weird guy?
I’m just unique.
What about your unique fringe?
For my dream,
it was sacrificed.
Son,
listen to me.
When your father feels happy,
he may approve of your admission
to ﻿the school team.
Cut it.
Fill it and give it to me.
May I borrow your pen?
You can play basketball?
After I’m in,
I’ll rewrite the history
of the Basketball Team
of No.1 High School.
How narcissistic!
Wait and see.
Come on!
Come on, Shi Che!
Come on, everybody!
Whether you can be admitted
to the school team
depends on the last ten seconds.
Shi Che did a good job.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
It’s down there.
Down there.
It’s here.
Where’s Shi Che’s name?
How’s it?
Nothing.
Go to the toilet with me.
Go.
What?
Let me have a look.
There’s...
There’s obviously something wrong.
It...
Isn’t that Qu Wei?
Last year, he won the first prize
of the ﻿National Chemistry Contest.
When he’s here,
we’ll fail again, won’t we?
Seriously?
Jiang Haoyue?
The contest demon from No.1 High School?
He’s said to win all first prizes.
Isn’t he in the Physics Group?
Why is he coming
to the Chemistry Contest?
Maybe he wants to win all science prizes
during the high school.
Then Qu Wei will fail
to win the first prize this year.
In the cube ABCD,
prove B1D1 is perpendicular to A1C1.
Ziye,
how shall I solve this problem?
Listen to the teacher first.
I’ll tell you after class.
Geometry proofs like this
will help you
to consolidate basic knowledge points.
You can’t do wrong
in steps or resolving theories.
With established resolving theories,
you’ll also find a solution
and make the problem simple
even when you meet harder problems.
Lu Miao, why are you interested in anything
but math problems?
Come and solve this problem.
Because ABCD is a cube,
BD is perpendicular to AC.
What S?
What do you mean?
AC, not S.
AC.
Go back to your seat.
Don’t be absent-minded again.
All right. So much for today.
Class is over.
Where’s Shi Che?
Don’t ask.
He failed the selection
of the school basketball team.
What do we do?
What else can we do?
As usual,
he will either
drop out of school
or harass the whole school.
He’s so conceited?
Because Principle Shi is his father.
Captain,
did someone ask you to reject me?
I understand.
When a basketball genius like me
failed the selection,
there could be only one reason.
My father ordered you.
He wants to stifle a basketball genius
in the cradle
and stop him from coming into being!
So, he forced you to reject me,
right?
Shi Che,
you’re a good player.
But we considered that...
I’m right, huh?
I knew there was a plot.
When you considered,
someone threatened you.
Right?
I don’t blame you.
You might have argued for me.
But...
The pure basketball world
mustn’t be staid.
Do you mean stained?
Whatever.
Go on with the practice.
I knew what happened.
Now that someone uses
such a mean method
to block a genius,
I’ll fight against him.
All right.
Go on with your practice.
I won’t sell you out.
Don’t worry.
Sell me out?
What’s the problem with him?
Hello.
I’m Qu Wei.
Last year, I won the first prize
of the National Chemistry Contest.
I want to compete with you.
Don’t feel stressed out.
It’s just a friendly communication.
There’s no winning
or losing.
You can’t defeat me by praying.
Don’t bother me unless you have to.
What?
Scared already?
You’ve gotten ink on your hand.
I know. I know.
Yes. It’s my bad.
I forgot that yesterday.
Or I would have sent it to you.
Yes. What poor memories I have!
Sorry for that.
All right.
I’ll keep it in mind.
I will...
Stop!
No, I don’t mean you.
I’m sorry.
All right.
I know.
Your head teacher talked to me today,
specially making a phone call.
Do you know why?
You think we’re dancing?
Mom.
You had low points in the quiz.
Do you know why?
You don’t do your homework every day.
When Haoyue isn’t in class,
you can’t do your homework alone
because no one keeps an eye on you. Right?
I’ll confiscate all your comic books.
You mustn’t watch TV this term.
Got it?
Mom, give them back to me.
Before you make progress in study
or complete your homework,
don’t call me Mom.
You think I can’t restrain you?
Hello, Mr. Liu.
So, you really met a rival
when you were there?
I asked you to be cautious
because of the unlucky divination stick.
Luckily, you’re taking the luck charm
I gave you.
You know what?
You must carry it with you.
It’s for self-protection.
All right. Rest assured.
When are you coming back?
You have no idea.
When you’re away,
my mother is just like a stepmother.
I was simply away for two days.
You’re coming back in three days.
It’s not even the middle.
Have you done half of the problems
I left you?
Sorry, the number you have dialed
is powered off.
Sorry, the number you have...
Dialed is powered off.
Please call back late.
All right.
Go do your homework.
Good girl.
Everybody,
handle your personal grooming quickly.
My hair...
If you’re done, take your seats.
When you’re not done...
I forgot to wear the hairpin.
You, stand outside!
Use this.
I’m born with curly hair.
Put it on.
I had the curly hair
as early as in junior high.
Yes.
You’re not qualified.
That’s great.
The boy in Class 10, Grade 1,
why are you covering your head?
Come up.
Everybody,
if you’re like him,
don’t have the idea
of leaving things to chance.
Take off your hood.
Cool, man.
Shi Che!
What do you mean?
Principal Shi,
I dyed my hair
with your private savings.
Does it look cool?
You’ll be recorded with a grave demerit.
Director Yang,
kick him out.
Before he dyes his hair black,
he isn’t allowed to come to school!
Silence!
What’s this about?
Like father, like son.
Goodbye,
Conan.
Naruto.
Goodbye, Sakuragi.
It’s here.
I wondered why I couldn’t
find the whole pack.
I haven’t returned it yet.
Why are you here?
Why are you returning the books
before you finish reading them?
My mother asked me to do this.
A poor student can’t enjoy comics.
How about this?
I’ll rent
all your comic books.
If you want to read them, come to me.
You’re Mr. Arrogance?
What?
You borrowed all books
I had wanted to read.
We have the same taste.
I’m not as cool as you.
I hear you have the red hair,
to revolt against your father?
Not exactly.
I wanted to have red hair long ago.
You know what?
It looks cool.
Don’t pull a long face.
Go.
Let me make you happy!
Here we are.
Basketball court?
All problems
can be solved by a slam dunk.
I don’t think I’m tall enough
to do a slam dunk.
It doesn’t matter.
Do you want it or not?
I...
Pretend that this is your problem.
Smash it hard.
Dunk.
To the left.
To the right.
Yes. Stop.
Remember to hang there.
That’s the essential part!
All right.
Here I go.
Good shot!
Move a little bit.
What do you want?
I think you have a soul
for basketball, too.
No, I don’t.
Get down.
Don’t panic.
The hoop won’t break.
Guoguo and I often do this together.
I can’t hold on.
Go down and get me a ladder!
I won’t.
I want to play basketball!
Math homework, go away!
Do you really
love playing basketball that much?
I’m not sure.
But at this moment,
I love basketball most.
If you simply want to play basketball,
you don’t have to play
in the school team.
There’s club recruitment.
When you establish a basketball club,
you can also play frankly.
With my father working there,
he’ll certainly decline my application.
You can
use my name.
Come to school tomorrow.
Then I’ll lose my red hair,
won’t I?
Just sacrifice it for your dream.
In return,
let me teach you something.
Do you know the most important thing
in application problems?
Application.
What are you doing?
Why do I hear paper cutting?
I’m doing the math problem.
Wait until I finish the...
The triangular pyramid.
What’s the angle of ABC?
When I measure it, I’ll know.
What an idea!
Are you going to hand in the model
when handing in your homework?
Sure.
It’s how I solve problems.
Then your teacher needs
a large office.
Why?
Before you graduate,
your models will pile up like a pyramid.
You don’t understand.
All roads lead to Rome.
I’m pushing application problems
back to problem.
Who taught you such a new idea?
Shi Che did.
Shi Che?
A new student in our class.
He’s Mr. Arrogance,
who borrowed all comic books that
I wanted to read.
I never expected him
to have the same taste as mine
in comics.
I appreciate him.
I’ll send you his photo next time.
By the way,
in the alley that night,
he helped us.
He was the unique boy.
But now,
he has cut
his weird fringe
for his basketball dream
and abandoned it.
With my help,
he even established the Basketball Club.
What a sudden change!
A rival is coming.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Have you solved the problem?
Not yet.
Try and make a perpendicular line.
Why didn’t you tell me earlier?
I didn’t have to make the model.
What do I do now?
I’ve pasted it.
You kept talking about that student.
All right.
Go to bed early.
I’ll hang up.
Not bad.
(Open it, please.)
Your student Lu Miao
is an interesting girl.
Many students in my class
are quite interesting.
Dribble with your hands, all right?
Mind your pace.
Dribble with your hands.
Preserve the formation.
Follow up.
Keep it low.
Our...
Our application...
It’s approved?
No.
Our application...
When we were checking the result,
the teacher for club business said
he didn’t see our application.
Yes.
But I’m sure that
I gave him the application personally.
Sounds so familiar.
I’m going to see him.
So, is he going to...?
As the principle of our school,
can’t you be fair?
I’m also a student!
What do you want?
(Principal’s Office)
Approve the basketball club.
No way.
Then I’ll drop out of school
and come back as a PE student
and serve in the school team.
You can have a try.
Hello, Principle Shi.
I’m Lu Miao.
Lu for Lu You
and Miao for trees.
We’re...
Hello, Principle Shi.
We’re members of the basketball team.
We applied,
strictly following the school rules.
If you don’t approve it,
please give us
a reasonable explanation.
Our school doesn’t need
two basketball groups.
Then please give us
a fair chance to compete.
We can compete with the school team.
All right.
As you wish.
If you lose,
come back and study!
How many members do we need
for the match?
Three, including alternates.
How can I find three students?
When you asked me to join the club,
why didn’t you consider it?
I didn’t know
there weren’t enough members.
I was too excited and I...
How daring!
I admire you.
Is it a curse or compliment?
All right.
Do we really stand no chance to win?
Let me explain.
When we compete with the school team,
it’s like...
Naruto who doesn’t have ninja arts
competes with Orochimaru.
Or Luffy who can’t use Haki
competes with a Shogun.
We’ll be crushed.
But it concerns
whether our club can be established.
They got the chance for us.
We can’t give up.
You’re suddenly getting serious?
I’m always serious
about basketball issues.
Recruitment!
Training!
Match!
Only three things.
Can’t we do it?
We can!
You don’t need to be so loud.
We can’t be stronger
simply by yelling loudly.
Can we make it?
We can!
Good.
Recruitment, training and match.
This Friday,
we’re having a basketball match
with the school team.
But so far,
we haven’t had enough players yet.
This afternoon,
Shi Che and I were handing out
the recruitment leaflets.
But only one student came.
Students like sports, don’t they?
Only three days left.
Will we lose
even before the match starts?
It’s my fault.
I was too impulsive.
I shouldn’t have set a goal so quickly.
Don’t worry.
Maybe when you wake up tomorrow,
you’ll have enough players.
You’ve received
higher education.
How can you talk nonsense?
Go to sleep early.
(Recruitment for the Basketball Club)
I had some prejudice
against you.
I never expected you
to be so hot-blooded.
Welcome to the Basketball Club.
Come for the training.
Cheng, why are you coming here?
Jiang Haoyue said
if I joined the Basketball Club,
I could do two sets of papers less.
I come for the same reason.
Huanggang papers are quite hard.
Yes.
Zhang Cheng,
go over there.
Wang Xinwen, go over there.
All right.
OK.
By the way,
here’s our team uniform.
Let’s have a look.
Why do I feel something missing
on our team uniform
compared to the professional uniform
of the school team?
Don’t you think so?
Leave it to me.
Where is it?
Looking for this?
What exactly do you want?
Want it back?
Compete with me.
You want a competition, huh?
OK.
But you should wager on something.
Whoever loses will buy midnight snack
for everybody.
Good idea.
We’ll enjoy midnight snack.
No problem.
Pick a contest problem randomly.
Whoever solves it first
will win.
Whatever.
Game starts. Please turn around.
(Chemistry Contest Problem)
What?
You’re afraid that you’ll lose?
I give you ten seconds ahead.
Jiang Haoyue is using a perfect way
to solve the problem.
He’s indeed the contest demon.
Qu Wei, I want barbecue
for midnight snack!
I want crayfishes.
I’m not picky.
I’m OK with anything.
(Chemistry Contest Problem)
I never expected Jiang Haoyue
to solve the problem so wonderfully.
We won’t win the first prize again.
How awesome he is!
Qu Wei was one minute later
in solving the problem.
Look, this is Shi Che.
This Friday,
we’ll compete with the school team.
Considering the strength,
the Basketball Club will be crushed
very completely.
Shi Che and his members
will be disgraced.
The game starts momentarily.
Come on!
We won’t show mercy.
Come on then.
Defense!
It’s OK. One more time.
Defense! Defense!
Come on!
Shi Che, you’re great!
Guoguo, come on!
Defense!
Come on!
Pass the ball to me.
Shi Che!
Come on!
Time’s up.
The school team won.
It’s OK, Che.
We did our best. It’s worth it.
Let’s go have lunch.
Principle Shi.
Lu Miao.
Principle Shi,
what do you think of our performance?
Good. You played the game bravely.
I’m proud of you.
The Basketball Club...?
Shi Che...
A rule is a rule.
Go back home early.
Lu Miao.
Why are you here?
I came as soon as I was back
from the training.
How was the basketball match?
We lost.
It doesn’t matter.
The result isn’t important.
You’ve tried.
Meng,
let’s go have lunch.
Who...?
Who is this?
Jiang Haoyue.
He’s my brother.
You’re Shi Che?
You’re Jiang Haoyue?
It’s you?
You’re the only student
who doesn’t know him.
Would you like to have lunch with us?
No.
Okay.
Let’s go.
(Chick Fortuneteller)
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪