♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
=Flourish in Time=
=Episode 8=
=Crush on You in Ten Seconds=
You have big eyes, too.
Meng,
what is this style?
Hip-hop?
You know nothing.
Take the hairpin back.
What?
You think it’s ugly?
No,
but it doesn’t suit me.
You found your own style?
Whatever.
What I used before was too troublesome.
From now on,
I’ll be me.
I’ll dress myself however I like.
(Result of Nanfeng No. 1 High School Physics Contest)
Jiang Haoyue has won three rounds.
When can we go on the autumn trip?
Qu Wei still comes second.
Why do you keep
talking about Qu Wei lately?
Are you going to confess to him?
Speaking of confession,
your eye-contact...
All right,
I’ll shut up.
Shut up.
Something’s up.
Quickly,
the dishes are getting cold.
Mom, come on.
It seems to be Jiang’s birthday
two days later.
I’m aware.
How do we celebrate?
Have it your way.
Just keep it quiet.
Mr. Jiang doesn’t like too much noise.
Let’s invite him to our house.
I’ll buy him a cake.
Let me choose the cake.
I’m sure he’ll like it.
Cake again?
What’s wrong with a cake?
Cake is for birthday, isn’t it?
What? Soup for birthday celebration?
Get me soup.
Soup on birthday...
He would have a cake on every birthday.
Jiang is about to be 17.
Shouldn’t we give him a present?
I agree.
So...
A pen?
Let’s buy him a pen
to encourage him to study harder.
It has a positive connotation.
A pen?
How about something else?
A pen seems too ordinary.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
I’m choosing
a birthday present for my brother.
Oh,
you know what?
In my Ten Rules of Love,
a birthday is the best chance
to test a relationship.
Why?
The birthday persons easily
get emotional
and reveal their true feelings.
That’s when
their true feelings are tested.
Wait a second.
Jiang Haoyue’s true feelings
have nothing to do with me.
“Cheers to Our Friendship”?
This is useless.
Take this.
No, this is too blunt.
What’s wrong with being blunt?
Don’t shilly-shally.
No, no, no.
Just take this.
You’re a tough girl.
Just get on with it.
Well, Mr. Xie,
what present should I
give to Jiang Haoyue?
Does he have any hobbies?
Study.
Not this.
Study is what we are supposed to do
as students.
Presents to encourage him to study
are way too boring.
Give him a snow globe.
This is worse.
That’s too sissy.
Sissy? Why?
What do you have in mind then?
(Being cool is easy to achieve)
I know.
Jiang Haoyue is sitting
right over there.
We’ll act as planned.
We measure his size in secret.
Can it work?
He’ll notice it.
No worries. Trust me.
Just stay with me later.
Go.
Come on.
Quickly.
Quickly, go.
Hi,
is this seat taken?
No.
What a coincidence!
You’re self-studying here?
Why are you here?
I’m here to study.
I love to study the most.
What are you studying?
English.
Are you sure it’s not a comic book?
No, I assure it is not.
Trust me.
My English is good.
My English is good. Don’t mind me.
Stay focused on your book.
Focus, got it?
You must be tired.
How about I give you a massage?
Jiang Haoyue,
the teacher told me that
there will be another exam next week.
Let’s go get the examination papers.
Okay.
Lu Miao,
why are you here?
I’m here to help my bro with his study.
The No. 1 student
in our grade doesn’t need your help.
Xie Ziye.
Hello, senior.
What is this?
Whose tape is it?
Is it not yours?
Not in a million years.
I’ll give it to lost-and-found.
Let’s go. Class is about to begin.
The waistline.
How do I measure that?
Are you okay?
I’m fine.
My legs got numb
because I stood for too long.
Get up first.
Be careful when you walk.
Your pretext is ridiculous.
See you around.
Did you get it?
Probably.
Go.
Everybody,
the date of the autumn
trip has been decided.
No class!
October 13. The day after tomorrow.
No class is the best!
Finally, I get to relax my brain.
What’s wrong with you?
Aren’t you happy about the trip?
The date of the autumn trip
is my brother’s birthday.
What shall I do?
(Mr. Jiang’s birthday)
Are you going on the
autumn trip the day after tomorrow?
No.
I’ll be preparing for the contest
in school.
You can’t be doing exercises forever.
What?
It’s your birthday
the day after tomorrow.
You forget that?
I don’t care about my birthday.
You need to care, though.
You need to properly
celebrate your birthday
so that
in the next year to come,
fortune will favor you
and all the unhappiness will go away.
If only it could be that simple.
Let’s go.
For this autumn trip,
I’ve prepared an alpenstock,
an all-purpose pickaxe
and a tent.
We’re not going into the wild.
It’s just a natural park.
You don’t need these.
Bear Grylls said
nature is beautiful
but also dangerous.
I’ll be honest with you,
I’ve taken professional
survival courses.
Well, in that case,
I’ll bring more snacks.
I’ll bring my edacious mouth.
Meng, what will you bring?
Or how about you join us?
I guarantee you enough food.
I’ll skip it.
Skip class?
Let’s do this together.
I don’t want to attend
the math class in the afternoon anyway.
I’ll skip the autumn trip.
Skip the autumn trip?
Why would she do that?
For Jiang Haoyue.
The date of the autumn trip
is Jiang Haoyue’s birthday.
Him again!?
Again.
Come on.
Che, I’m Guoguo,
I’m not Jiang Haoyue.
Don’t take it out on me.
She just wants
to celebrate his birthday.
Be the bigger man.
It comes only once in a year.
The autumn trip comes
once in a year as well.
But all she cares about
is Jiang Haoyue.
Even a fool can tell.
I don’t believe it.
My fire will melt her iceberg.
But after the iceberg melts,
it puts out the fire.
All right, I’ll shut up.
What are you going to do next?
I can’t play anymore.
I won’t let Lu Miao...
Skip...
Autumn...
Trip!
Hello?
Okay.
I’ll see you an hour later.
What?
Jiang Haoyue’s birthday cake is coming.
I’ve only gotten one hour.
Hey, everyone,
wake up.
We’ll reach our destination in a bit.
We’ll have a
two-man-three-foot game first.
To be on the safe side,
we’ll choose a girl and a boy
to participate in the game.
The boy will be...
Shi Che.
Okay?
And the girl will be...
Lu Miao.
Okay?
So wakey, everybody.
And pack your stuff.
You’re stuck with me.
Charge! Charge!
What? Why does it take
you so long to tie your shoes?
Meng,
you know what?
I’ve had this game before.
You’ll easily sprain your ankle.
So you must
tie your shoes firmly
to avoid the injury.
Fussy.
You know what?
This is what a professional
athlete would do.
I’ve asked the PE teachers,
this will be a race
where two people team up as one.
Practice well
before we sign up.
No rush. Safety comes first.
- Okay, Mr. Wen.
- Carry on.
What time is it?
Only half an hour left.
Let’s sign up for the race, quickly.
Come on.
What’s the rush, Meng?
I’m in a rush!
All right.
This is about the honor of our class.
We must practice well.
Honor is bigger than my life.
We cannot disappoint our classmates
or Mr. Wen.
Now.
Let’s move.
My bad.
I’m such an idiot.
It’s the ribbon.
The knot isn’t tight enough.
You’re not an idiot.
You just don’t want to knot it well.
How can you say this?
It’s the ribbon’s problem.
It has nothing to do with me.
Che, how about I help you tie the knot?
Do you think it’s my problem?
It’s sure...
It is your problem.
You’re stalling.
I’m stalling?
You try it.
Don’t just make comments.
Why would I try it? It’s your race.
I’m doing it for the group,
for the class,
for us all! Okay?
Don’t you think I can
see through your trick?
You didn’t tie the knot well on purpose.
I think you two
can be great teammates,
so how about you two
participate in the race?
I’m off. Goodbye.
Meng, where are you going?
Next, Class 10 and Class 5, Grade 1.
Get ready.
Are you ready?
Why you two?
Lu Miao...
Has got diarrhea.
All right, then.
Coming right away.
Move.
Quickly.
Ready. Go.
Come on!
One! Two!
Hey!
Where are you taking me?
Let’s go.
We don’t have time.
Where are you going, Meng?
Let me go.
You can’t leave the crowd
without permission.
Jiang Haoyue’s birthday
comes only once in a year.
It is important.
The autumn trip comes
once in a year as well.
Let me go.
Get down.
Thanks, Ye.
I’ll treat you for snacks.
Are you a dog, Chlorophyll?
Go!
It’s your fault!
You took me here with you.
Stop talking. Make haste!
What’s taking you so long?
Speed up!
Are you done? Come on!
Idiot.
Hello.
Sorry.
It’s okay.
Your cake?
Yeah.
Here you go.
All right, bye.
Why did you come back?
Skipping the autumn trip is so cool.
How could I not do it?
Who is there?
Who?
Mr. Yang is coming.
We split up.
I saw you.
Which class are you in?
Stop!
I’ll catch you.
Lu Miao?
Why are you here?
Never mind this.
Come with me!
Shi Che, stop!
Stop!
Why are we hiding here?
I wanted to celebrate your birthday.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Ten seconds already.
He moved away his eyes first.
You...
Gotcha!
Follow me to my office!
Oh, no!
What?
Have you become thinner?
I got it.
(Office of Educational Administration)
Lu Miao?
She’s in my office.
Shi Che in your class is here, too.
They’re all in school.
Whose birthday is it?
Mine.
Jiang Haoyue,
although Lu Miao is your sister,
you can’t cover for her every time.
Today really is my birthday.
Lu Miao,
Shi Che!
I must stress it one more time.
You mustn’t leave the group
without permission again!
Your teachers are trying
to be responsible for you.
Please stop causing
us more trouble.
- Got it!
Eat the cake, then.
Happy birthday to you.
Haoyue, happy birthday.
Meng...
Don’t come over.
Watch me!
Mr. Yang, I didn’t do it on purpose.
Shi Che!
I didn’t! I swear!
You!
You stop!
You stop there!
Shi Che, get over here!
You guys who play overnight,
pay the money now.
It hasn’t passed 13th yet.
What’s the rush?
What day is it today?
Did you get yourself drunk again?
13th.
You don’t remember the date?
(Brat)
Sorry,
the number you have dialed
is not available from this service.
Stupid signals.
You’re the host.
Come on, finish the last game.
What’s the rush?
You’re too eager to lose money?
(Son! Happy birthday!)
Son! happy birthday!
You’re here as expected.
You’re still awake.
This is for you.
What’s this?
Open it and have a look.
A shirt.
Try it on.
Where did you buy it?
I had it tailored for you.
Tailored?
How do you know my size?
Just try it on first.
Just as thought,
it’s too loose at the waist.
No, it’s fine.
I like it to be loose.
So...
You like the present, don’t you?
I do, very much.
Thank you.
Honestly,
you look more handsome
in the white shirt
than those stars on TV.
Do I?
Yeah.
Well,
handsome guy,
the seventeenth year of your life
has officially started.
Do you have any thoughts?
Thoughts?
I want to...
Be an adult as soon as possible.
What’s so good about being an adult?
When I’m an adult,
I get to make my own choices.
Then I want to be an adult, too.
You?
You can be a kid forever.
It’s your birthday,
so I’m going to let you off.
Oh, yeah.
This card was going to...
Never mind.
Open it when you get back.
(Mom)
Hello, mom.
Hello, son.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
I was busy all day.
Sorry for being late.
I wanted to call you in the daytime.
It’s okay.
I have a present for you.
You’re a big boy now.
I want you to live with me,
so you can receive better education.
Also...
Also you can be rid of Jiang Yi
for good.
You and I both know that
Jiang Yi will never turn good.
He’ll eventually become your liability.
But he won’t let me go.
You’ll be an adult a year later.
You’ll be able to choose your own path.
I also wish to make my own choices.
No worries.
Oh, have you made a wish?
Not yet.
Make one to me, then.
I want...
It’s okay if you have no idea.
I owe you one.
When you’re here with me,
everything becomes easy.
I wish that all of your dreams
would come true.
Haoyue,
this is your birthday present.
You can have it.
Say thank you.
Thank you.
Why did you give the present from me
to a stranger?
You!
This is for you.
Why did you throw away
the present from me?
Too many snacks decay your teeth.
Are you a fool?
You can share the snacks with me.
You’re wasteful.
I’ll eat these, then.
Yummy.
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪