♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
=Flourish in Time=
=Episode 7=
=Genius Doesn’t Understand Girls=
Is that the belle?
Yes. But why does she look so weird?
I want dried bean curd.
And cabbage.
Hurry up.
There will be no seats.
Rest assured.
My brother must’ve reserved one for me.
Hello, Daifei.
Hello.
Do you know each other?
Yes.
Good luck!
I’m sorry but it’s occupied.
I can’t stand up now.
My shoes...
I’m going somewhere else.
No!
If you leave,
I’ll be more embarrassed.
Please.
Is this your new friend?
I don’t know her.
Excuse me.
Please move away.
This is my seat.
How about you sit here?
Her sole is broken.
Her name is...
Daifei.
Daifei (Literally Empress)?
I am Empress Miao!
Jiang Haoyue.
Do you really think you are an emperor?
Sorry.
You misunderstood it.
My name is Daifei.
It literally means red flower.
How come someone has such a name?
Stop making a scene.
Just sit here.
Am I making a scene?
Alright.
She won’t leave.
I will.
Me too.
Thanks.
Are you still angry with Jiang Haoyue?
Don’t bring up that name.
You are quite possessive, huh?
Is it my fault?
Of course not.
That’s originally my seat.
How could he leave it to her?
Yes.
Jiang Haoyue went too far
this time.
He even affectionately
called her Daifei.
He never called me Miao that way.
It’s understandable for the first part.
But for the other,
it sounds like you are jealous.
Isn’t he your brother?
Could it be that you like him?
No way!
How could I like him?
It’s normal if you like him.
He ranks number one
in my heart.
That should be my question.
Do you like him?
Didn’t you say you don’t like him?
Why are you so nervous?
Let me calculate the intimacy index
for you two.
How?
Have you ever clasped hands with him?
Let’s get started.
I won!
Arm-wrestling.
Arm-wrestling isn’t hand-clasping.
Doesn’t it count?
That’s nothing about intimacy.
That’s absolutely confrontation.
Let me try another way.
Is there more?
Yes!
If you can look into his eyes
over ten seconds,
then you two are purely
siblings.
If you can’t...
Wait.
It’s easy.
Looking into his eyes for ten seconds?
That’s quite easy.
You can have a try.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Let’s go.
How about I hold it?
Let me hold it.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Why didn’t you wake me up?
I meant to do it when we arrived.
How many stops to go?
Three.
Today in the canteen,
that girl’s sole was off.
So, she couldn’t walk.
Then why did you sit there?
She’d be embarrassed if I left.
Are you so considerate now?
Why are you so angry?
You shouldn’t do that anyway.
Here.
Your favorite chocolate.
Next time, I’ll leave
and you’ll sit there.
So beautiful!
It’s like a planet!
Look into his eyes for ten seconds.
Lu Miao. You can do it.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
This actress is so pretty.
Which actress is pretty?
Which one?
Miao.
Your mother was very pretty
when she was young.
Back in the school,
she had a well-known nickname.
What was it?
“Li Zi in Class 2”.
Really?
“Li Zi in Class 2”?
Who is Li Zi?
No kidding. It’s true.
All my classmates knew my nickname.
In the old days,
we liked watching Hong Kong movies.
All the girls
were given a Hong Kong nickname.
Like “North Street Joey Wong”.
“Western City Maggie Cheung”.
Because there were many beauties
in my class.
That’s why your dad
always went to my class.
I went to see you.
Save it.
Jiang.
Back then these belles were popular
nationwide.
Who do you think was the prettiest?
They were all good-looking.
Do you like all of them?
Playboy.
What are you doing?
Have you finished your homework?
I am correcting the answers.
You have my test paper.
Do you know
why the stars have different colors?
Because
stones have different kinds.
These stars. Not stones.
Why then?
Stars are different in color,
because their surface temperatures
differ.
Some stars give off white light
whose surface temperature
is up to
11.5 thousand degrees.
Some stars give off red light
whose surface temperature is
about 2,600 or 3,600 degrees.
Some stars give off blue light
whose surface temperature is
up to 25 thousand or 40 thousand.
What about the sun?
On the sun,
the surface temperature is
about 6 thousand degrees.
That’s why it looks yellow.
Mr. Genius.
May I ask you another question?
What kind of girls
do you like?
What is it to do with what I said?
I’m just curious.
Just tell me.
I like girls
with big eyes
and sweet smiles.
Big eyes.
Sweet smiles.
My name is Daifei.
It literally means red flower.
Doesn’t he mean Su Daifei?
Look at the poem you wrote!
“When shall we be trimming wicks again,
together the couple sit until dawn.”
Since the wick is trimmed off,
how can they sit until dawn?
Don’t laugh at me!
Give my test paper back!
No.
Give it back!
Jiang Haoyue.
Give it back to me!
No.
My hair...
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Don’t move.
Okay.
I’m going home.
Oh, no!
Do I really...?
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Oh, no!
I can’t even look at his photo.
You agreed to be friends with him
and he still rejected?
Who would be friends with him?
Did he really say that?
For Lu Miao?
That makes sense.
You don’t wear AJ6,
yet you wear Warrior shoes.
At the beginning,
I thought he’s Akagi Takenori.
Turns out he is Rukawa Kaede.
It’s not too late to know it now.
No.
I must let Miao stay away from him.
Can this thing
really make my eyes look bigger?
Trust me.
Come on.
Sorry.
Paper.
Why did you do these things lately?
You changed hairstyle
and learned makeup.
Is it because...?
Definitely not.
Hello, Panda.
Good cosplay.
Who did the makeup for you?
It’s hideous.
- None of your business!
Look at my hairpin.
Fashionable, isn’t it?
As you please.
Girlish.
I’m so manly.
I can hold it.
Are you manly?
Now it looks better.
Take it as a gift.
No, I’ll buy one myself.
It’s fine. I have plenty.
Plenty?
Are you a girl?
Watch your tongue!
(Shi Che. Badmouthed - 10086)
Ziye. Don’t be angry.
Think about your motto.
Calm.
Science.
Rationality.
That’s it. Don’t be angry.
By the way,
did you get your answer
from the gaze?
No.
Gaze? What gaze?
I’ll buy you a drink after class.
Sir. Bill, please.
Okay.
Can you eat so much?
My treat.
Well.
What did Miao say to you just now?
Do you want to know?
Open it.
Watch your service attitude.
That’s more like it.
42.
42?
Do you know Skinship rules?
Skin and ship.
What?
You are really bad at study.
Have you ever held
a girl’s hand?
Great!
Yes.
How did you feel?
Very happy.
Have you ever
embraced a girl?
Did you hear that?
Our score is the highest now!
Yes.
Also very happy.
The last question.
Have you ever looked into her eyes?
Yes.
Who looked away first?
Me.
You
like that girl.
I...
I’m back to the classroom.
This is Skinship principle!
Big eyes.
Sweet smiles.
Daifei. Let’s go shopping later.
Looking closely,
her eyes are not that big.
Nuts!
Why is she gone?
Was that
indirect hand-holding?
Of course not.
Haoyue.
Do you find
anything different on me today?
Different?
Have you gained weight?
Have a close look.
A hairpin?
Is it beautiful?
Not very good.
Go.
Isn’t it too red?
If I apply this,
Director Yang would openly criticize me.
What color is this?
It looks too mature.
No.
It’s not for my age.
This looks good.
(Nanfeng No.1 High School)
We wear the same uniforms.
Why does it fit well
on the exercise leader?
They got their uniforms trimmed.
Really?
I’ll go trim it tonight.
Will you join me?
Yes.
Yours looks better.
Yours is good, too.
Thank you, sir.
We’re leaving.
- Goodbye.
- See you.
Goodbye.
Sir.
To trim your school uniform?
How did you know it?
You students
come to a tailor’s shop.
What else could it be
if not trimming school uniforms?
Is it your first time here?
Did you know it as well?
Students who come here
for the first time
all come with black plastic bags
like this.
Furtively.
Sir.
Those two girls’ uniforms
were gorgeous.
Could I trim it that way?
Make it short and shrink the waist.
Then your waist looks thin
and your legs long.
That will look great.
That makes sense.
I’ll make it shorter then.
To here.
Girl.
Wind will get in if it’s too short.
You’ll have a stomachache.
Really?
Alright.
Sir.
Is that white shirt
made by you?
Of course.
However,
it was customized for someone.
Is it costly?
No.
You look different today.
Let’s go.
You are in a good mood today.
Yes.
Is your uniform...?
Miao.
Shrunk from washing?
I trimmed it short on purpose.
Jiang Haoyue.
Miao!
You look different today.
Thanks to your hairpin.
Is the hairpin from him?
Yes.
The same ones.
A good match, isn’t it?
Wait for me.
This is well crafted.
You can have it.
It’s nice of you.
Any problem?
No.
Speak.
I have a friend.
She suddenly
pays attention to her dressing.
Why is that?
Lu Miao?
Your friend
is either me or Lu Miao.
What else could it be?
She is into someone.
She gets along well
with her boy classmates.
Didn’t you give it to me?
I changed my mind.
Do you find out that
Miao has gotten pretty lately?
Why do you care about her so much?
No, that’s just how I feel.
You are overthinking.
She did all of that for me.
Have you noticed it?
Since she wore the hairpin I bought,
she’s been
dressing up all for me.
Does it ever come to you...?
No.
For Miao and me,
Jiang Haoyue is just a supporting role.
No. I mean...
Alright. Leading role.
Get back the trash can.
Sorry.
You are kinder.
Did you see
who knocked me?
Will you deduct his points?
Of course.
That’s a hit-and-run.
Your sister has a good figure.
Infuriated.
Trimming school uniforms isn’t allowed.
Do you know it?
I didn’t scribble on it.
I just changed the size.
Hi.
These are heavy.
Let me carry them in for you.
Thanks...
What’s your name?
You’ve thanked me.
Xie...
Xie Ziye.
My name is Xie Ziye.
Let’s go.
I think it’s beautiful.
It’s not.
What?
You should behave like a student.
Why do you learn from those bad guys?
It’s trending now.
People all get it trimmed.
Do you have to follow them?
You know nothing!
Jiang Haoyue!
You idiot!
You are heartless!
You fool!
You zombie!
You...!
Congcong.
He’s so clever.
How come he can’t understand
my feelings?
I just want to look good.
I’m sick of the sack-like uniform.
I want to be shiny. Can’t I?
I don’t care about others.
I just want his recognition.
Is it so hard?
(Chick Fortuneteller)
The uniform is shortened.
It’s true that I’ll easily get a cold.
I’d better wear my original clothes.
Can I have some fashionable hairpins?
Those inside are all new styles.
Thanks.
This is good.
I’ll buy it.
Sorry.
Jiang Haoyue.
It’s you!
I didn’t think you’d come here.
I’m just passing by.
I’m going.
What a coincidence.
Could you help me
pick a hairpin?
I can’t decide.
Yeah.
That’s the lowest price.
Mom.
Where is my uniform coat?
Yes.
No one else will offer you
a lower price.
Is it being washed?
Why didn’t you ride the bike today?
Nor did you.
- Yesterday...
After you.
I was too meddlesome yesterday.
Afterwards,
I will no longer meddle
in your business.
Good.
You...
What did you want to say just now?
I forgot.
You should behave like a student.
Look at what you wear!
How gaudy these are!
How should I explain it to your parents?
Go deal with them now!
Got it?
Go for classes.
Hello, Director Yang.
Why are you hiding your hands?
Get your hands out.
Your hands are not okay.
I’m gonna remove the polish.
How come he has this in his pocket?
Your hair is not okay either.
I’m tying it up now.
Tidy up your dress.
Go for classes.
Thank you, Director Yang.
Somebody said he wouldn’t
mind my business.
Take your school uniform.
My uniform will be dry tomorrow.
Wear it
for the morning exercise in a while.
Wear mine.
By the way,
where did you get this headrope?
I picked up on the road.
Did you?
It’s good on you.
Liar.
You said that
you fancy girls like Su Daifei.
When did I say I fancy her?
Didn’t you say that
you like girls
with big eyes and sweet smiles?
Also, she trimmed her uniform
and you didn’t say anything about that.
You have big eyes as well.
Alright. Be good.
Go.
I stole my mom’s lipstick.
Can you help me make up?
Make up?
Why do you come to me?
Mom said pretty guys can make up.
But I’m a boy.
But you are pretty.
Come on. Try it.
Hurry.
Jiang Haoyue.
Come out! Stop hiding!
I know you’re inside!
Jiang Haoyue! Come out!
Come out or I won’t leave!
What are you drawing?
Nothing.
What’s in your hand?
Show me.
Nothing.
No.
Give me!
One.
Two.
Here you are.
Go home with me!
No!
You only scold me but not him!
He drew on my face!
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪