♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
=Flourish in Time=
=Episode 1=
=I’m Not Qualified To Be
Jiang Haoyue’s Sister=
My name is Lu Miao.
It’s the first day for my high school.
I try my best to avoid one person.
He is my neighbor.
My childhood friend.
He’s also the one who covered my glory
since childhood.
Jiang Haoyue!
Since the first day when he appeared,
I was forced to be his little sister.
We eat the same meals.
We drink the same water.
Even we take the same bus
to go to school.
But everyone can only see
his excellence.
After years of knowing each other,
I deeply realize that
what being nobody means.
So I decide that
I can’t let others know
our relationship.
Because
with him by my side,
I always become a nobody.
From today on,
I will stand out.
I don’t want others to recognize me
because I’m Jiang Haoyue’s sister.
Please give me a cabbage.
That’s right.
Miao, going to school?
Shh.
Miao…
That’s all I want.
Okay. I pack them for you.
Please weigh them.
Sir, here are your vegetables.
What’s wrong with you?
Lu Miao, what’re you doing?
Be careful!
Here you are.
Sir, sorry.
Sorry.
It’s fine.
These bricks can be piled
as the goal.
Yeah.
Don’t take my bricks away!
Well, put them down.
Run.
Let’s play football.
Let’s play.
Wait to be punished later.
You are avoiding me?
I’m not.
I’m attracted to rock climbing
because I watched the Olympics
some time ago.
So I climb the wall
to experience it.
There is no rock climbing
in the Olympic.
You put me down first.
Well, you…
Put me down.
Why avoid me?
I don’t want others to recognize me
as your sister in high school.
I want others to know me
because I am Lu Miao.
Fine.
I wait for the bus at the last stop.
He is so obedient.
You bastard!
I bring you up for nothing.
You can’t take the ball by hands.
You little kids!
You dare to challenge me.
Our bricks…
Stop!
Excuse me!
Be careful!
Sit here.
Why is she holding a brick?
I have no idea.
I actually meet you again!
If you don’t go to take the brick,
you won’t meet me.
You sit here.
Sit down.
Look! What is she doing?
Put your brick away.
You’re a bit handsome.
But I can’t use it right now.
A piece of film is expensive.
I will use it
for more meaning things.
What are more meaning things?
For example,
a speech for freshmen.
Won’t you give a speech
on the stage?
How about I take a picture
for you by then?
Forget it.
You will give the same speech
as before?
So,
what’s the problem?
It’s boring to read the example.
I change something for you.
What do you think?
Chang, like how?
I remember the last sentence
in your note is new…
New Journey.
Hope you work toward your new goals.
Right.
I change it into that
the past is meaningless.
For the fate you dislike,
from now on, don’t accept it.
How do you think?
Childish!
Forget it!
Sit here.
(Nanfeng No. 1 High School)
I go first.
You wait here for 20…
30 seconds.
Wait.
What’s up?
Hope you have good school days.
So do you.
Keep a distance.
Let’s pretend to be strangers.
(A Warm Welcome to Freshmen)
(Class 10, Grade 1)
Look over there.
Hello.
A new school is really a new start.
Everyone is kind and friendly.
Hello.
My name is Chen Guoguo.
C-H-E-N.
G-U-O, the pronunciation
from cashew nut.
G-U-O, the pronunciation from apple.
What’s the difference?
Here’s the thing.
My dad likes cashew nuts.
My mom likes apples.
So they are definitely different.
Hello.
I’m Lu Miao.
The same surname with the poet,
Lu You.
M-I-A-O,
the pronunciation from seedlings.
Actually, at the entrance to school,
I have noticed you.
After getting rid of Jiang Haoyue,
I finally find myself.
Really?
Really.
Because
your selfie on your back is very good.
Jiang Haoyue!
You…
Sorry.
Let it go.
Give me that!
Look at her.
Why are you laughing?
So funny?
This girl is very funny.
I have my reason
to bring this brick here.
Enough! Stop explaining it.
I don’t feel strange
whatever you put in your backpack.
Just don’t disturb me.
Sorry about earlier.
Lu…
…Miao.
(Class 1, Grade 2)
Be quiet, students from Grade 1.
Why our class don’t move
to the second floor with other classes?
Why do you think?
Teachers look after Jiang Haoyue.
We have to stay in the same floor
with freshmen of Grade 1
and be mocked by students
from the second floor.
Will we stay here for three years?
It’s like we’re repeaters.
It sucks.
Why am I in the same class
with Jiang Haoyue?
He…
The opening ceremony is about to start.
Students of all classes
please go to the auditorium.
The hot summer has passed.
We usher in cool Autumn.
(Nanfeng No. 1 High School)
Our school is full of energy
because of you.
Today, I feel honored to
make a speech here
on behalf of students.
I’d like to extend my sincere respect
to all the students and faculty
and give my best regards
to all freshmen.
It turns out he is Jiang Haoyue.
I thought all super learners are ugly.
Who has this senior’s
contact information?
He’s cool.
Senior?
Naive!
Everyone will become a person…
Boring.
Perfunctory.
Routine.
Prior to admission…
Hold on. Let’s me check it out.
Alright.
Prior to admission,
everyone, more or less,
has gains and losses,
has joys and grievances.
But now,
your future is unknown.
I want to tell you,
no matter what happened in the past,
the past is meaningless.
After entering the high school,
for the fate you dislike,
from now on…
Don’t accept it.
…don’t accept it.
A nice speech.
Never thought a super scholar
also watches Naruto.
This guy sounds interesting.
I told him about that.
Who are you?
You are qualified to lecture
Jiang Haoyue?
He’s my…
Your…
My senior next to my class.
Wake up!
Stop dreaming!
Just wait and see.
Finally,
I will stand on the stage
of the auditorium
and let Jiang Haoyue
think highly of me.
(Being excellence is a choice)
(The difference between you and the best
lies in efforts, but not intelligence)
(No need to sleep too long when living,
you will sleep all the time after death)
(Bed is the grave for youth)
The meaning of sets
is not complicated.
(Bed is the grave for youth)
In our lives,
we can meet all kinds of sets.
See here.
On the blackboard,
natural numbers and nonnatural numbers
have different scopes.
The representing methods of their sets
are also different.
Okay. We learn
the nature of integer next.
If a number has an odd number
in the last place,
then this number can be divided by two.
If one number has a number in the units
which can be divided by three,
then this number can be divided
by three.
If the last two digits of one number
can be divided by four,
then this number
can be divided by four.
(Being excellence is a choice)
Let me have a breath
of honorable air on the stage.
(Nanfeng No. 1 High School)
I am Lu Miao from Class 10, Grade 1.
Today,
I can’t stay awake in the class.
It makes me one step away from
being an excellent person.
I’m guilty.
I confess my mistake.
As a punishment,
I won’t have lunch today.
But
I still want to take a picture.
Who is there?
Today is such a bad day for me!
If found,
I will be listed in the blacklist.
Who’s there?
Who did this?
Come out!
He finally leaves.
Is anybody here?
I’m screwed.
It’s such a mess.
I have to tell Mr. Yang quickly.
Hello.
I left this camera
when I gave a speech this morning.
It is yours.
You take it well.
Don’t drop it again.
Okay. I see.
I’ll be right there.
Is anybody here?
Jiang Haoyue.
Be quick!
Help me open the door.
Door!
Hurry up!
Open the door for me.
No.
Don’t shoot.
Hurry up!
Why stand still?
Jiang Haoyue!
Open the door.
Stop shooting!
Stop!
Let me out!
Jiang Haoyue!
Why are you doing there?
(Office of Educational Administration)
Why were you in the auditorium?
The door is unlocked.
Why didn’t you have classes?
You two are in love?
No.
What on earth is your relationship?
What’s your relationship
with Jiang Haoyue?
He is my old brother.
Good.
You deserve to be
Jiang Haoyue’s little sister.
Thank you.
You’re Jiang Haoyue’s sister.
How could you fight with others?
Mr. Yang, we have no relations.
I went to the auditorium to…
To…
Make a pilgrimage.
Pilgrimage?
That’s right.
The holy pattern
in the school flag
made me
stretch hands
to touch it and get some wisdom.
But I was too excited
in my heart.
I couldn’t control
my strength.
I love our school so much.
About this,
Jiang Haoyue can be my witness.
Right?
Is it true?
Mr. Yang.
It’s true we don’t know each other.
No, we don’t.
I went to the auditorium
to get my camera back.
They have the same father,
Lu Yongfei.
No wonder
they are unwilling to admit it.
They are brother and sister
from a blended family.
Lu Miao,
do you know
you have destroyed public facilities
and violated school rules
and regulations?
Do cleaning for one week
as the punishment.
Go back.
Mr. Yang,
I will go now.
Go.
He is heartless.
I didn’t admit our relationship.
He actually cooperated with me.
Since the childhood,
I took blame for him
and suffered a lot.
If you took blame for me,
I would have been dead long ago.
What?
You block my way.
It’s no need to kowtow.
I was in bad luck
because of this lace.
This kind of lace like nylon
is easily to get loose.
I teach you only once.
Look carefully.
Nothing to be proud of.
I have no interest in it.
Yes, you’re interested
in making troubles.
Don’t forget to sweep the floor.
See you.
Jiang Haoyue…
Hey, desk mate.
We meet again.
You also walk this way?
Which bus do you take?
I just saw Jiang Haoyue tie your lace.
Don’t tell others.
Just pretend that nothing happened.
Nothing happened.
You cooperate with me
and answer several questions.
I consider keeping it secret.
What questions?
What’s your relationship
with Jiang Haoyue?
Neighbors?
Childhood friends?
Family members?
If others were you,
they would wake up with laughs.
Why do you hide it?
I don’t want to be a nobody
behind Jiang Haoyue.
I want to have a brilliant life
belonging to me.
I don’t see any shining points
about you.
Except my bad grades,
I have many merits.
For example,
I’m ready to help others.
I’m outgoing.
I have no interest in you.
Desk mate…
Win by my own draw. I win.
Why do I lose again?
Bad machine!
Pay me the money!
He must cheat.
Yes, don’t fool us.
What’s up, buddy?
Find him to ask for money.
I’m leaving.
You are the owner?
Did you do something to the machine?
I’m talking to you.
Where are you looking at?
Are you deaf?
Go on.
It hurts.
Please be gentle.
Come on!
Bro.
What?
Don’t pay me, right?
It’s nothing.
You go on playing.
Bro,
let’s talk at the door.
Okay?
It hurts.
Bro,
please be gentle.
it hurts.
Don’t pay me, right?
Come on!
Bro…
You got a death wish.
I pay you
all expenses.
Okay?
Give him money.
Pay me?
Hurry up.
You ask me to pay, right?
Give him money.
Money!
Bro, it’s done.
Go away.
Don’t you have eyes?
Are you blind?
Just wait and see.
Shut up.
Stop.
Are you blind?
You see me,
but you don’t call me dad.
Take it.
I don’t go back recently.
What relationship is the guy
with the owner?
He may be his son.
The owner is your dad?
Get out of my way.
Call your dad.
As long as he pays us,
we won’t hurt you.
I have nothing to do with him.
Get out of my way.
Where do you go?
It’s your choice.
Get out of my way.
Get out?
I’ll beat you up today.
Bad choice.
Beat him!
Pay me or not!
Pay me back.
Wanna run?
Go. Go to your dad.
Will I have no girlfriends
in my high school?
You have the nerve!
Beat him!
Bro,
he is disabled.
What about let him go?
Will you pay my money back?
Where are you going?
This guy is stubborn.
If you pay me money back,
nothing will happen.
Rubbish!
How dare you!
Who are you?
If you dare to beat my brother,
I will give you a lesson.
Jiang Haoyue.
Go away.
It’s dirty.
Neither of you can leave.
You play the hero!
Go to hell!
Stop!
Are you powerful enough?
You are powerful, right?
Stop!
Bro,
if we continue, he will be dead.
Stand up!
Jiang Haoyue!
If you dare touch her,
I risk my life to fight with you.
You stop!
Bro…
Don’t run.
I help you chase them.
Bro, does he still chase us?
I can’t run.
Not yet.
I see you bully others
from a long distance.
Since you have the nerve to fight,
then don’t be afraid of
being caught.
Go.
Beat him!
Don’t cry.
I’m not crying.
Your hair is a mess.
Your eyes swell up.
Listen to me. Don’t cry.
If you continue to cry,
you will not look good.
Later, we go to my house first
and get your clothes changed
before you go home.
I help you wash your clothes.
Okay.
Well…
Don’t tell your parents
about what happened today.
In recent days,
I don’t go to your house for dinner.
If they ask you why,
you tell them
Jiang Haoyue is in bad mood.
Then they won’t ask more.
You should be scared today.
It’s all my fault.
I shouldn’t avoid you.
I should go home
together with you.
It’s not your fault.
If no one came
to help, what should you do?
You appeared finally.
What’s wrong?
Sit down.
Does your leg hurt again?
I’ll get your medicine.
I’m fine.
You sit down.
No…
How is your leg?
It’s fine.
I want to see pictures.
Let’s go to and leave school
together afterwards.
You’re not afraid…
That’s not important.
Only you are the most important.
You take me as your brother?
(Emergency building)
(Operating room)
Haoyue!
Kid…
Where is the kid?
Sorry.
Who hit my kid?
Don’t be anxious.
I’m asking you who hit my son.
It’s me.
Why did you beat him?
Step aside!
Wait,
your kid is inside.
We hit your kid.
It’s our fault.
Either punishment
or payment,
we never deny it.
I’m asking how serious
you hit my son.
Tell me.
What are you doing?
It’s hospital.
It’s not a place where
you can make troubles and fight.
Are you the patient’s relative?
I’m his dad.
We will have an operation,
so you need to sign.
Amputation?
What does it mean?
I’m asking you.
What is amputation?
Sir,
please listen to me.
It’s all my fault.
But the consequences
are irrevocable.
Please sign your name first.
One signature for one leg!
Are you willing to do that?
I’ll be responsible for this kid.
You have to sign your name now.
Your kid is waiting
in the operating room.
Without your signature,
the operation can’t be made.
I’ll kill you, you hear me?
I kill you!
I must kill you.
Don’t be impulsive.
Let go of me.
Bro…
Please calm down.
Your kid is in critical condition.
Sign your name first, okay?
Sign your name first.
Save the kid first.
Calm down.
We will take all responsibilities.
Don’t blame yourself too hard.
Sorry.
I will think of ways.
My son is only 9.
From now on,
he is disabled.
I also have a kid.
It’s a girl.
I can understand
your feelings.
Listen up.
All of your family
must be responsible for my son.
Fully.
Or I will kill you and your family.
I know.
From now on,
Jiang Haoyue is also my son.
Miao,
do you remember what I tell you?
I remember.
Call him Haoyue after I go inside.
I can’t make him angry.
Good.
Miao.
Don’t keep looking at his leg.
You know?
So troublesome!
I don’t want to see him.
Do you want to raise chicks?
I do.
Then be good.
Okay.
Miao.
Remember to share it with him.
No problem.
You can’t eat first.
It’s flavor of crispy rice.
Your mouth is watering.
Jiang Haoyue, glad to see you.
My name is Lu Miao.
I’m studying on Grade 2
of Dongnan Elementary School.
I’m eight.
Are you sleepy?
I will finish quickly.
You have a sister now.
That’s me.
My name is Lu Miao.
You can call me Miao.
Haoyue, I give you my chocolate.
Haoyue,
get well soon.
Let’s raise chicks together.
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪