Elizabeth! Hey!
Elizabeth!
Drawn by a landscape as white as snow,
Masshiro na keshiki ni ima sasowarete
I'm headed toward an unseen world.
Boku wa yuku yo mada minu sekai e
I've been traveling while lost
Maigo no mama tabi shiteita
Under this gray sky.
Nezumiiro no sora no shita
Higawari no chizu ikutsumo no yume ga nijindeita
Every day with new maps, stained with my many dreams.
I wonder if someday,
Itsuka wa sa
Even with these tiny steps of mine,
Chippoke na boku no kono hohaba demo
I'll be able to travel beyond those clouds.
Ano kumo no mukou made yukeru kana
I put on a bold front.
Tsuyogatte
End up hurting myself.
Kizutsuita
I feel empty inside.
Kokoro sukashita youni
It's started to rain,
Furidashita
And the raindrops
Amatsubu tachi ga
Began to repeat their scattered reflections.
Ranhansha kurikaesu
These straight rays of light
Massugu na hikari ga
Kousa shite
Start to cross one another.
And without telling anyone where they're headed,
Yakusaki mo tsugenumama
Across the endless distances,
Doko made mo
They pass through all matter.
Tsukinukeru
I burn these faint afterimages onto my eyes.
Awai zanzou ryoume ni yakitsukete
Under this sky,
Kono sora no shita
Wherever I am,
Donna toko ni itemo
I should be able to reach
Todoku hazu nanda
The unseen world.
Mada minu sekai e
I'm not supposed to tell anyone this, but according to Barry,
the Colonel is trying to expose the people in the military involved in that Lab 5 place.
Research Laboratory 5...
Al...
I have to go.
I might find out something about
the person who killed Mr. Hughes.
Hey, hang on! What about the secret to your body?
I'll tell you when I get back.
What's up with that?!
Well, I'm off.
Make sure you come back.
Yes. I promise.
Death of the Undying
Done already?
Can I eat you now?
Shut up, you're in the way!
Lieutenant!
Out of bullets? Out of bullets?
Then it's time for dinner!
Looks like I made it in time.
Colonel...
Why did you come?!
Despite whatever may have happened to us, if you had just ignored it, you could have escaped suspicion!
And yet, you came out here?!
Seriously, are you an idiot?!
Okay, okay. I'm an idiot.
What the hell was that guy...
Colonel! Our target is on the run!
Sergeant, pull out!
Don't leave a trace!
Hayate, you stay with the Sergeant!
Yes, sir!
Colonel.
What is it?
Thank you.
Save it for later. We're in the middle of an operation.
Yes, sir.
Get in!
This has something to do with Mr. Hughes, right?
Do you want to come?
Yes.
Don't lose sight of him!
I won't let him get away!
My soul keeps shaking...
It's telling me where he is!
I wonder if other monsters like that fat one are going to show up?
I don't know. What the hell was that?
I hit his vitals many times,
but it didn't seem to bother him at all.
Did he have a tattoo of Ouroboros?
Tattoo?
Oh, maybe that thing...
He had something on his tongue.
That's probably a homunculus.
That was close, idiot!
Wait, wait, wait! A homunculus?!
There's no way something like that could exist!
I met a homunculus by the name of Greed in the south.
And this is what he said.
"There's no way there's no way."
Homunculi have extraordinary regeneration abilities.
Greed had half of his head blown off, but he fixed himself right away.
But I guess that's hard to believe, huh...
We'll just have to believe you after seeing that thing.
You're not going to tell me he's still alive after being burnt to a crisp and falling from the top of the tower, are you?
Probably.
What is this... a nonsensical mutant all-around freak show?!
My body escaped into here.
Research Laboratory 3, huh?
Now we have a chance to blackmail the upper echelon.
That's sufficient for this operation.
We're withdrawing.
No, it's not!
No! Idiot!
This is bad, Colonel.
No, it's actually convenient.
What?
Outta the way!
I'm not interested in your meat!
Where are you, my meat?!
All personnel are to evacuate immediately!
C-Colonel!
The intruder is a vicious criminal.
Leave his capture to us.
The guards are to seal off all entrances!
Yes, sir!
That damn Barry... which way did he go?
We're splitting up.
Roger.
Looks like it's been quite some time since this place was abandoned.
Could it be... an experiment room?
If that were true, it doesn't seem any pleasant experiments were carried out here.
Oh my, what a coincidence.
I can't believe you stood me up.
You know, I was waiting for you.
I wanted to see you, Jean.
Solaris...
Why are you here?
Hey Havoc, she's got a tattoo of Ouroboros!
I just noticed that, myself!
Sorry for tricking you.
Well, I can see how you were tricked.
You like big breasts, don't you?
Yes! You bet I do!
...I do! ...I do! ...I do!
Did you tell her anything?
I didn't tell her anything related to my work!
Do you know Maes Hughes?
He was a handsome, smart man.
It's a pity I couldn't finish him off-
Get on your knees!
Tell me everything you know.
That's impossible.
You boys can't make me kneel-
As expected from the hero of Ishbal.
You're relentless.
H-Homunculus?!
Oh my, looks like you did your homework, Jean.
As a reward, I'll show you.
Do you see it?
It's a philosopher's stone.
Humans created with this stone as their core...
That's what we, homunculi, are.
You monsters!
How rude.
We have feelings and love for our parents.
We're...
...human.
If you're telling us your huge secret,
you must not be planning on letting us go alive.
Yes, unfortunately for you.
Too slow!
Oh my, you can't even make your fire now.
What do we do now?! At this rate, we'll get tortured to death!
No, it's actually convenient.
If there's a lot of water...
...I just have to decompose it to create hydrogen and oxygen!
Geez, just look at this thing...
I got it from my ex, too...
Damnit!
Colonel, could you give me a light?
I guess it's impossible.
What am I, a wet match?!
That woman definitely burned up.
How can you tell?
By the smell.
I'm used to the smell of burnt corpses.
From Ishbal?
But we can't take her regeneration ability lightly.
Stay alert.
Roger.
Havoc!
Havoc, hang in there!
It's no use.
You can't save him anymore.
No!
It's pointless!
It'll take more than that to kill me!
I can save him with this!
I'm going to use it to treat him.
Medical alchemy isn't my specialty,
but if I boost my ability with this stone...
It's not very gentlemanly of you to suddenly stick your hand into a lady's chest.
F-Führer President!
An intruder?
Yes, sir! The culprit who attacked the western district jail is inside!
Colonel Mustang is after him!
I think I'll lend him a hand.
We'll come with you, too, sir!
No.
I'll be fine on my own.
I thought I told you.
The philosopher's stone is my core.
I'm sorry.
You're a candidate for sacrifice,
but you're going to die here.
You bitch...
Why don't you die as you lay there, watching your man go cold?
Second Lieutenant Havoc...
Answer me... damnit...
I'm not going to allow you to die before me...
Havoc...
You sure took your time, lady.
Just look how rotten my body has become.
It's impossible to place a soul on a body that doesn't belong.
If separate souls and bodies can't be mixed,
then I, who am made of a human soul and an iron body...
That's right, there's no guarantee this body will last to the time we fulfill our goal...
Brother...
There you are, Miss Lust.
Number 66, why did you join forces with the Colonel?
Because it seemed like it'd be fun!
And also...
...I want to cut you up, more than anything!
What a troublesome man.
And the armor boy, too? What are you doing here?
What a loss.
That I have to kill two candidates for sacrifice in one night!
Sacrifice? Two?
Yes. You and someone else.
What are you blabbering on for, Miss Lust?!
I hate persistent guys.
Now, Lieutenant. I'll send you to the place where I sent your superior right away.
Wait...
You said two sacrifices in one night, right...
Don't tell me... you didn't...
Y...You bitch!!!
Finished?
You humans really are foolish, weak, pitiful beings.
Lieutenant, get up and run.
Do you want to die first?
I see... so you opened the gate.
It's a shame.
Forget candidate, you're a confirmed sacrifice.
Alphonse, leave me and run.
No.
Run!
No!
Save yourself, at least!
I said, no!!!
Seeing people die before my eyes...
I hate it! I'm tired of it!
I'm not going to let anyone die anymore! I'll protect you!
Well said, Alphonse Elric!
You finally got down on your knees.
Using flint as the starter, and magnifying it with
a transmutation circle made of your own blood...
How can you even move with that wound?!
I sealed it with fire!
Although I almost fainted a few times.
You said, "It'll take more than that to kill me", right?
Then I'll just keep killing you until you die!
Colonel!
I lost.
It's a shame, but it doesn't feel
too bad to be killed by a man like you.
With honest eyes with no hesitation.
I can't wait...
The days when those eyes will show anguish...
...are... close...
Colonel!
You were all right...
Please worry about yourself!
Alphonse, you have my gratitude for protecting my subordinate.
Forget that! We need a doctor!
That's right... Please... hurry and have a doctor see Havoc...
He'll be all right... he'll be all right...
Hey... I'm back.
Idiot! Welcome back!
W-Well...
U-Umm... Where to start...
Umm...
It broke off!
Oh no! I can't fix this!
Dear me, I barely managed to survive...
...but in a form like this...
I wonder if someone can't fix me up...
Whoa! You were still alive?!
H-Hey... stop! What are you doing?!
I still haven't killed enough!
S... Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! W-Wait!
S-S-S-Stop!
No way...
Impossible...
Hohenheim!
I don't have to act tough, right?
Tsuyogaranakute iindane
The scribbling someone made...
Dareka ga kaitetta
On the wall, of a flower is swaying.
Kabe no rakugaki no hana ga yureru
Jibunrashisa nante dermo wakaranaiyo
No one knows their true selves.
Even though we both lose and gain
Nagai nagai michi no tochuu de
By embarking on this long, long path,
Nakushitari hirottari
And though there may be days loneliness strikes and makes us weep...
Kyuu ni samishikunatte naichau hi mo arukedo
Let's transform our tears and pains to stars.
Namida mo itami mo hoshi ni kaeyou
Let's light a candle to illuminate our tomorrow.
Ashita wo terasu akari wo tomosou
And we'll hold our small hands over the fire to create stardust,
Chiisana te kazashite futari de tsukurou
And an eternity that shines so brilliantly.
Hoshikuzu wo tsuyoku hikaru eien wo
Farewells may be unavoidable,
Sayonara itsuka wa kurukamoshirenai
Yet the seasons continue to change obliviously.
Kisetsu wa soredemo meguri megutteku
Even if I lose myself, I'll continue to walk...
Chiisaku mayottemo aruiteku
Kimi to aruiteku
Walk by your side.
That's the only thing I'd like to never change.
Sore dake wa kawaranaideiyoune
The truth revealed both of his emotions: joy, and unhappiness.
When the boy had to take a stand against the past he threw away,
what he had been hiding behind his resolve was exposed.
Next time, Fullmetal Alchemist:
Father Before the Grave
Episode 20, Father Before the Grave.
It is possible to cry without tears.
If you're a human.