Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
Flourish in Time
Episode 19
Response from God
Jiang Haoyue, leave me alone.
Time to go home.
I don’t want to.
No one is home, anyway.
Have some water to calm down.
You know what?
I was very happy
to tell my mom about my scores.
I thought she’d come back,
but she asked me
which one I would choose.
My dad or her?
I never expected
such kind of irrational event
would happen to me.
Jiang,
tell me a story, OK?
What kind of story?
I want to listen to
a warm
and sweet
fairy story about love.
Once upon a time,
Ms. Rabbit
opened a mushroom shop in a village.
One day,
Mr. Dog who always wandered around
happened to pass by.
Come on.
He was falling in love with
Ms. Rabbit at first sight.
But Mr. Dog
liked entertainment
and had bad reputation.
So, Ms. Rabbit
refused to date with him.
One day,
a local tyrant Wolf
came to Ms. Rabbit’s mushroom shop
and threatened her
to send him mushroom
every day.
For protection.
Or he’d destroy her shop.
Why does your fairy story
have protection fee?
Do you want me to continue?
Yes.
Go ahead.
Continue.
Later…
Bro!
The news
was heard by Mr. Dog.
Gosh!
Mr. Dog came to stop Wolf immediately.
Stop!
Sir, please!
Please don’t!
Smash it!
Freeze!
Stop it.
Ms. Rabbit was sad
and felt sorry.
Step into my business?
No.
Then,
Mr. Dog
bit the Wolf’s neck,
and Wolf fell in blood.
Then, this matter was reported
to the village head,
and Mr. Dog was caught.
How could justice be at disadvantage?
Several years later,
Mr. Dog was released.
He still loved Ms. Rabbit
and proposed to her.
I don’t have any skills
or money.
He told Ms. Rabbit that
he could
give up his life for her.
Ms. Rabbit was moved
and agreed his proposal.
The love story ends here.
What happened next?
You want to know?
Tell me more.
Mr. Dog and Ms. Rabbit
had a baby soon.
It’s Cat.
Rabbit
and Dog.
Why should they have a kid Cat?
I’ll be quiet. You continue.
Continue.
Milk is coming.
Later,
Ms. Rabbit
was always busy doing her business
and looking after their baby.
But Mr. Dog always
sneaked into the mushroom shop
and stole the most expensive mushroom.
Jiang Haoyue.
He always came home drunk.
Smile.
You’re back.
Good. You feed him.
I’ll cook.
Someone is waiting for me.
What?
I can’t do it myself.
Come on.
Stop it!
I told you. I can’t do it myself.
Someone is waiting. I’m going!
Jiang Yi, will you go to drink again?
Ms. Rabbit
and Mr. Dog
argued many times.
But Mr. Dog…
Here, baby.
Has never changed his bad habit.
Mr. Dog could give up his life
for Ms. Rabbit,
but why couldn’t he
change his habit?
Yeah.
Mr. Dog could give up his life
for Ms. Rabbit,
but couldn’t live ordinary life
with her.
You can bet now.
Is this OK?
Yes.
Straight!
This is our bill.
We only have money out,
nothing in.
Have a look.
Jiang Yi, tell me,
will you make a living?
What are you doing?
Beat me? Come on!
You can only do this, right?
You can’t make money.
You can only beat me.
You said it. Right?
- Beat me!
- You asked for it!
I can’t make money?
You can’t!
Ms. Rabbit decided to
leave Mr. Dog finally.
What about their kid Cat?
Ms. Rabbit thought Cat was a trouble,
and
left him behind.
Cat liked to
stay with Mr. Dog.
One day,
Cat went to a hill
and fell in the valley,
breaking one of his legs.
But luckily,
Cat met Chick in the valley.
Chick has round head,
big eyes,
and twitters every day.
She’s very happy every day.
Cat and Chick grow up together.
Chick has worries suddenly.
She begins to worry about
the world outside the valley.
Someday in the future,
Chick will have to leave the valley.
What should she do
to face the strange world outside?
Cat holds Chick’s hands and says,
“Look at me when you’re scared.
I have visited
the outside world for you.”
You’re upset?
No.
Look, give me a smile.
I’ll give you a smile.
Leave me alone.
What happened to you?
My parents may divorce.
Why?
What happened?
I thought it was because of
my bad performance.
But it seems that I was wrong.
I can do nothing to help.
If your parents divorce
and get married with others,
you’ll get four red packets
in the Spring Festival.
So they divorce because
they want to marry others?
No.
I didn’t mean that.
Meng, I spoke out of turn.
Shut up now.
How about this?
This is a supreme comic card.
Swipe it anytime with my name.
Take it as my apology.
Teachers’ Office
Nothing serious.
I just want to know
something about Lu Miao.
What’s wrong with her?
She’s not in good state recently.
She slept in the class.
Now she even doesn’t do homework.
So I want to know
what happened to her.
I know
you’ve been supervising her study.
I hope you can
help her make some adjustments.
If she continues like this,
I will inform her parents.
I see.
Don’t inform her parents.
I’ll speak to her.
This is what I mean.
Uncle Lu.
Jiang,
you’re back so late.
Go back to have rest now.
Uncle Lu,
you didn’t smoke before.
Well,
I smoked occasionally.
Will
Aunt Fang come back?
She will.
Uncle Lu,
are you arguing with Aunt Fang
for me?
Silly boy,
you’re over thinking.
How could it be for you?
Go home and study now.
Come on.
I’ll add some fuel for my car.
30th day of this month,
Blue moon is coming
the second full moon will come.
The one who loves astronomy
may witness the wonder of blue moon.
How to make a webpage?
Look at this place.
I think we should make some adjustment.
But the text is not enough.
Jiang Haoyue,
are you kidnapped?
Look what you are doing now.
“Miracle Comes” Make A Wish
Fantasy girl style.
Isn’t it good?
It took me several hours last night.
For Lu Miao?
She’s upset recently.
I should do something
to cheer her up.
Life is difficult.
Even you begin to do this.
But I don’t think
Lu Miao will like it.
She’s is girlish.
Are you sure she’s girlish,
not boyish?
Jiang,
why are you here?
Don’t you have night classes?
It’s 9:30 PM.
It’s so late.
Are you coming to ask me back?
I don’t want to go home now.
I’ll read some books here with you.
Look at this.
Don’t you want to make a wish?
It must be deceptious.
Don’t you believe it?
But this leaflet is obviously fake.
Look at this edge.
It must be drawn by hand.
“Miracle Comes” Make A Wish
Look at this side.
There’s a website.
Why not log in and have a try?
First step.
Wishing Guide
Register at the website of Good Wishes.
It’s a true website.
Good Wishes
Register and try.
What’s next?
Enter lucky number.
Any number from 1 to 999 is OK.
Register Today
Register continuously
to accumulate luck.
If you’re lucky enough to get a
wishing coin with your lucky number,
come to No. 24, Qinglongwu,
and
your eudemon will come to wishing pool
to realize your dream.
Not 19.
It’s not easy to get it.
I think this webpage is good.
Why don’t you
try again?
Since you said so,
I will try again.
Not again.
Why doesn’t it come out?
She really believes it?
How could you ensure
she’ll get her lucky number?
It’s preset that the entered number
will come out after 50 tries.
50 tries?
How could you ensure
she won’t give up before 50 tries?
She will never give up.
Still trying?
Not again.
1 to 999.
There are a lot of possibilities.
Why not share the website link to me?
Let me give you a hand.
Can it be done this way?
The Wishing Guide
doesn’t specify it.
Forget it.
I should be sincere to make a wish.
I’ll do it myself.
I got it.
Impossible.
You got it?
I got it!
Well...
Is this the wishing pool?
It’s too scaring.
You see it now.
You may leave.
Are you sure?
You have a lot of work to do.
You can’t do it without me.
How did you find
such a shabby place?
I came here when I was a kid.
Hang all the wishing cards on the tree.
Well...
This tree is too big.
Jiang Haoyue,
it must be the first coin you made.
Thank you for your help.
Look,
Lu Miao is a high school student.
Will she believe this?
You have no idea.
She’s curious about everything
that science can’t explain.
For example,
she always bows to Conan
before exam
and draws lots before leaving home.
Or why would I
make such a coin for her?
I never expected materialistic
Jiang Haoyue would do this.
Sometimes, there is only a fine line
between Science and metaphysics.
30th day of this month,
the blue moon will come.
I knew you had something in reserve.
But what if it rains that day?
The blue moon won’t come in rain.
I checked it.
It’ll be sunny that day.
I’ll make her believe again that
miracle will happen.
It looks more like a wishing place.
Let’s go.
You received it?
I want to make a wish, too.
It’s too late.
I accumulate luck every day.
Never mind.
I’ll do it next year.
Don’t bother.
It’s just a coin.
Game coin is the same.
Jiang Haoyue.
Look.
This is my exclusive wishing coin.
I spent many days to get it.
Am I lucky?
I think this wishing coin
is really special.
Really?
You have good taste.
Let’s go. Time for class.
I’m leaving now.
Dad,
what’s wrong?
I got burned.
These days,
I felt more about how hard
your mom worked before.
She had to make money
and look after both of us.
I miss
the braised pork chops my mom cooked.
Hello, are you Lu Yongfei?
Do you know Jiang Yi?
Yes.
What’s the matter?
He’s in our police station now.
What?
Come here now.
I’ll be there soon.
Have a drink?
With you?
Don’t you like betting?
Dare you bet with me?
For what?
If I drink more than you,
you quit betting.
Lu Yongfei,
I never lose to anyone in drinking.
Let’s go!
Drink!
Jiang Haoyue?
Are you going to make a wish?
Yes.
Looks like it’ll rain.
Why don’t you
quit?
No.
The leaflet says
that it’s a good day
to make wishes tonight.
She’s happy now.
I’d better not let her down.
I’ll go with you.
Don’t bother.
If it does rain,
it’ll be troublesome.
Let’s go.
Are you very curious?
Can you drink more?
Here,
cheers!
Cheers!
What do you mean?
You can’t drink?
You lose, right?
From now on,
can you stop coming to me for help?
I beg you!
Who can I come to?
I have no money.
Should I come to Jiang Haoyue?
Look,
you’re a good guy.
But
you hit my son.
You owe us
for all your life.
I admit
that I owe you,
but why should my wife and daughter
suffer with me?
Why?
I owe Jiang Haoyue.
I owe my wife.
I owe Miao.
But I
never owe you,
Jiang Yi!
You hear that?
I never owe you!
But you met me.
You deserve it!
Jiang Yi!
What?
Why not behave yourself?
Spicy Hot Pot
It’s cold today.
Let’s go back soon.
I’m afraid you may get sick.
I’m fine.
This is Qinglongwu.
It’s shabby here.
And it’s cold.
Why not make your wish the other day?
Maybe this eudemon
is so unusual.
Look, there is no one else.
It’s impossible to realize your wish.
Why not come the other day?
The fewer people, the better.
Then I’ll be an exclusive VIP
for this eudemon tonight.
I’ll make my wish now.
I wish...
Bad luck!
What are you doing?
I’ll go find it.
It’s too cold to stay in water.
It’s fine. I saw it falling in water.
I’ll surely find it.
No.
What if you get ill?
I won’t.
Don’t worry.
How could it be?
I’ll be anxious if you get ill.
You know?
It’s fine. I won’t get ill.
And there will be a blue moon tonight.
I will find my coin to make a wish.
It’s fake.
There is no eudemon,
no miracle.
No one believes this wishing pool now.
You believe it.
I know you believe.
When we were kids,
I saw you come here.
This is the only place you made a wish.
The wish I made then
hasn’t come true till now.
Do you give up?
I won’t give up.
Although I don’t know
what your wish was,
I believe it can come true one day.
So the wish I’ll make
will come true, too.
Jiang Haoyue, why are you here?
I’ll help you.
No. Jiang Haoyue, leave here.
Let’s find it now.
No. Leave here now.
I’ll leave after we find it.
I don’t want it. Let’s go now.
Didn’t you say
you wouldn’t give up?
But
your leg...
It’s fine.
Let’s go.
I mean it.
I’m fine.
♪I want to accompany you♪
♪I want to be your castle♪
♪I’m murmuring under the starry sky♪
♪I won’t regret at any time♪
♪With you Even hurt♪
♪Doesn’t matter♪
♪Listen to me♪
♪Don’t fear darkness♪
♪I want to fly with you♪
♪But I’m afraid I can’t♪
♪I can’t give you that feeling♪
♪So I let you fly♪
♪I’ll stay there♪
What’s your wish?
I wish...
My parents can stay together forever.
Never depart.
♪Don’t worry I will keep our♪
♪Initial beautiful time♪
Make your wish now.
You find it.
♪With smile♪
♪Make you perfect♪
♪I want to fly with you♪
♪But I’m afraid I can’t♪
♪I can’t give you that feeling♪
♪So I let you fly♪
♪I’ll stay there♪
I hope
our voice
can be heard this time.
It must be heard.
Because
the miracle comes.
♪I want to fly with you♪
♪Forget beauty will go easily♪
♪I want to accompany you♪
♪I will let you fly♪
♪I’ll stay there♪
♪I want to do it for you♪
Mom,
does grandpa
feel better now?
Yes.
In a few days,
I’ll take grandpa
to a hospital near our home.
You mean you’re back?
Great!
Mom, look outside now.
Tonight,
the moon is blue.
It seems that my dad is back.
I’ll tell him this.
Dad.
My mom said she’d be back soon.
Great!
What’s wrong, Dad?
I’m fine.
Let me see.
How did you get hurt?
It’s slippery outside.
I fell down. It doesn’t matter.
Come on.
Sit on the sofa.
I’ll deal with it for you. Come.
How could you get hurt?
Is it hurt?
No.
Miao,
I want to tell you the truth.
What’s it?
Your mom
is angry
not because of money,
or your performance at school.
It’s all my fault.
I am too selfish.
Your mom is right.
I am not a real good man.
These years,
I wanted to be responsible for Jiang,
but I
ignored you and your mom’s feelings.
Sorry.
Dad,
Jiang Haoyue is our family too.
I support you
on this.
Miao.
My mom will understand you
like me.
She loves us so much.
She won’t leave this home,
am I right?
You fought again?
Lu Yongfei was
upset at home.
He vented anger on me.
Luckily, I’m strong enough
to beat him.
You beat Uncle Lu?
Why?
I am your dad, not him.
Just because of money.
Bail Bill
Lin Wenfang’s reluctant to pay for you.
She’s angry and gone.
Lu Yongfei
is crazy.
The artificial leg was paid by Uncle Lu.
So Aunt Fang and Uncle Lu argued
because of you.
Why are you mad at me?
They hit your leg.
They should pay for it.
Do you remember what my mom said?
She said,
you
are a bastard!
I won’t let you hurt them again.
Behave yourself.
Mom,
I decide to come to you.
Finally you think it through.
I want to go there soon.
OK. I’ll hand the formalities.
I’m so glad that
we can reunite soon.
When you come abroad,
we can get rid of Jiang Yi completely.
I wish my mom can come to see me soon.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪