Sub by KISSKH & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
Flourish in Time
Episode 21
The End of Universe Is Chocolate
Hey, where’s Lu Miao?
Meng is now a loner.
She doesn’t speak,
doesn’t go to the milk tea store
and the book store.
Looks like Miao’s changed.
She’s really in a hard time.
Her grandpa’s sick,
her parents are divorcing
and Jiang Haoyue is leaving.
She must be heartbroken.
Is Jiang Haoyue so important to her?
You’ve gone through plenty.
Jiang Haoyue is very important to her,
don’t you know?
So we’ve got to do something.
Yeah, we can’t just watch.
We’ve got to do something.
Can you prevent her parents
from divorcing?
Prevent her grandpa from being sick?
And prevent Jiang Haoyue from leaving?
What’re you thinking about?
Preventing Jiang Haoyue from leaving.
Don’t do anything stupid.
Well, Che,
calm down.
I’ve decided.
I’d do anything for Meng.
What’s it?
Why are you leaving?
Why?
You want me to stay?
I want you to leave,
as far as you could.
But Lu Miao wants you to stay.
Have you thought of her?
She cares about you,
and you’re leaving at this moment.
I wish her to live well.
So stay if you do!
Can’t believe what you are thinking.
A studious idiot, hah?
I leave so she could live well.
The second role in a soap opera, hah?
What are my lines?
Lu Miao is mine
and I’ll take good care of her.
Dose Lu Miao adore me?
Morocco
Che, why do you make
so many paper planes?
Confession.
What?
Again?
Not again.
It never worked.
Is it where you fell down
where you lie down?
It’s different.
Yeah, it is. You got me in.
And the result will be the same.
The result
doesn’t matter.
What do you mean?
Jiang Haoyue is going abroad.
And you’ll have an opportunity?
I have a plan.
Jiang Haoyue is leaving
and I’m happy.
But I want Meng to be happy, too.
So I’ll make him stay for her.
I appreciate your attempt.
But do you believe Jiang Haoyue
will stay because of
your confession?
If I were him, I would.
If I were a girl I’d make you my man.
I’d not make you mine.
Miao, is that bad?
Tell me, what’s the matter?
I planned to say goodbye
to Jiang Haoyue,
but I cowered before him.
It looked like
I was not ready to say goodbye.
Growing up is a course
of losing and saying goodbye.
When I was your age,
I was not as brave as you are.
So how did you
become braver and braver?
Am I brave?
To me,
you’re the bravest man in the world.
My bravery is in my trunk.
Miao, take the pump, please.
Look what I’ve got.
What is that?
Miao, this is a water rocket.
Where did you buy it?
Buy?
When I was young,
we couldn’t afford toys.
We made our toys. Awesome?
Come, Miao,
put water in it.
When I was unhappy as a kid,
I’d come to the sea
with the water rocket,
whoosh, I fired it away.
All the unhappiness was gone to the sky.
Now write your unhappiness
on the water rocket.
Jiang Haoyue, goodbye
Dad, your turn.
It’s my turn.
Fang comes home
Done.
Let’s blow it up.
Come, Miao,
hold my arm.
Let us
fire our unhappiness to the sky.
One, two, three.
Dad, you’ve got water on your face.
Go, go, go.
She’s coming.
Ready?
Three, two, one.
Look up there!
Planes! Many of them!
Lu Miao,
do you know how many
countries there are in this world?
One hundred and ninety-five.
I don’t know how to make you happy.
I’ve made you flights
to every one of them.
Don’t be afraid to start.
I promise,
wherever the destination is,
it’ll be the most beautiful trip.
I’m going to Morocco!
I’m going to France!
I’m going to Mauritius!
This is not an unrealistic dream.
This is our future.
Lu Miao,
I adore…
What did you say?
I didn’t hear it!
Wait up there!
I’m going to you.
No way!
Again?
Out of power?
I must do the confession!
Switzerland
Go, Go, back to class.
Che,
what are you doing?
Lu Miao, I adore you.
I’m not
the victim of your prank.
Come on, let’s go.
I adore you.
Do you adore me?
Sorry,
I adore someone else.
I’m sorry.
Got you there, victim.
Wish you’ve seen your face,
yeah.
Sorry,
I adore someone else.
Is that funny?
No…
Dare you do it again?
Shi Che, stop!
Stop!
What do you mean?
What do you mean!
Packing up?
In your dreams.
You’ll not take
anything from the house.
Wow, that’s good!
Time Book
Are you sure that was a prank?
A prank has a reason.
But a guy like Che,
I’m not sure.
I’d tell you the truth.
He always adores you.
He adores you
and envies Jiang Haoyue.
The confession at the school games,
he wrote it to you.
It can’t be!
I know it, and Guoguo does, too.
He doesn’t allow us to tell you.
He hopes you will
feel his heart.
I just tugged his armpit.
So,
any idea about
how to get along with him?
He said it was a prank
and you believe it was a prank?
If the one I adore doesn’t adore me,
pretending nothing happened,
and making fun of me every day,
it’s killing me.
I’d better avoid him.
Qu Wei got a full mark.
Did you confess to him?
Confess?
Didn’t you promise that
you’ll confess to him
if he gets a full mark?
Checking the assessment result.
Yeah.
I was busy with the exams.
I’ll check it later.
I envy you.
I wish I could
control my mood
Switzerland
like doing math.
Wake up, Xie Ziye,
you’re dating a full-mark guy.
Ziye.
Wei.
You want a talk with me?
For me?
Emm.
Thank you.
This is a confession gift.
Confession?
Too sudden.
Not at all.
Since grade one,
I’ve been assessing every boy
I meet.
Wei, you top my list.
You fit my criteria best.
Jiang Haoyue 96 Qu Wei 100
Didn’t expect I win over Jiang Haoyue
in your system.
Wei,
is my confession accepted?
Sorry, it’s not.
Why?
Wei, doesn’t the system
prove
I fit your criteria best?
But I didn’t feel
you adore me.
Well, Wei,
you’re good at chemistry
and you should know
adoring is a reaction of substances.
At first-sight or coming in time,
as long as your brain
produces enough phenethylamine,
you’ll feel you adore someone.
Love is indeed chemistry,
but in the right sequence.
You meet someone you adore first,
then you produce phenethylamine.
Phenethylamine doesn’t decide
who you’ll adore.
Ziye, don’t despair.
Use your heart to feel the chemistry.
Thank you.
Sub by KISSKH & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Is the noodle
for me?
Emm.
Do you not want to go?
If you don’t, stay. Tell me.
Tell me.
I’ll talk with Chen Lu.
Air ticket booked
Don’t bother.
Take care of your own business.
Export completed
I wish her to live well.
So stay if you do!
Can’t believe what you are thinking.
I leave so she could live well.
Dose Lu Miao adore me?
Lu Miao is mine
and I’ll take good care of her.
Are you sleeping here?
Leave me alone.
My heart’s broken.
Fix it then.
You’ve helped me, anyway.
Shouldn’t you
say something to comfort me?
I said you have no hope,
and you…
Are you crying again?
I knew it from the beginning.
But it still hurts.
I got it.
I know something
that can heal your sadness.
What’s it?
I’m afraid you dare not to try.
Hey,
Shi Che
dares to do anything in this world.
Are you afraid?
Hey,
Shi Che is not afraid.
It’s fine. It’s about the fifth floor.
Fifth floor? Let me go!
Too late.
♪Laugh together♪
Let me go!
♪To make the starry sky a riddle♪
Come on!
This is not horrible.
I quit!
Are you still a man?
♪We run into the young secret♪
♪Like the asteroid♪
♪Travelling along its orbit♪
♪Without an end♪
♪The young riddle remains unknown♪
♪Needs an answer♪
♪The childish question always asked♪
♪Needs a key♪
Come on!
Flying High Entrance
Open your arms,
and you’ll feel you’re flying.
♪I adore you that adore me♪
♪And keep it untold♪
Do you feel like flying?
Do you feel like flying? Not afraid?
♪I adore you that adore me♪
♪It’s a secret♪
♪All I need is to look at you♪
♪And you’ll know♪
Feeling better?
Thank you, I can’t feel my legs.
Where’s your assessment note?
Write it down.
Courageous,
self-challenging,
fearless,
they make at least ten points.
I don’t.
Because
I’ve identified my No. 1.
I confessed to him,
but was declined.
Why?
He said
fit doesn’t mean adoring.
Adoring
is from the bottom of your heart.
Another loser.
Now we’re the Losers’ Alliance.
Are we?
It’s fine.
You did nothing wrong.
Adoring is sort of
a lucky draw.
Sometime
you meet someone similar to you.
But most of us are unlucky.
But someday you’ll
meet someone who truly adores you.
When that day comes,
you’ll be truly happy
for meeting the one.
You will.
I’m truly happy today.
I was a bit scared,
but I’m very happy.
After you.
It’s so nice of you, Meng.
No…
Still mad at my prank?
I admit.
You take me as a brother
but I tried to woo you.
It was definitely my bad.
But you have a generous heart.
And I’ve decided not to adore you.
Let’s turn to a new page.
It’s a lifelong brotherhood.
A lifelong brotherhood?
Or, sisterhood?
Great, a lifelong brotherhood.
Take anything you want. It’s on me.
Come on.
Okay.
Thanks, Meng, for the treat.
It’s fine. I hit you.
This is for your armpit.
It didn’t hurt.
Excuse me.
Jiang Haoyue, we need a talk.
I yelled at you.
I failed to control my emotion.
I’m sorry.
I’m the one who should say sorry.
I shouldn’t leave you at this moment.
Nonsense.
You have a future.
You wanna go somewhere far and better.
It’s natural.
I’m your childhood friend
and I should support you.
I made this with my own hands.
You must wear it. An amulet.
That was all I wanted to say.
Goodbye.
Take You To The End Of The World
My life would be like this,
going to school alone.
It’s not bad, anyway.
Nobody tells me not
to eat too many snacks.
I’ll eat as much as I could.
Nobody pushes me to do my homework.
Freedom!
I’ll not be afraid of
failing exams and disgracing him.
I’ll be happier than I was.
Cheers!
Is this Jiang Haoyue’s laptop?
Checking it out
is not infringement of privacy.
And I don’t really want to.
To Congcong’s mother
Theme: Farewell
Jiang Haoyue was sending it to me?
I thought we’d lead
the college of science,
but you’ve changed the track.
I’d be bored if you go.
You’ll get used to it in 21 days.
That’s coldblooded.
Did Lu Miao hear the same thing?
She was quiet, and she understands.
That’s fine.
Or you’ll feel guilty.
I shouldn’t leave you at this moment.
You have a future.
You wanna go somewhere far and better.
It’s natural.
I’m your childhood friend
and I should support you.
I made this with my own hands.
You must wear it.
An amulet.
I’m starting to regret.
Where are you going?
Dike!
It’s April 18, 2018,
eight years since
we first met.
When we were little,
I actually hated
you stuck to me every day.
Jiang Haoyue, nice to meet you.
I’m Lu Miao.
You may call me Miao.
Now you have a sister.
She’s me.
Jiang Haoyue, don’t go.
Jiang Haoyue.
You’re now Terminator No. 2.
And I’m No. 1.
You’re terminated by me.
I don’t know when it started.
I got used to it
that you waited for me in the games.
Because of you, my childhood
had colors.
Jiang Haoyue, come out!
Come out, or I’ll be sitting here!
Don’t cry. It’s noisy.
For me?
You said I’m brave.
I’m brave because of you.
He’s my brother!
Nobody touches him!
I count to three
and you’ll catch me.
One.
You’re brave,
and you made me brave.
Go! Go! Go!
You let me know,
though I’m physically disabled,
I have my values.
Happy birthday to you.
Did we notice that
we both grew up?
I thought
I’d always be your brother,
your neighbor, and your friend.
We’d go to school together,
and have fun together.
You have big eyes.
Take this with you.
It brings you good luck.
But I didn’t know
something I took for granted
now
♪And what I think is the best♪
are going away.
♪From youth to the end of life♪
I’m leaving next month.
Sorry, I can’t be with you.
The elders say
the end of the world is the sea.
So, I want to give you the best sea,
the best sunset.
For you.
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
Without you,
it makes no sense.
Jiang Haoyue!
I will not forgive you!
Will you not go?
Don’t go!
Jiang Haoyue, don’t go!
Will you not go?
I won’t.
I will stay.
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
Sub by KISSKH & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
What do you want?
Brat.
Are you calling your mom again?
I’ll call my mom. Is it not right?
She abandoned you, got it?
I’ve told you thousands of times.
She didn’t abandon me.
You kicked her out.
What did you say?
Answer me! What did you say?
You don’t belong here.
- What did you say?
- Jiang Haoyue, Jiang Haoyue,
what did you say?
I got chocolate for you.
Nobody touches Jiang Haoyue.
Get off me!
I blow it and it won’t hurt.
It doesn’t hurt actually.
Why did you come to me?
Mom bought me chocolates.
New flavors.
I have some for you.
Yummy, isn’t it?
Too sweet.
Sweet makes you happy.
Look at me. I’m happy.
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪