CLASS A VS CLASS B
Class 1-A and Class 1-B of U.A. High
are having a joint training.
After the third battle, each class
has won one battle so far.
And now, the fourth battle will begin.
What? What is going on? For real?
You can't be serious with this.
That's it.
I'll show you what I've got, stupid Deku!
♪When we are stranded on the same spot,
make our heart beat♪
MY HERO ACADEMIA
♪Rather than searching for an answer
in this world full of uncertainties♪
♪I want to live even though my constant
doubts are a waste of time♪
♪Take off the unseeable armor and feel the wind♪
♪I make my effort sound worthless
as a way to hide myself♪
♪The No.1 who came out of nowhere
is pointing at the endless sky♪
♪It's our desire to see the view
from greater height and distance♪
♪Ignite the heart of unquenchable desire♪
♪Ignite the path to our future,
burn the illusions to ashes♪
With Jiro and Sero on this battleground...
I have bad feeling about this.
They are both very tough opponents.
Not to mention Bakugo and
Sato are both powerful as well.
Their team balance is impeccable.
It's best to assume they could wipe us out
if they have the upper hand.
Whatever it is,
we should chop them up now!
Let's strike them them with a preemptive attack!
EARLY BIRD!
Class A and Class B has each won one battle.
Do you think their strength is equal?
But Class A only won thanks to Shinso!
"VLAD KING, QUIRK: BLOOD CONTROL"
Well,
is their strength really on the same level?
King Vlad, that's too much!
"MIDNIGHT. QUIRK: SOMNAMBULIST"
He can control blood, but not his brain.
"ALL MIGHT, QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL"
He loves his student a little too much.
"SHOTA AIZAWA, QUIRK: ERASURE"
Are you done over there?
Sir, we are simply against this bias broadcast!
Are you going to protest if you lost a battle?
Class B's tactic is much more formidable
than you think.
That is a fact.
It seems like Vlad is the better teacher.
In the end, you're just troublemakers!
Don't you see that?
Only failures will cause trouble to themselves!
NEITO MONOMA, QUIRK: COPY
Class B has been training day and night
to improve their skills and Quirks.
But Class A should be capable of more than that.
All Might, you're still very fond of Class A.
I like all the students.
I look forward to your performance.
Young Bakugo...
Move faster, slowpokes!
I have to listen to their movement!
Stop nagging, just catch up!
"RIKIDO SATO, QUIRK: SUGAR RUSH"
He always wants us to catch up.
"HANTA SERO, QUIRK: TAPE"
He hasn't changed since the sports day.
"KYOKA JIRO, QUIRK: EARPHONE JACK"
In any case, he always helps out.
However...
Listen up, you second-rated jerks.
Just follow my lead.
Don't call us jerks.
And stop saying we are second-rated.
I'll take the lead into the battle.
"KATSUKI BAKUGO, QUIRK: EXPLOSION"
Your job is to provide me support.
Ears, check for any sound of their movement.
Find out where they are.
Stop calling me names. My name is Jiro!
Bakugo, are you going to attack them head-on?
Their team is mostly people
who can take counter our attacks.
Since we have Jiro with us,
we can look for an opening
and proceed with cautions.
Fools.
That is exactly why we should strike first.
We don't look for an opening.
We create it ourselves.
As long as we can track them down, we can win.
Do you get it now?
Be careful!
This is dangerous!
Hold onto those.
These aren't very powerful,
but they will come in handy.
And there's more.
Is he certain
this is the right tactic?
I spot someone!
Ear!
It's Jiro!
They are all in the area.
Find them!
Hurry up!
Be patient!
We fell for their trap!
Indeed. It's over for you.
We used Jiro's scouting ability
to our advantage.
Class B, Setsuna Tokage.
Hero name: Lizardy.
Quirk: Lizard Tail Splitter.
She can divide herself into parts
and control them at will.
After further improving her Quirks,
she can control up to 50 different parts!
Get out of my way!
Bakugo, over here!
All right, it's game over!
Glue Squall!
It's glue!
This is bad, we walked right into it.
It's like he created a web
to capture even himself!
I did it. It's just as Setsuna planned.
Class B, Kojiro Bondo.
Hero name: Plamo.
Quirk: Cemedine.
He can spray a large amount of glue
and adjust the rate at which it dries.
You are too slow!
Class B, Togaru Kamakiri.
Hero name, Jack Mantis.
Quirk: Razor Sharp.
He can produce large blades
from any part of his body.
We disrupted Jiro's hearing by making noises.
The pipelines and tapes are covered in adhesive.
There is no way to escape if they touch it.
I must protect them!
Bakugo!
The perfect timing!
I'll finish off Jiro first!
He saved his team and won the fight.
Win and save them all.
I'm much stronger than I used to be!
Don't forget,
when you're in danger, I will aid you.
You managed to withstand that.
You sure are fast as a bug!
For real?
Thanks!
Shut it!
They got away. Search for them.
I don't care if this is training or what.
I'd made up my mind long ago.
I must win every battle with undeniable victory!
I won't let them capture anyone!
That is...
the real victory for a true fighter!
This is strange.
Am I seeing things now?
I think he was protecting Jiro.
He did. But he also kicked her.
Bakugo is always so unpredictable.
Monoma, don't worry.
Your eyes are perfectly fine.
He changed his fighting style!
Yeah...
This is the first time I've seen him
standing out to protect others.
I shouldn't fight him head-on. Retreat.
If we get into a real fight,
there is no way we can win.
As soon as the capture operation failed,
we must retreat.
We must keep ambushing them
to maintain our advantage.
There are too much noises.
But the number has dwindled.
The number has dwindled?
They are falling back.
Are they regrouping?
Jerks, they are looking down on us.
They are a one-man team that follows
Bakugo's lead in any strategy.
We can keep baiting Bakugo
by giving him more pressure.
When he makes a mistake,
the team will crumble!
I can't locate them.
However,
I can recognize the sound if I concentrate!
Let's go!
They went into hiding!
They are using their Quirks again!
Construction-Done-Kwik,
Weldcraft!
Complete!
Class B, Yosetsu Awase.
Hero name: Welder.
Quirk: Weld.
He can fuse different objects
at a molecular level.
But he can't activate his ability
unless he touches the objects.
Impressive precision!
There is no way your tape can hit me
in this environment.
Is this part of Tokage's plan?
She foresees everything.
Sugar Rush!
Go!
Curse you! Don't you dare stick me to the pipes!
Do you have to be so upset?
I'm counting on you!
Leave it
to me!
When you're in danger, I will aid you.
On the other hand,
when I'm in trouble...
Heartbeat Surround!
I'll count on you guys to help me out.
Awase!
He's headed for Bondo!
This can't be happening!
I'm feeling great in this winter day!
Do you feel warm now?
I got him!
Their coordination is flawless!
They captured two of my lovely students
in a blink of an eye!
I thought he knew nothing about teamwork...
He didn't just gain a nicer personality...
Bakugo!
Bakugo is decisive.
The others assist his attack.
There will be some gaps in between.
We can make use of those gaps
and crush them from within!
That should do it!
Explode-A-Pult!
How? Their teamwork is perfect!
OCHACCO URARAKA, QUIRK: ZERO GRAVITY
Bakugo let them attack freely
because he trusts his teammates!
Their coordination worked.
His drumming practice was useful after all.
Tokage can split her body into 50 parts
and control them freely.
But the separated parts will stop moving
after a certain time.
Then the parts will regenerate from
her main body.
If that assumption is correct,
there must be a limit to how much
she can regenerate.
Just as Yaoyorozu,
she will be worn out
and her level of concentration will drop.
If she split her body into parts to make noises,
that would work against her regeneration.
Which means these parts will return to her body
to reform and reset.
Jiro mentioned there were less sounds,
that proves my hypothesis!
That was close.
You...
How much have you changed?
I've always been the same.
Whenever it is, my goal...
is to become the No.1 Hero
that surpasses All Might!
What...
WELCOME
In less than five minutes,
Class A's flawless teamwork
won the battle without losing any teammate!
KATSUKI BAKUGO, QUIRK: EXPLOSION
HIS SWEAT CAN CAUSE EXPLOSION LIKE NITROGLYCERIN
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH CLASS 1-A
BIRTHDAY: APRIL 20, HEIGHT 172CM
BLOOD TYPE: A
FAVORITE FOOD: SPICY FOOD
KYOKA JIRO, QUIRK: EARPHONE JACK
THE EXTENSION JACK FROM HER EARS
CAN CAUSE SONIC BOOM INSIDE HER ENEMY
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH SCHOOL CLASS 1-A
BIRTHDAY: AUGUST 1, HEIGHT: 154 CM
BLOOD TYPE: A
FAVORITE: ROCK MUSIC
There was no unnecessary casualty.
The capturing operation was swift and smooth.
Bakugo acted as the main attacker
with his mobility and firepower.
The other three coordinated well.
You came up with a tactic based on past data
while considering the difference in power.
But you didn't adapt to the situation.
You lack Honezuki's flexibility.
We failed miserably because of my mistake.
Never mind, let's take as a learning experience.
That impulsive guy won't go for an ambush
when he calms down.
You got that right.
That was surprising for sure.
Kacchan, there is nothing you can't do!
Jiro stole the spotlight as well!
I'm a hero, OK?
You look like a stray kitty
taken in by a delinquent.
I'm a human being, all right?
I was shivering.
Did you catch a cold or something?
Kacchan!
Stand aside, junk!
But I'm not even in your way...
IZUKU MIDORIYA, QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL
I've moved forward even more.
Indeed. You were amazing.
I'll become stronger at a pace
you can't catch up.
I will surpass you.
Shut it! Was that supposed to be a threat?
There is no way I would let you surpass me!
You useless trash!
We'll see about that.
You have a great childhood friend.
Jerk!
I wish his attitude could be better.
HITOSHI SHINSO, QUIRK: BRAINWASH
That hysteric explosion guy...
This is going to be fun.
Sorry, Monoma.
One win, two defeats, and one draw.
There is no way we can win this.
Your apology is not needed, Tokage.
Your teammates will learn from their mistakes.
Isn't that a great experience?
It's true Class B can't win,
but we haven't lost yet.
But I want all of you to understand one thing.
The people who get serious
and don't become a liability,
the attention seeker who
resort to unpleasant means,
who is on the correct path?
We are all supporting characters
of others' lives.
But we are the protagonists of our own lives!
"REIKO YANAGI, QUIRK: POLTERGEIST"
What do we do then?
Don't get so discouraged!
"NIRENGEKI SHODA, QUIRK: TWIN IMPACT"
I think it's best to follow
Tokage's tactic.
In terms of team balance,
both teams have almost the same composition.
Most of us have technical Quirks.
There are various ways to launch an ambush.
Most importantly, we have five combatants
on our team.
Head-on battles won't do us any good.
After watching the last battle,
I feel great resentment towards Midoriya.
Resentment?
That's her way of saying "scary".
Midoriya...
His mobility and power is on par with Bakugo's,
if not better.
He even learned ranged attacks recently.
If we make the slightest mistake,
we'll be decimated as the last team.
Midoriya will break through our defense.
Then let's make Midoriya our priority.
We must take him down first.
But he is capable of breaking my Brainwash.
However,
with Monoma's Quirk,
there might be a way to subdue Midoriya.
I feel a little daunted with the high hopes.
"YUI KODAI, QUIRK: SIZE"
After all, there is a chance it might fail.
It might fail?
That means he can't copy his opponent's Quirk.
I see...
Well, we must stop him if we want to win.
We're counting on you, Shinso.
The fifth battle is the last round.
How will Shinso perform?
The battle is a test to see if he is qualified
to transfer into the Hero Course.
He put up a great performance
in the first battle.
But the same trick might not work twice.
That's true enough.
Class A is very strong too.
I wish him all the best.
We should first deal with Shinso.
"MINORU MINETA, QUIRK: POP OFF"
I'm worried.
I don't want to get brainwashed.
"MINA ASHIDO, QUIRK: ACID"
Don't dwell on that.
They are capable of many ways
to ambush us without even showing themselves.
And our Quirks...
I can float.
I can melt!
I can stick!
This is not looking good.
I have a bad feeling about this.
We can't go on defensive nor offensive.
Very well!
We should use my Gloves that Pluck!
No one would fall for that.
We must find them and
let them fall into our trap.
I will act as the decoy.
Deku...
But how?
You mentioned your Quirk was acting weird.
I'll be fine.
But after watching the fourth battle,
my guess is they will be wary of me.
I must be even more mobile.
Are you sure about this?
We are counting on you to win.
Don't worry.
We will win!
The old you would have panicked instead.
Everything feels normal.
I've moved forward even more.
I'll become stronger at a pace
you can't catch up.
He left me with a challenge.
I mustn't let everyone down!
5TH BATTLE
All right! It's the fifth battle!
This is the last round.
Are you ready?
Never let your guard down! All the best!
Start!
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪I hope my destination♪
♪Is where we shall meet again♪
♪I'm always seeing the world through your eyes♪
♪Tears are somehow falling down my cheeks♪
♪I hate it when you say it's all right♪
♪Your gentle whisper turned
into an unsettling silence♪
♪I want to believe the clouded sky before us♪
♪Our longing is the very thing that breaks us♪
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪But why? I'm already covered in wounds♪
♪Why must I search for the answer♪
♪Goodbye, we will meet again♪
♪I hope you would still be the same♪
♪I hope that the memories we share♪
♪Would once again bank up♪
♪So I could see you again♪
Next episode.
It's the final battle of the joint training.
Class A will only need a
draw to secure the victory.
But we mustn't be complacent.
Class B has Shinso on their team.
There is also Monoma who can copy our Quirks.
I'm the key to win this battle.
That's why I must strike!
Next episode, "That Which Is Inherited".
An anomaly manifests inside of me
during the battle.
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!