Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪At the young age♪
♪I turn and meet him♪
♪Go into his heart immediately♪
♪And have a crush♪
♪Dreams up in the sky♪
♪Are piled up♪
♪Whoever has dream will realize it♪
♪As long as he tries hard♪
♪Make the paper plane♪
♪And give it to her♪
♪The secret in your heart♪
♪Make fun of it♪
♪Moonlight shines through fireworks♪
♪Over the bikes♪
♪What you said on the rooftop♪
♪You always remember don’t you♪
♪Na Na Na Na Na Na♪
♪Turn the clock back♪
♪Review the long-lost past♪
♪Do the best you can do♪
♪Be the best you can be♪
♪In your youth♪
♪Be the most beautiful memories♪
♪The point of growth is♪
♪We staying together♪
Flourish in Time
Episode 23
Gaokao Is Important!
100 days countdown to Gaokao
Everyone.
Only 100 days left!
You have to shoot ahead immediately.
Time is score!
He starts preaching again.
He never stops.
I hope you study harder!
OK.
Let’s begin our class.
I think I should learn more from Ziye.
- Count me in.
- Take out your paper answered yesterday.
So active?
I feel something strange.
I will become a basketball talent
in the future.
I should study hard.
You should understand
the main parts of the question,
then you’ll know how to answer it.
Many students gave wrong answers,
because of the misunderstanding.
Given A1 B1
is perpendicular to the plane BCDE,
and plane A1 B1
intersects plane BCDE at B1.
From question 1,
A1O is perpendicular to the plane BCDE.
Got it?
But, why?
Did you look into her eyes?
Yes!
Who looked away first?
You
like that girl.
But,
why A1O is perpendicular to BE,
and A1O is perpendicular
to the plane BCDE,
Ziye?
What are you thinking?
I got it.
I’ll tell you.
Listen to me.
Target score: 580
The Sui Dynasty was unified in
985,
no,
6,
7,
8.
It’s 589.
Keep it in mind.
I envy you so much.
How I hope I can remember everything
at a glance like you.
Did you recite these knowledge
by rote learning?
Didn’t you have other methods?
The essence of liberal arts
lies in rote learning, doesn’t it?
But I know you can remember
every comic at a glance.
How could you compare this to comics?
It’s boring,
but comics are interesting.
My comics!
When can I see you again?!
Ziye,
Miao!
Rule 8 of Love,
seating rule,
if a boy likes you,
he’ll choose the seat next to you.
Miao is really an
emotionless machine for doing exercises.
Thank you for praising.
What exercise are you doing?
Rule 9 of Love,
drinks rule,
if he drinks the beverage you drank,
it must because he likes you.
Gosh!
Does this guy like me?
It tastes good.
Where did you buy it?
I’m going to the tutoring class.
I have to go now.
Let me give you a ride.
Don’t bother.
I can...
Go away!
I’m leaving.
What’s wrong with Ziye?
Why is she in such a hurry?
Che,
you’re in luck.
Buy some lotteries?
Is it good?
The left is higher.
God rewards the diligent
Turn around.
This is the left.
Yes, it is.
It’s my fault.
See, I knew it.
Is it right now?
Is it good?
It’s useless!
God rewards the diligent.
Is it useful?
It’s blessed by a master, you know?
It’s blessed?
The key to Gaokao is
time,
place
and people.
Sorry, master.
I was wrong.
Sorry.
Let’s take some practical actions.
What about
taking Miao out to get some fresh air?
Where to go?
Beijing.
To visit Jiang.
It’s too far.
She may be distracted.
Look, listen to me.
what’s in my mind is,
we didn’t take Miao out
these years
and they two grew up together.
When there was any problem,
they solved it together.
Maybe when she sees Jiang,
she will study harder.
She can’t rely on Jiang for a life.
It’s hard to say.
Hard to say?
What do you mean?
Be gentle!
Here.
Good.
Be gentle!
Your waist needs good treatment.
Don’t shout for it.
Miao,
well,
this weekend,
let’s go out to get some fresh air, OK?
No.
Miao, think it over.
It’ll disturb my study.
What did you say?
I said it’ll disturb my study.
You won’t go, even to visit Jiang?
Yes.
If there is nothing else,
I’ll go study now.
Look, she resembles me.
Determined.
Won’t be swayed by you.
Hello, delivery.
Coming.
Lu Miao.
Lu Miao’s?
Miao.
Your delivery.
Coming.
OK.
Take this bill, please.
Did you buy comic books again?
No, I didn’t!
Let me see.
It’s from Jiang.
It must be learning stuff.
Take it.
Go to study.
Che.
Which city will you go for university?
Beijing, Shanghai,
Guangzhou or Shenzhen.
Where will you go?
I...
I should stay in the south.
It has a good climate.
What about Ziye and Miao?
Miao
must go to Beijing for Jiang Haoyue.
As for Ziye,
I heard she’ll go to Shanghai.
Shanghai?
Sounds good.
Che,
do you love Ziye?
Why do you say so?
Don’t pretend.
I can tell it.
You always mention her recently.
Actually,
I don’t know.
You don’t know?
How could it be?
When you were pursuing Miao,
you were not like this.
Well,
I didn’t think so much then.
I liked to play with her.
But love should be
more complicated than just playing.
I can’t tell it.
She’s so manly.
I think I’d better
be her friend.
Good, Che,
you can think for others now.
You can argue with me now.
Let’s go!
Waiting for messages?
No.
In the past five minutes,
you watched your phone
at least 10 times.
Lu Miao didn’t send me messages
for a week.
Has her phone been broken?
As a senior,
she’s too busy to send you a message.
It’s really a normal thing.
Don’t be so nervous.
No matter what,
she should have time for a message.
Why don’t you send her a message first?
No.
What if she’s studying?
I don’t want to disturb her.
How hesitant you are!
Is it
that she doesn’t need me anymore?
Why do you think so?
Since childhood,
except study,
I can’t help her with anything else.
Now she can study by herself.
I shouldn’t have sent her
so many papers.
Lu Miao.
Mr. Jiang,
you are amazing!
You combine history knowledge
with comics.
You received it?
I hope it’s useful to you.
It’s really useful!
I never expected
the boring history knowledge
can be turned into comics.
I will definitely succeed this time.
I’m looking forward to your performance.
Thank you.
You must be busy in the university.
I’m sorry to worry you with this.
I heard
you’re afraid I’ll disturb your study,
so you decided not to come here?
It will cost me two days.
I can do four sets of exam papers.
You’re so fond of doing exam papers?
Yeah.
Every time when I do the exercises,
I think
I am fighting with the question setter,
which makes me very excited.
Then I’ll give you a question.
OK. Go ahead.
Any real number plus 52.8,
then multiply 5,
minus 3.4343,
then multiply 2,
and less ten times of this real number,
calculate it.
You spoke too fast just now.
repeat it again.
No question will be repeated
in the listening exam.
Come on, calculate it.
521.1132.
Never mind.
Study harder.
I’ll stop disturbing you now.
You can give me another question.
Stop here now.
A real number.
Any real number
plus 52.8,
multiply 5,
minus 3.4343, and multiply 2,
and less ten times of this real number
equals
521.1314.
Jiang Haoyue,
you are so tricky!
But with Lu Miao’s calculation ability,
I think she’ll never figure out
what you mean.
Didn’t you listen to music?
Mind your own business.
Che, you’ve made
great progress recently.
Yes.
Skills improved.
I’m a genius.
You are here.
Let’s play.
Come.
I remember nothing.
Everyone.
Only five minutes left.
Please check
your name,
exam number,
and your answer sheet.
How come only five minutes left?
I haven’t started
writing the composition.
I’m doomed.
Everyone,
put down your pen.
Sweat and shed blood, no tears,
Move forward no matter what.
I have to finish my reading
before sleep.
I want to express my ambition,
with a dog in the left hand,
and an eagle in the right,
generals and soldiers come like a gale.
I want to express my ambition,
with a dog in the left hand,
and an eagle in the right
generals and soldiers...
Thunders...
the wonderful capability.
How long will the full moon appear?
Wine cup in hand, I ask the sky.
I drink alone and get drunk,
a couple comes into my dream.
Mr. Jiang?
Miao?
Why are you here?
I’m reciting my book.
Reciting?
You have to understand the poem
before you recite it.
Mr. Jiang, you’re drunk.
Go home and have a rest.
No.
No one is home.
Didn’t you promise Jiang Haoyue
you’ll quit drinking?
I’ll tell him if you continue drinking.
Did he call you these days?
Yes, the day before yesterday.
The day before yesterday?
He didn’t call you yesterday.
Absurd.
I’ll call him for you.
Don’t, Mr. Jiang.
It’s too late now.
Is it that you miss him,
but you’re too shy to call him,
so you want to call him in my name?
I’m afraid that you miss him,
you know?
I do miss him so much,
but I’m afraid he’ll be disappointed.
How could he be disappointed?
Gaokao.
I’m afraid I can’t perform well,
and I can’t catch up with him.
Every time when I do the exercises,
I’m under great pressure.
I even can’t fall asleep.
Juveniles are not allowed to drink.
Why juveniles are not allowed to drink?
Why only adults
can drink?
We have a lot of exercises,
we have exams,
we have a lot of difficulties,
we can’t make it.
We have a lot of pressure!
When can the wine for juveniles
be developed and launched?
This little jerk,
can’t you give me a call?
Hello, Dad,
what’s up?
Nothing special.
It’s about the girl next door.
Lu Miao?
What’s wrong with her?
She...
She’s under great pressure recently,
and loses a lot of weight.
She even has dark circles now.
Look, Gaokao hasn’t come.
I’m afraid she may
ruin her health before that.
She’s very stubborn
and can’t listen to
others.
So I’m thinking,
if you can spare some time,
you may come back to see her,
and she may become better.
I get it.
I’ll be back in two days.
OK.
Bad performance, minus 2 points.
Like arguing, minus 2 points.
What are you doing?
Review Shi Che’s shortcomings.
Why should you do that?
Ziye,
do you like Che?
I...
I don’t.
Then there’s a problem.
He asked me to confirm it.
Confirm what?
You can’t deny it now.
I have no idea.
We’d better talk about it after Gaokao.
7 days countdown to Gaokao
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Why are you here?
You don’t come to me,
so I come to you now.
Do your exercises.
I’ll have another bowl of rice.
She has a bad appetite?
Miao,
you’ve had too much food.
Your face is...
Really?
She loses a lot of weight?
She does have dark circles, doesn’t she?
I don’t think you are fat.
But I think
Jiang
lost a lot of weights
this semester.
I don’t quite adapt to the life outside,
I like the food here better.
Jiang,
since you are home,
your auntie will make
your favorite dishes for you.
Yes.
I’ll cook you my best dishes,
braise ribs with lucid ganoderma.
How long will you stay this time?
A week.
Just a week?
Hurry up,
ask what you want timely.
No ink.
No ink?
Here it is.
Take these.
Admission card
Isn’t it the set of school supplies
you used in Gaokao last year?
You give it to me?
Wish you pass all the exams.
This set of school supplies
were used by you, the best student,
I surely can perform well in Gaokao.
Jiang,
I want to ask you a question.
When you arrived in Beijing,
did you have the feeling
of getting lost?
I mean
the feeling of unknowing where to go?
Unknowing where to go?
No.
I know I should go to the university.
You should say yes.
You have.
Well,
yes.
Then what?
Then,
you will
especially miss...
Miss what?
Miss Lu Miao!
Why are you laughing?
No anxiety.
No indolence.
No
Jiang...
No Jiang Haoyue?
Don’t mind these details.
Do the exercises.
Why no Jiang Haoyue?
I’m worried!
Worried?
I’m worried I’m not good enough
to go to your city.
Lu Miao,
did you think about the worst result?
I dare not.
I thought about it.
The worst result is you fail in Gaokao.
Then you choose another university.
Or you choose to repeat grade three.
At that time,
we have to separate.
But it doesn’t matter.
You know,
Beijing has a lot of universities.
If you choose other university,
I can go there to find you.
If
you choose to repeat grade three,
I’ll do what I’m doing now,
come back to accompany you.
No matter what difficulty you’ll meet,
I’ll stay beside you.
If
this is the worst result,
can you accept it?
What about your study?
I can arrange my study well.
Don’t worry about me.
Will I become your burden?
In my mind,
Lu Miao is the best.
Really?
How come I’m so good?
Tell me the reasons.
When I went to a new city,
everything around was strange.
Strange street,
and strange people.
Since then,
I especially
especially
especially miss Lu Miao.
I thought if Lu Miao were here,
it’ll be great.
Jiang Haoyue,
I won’t let the worst result come.
You’ll fly higher!
Fly higher!
Pass the examination
Dance like wild wind,
without any strings.
Dad,
did you wash your car?
It’s so clean!
Come, Miao,
look,
student in car, no honking!
Who dares to honk,
I’ll beat him.
Moreover,
come.
Moreover?
See?
Pass the examination.
Thank you, Dad.
What do you think of this car
I specially prepare for you?
Moreover,
I prepare this memo,
pass the examination.
7:00 tomorrow morning,
call Miao to get up.
Have breakfast at 7:30.
The breakfast is standard,
one fried bread stick and two eggs,
meaning 100 points.
Leave home at 8:00
and arrive at the exam venue at 8:30.
Thank you, Dad.
With all these blessings,
I will surely gain
a decisive victory in Gaokao.
That’s right.
Gosh, I have to go cook now,
or we’ll have to eat
what your mom cooks.
Let’s go, come on.
Come on.
Remember to
check your answer sheet repeatedly.
Don’t make any mistakes, OK?
Got it, Mom.
And
the mobile phone,
never bring it to the exam room.
Last year,
a kid took a phone to the exam room,
and his score became invalid.
I got it.
We’ll check it
before entering the exam room.
And
2B Pencil.
Is your pencil right?
Some parents said,
some scanners
can’t scan the characters
from other pencils,
- except 2B.
- No worries.
No worries, Mom.
Jiang Haoyue gave me
the school supplies he used in Gaokao.
Everything is good
and blessed by the top Gaokao scorer.
What else?
Stop talking endlessly.
Don’t you want her to eat?
I can’t remember it now.
Miao,
this is specially made for you.
Eat more.
Thank you, Dad.
Here, eat more.
Don’t listen to your mom.
I’m reminding her.
Gaokao Features
10 things to do before Gaokao
You scared me.
You scared me!
It’s so late.
What are you doing here?
10 things for parents to do
before Gaokao.
Ten?
Let me see.
I thought you’re better than me.
You are nervous too.
How can I not?
Gaokao is the most important thing
in life.
It says that,
Gaokao
tests mindset,
not only the students’ mindset,
but also the parents’ mindset.
So in front of our kid tomorrow,
we must keep calm.
I think I forget something.
How could there be ten things?
Did I finish them all?
I recorded them all.
Go have a rest now,
will you?
How could I?
I’m awakened by fright.
Ten things!
I didn’t do that much.
Look, I should pay more attention.
She didn’t take
her admission card and pens.
Go have a rest.
You record them all.
I’ll record them all.
Go have a rest now.
Go ahead.
Lu, we’re waiting for you.
Have you finished?
Right away.
Just a second.
I’ll be there soon.
Mom, is Dad alright?
He must have drunk too much
cool milk last night,
and hurt his stomach.
Time is running out. We have to go now.
What to do?
Lu,
how are you?
Done.
Let’s go now. Time is tight.
Can you do it?
It’s fine.
Mom, you send Dad to the hospital,
I can go there by taxi.
How could it be? I...
What to do now?
What about letting my dad drive the car?
OK.
I’ll collect my stuff now.
I’ve packed it for you.
You can take it and go.
Let’s go. Time is tight.
Wait for me!
Lu, we’re leaving now.
You go to the hospital by yourself.
Do you take all the things?
Yes.
Is there enough time?
Yes, I think so.
What’s up?
Gosh,
I left too hurriedly
to turn off the fire.
It’ll be late
if we return home now.
I’ll go back to do it.
Go for it. Waiting for your good news.
OK.
Take it slow.
Be careful!
Let’s go!
Is there still time?
Yes.
Everyone,
after ten years of hard study,
you’ll have the final exam today,
I hope you succeed in the exam.
- Go for it.
When you are in the exam room,
don’t answer the questions hurriedly.
Take it easy.
Keep calm.
I believe you can do it.
Now, take out your admission cards
and get ready to enter the exam room.
Thank you, teacher.
Go for it.
Let’s go!
It’s fine.
Go for it.
I’ll stew pork for you tonight!
It’s wrong. What to do now?
What shall I do?
What to do?
Make way!
Let’s go!
Mr. Jiang
Hello.
Jiang Haoyue!
I took the wrong admission card.
I took yours.
Don’t get into a flap.
Do you remember where you put it?
I put it in the center of my desk.
My mom has gone back now.
I don’t know
whether she can come back in time.
It’s half an hour left.
I’ll send it to you.
Don’t worry.
OK.
Lu Miao, what’s wrong?
I took the wrong admission card.
Mr. Lu.
What to do, Mr. Wen?
Don’t worry.
I’ll check it for you.
Mr. Lu.
Jiang, how’s everything going?
Have you arrived?
Are you home now?
I’m on the way to the hospital.
Sir, how long will we need?
The road ahead is blocked for the exam.
We can’t get in.
A student doesn’t take
her admission card,
what should we do now?
Sir, please stop
at the next intersection.
OK.
Sir, may I borrow your bike?
Yes. Ride safely.
Thanks.
Why hasn’t that girl entered the room?
She forgets to take her admission card.
What a careless girl!
Even she can enter the room,
she can’t stay calm.
Make way!
Make way! Excuse me!
Lu Miao!
Examination time, no honking
Nanfeng No. 1 High School
It’s not too late.
Thank you.
♪We grow up together♪
How long will you hug me?
Go ahead.
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Do you need help?
No.
Beg me,
and I will help you.
I don’t need your help.
Look,
you do need my help.
♪There’s a window in my heart♪
♪Open it and there’s light♪
♪Maintain old memories♪
♪That are simple and beautiful♪
♪Time goes by♪
♪Making memories into nets♪
♪That sway with wind in my dream♪
♪I asked about the lifetime♪
♪It would be very long♪
♪I like to share with you what I like♪
♪And what I think is the best♪
♪In this world♪
♪Only you’re like me♪
♪From youth to the end of life♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪
♪We go insane we laugh
and we feel sad together♪
♪We go everywhere together♪
♪We get wet in rain
and watch the snow fall together♪
♪We grow up together♪
♪We embrace every hope together♪
♪Thank you for the moments
when we’re together♪