My dear, foolish brother.
Why do you stand against me?
This voice...
I will never forget this voice!
All For One!
As long as you are willing to aid my cause,
I will give you what you desire.
The Quirkless will be given their choices.
The sinners will know mercy.
Did you skip your meal again?
Poor thing. There's barely anything left of you.
I'll...
never let you do as you please!
Reality doesn't always go as we planned.
Now, I will cleanse you of your defiance.
You mean a lot to me.
Stop it.
I found a power even
a weakling as you can wield.
Join my cause.
Stop!
You must be the ninth wielder.
I wanted to show you more.
But 20% is all I can conjure for now.
Stay cautious.
The singularity has come to pass.
But fear not,
you are not alone.
♪When we are stranded on the same spot,
make our heart beat♪
MY HERO ACADEMIA
♪Rather than searching for an answer
in this world full of uncertainties♪
♪I want to live even though
my constant doubts are a waste of time♪
♪Take off the unseeable armor and feel the wind♪
♪I make my effort sound worthless
as a way to hide myself♪
♪The No.1 who came out of nowhere
is pointing at the endless sky♪
♪It's our desire to see the view
from greater height and distance♪
♪Ignite the heart of unquenchable desire♪
♪Ignite the path to our future,
burn the illusions to ashes♪
IZUKU MIDORIYA
QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL
I couldn't sleep after that dream.
Midoriya?
What was that ruckus?
No, it's nothing!
It's nothing serious.
"AOYAMA YUGA, QUIRK: NAVEL LASER"
Are you under a lot of stress lately?
Did you not have enough cheese?
I think so.
I'm sorry if I woke you up.
It was clearly a dream.
But I remember every detail.
That moment when his hand touched mine...
When the dream came to an end,
I saw the previous wielders...
"ALL MIGHT, QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL"
You saw the memories...
of the previous wielders?
Yes, I think so.
It was also All For One's memory.
One For All's look...
You must have seen him when you were younger.
Indeed.
After I saw my master,
my predecessor told me about
the existence of that vestige.
I was able to tell you the ins and outs
of their past because I saw it too.
I only saw the memory up until
he was given the power.
Then the first wielder told me
he could only show me 20% of it.
He also mentioned a singularity.
That's all he told me.
All Might, you said the memory I saw
during the sports day borne no meaning,
but I think it did.
He talked to the first wielder?
I never experienced that.
My master said the same thing.
As far as I know, the first wielder
only talked to you.
That wasn't a dream.
It was a vestige.
Master, what do you mean by that?
That Quirk must have accumulated
many thoughts over time.
"I want to do it, I must do it."
"I want to become this, I must become that."
When it concerns power,
people will have their own thoughts about it.
People who cultivated that power all this time,
their thoughts became part of the power
and are embedded as memories.
That's what I think.
Is this considered supernatural?
It's romantic.
Even if we fall,
we can still reunite in One For All.
Isn't that romantic?
All Might...All Might?
So you woke up after the surge of energy?
Were you hurt?
Not at all.
I'm glad to hear that.
Judging by the circumstances,
we only have details I can't understand so far.
That's all there is for now.
But about that singularity...
Could this have something to do with
Quirk Singularity Theory?
The Quirks are inherited from parents,
and continue to mix,
growing in complexity with every new generation.
Quirks will develop to a point
where it becomes too complex...
for anyone to have control over them.
That's what the theory says.
We have no way to prove this for the time being.
We don't know for sure if you were the cause...
or was there any external factor.
Was there anything noticeable?
Well...
There were two wielders I couldn't see clearly.
Even your silhouette was blurry.
Was it because you were considered
one of the latest wielders?
I'm sorry.
I can't be sure about this either.
But that power is siding with you.
Let's find the answer together.
Yes, I won't give up so easily.
And by the way...
Your master...
She resembles my predecessor.
My mom?
It's their hairstyle.
Their hairstyle...
She must be very beautiful then!
Indeed!
The drill starts this afternoon.
You should get going.
Yes!
I'll be watching the whole time.
I feel so happy today.
You do look happy...
You two...
"PRO HERO SHOTA AIZAWA, QUIRK: ERASER
"
You still look closer than ever.
Aizawa!
He dragged me here and...
Don't make it sound like
you were cheating on me.
It's so lame.
That was a little harsh.
Shinso!
As I recall, you were with Mr. Aizawa too.
"HITOSHI SHINSO, QUIRK: BRAINWASHING"
Yeah.
Midoriya, you should be doing your warm-ups.
It's going to be a busy day.
Yes!
CLASH! CLASS A VS CLASS B!
GROUND GAMMA
The day has come!
"TORU HAGAKURE, QUIRK: INVISIBILITY"
This is so exciting!
"KYOKA JIRO, QUIRK: EARPHONE JACK"
Hagakure, don't you feel cold?
It's so cold out here!
I admire your spirit.
"MINA ASHIDO, QUIRK: ACID"
I put on my winter outfit, it looks so cool!
"MOMO YAOYOROZU, QUIRK: CREATION"
Yes!
"MASHIRAO OJIRO: QUIRK: TAIL"
The weather has gone cold lately.
"TENYA IDA, QUIRK: ENGINE"
Our costumes have changed a lot...
since we first came to U.A. High.
"RIKIDO SATO, QUIRK: SUGAR RUSH"
I'm surprised you managed to wear this...
during the hot summer.
Kacchan's outfit looks different too.
"DENKI KAMINARI, QUIRK: ELECTRIFICATION"
"EIJIRO KIRISHIMA, QUIRK: HARDENING"
"KATSUKI BAKUGO, QUIRK: EXPLOSION"
Say it to my face!
You stupid nerd!
Does your battle suit help to keep you warm?
Your sweat is your weapon,
so the mobility this suit grants you
is very beneficial.
I didn't ask for your compliment!
But your suit has gone through the most changes.
You added some new devices lately.
I can pull off more moves now.
These gloves are amazing.
"OCHACO URARAKA, QUIRK: ZERO GRAVITY"
This is the second iteration already.
Hatsume adjusted the strength output for me.
I see, it's Hatsume's work.
Get lost!
Uraraka!
Hey...
You all seem very relaxed.
Are we not worthy enough for you?
Here you are.
We're just getting fired up.
Is that so?
Unfortunately for you,
we clearly have the upper hand.
Bring it on, Class A!
Let's settle the score today!
"CLASS 1-B OF HERO COURSE"
YOSETSU AWASE
SEN KAIBARA
TOGARU KAMAKIRI
KUROIRO SHIHAI
ITSUKA KENDO
YUI KODAI
KINOKI KOMORI
IBARA SHIOZAKI
JUROTA SHISHIDA
NIRENGEKI SHODA
PONY TSUNOTORI
KOSEI TSUBURABA
TETSUTETSU TETSUTETSU
SETSUNA TOKAGE
MANGA FUKIDASHI
JUZO HONEZUKI
KOJIRO BONDO
NEITO MONOMA
REIKO YANAGI
HIRYU RIN
Look at this questionnaire!
I prepared this during the School Festival!
The difference between Class A's live band
and our high-end drama!
Can't you see which got the better reviews?
We came out on top with two votes more than you!
Ever since school started,
you kept drawing attention by constantly
inviting bad news! But things have changed now!
For real?
I didn't watch their performance
so I can't say much about it.
The day has come!
Class A vs. Class B!
This is our first battle drill!
We...
Shut it.
Monoma!
"PRO HERO VLAD KING, QUIRK: BLOOD CONTROL"
We have a special guest today.
So please stop embarrassing yourselves.
A special guest?
I'll crush them!
Is it a girl?
Let's give it our best!
He plans to transfer to the Hero Course.
He's from General Department, Class C.
Hitoshi Shinso.
PRO HERO SHOTA AIZAWA, QUIRK: ERASURE
STOP ANYONE WITHIN HIS SIGHT
FROM USING QUIRKS
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH SCHOOL, HERO COURSE
BIRTHDAY NOVEMBER 8TH
183CM TALL, BLOODTYPE: B, LIKES CATS
TSUYU ASUI, QUIRK: FROG
GIVES HER A FROG'S PHYSIOLOGY
AND DO ANYTHING A FROG CAN
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH SCHOOL CLASS 1-A
BIRTHDAY FEBRUARY 12TH
150CM TALL, BLOOD-TYPE B,
LIKES JELLY
We have a special guest today.
He plans to transfer to Hero Course.
Hitoshi Shinso.
He wants to transfer to Hero Course...
Isn't that Mr. Aizawa's bandage?
Is that his original mask?
Nice to meet you!
He can brainwash you by talking to you, right?
It's a kill on first sight.
However,
Midoriya fell for his Quirk
but managed to broke free.
It was only a fluke.
I saw One For All's vestiges...
because Shinso was controlling me.
It was the timing...
Or was it...
Shinso, do you have anything to say?
Your Quirk is brainwashing people?
You can basically control anyone you want.
You can do nasty things whenever you like.
No one would ever catch you.
Please don't do bad things to me.
That's what everyone says.
I'm Hitoshi Shinso.
Some of you have met me during the sports day.
They say a fight helps you know someone better.
But sadly, I'm not one who upholds
sportsmanship nor do I have friendliness.
I'm already falling behind all of you.
Sorry, but I must do my best.
You're already gifted, you wouldn't understand!
You were born with a Quirk meant for your dream!
You get to use it however you want,
so you wouldn't understand!
I want to be an outstanding hero.
I want to help people with my Quirk.
Each of you is a challenge I must overcome.
I don't plan to become your friend.
That's all from me.
I can feel his aura from here.
"FUMIKAGE TOKOYAMI, QUIRK: DARK SHADOW"
This is getting intense.
"HANTA SERO, QUIRK: TAPE"
He reminds me of you, Todoroki.
"SHOTO TODOROKI, QUIRK: HALF COLD HALF HOT"
Really?
He seems interesting.
Without further a due, let's begin.
Battle drill, commence!
It's Class A against Class B.
It takes place somewhere in Ground Gamma.
There must be four students in each team,
and you take turns to battle.
Four students in one team?
That sounds fun.
I know!
But there will be 41 of us including Shinso.
What do we do with the remainder?
Shinso will participate in two battles.
One as Class A, and another as Class B.
He will battle against both classes.
Which means,
there will be two battles
where one team will have five students.
But the other team will be at a disadvantage.
Having the inexperienced Shinso
on their team is a disadvantage.
That should balance the number advantage.
The objective is to surround and
capture the enemies as heroes.
Both teams must see each other as villains.
The first team to capture four people wins.
Well, the villains are getting
more organized after all.
It's simple, I like it.
We are both the heroes and villains!
Which role should I play?
I think we can see ourselves as heroes.
There are super cute prisons for both teams.
As soon as the opponents are in it,
they will be disqualified.
It doesn't match the atmosphere!
It's most effective to render our opponents
unable to battle on their own base.
But I doubt it would be that simple.
The first to capture four wins.
So this is the balance they mentioned?
Huh?
Yes. With an unfamiliar member on your team,
you'll have five members.
But as long as four are captured, you lose.
You want us to carry a dead weight around?
This is lame.
Don't be so rude.
I'm fine with that. It's true.
His politeness is way beyond our reach!
Well,
let's draw straws.
CLASS A VS CLASS B
FIRST BATTLE
SECOND BATTLE
THIRD BATTLE
FOURTH BATTLE
FIFTH BATTLE
Shinso, it's your turn to draw.
The number will decide which team you join.
We heard what you said earlier,
but let's work as a team.
Nice to meet you!
Could you tell us more about your Quirk?
You have a handsome look.
The girls must like you a lot.
I can tell as much.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, you! Not bad!
Let's crush the cursed Class A together!
Please ignore his outrageous manner.
Nice to meet you.
Same goes for you!
Team five of Class B.
Deku and Shinso have matched
against each other again...
for the first time after the sports event.
The vestige of One For All still bugs me,
but for now...
I look forward to his improvements.
What does he going to show us this time?
Where did you pull that out?
The day has come.
I'm finally on the starting line.
The starting point is your base.
The time limit is 20 minutes.
If you can't settle the score in time,
the team with more remaining members wins.
All Might and Midnight are here!
Are they dating?
Give me a break, I don't like older guys.
"PRO HERO MIDNIGHT, QUIRK: SOMNAMBULIST"
Which team do you think will win?
It's hard to tell.
Class A has become much experienced
after so many crisis.
However,
Class B shows more growth
when it comes to results.
They could focus more on their lessons
without much troubles going on.
They steadily grow over time.
Would it be Class A that shows
true potential in the face of danger?
Or would it be Class B that shows
better overall improvement?
This is exciting.
First battle!
You're all fired-up.
Start!
We all know each other's abilities.
But to maintain life advantage,
we should stick together.
Asui's camouflage.
I can spot her if I know where to look.
So, I should keep my distance from you...
to shoot my one-million-volt lightning.
What if we got separated?
You'll be isolated.
You have a point.
Shiozaki can be quite the handful.
Her Quirk is so powerful.
The attack range is huge, and she annihilated me.
We should start with
the most challenging Quirk to deal with.
That's brilliant, Shinso.
That's just common sense.
Just like we want to take out Ibara first,
they will try to get rid of Kaminari too.
Then we have to deal with
our lack of experience.
Shinso's Brainwashing is very powerful.
I'm counting on all of you!
I hope we get to see Kaminari and Shinso
unleash their true strength.
Thank you.
Have you found them already?
Shiozaki is coming from the left side.
She seems to be alone.
She is spreading her vines to search for us
while heading our way.
Attacking a girl all at once leaves
a bad taste in my mouth.
Roaring Rage!
Kirishima! Tsuyu!
We knew Koda could track us down with ease.
Of course we expected you
to be wary of Shiozaki.
We used her as a decoy and closed in on you.
We isolated you to leave you to your own device.
So I seized the opening to attack!
My nose can sense anything!
Shishida Jurota.
Quirk: Beast.
Monster form drastically augments his strength,
speed, and durability, as well as his senses.
He also becomes more wild, making him reckless.
Now you can't electrocute
us without hurting your friends!
Denki Kaminari!
Check out the new move I developed!
Air Prison!
Not even sound can escape this space!
Okay, let's finish them off!
Leave it to me!
Are you kidding me?
He's been brainwashed.
That guy...
He spoke with my voice!
That mask...
It works as a vocal cord.
Persona Chords.
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪I hope my destination♪
♪Is where we shall meet again♪
♪I'm always seeing the world through your eyes♪
♪Tears are somehow falling down my cheeks♪
♪I hate it when you say it's all right♪
♪Your gentle whisper turned into
an unsettling silence♪
♪I want to believe the clouded sky before us♪
♪Our longing is the very thing that breaks us♪
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪But why? I'm already covered in wounds♪
♪Why must I search for the answer♪
♪Goodbye, we will meet again♪
♪I hope you would still be the same♪
♪I hope that the memories we share♪
♪Would once again bank up♪
♪So I could see you again♪
NEXT EPISODE
The clash between Class A and Class B.
The first battle has begun.
However,
Class B has strengthened their Quirks
with intensive training.
They are closing in on Class A.
Next episode, Make It Happen, Shinso!
Shinso's new ability,
the Persona Chords, will dominate this battle!
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!