CLASS A VS CLASS B
1ST BATTLE
Hero Course of U.A. High.
Class A and Class B are having
the first round of joint training battles.
2ND BATTLE
The third match began after each class
has won one battle.
THAT HURTS!
3RD BATTLE
Class A managed to launch a preemptive strike
on Class B with Todoroki's attack.
But Honenuki's Quirk turned the match
to their advantage.
Class B is slowly gaining the upper hand.
Curse it!
Sorry.
There is a time limit to your Recipro.
You shouldn't have used it
right from the start.
All right. I should give Tetsutetsu a hand.
Time limit?
That's a long time ago, Mudman.
Ingenium will never be absent from a fight.
My legs exist for that sole purpose!
Right now,
I'm always going full-throttle!
New Style: Recipro Turbo!
♪When we are stranded
on the same spot, make our heart beat♪
MY HERO ACADEMIA
♪Rather than searching for an answer
in this world full of uncertainties♪
♪I want to live even though
my constant doubts are a waste of time♪
♪Take off the unseeable armor and feel the wind♪
♪I make my effort sound worthless
as a way to hide myself♪
♪The No.1 who came out of nowhere
is pointing at the endless sky♪
♪It's our desire to see the view
from greater height and distance♪
♪Ignite the heart of unquenchable desire♪
♪Ignite the path to our future,
burn the illusions to ashes♪
Ten minutes.
I am unstoppable
for the next ten minutes!
Are you trying to take me down
with your new move?
However...
He's too fast!
He's going too fast!
I still don't have full control over it.
No, this is bad.
There is no way to fight him.
Surrender yourself, Mudman!
"JUZO HONENUKI, QUIRK: SOFTENING"
Sorry.
I'm not foolish enough to fight my opponent
while I'm at a disadvantage.
It's not safe to leave Ida rampaging.
But I can't fight him right now.
In that case, I should hurry to aid Tetsutestu.
TENYA IDA, QUIRK: ENGINE
He undid the effect on the ice.
Is he hiding to start a retaliation?
He should know by now
how futile that would be.
Did he leave to aid his teammates?
THE THIRD BATTLE'S CONCLUSION
"OCHACCO URARAKA, QUIRK: ZERO GRAVITY"
Ida is moving so fast!
"IZUKU MIDORIYA, QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL"
Recipro Turbo...
"MINORU MINETA, QUIRK: POP OFF"
He is even faster than Gran Torino.
Your shoot style somehow inspired Ida
to figure out his own fighting style.
I should ask him for advice on kicking.
"MINA ASHIDO, QUIRK: ACID"
Enough! Look at Ojiro!
"KYOKA JIRO, QUIRK: EARPHONE JACK"
Ojiro is fighting as usual.
"HANTA SERO, QUIRK: TAPE"
He may be at a disadvantage,
but he has learned much over time!
Go for it!
My chest hurts!
You can't win a fight by simply dodging.
"MASHIRAO OJIRO, QUIRK: TAIL"
He can easily reflect my attacks.
"SEN KAIBARA, QUIRK: GYRATE"
I can try guarding it,
but his support item is too sharp
and tough to withstand.
You're a mean one, Kaibara!
Eat this!
Ida?
I'll put Spiral into the prison now!
I'll be gone for a moment,
but it won't take long!
Ojiro, help the others!
I think Mudman is already on his way!
I'll be right back!
Understood!
Even the speed of his speech has become faster.
Let me go! It should be my turn to shine!
Stay still!
I won't let my opponent have any chance
to defeat me!
Did you let Honenuki get away?
You know how troublesome he can be.
Anyone else would have gone after him instead.
You shouldn't interrupt my fight, Ingenium!
My brother would do the same.
He is the hero I must become!
If I stray away from my standard
during training,
the same thing will happen in a real battle.
You're so stubborn.
Indeed. People tell me that a lot.
Steel Fist!
He hardened his entire body, so being
partly frozen won't hinder his performance.
His hardened skin doesn't even peel off.
Tetsutetsu, I will learn much from you.
"KATSUKI BAKUGO, QUIRK: EXPLOSION"
Stop using your ice, it's not working on them.
You're acting like a wimp.
"TETSUTETSU TETSUTETSU, QUIRK: STEEL"
Your ice wall means nothing to me!
I will crush it with my fists of justice!
"SHOTO TODOROKI, QUIRK: HALF COLD HALF HOT"
In that case...
I'll put on a wall of flame for you!
Ouch!
Shoji! Take care of Tsunotori!
All right!
Back down, I must create a distance between him.
Why am I fighting you?
I bet you didn't know.
Your attacks won't work on me at all!
He's turning red from the heat.
My steel is burning red!
Hey!
"PONY TSUNOTORI, QUIRK: HORN"
Fight, Real Fist!
This is how my Quirk has improved!
Have you ever lived inside a burning furnace?
Tetsutetsu, restrain Todoroki!
Subdue him in close combat and stop him
from using wide-range attack!
Half Cold Half Hot...
Your Quirk won't work on me!
This is...
the fruition of my hard work
for going beyond my limits!
Push your heat to its limit!
Then go beyond that limit!
There is no way you can't do it.
You're simply not trying hard enough!
I'll keep punching until I knock you out.
Feel it.
The power within you is stronger than anyone!
Why now?
Why am I thinking of him now?
Curse it...
Prepare to lose!
If my ice and fire can't hurt him...
With this,
you'll become the perfect incarnation of myself!
Isn't that part of your power too?
Back down.
That burns!
More flame...
"VLAD KING, QUIRK: BLOOD CONTROL"
The camera broke down from the heat.
More flame...
I can still generate more heat.
Burn on!
I must become the hero I want to be!
TETSUTETSU, QUIRK: STEEL
HE CAN TURN HIS BODY INTO METAL
AND STILL MOVE FREELY
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH CLASS 1-B
BIRTHDAY: OCTOBER 6TH
HEIGHT: 174CM, BLOOD TYPE: B
FAVOURITE THINGS: FIGHTING GAMES, SPINACH
SHOTO TODOROKI, QUIRK: HALF-COLD HALF-HOT
HE CAN GENERATE ICE FROM HIS RIGHT SIDE
AND FLAME FROM HIS LEFT SIDE
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH CLASS 1-A
BIRTHDAY: JANUARY 11TH
HEIGHT: 176CM, BLOOD TYPE: O
FAVORITE FOOD: COLD SOBA NOODLE.
"ALL MIGHT, QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL"
Young Todoroki...
He is using Endeavor's flame.
It's burning me!
This heat is insane!
I can understand your feeling, Todoroki.
I keep burning metal inside my body.
I know you're suffering.
I doubt you could last long in this state.
Well then...
Endurance is my specialty!
Go beyond!
You...
I won't let you get away
with just some burn marks.
If you can't risk your life in training,
you won't risk your life in real battles!
Superiority and limits
are meant to be broken!
You are talking too loud.
I can still feel the heat at this distance.
I should go support Real Steel now.
"MEZO SHOJI, QUIRK: DUPLI-ARMS"
Sorry, Tentacole.
I always skip the octopus when I go
to a public aquarium.
I don't like it.
I'm used to being feared by everyone.
I'll send you to the prison.
Let's settle the score now.
That's more like it.
Thunder Horn!
Octoblow!
I'm winning.
No!
Thanks, Ojiro.
Tornado Tail Dance!
You won't be a threat to us
if you can't fire your horns.
The way you got me...
It's so darn ordinary!
I'll take her to the prison.
Aid Todoroki now.
Honenuki?
I'm taking Tsunotori back.
I'm a surprisingly loyal friend.
When he struggles to break out,
his tail will loosen up.
Curse it!
Fist of Tail: Swamp Smack Spin!
I got you.
Thanks.
He put so much power into shaking me off.
Please step aside, Honenuki.
I won't let go even if you stab me!
I don't need you to loosen up!
Ojiro!
I'll use my horns
to send you into the prison!
Under any circumstances,
you're disqualified
when you step into the prison.
The score is 1:1.
What's wrong? Your flame has gone weaker.
Todoroki!
Your movement is getting slower too.
I feel dizzy.
I can't move my body.
If I want to cool down,
I must first knock this guy out.
Go beyond.
Tetsutetsu, you're going to melt.
Honenuki...
This is bad. I'm losing my consciousness.
Solidify.
I won't miss again!
Mudman!
That burns...
Hey you...Don't you run away from me.
You should save him first.
When there is a lost child,
I take them to the Lost Children Center.
That's the coolest anyone can be.
Mind your tongue, villain!
Saving lives must always be the priority!
I'm going to pass out.
If he lands that attack...
To think he said he couldn't
control this power yet...
It's a fatal mistake to leave Ida rampaging.
We're going to lose.
When I pass out, the Quirk effect will be gone.
I can't leave items to help my team
as Yaoyorozu did,
I don't feel frustrated.
I feel defeated.
However...
I can't let my mistake be the cause
of our defeat!
Tetsutetsu! Push this!
What was that?
All combatants are down!
But they are still in the battle
until they are sent to the prison!
What will happen now?
That hurts...
My left arm and leg...
It's too heavy.
I can't move with just one leg.
Todoroki, I've failed you.
If I could just move faster...
Had I reached you sooner back then...
Ida is still conscious,
but he's unable to battle!
I think Kaibara's struggle
had taken a toll on him.
He struggled hard after being captured,
contributing to Ida's demise!
Well done, Kaibara!
You're the MVP of the day, Kaibara!
Vlad King is starting his bias broadcast again.
Class A and Class B each have one prisoner.
Four combatants are down.
All that is left is...
Todoroki!
I can't let Shoji toss them into the prison.
But what should I do now?
I can't defeat Shoji even
with all my horns attacking.
I lose for sure if I fight him head-on.
We'll be in the lead if I send
Todoroki to the prison first.
But I have three unconscious teammates.
He might catch up to me before
I even reach the prison.
It's over if I lose.
I got you!
Well then...
Is she...
I'll wait for my chance somewhere
you can never reach.
I can't win, but I won't lose either.
Sorry, Tentacole!
I don't want my team to lose.
She took her teammates and Todoroki to the sky.
Shoji's can't fly even with his Quirk.
She got away.
Deku, what is Class B up to now?
My guess is they are playing it safe.
Shoji would put her teammates into
the prison if she put them down.
Why is she taking Todoroki with her?
If Todoroki woke up,
it would be impossible to dodge
his ice and flame, even while flying.
She is taking him as a precaution.
But she can't win unless
she puts him into the prison.
It can't be helped.
But the outcome is almost certain.
They are running out of time!
Time's up!
The third battle ends!
Both teams got one prisoner! It's a tie!
This doesn't feel good at all! It sucks!
"JUROTA SHISHIDA, QUIRK: BEAST"
If this was a real battle,
the best way is to retreat and wait for backup.
Ida.
It must be hard for him to accept this.
However...
He was awesome.
Too many combatants are unconscious.
Like the second battle, we'll start
the post mortem meeting later.
Get ready for the fourth battle!
RECOVERY GIRL, QUIRK: HEAL
Todoroki!
You're finally awake.
Have a calorie bar.
Ojiro finished his and went back.
Todoroki!
I know the battle ended with a draw.
But I feel defeated!
Your flame was insane!
We should fight again!
You are too loud.
A draw...
Had I moved faster,
we could have won.
Ida...
I wasn't fast enough.
I couldn't overcome Honenuki's
flexibility in battle.
But you saved me.
I can remember as much.
Not to mention I made the first mistake.
We would have been trapped
had you used your flame more fiercely.
I'm used to striking preemptively with my ice.
No, that mindset had been
planted into my muscles.
You were fast enough.
But I couldn't react in time.
I made you worry because I was too slow.
I must become the hero people can count on.
No, you're definitely reliable...Ouch!
I must make it in time for everyone
no matter what danger awaits.
This is the spirit I inherited from Ingenium.
Your flame and his Recipro...
I have some problems to deal with too.
Could we train together sometimes?
Of course.
Go back there if you're feeling all right.
Stop chitchatting in my infirmary!
Yes! We're so sorry!
There is no way out of this.
Class A and Class B have the same score.
We can win if we lose or end up with a tie!
"NEITO MONOMA, QUIRK: COPY"
He just has to let it out sometimes.
I'm so excited for the fourth battle!
After all, we have Tokage with us!
Isn't that right? Bakugo?
All right, let's go.
Setsuna Tokage.
Another student from Class B
who got in through official recommendation.
She is a tough opponent!
Kacchan.
Hold on, are you serious?
Are you kidding me? Your strategy...
That's right.
Wait and see, stupid Deku.
We'll start after everyone is in position!
The fourth battle! Start!
4TH BATTLE
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪I hope my destination♪
♪Is where we shall meet again♪
♪I'm always seeing the world through your eyes♪
♪Tears are somehow falling down my cheeks♪
♪I hate it when you say it's all right♪
♪Your gentle whisper turned
into an unsettling silence♪
♪I want to believe the clouded sky before us♪
♪Our longing is the very thing that breaks us♪
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪But why? I'm already covered in wounds♪
♪Why must I search for the answer♪
♪Goodbye, we will meet again♪
♪I hope you would still be the same♪
♪I hope that the memories we share♪
♪Would once again bank up♪
♪So I could see you again♪
Next Episode.
The fourth battle begins with
both teams scoring one point so far.
Class A is sending out Jiro,
Sero, Sato and Kacchan.
But Class B has Tokage on their team.
Watch out, she is likely to set up traps.
Next episode, Early Bird!
Kacchan changed his fighting style?
No, he's evolved!
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!