The Hero Course of U.A. High
held a joint training between
Class A and Class B.
Class A won the match with
three victories and one draw.
CLASS A WON
I still have a long way to go.
I've seen how strong the Hero Course is.
I won't be satisfied with just passing the test.
I will work harder and push myself
to reach greater heights.
Good.
Move forward with the spirit of Plus Ultra.
Yes!
♪When we are stranded on the same spot,
make our hearts beat♪
MY HERO ACADEMIA
♪Rather than searching for an answer
in this world full of uncertainties♪
♪I want to live even though my constant doubts
are a waste of time♪
♪Take off the unseeable armor and feel the wind♪
♪I make my effort sound worthless
as a way to hide myself♪
♪The No.1 who came out of nowhere
is pointing at the endless sky♪
♪It's our desire to see the view
from greater height and distance♪
♪Ignite the heart of unquenchable desire♪
♪Ignite the path to our future,
burn the illusions to ashes♪
Shinso, in the end you were trying
to cause disruption and shift the battle
to your advantage, right?
You were quick to block my way
with those pipes.
You were moving like Mr. Aizawa
with your binding cloth.
In the first battle,
I thought the team's coordination
enabled you to unleash your potential.
But that wasn't the case.
Shinso's mobility and reactions were impeccable.
You were on par with those from the Hero Course.
You had me nervous for a moment.
You're much better at using your strength
for others than I ever was.
"SHOTA AIZAWA, QUIRK: ERASURE"
Indeed.
"VLAD KING, QUIRK: BLOOD CONTROL"
We will make another assessment.
But it's likely...No, it's almost certain
that Shinso will join the Hero Course
in his second year.
Don't you let him overtake you!
Yes!
"DENKI KAMINARI, QUIRK: ELECTRIFICATION"
Sir, which class will he be joining?
Class A?
Class B?
We'll decide when the time comes.
It's too early to be certain.
Sir!
Mineta's actions were so low!
Please punish him now.
It was nothing but a lucky coincidence.
Not to mentioned I was giving my all
to deal with Shota and his teammates.
It's undeniable that Class B lost.
However,
we didn't lose to you when it came down
to the marvel we displayed!
Had I known Midoriya's Quirk
wasn't compatible with mine,
I would have come up
with a strategy against that!
Which means,
"NEITO MONOMA, QUIRK: COPY"
the outcome might be different if fought again!
That's not going to happen.
The lesson ends now!
Speaking of which,
Monoma activated Shota's Quirk on me,
so we must have made physical contact.
So One For All was copied too.
About my Quirk, the One For All,
it condenses multiple physical abilities
that are honed to their limits into one.
A half-baked body won't be able to take it.
Your limbs will explode into a million pieces!
That was what made me worried.
Had I known Midoriya's Quirk
wasn't compatible with mine...
What does he mean by compatible?
Excuse me, but I have some questions.
Monoma, come to Eri's place tomorrow.
They are visiting Eri tomorrow...
"MILIO TOGATA, QUIRK: PERMEATION"
You've learned how to write.
"ERI"
Yes. I want to write a letter.
A letter? For whom?
For Lemillion and Deku.
I don't know what I should say
so I want to write them down in a letter.
I want to thank you.
THE NEW POWER AND ONE FOR ALL
What's wrong with you?
Are you scared, you jerk?
I told you to wait!
Hold on! It's not coming out!
Stop!
It's not what you think it is!
Cool it down!
KATSUKI BAKUGO, QUIRK: EXPLOSION
His new power came out when he was in danger!
No. We are training to keep it in.
Young Midoriya, how do you feel?
It's not coming out.
I can no longer sense it.
A Quirk from the preview wielder...
Is this what One For All has developed into?
Do you always chitchat in this place?
I was surprised when you came here.
After all, Bakugo is also
keeping this a secret for us.
All Might, do you know what happened?
About those black tentacles?
I was seeing those for the first time too.
A bald wielder in the past...
The wielder before my master
was a young man with dark hair.
One For All holds the powers of
all its previous wielders...
Perhaps even my master didn't know it.
So you're the first to have it all, trash.
Don't call him trash.
Was there anything that triggered it?
Nothing at all.
The bald guy told me the time has come.
There might be other external trigger points.
Could it have anything to do with All For One?
After all, that guy gave birth
to the Quirk of One For All.
Having multiple Quirks at once.
I see. It's the same as his power.
You just said what I hated to admit the most.
In any case, to prevent Midoriya
from becoming him,
we need to know more about this new power.
You lack danger awareness!
If I keep crushing you,
it will come out for sure!
So if I crushed you while
the tentacles are out...
Please tone down your motivation.
If One For All is answering to my thoughts,
then at that moment...
This power...
exists before my power.
I decided it was a power I couldn't master
at the moment.
Perhaps that's why the Quirk seemed
to be sealed away.
In that case, I should try to imagine it
as locking and unlocking a door.
I must first learn how to
unleash those tentacles.
This is too boring, jerk!
It's pointless if you can't use it!
I'm out of here.
Your nagging is getting on my nerve!
I think that's all for today.
Yes.
A power of All For One...
You fool!
"TETSUTETSU TETSUTETSU, QUIRK: STEEL"
You fool! How can you be so discouraged?
"EIJIRO KIRISHIMA, QUIRK: HARDENING"
But my performance today
was nowhere as remarkable as yours.
I could withstand the heat because
my body is made out of metal.
And because it's metal,
there is a limit to its hardness.
Unlike you, I can't get
denser after taking a beating!
You and I,
we each have our own uniqueness!
Tetsutetsu!
"TENYA IDA, QUIRK: ENGINE"
We have beef stew for dinner tonight.
That's great!
Class B is here too.
Some of them are here for
post mortem and exchange thoughts.
Midoriya, I've been looking for you.
"SHOTO TODOROKI, QUIRK: HALF COLD HALF HOT"
Todoroki.
Do you have two different Quirks too?
On the sports day...
Show me your best!
You looked very earnest back then.
So if you were hiding a Quirk from us,
it would be shocking to me.
No!
How should I put it?
I think it's an extension of my Quirk.
I think they are still the same thing at core.
I was terrified when it happened
for the first time.
I see, it must have been hard for you.
I apologize for ever doubting you.
What happened today was too shocking.
That sharp and dim-witted fool.
You did well too, Todoroki.
You already have so much
control over your flame.
No, I still have much to learn.
I was just as surprised as you were.
Which is why...
I must work to improve myself.
-WE NEED TO TALK, PLEASE REPLY.
-THERE IS SOMETHING I WANT TO ASK
I can't believe it.
ENDEAVOR, QUIRK: HELLFLAME
You actually came to me.
Well, that settled it.
I can handle the related paperwork.
You should focus on the teaching.
I appreciate your help.
"PRESENT MIC, QUIRK: VOICE"
Shinso is very much like your younger self.
Do you see yourself in him, Aizawa?
Or perhaps you saw...
Just get to the point.
I still have work to take care of.
It's nothing, just chitchat.
The dark side of U.A. High...
What is this kid talking about?
I told her during the school festival
"DARK SIDE OF U.A. HIGH"
that you were the dark side of U.A. High.
I'm a man who walks the path of righteousness!
What are we doing here exactly?
Midoriya, Togata.
I'm sorry to ask you here.
But I need a favor from Monoma.
It's frustrating because Eri and Monoma
don't have much in common in their personality.
What do you take me for?
Well, Monoma?
It's a feint.
I'm sorry but the result
is disappointing, Eraser Head.
I see. What a shame.
He copied Eri's Quirk.
But for what purpose?
Monoma, what do you mean it's a feint?
Both of your Quirks are of the same type.
Your Quirk is the accumulation type.
My Quirk allows me to copy
the fundamental quality of other Quirks.
But if the Quirk stores energy to be unleashed,
I can't copy the energy that
has already been stored.
I see.
Fat Gum's Quirk allows
him to store energy from fat.
If Monoma copies the Quirk,
his body will still be as weak.
This kind of things happen.
I copied your Quirk but I couldn't use it...
because of this principle.
Had it worked the other way,
I would have caused Monoma to explode!
But why is he copying Eri's Quirk?
Even if we let Eri activate her Quirk again,
the same disastrous incident will happen
unless we know how to control it.
So I thought I could ask Monoma to copy
her Quirk and show her how to use it.
It would have made her life much easier.
But I don't think that's possible now.
Sorry.
I am always causing you trouble.
My power will only make everyone worry.
I wish I could get rid of this power.
Eri...
It doesn't just make people worry.
Remember, you once saved my life!
What matters is how you use it.
Take a kitchen knife as an example.
The knife can be dangerous,
but a sharper knife makes it easier
to make delicious cuisines.
Your power is amazing.
After all,
that guy gave birth to
the Quirk of One For All.
That is true,
but this power will become my comrade.
I will try my best.
I must master the power of One For All
and make it my own extension.
MIRO TOGATA, QUIRK: PERMEATION
HE CAN PHASE THROUGH OBJECT
AND ALLOW AIR TO PASS THROUGH HIS BODY
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH SCHOOL YEAR 3
BIRTHDAY: JULY 15, HEIGHT: 181 CM
BLOOD TYPE: AB
FAVORITE: RAMEN AND JOKES
ALL MIGHT, QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL
THE POWER HE INHERITED CAN CRUSH POWERFUL FOES
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH SCHOOL TEACHER
BIRTHDAY JUNE10
HEIGHT: 220CM, BLOODTYPE A,
FAVORITE: JAPANESE CEDAR
It's snowing!
Rubbing dry cloth will cleanse the mind!
"MOMO YAOYOROZU, QUIRK: CREATION"
Your cloth is drenched!
Be careful not to fall down!
"TSUYU ASUI, QUIRK: FROG"
Close the windows! Tsuyu stopped moving!
"KYOKA JIRO, QUIRK: HEADPHONE JACK"
Sorry, Tsuyu!
"HANTA SERO, QUIRK: TAPE"
Let's check the weather forecast.
When is Todoroki coming back?
I want to borrow his next volume of comic.
Around 6 pm.
This is the last day of
the provisional license test.
If they pass the test today,
all of us from Class A
will be provisional license holders!
"GANG ORCA, QUIRK: ORCINUS"
After today,
I won't see you fools again.
This is worth celebrating!
Are you ready, puny plankton?
All right, let's begin.
They should be taking the test now.
"TORU HAGAKURE. QUIRK: INVISIBILITY"
I wonder if they are doing well.
Don't worry.
Bakugo seems to be doing well lately.
But he is still a jerk.
"RIKIDO SATO, QUIRK: SUGAR RUSH"
I should make a cake for when they come back.
Great!
MEIZO SHOJI, QUIRK: DULPI-ARMS
The only thing I beat them at
is getting my provisional license.
Don't be so petty.
Petty Kaminari!
What was that?
"EXPANDING INTO NEW MARKETS"
Kaminari, you're special too.
"DETNERAT IS ENTERING THE FIELD OF HERO SUPPORT"
Thank you, Shoji.
They have announce to venture into
the market of hero support.
The fish took the bait!
-My bag! Give it back!
-Curse it.
The heroes will be here soon.
Is there trouble?
Where are the heroes?
It's less than 30 seconds since it happened.
Then leave it to me.
No, we should confirm the situation first.
I checked. Please handle the evacuation.
You can't fight, but we can.
You have a point.
Boss, you were right to pick a holiday!
This is a torrent of wallets!
But you've only
got your license for 30 minutes...
So, 30 minutes?
Well,
how long does it take to be a hero?
What's wrong with you two?
Do you think you're heroes?
Leave this place now!
My goodness, it's All Might!
Those wallets and bags...
It's wrong to rob.
Cursed kid. Do you think your ice
is enough to make me...
give up the money?
To pull this off,
we probed all the patrol routes
in this area thoroughly!
It's near the end of the year!
It took us one month to plan this!
A place and time with crowds and no heroes,
this the perfect place!
Go get a job!
Sorry to disappoint you,
but your plan is ruined.
Ruined? You are too naive, kids.
You two still have much to learn!
Listen up! I can control carbonic acid.
I live to seek thrill!
My resolve is much stronger than
kids who go home from school every day!
I have the resolve to get away!
They passed out.
I was only using enough firepower
to immobilize you.
Have you lost your resolve?
Show me your resolve to lose!
Who would want that?
It's too strong!
A carnival of ice and snow!
Lady, please stay away from there!
Go somewhere else if you want to end your life!
This is my most powerful attack!
It could get a little ugly, but I guess
there is no other way.
Flashfreeze Heatwave!
With heat,
carbon dioxide will evaporate.
Curse you, that move just now...
I controlled the output.
Are you hurt?
No way, jerk. Are you looking down on me?
What about that girl?
She's fine, jerk!
Are you two all right?
You must be students from U.A. High.
Mind your words!
You two took care of these villains?
They robbed those on the street
of their wallets and belongings.
We confirmed the enemy's number
and apprehended them.
And the things they took?
I gathered everything
before they were burned.
A flawless execution!
This is amazing! I can't believe
you're still students!
Thank you so much!
You'll become outstanding heroes in the future!
Leave the cleaning up to me, Slidin' Go!
His gauntlet exploded.
Indeed.
It must be some half-baked good
from the black market.
You two did well.
Thank you.
All right, let's go back.
You must be starving.
I have to melt the ice first.
I'm not going to help you.
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪I hope my destination♪
♪Is where we shall meet again♪
♪I'm always seeing the world through your eyes♪
♪Tears are somehow falling down my cheeks♪
♪I hate it when you say it's all right♪
♪Your gentle whisper turned into
an unsettling silence♪
♪I want to believe the clouded sky before us♪
♪Our longing is the very thing that breaks us♪
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪But why? I'm already covered in wounds♪
♪Why must I search for the answer♪
♪Goodbye, we will meet again♪
♪I hope you would still be the same♪
♪I hope that the memories we share♪
♪Would once again bank up♪
♪So I could see you again♪
Why is it so dark in here?
Has everyone gone out?
Congratulations...
on getting your provisional license!
Have some cake!
No one can eat that much!
Todoroki!
Congratulations!
Nice job, Bakugo!
Kacchan, we can no go
on hero activities together!
Don't act so high and mighty, stupid nerd!
That's not what I meant!
Don't argue with me!
Next episode.
Kacchan and Todoroki
got their provisional license.
All of Class A can now take part
in hero activities.
The second semester ends on December 25.
Let's throw a Christmas party!
Next episode, Merry Christmas!
But we wouldn't know
that darkness is brewing while
we celebrate in joy.
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!