Shigure, do you love me?
Have you been walking around
asking everyone that?
I'm the one asking the questions.
Do you love me?
I care about you more than anyone.
That's an unwavering truth.
Yes, Akito, I love you.
"Fruits Basket"
Oho!
You're making paper flowers!
That's a blast from the past.
Are they for school?
Yes, they're for the graduation ceremony!
Our class is in charge of
the flower decorations.
Graduation season already, eh?
So you three will be seniors?
Time sure flies.
Hey, can I try opening one up?
Oh, yes, go right... ahead...
The only ones who know
that Akito is female...
Sh-Shigure-san...
Yes?
Is A...?
Um, all right, I-I'll go make some tea!
Okay!
Yeah, I guess that's
a tough topic to ask about.
It's hard to ask about!
I'm not sure how meaningful
it would be to ask...
Wouldn't I just be interrogating him?
And the things Kureno-san told me
make me feel like I'm looking
into a deep, dark well.
Your class is making
flowers too, huh, Tohru?
Mine is, too! We're twinsies!
Yes, we are!
I'm having fun with my class,
but the seniors have to graduate,
so I bet they're sad.
--I imagine--
--Indeed I am sad!
Yuki-kun...
--Just repeat senior year.
--Yeah, right!
Why do you always appear
out of nowhere just to be rude?!
Oh, I thought about repeating a grade!
Because Papa said Momo
wants to come to this school.
Papa was panicking. But I'll graduate
by the time she starts, you know?
--Momiji.
--Hmm? What?
I can't tell Momiji-kun, either.
Not even about Uo-chan and Kureno-san.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what
I can talk about, or how much.
What would people think if I did?
How would they feel?
--Huh?
--Halt, thieves!
Give those back!
Crap, they must have waited
until most of our class left.
U-Um, what just happened?
They stole all the flowers Yuki made.
Wh-Why would they do that?!
Well...
--Because they're Prince Yuki.
We did it! We did it, girls!
We overcame all obstacles to obtain these!
Yes, Motoko-sempai!
And they didn't see through our disguises!
"Yes, they did."
Give them a talking-to, Hanajima-san.
It would bring me no personal gain.
That does it. Our only choice is...
You fold more flowers, Kyon.
There you go again.
They stole that jerk's flowers, not mine.
Yeah, but he already left
for the student council.
So what? I just finally
finished my share--
--They're gone!
--Not my problem.
Dammit...
Where'd they go?!
I did it! Whoever gets Kyo's
flowers gets his love!
For real?
You just decided that.
He'd love all of us if that were true...
Whoever took these, I won't say,
"I'll kill you." But go to hell!
Not how normal people do "kindness."
That was kindness?
Now you'll have to start over either way.
You're kidding me!
Seriously, though,
what do we do about the prince's?
It doesn't seem right to call him
back here to make more.
Not like this was Yuki-kun's
fault anyway.
Wait, does that mean we have to make them?
Grrr! Who do they think they are, dammit?!
We're gonna find those girls
and take the flowers back!
--Yeah!
What? B-But, um, I think it would be
better to make more...
Don't be soft on crime, Tohru!
You just don't want to make them.
Let's go! You, too, Hanajima!
Well, if you require firepower...
Hold the fort, Tohru!
What?!
I think you can just wait
until they get back.
--Up a little, maybe?
--Yeah.
Can I help with anything?
S-Soma-sempai!
N-No, don't be silly!
W-We couldn't ask
the president to help us!
--Help?
--We couldn't ask you to do that, Yuki.
No, no need.
We know you're already busy
with other stuff, Soma.
They really don't need to be so polite...
That looks like fun.
Machi?
You startled me.
What's got you running so fast?
--When you...
--What?
When you roam around
in such strange patterns,
I can't predict your route and I lose you.
Oh, were you looking for me?
Sorry. Did you want me for something?
No.
Okay, hold it.
You ran around looking for me till you
were out of breath for no reason?
I did want something.
Which is it?
T-To say hello.
I saw you, so I just...
thought I'd say hello.
But you kept roaming
on an unpredictable route...
Please say "patrolling."
Anyway! I just got stubborn because
you were hard to catch, that's all.
Okay...
It's not like she couldn't say hello
when she saw me again later.
She chased me just for that?
She came to me, of all people?
Thank you.
Ow!
What did I do to deserve that?
And what is this?
--A flower.
--What? No way. Really?
It's even worse than the ones I made.
It's a flower!
They're taking forever.
Maybe their investigation got bogged down?
I bet they got distracted
by something more fun.
They seem like they only live
for the moment.
I-I don't think so...
My curse has already broken.
Kyo-kun...
What would you think if there
were someone in the zodiac
whose curse was broken?
Huh?
What do you mean?
There's no way for me to know that.
Don't ask me hypothetical questions
about stuff like that.
O-Oi! Why are you depressed now?!
I-I'm sorry. That was thoughtless of me.
Whoa, whoa, don't apologize.
I'm not mad, I swear!
--What should I do?
--Was it my phrasing?
Is that it?!
--What should I do?
--Look, I'm sorry.
I should've said that better.
--I don't want to upset him.
--Look, I'm sorry.
I should've said that better.
I can't raise my head.
I'm afraid I'll cry.
We arrested the culprits.
But I'm tired now.
Let's go home, Tohru-kun.
What on earth happened?
We caught the perps, but...
We just ordered them to make
replacement flowers.
They're lucky we didn't
confiscate what they took.
Our punishment was humane.
How are you today?
This is a little present.
I thought you might not
have seen one, Akito-san.
Hey. Do you still remember?
Remember what?
Isuzu-san!
"Isuzu"? What, is something up with Rin?
Oh, um, it's nothing!
My mind was wandering!
Okay...
I can't believe I forgot about
Isuzu-san until just now.
She's desperate to break the curse, too.
I'm sorry. Should I tell you, Isuzu-san?
Come to think of it, I don't think
I've seen her since... New Year's...
Shigure says he'll be out late.
Late? Isn't he having dinner
with his editor today?
Taking his time torturing her, probably.
I'll go visit her.
I'll just go--
Please come!
Please just come save me!
I think I've tried really hard,
and I'm not sure I can make it
home tonight psychologically intact!
Mitchan, you're too sensitive.
And you're Soma-sensei's editor!
That seems like a problem.
Shouldn't we call the manager?
Let's give her some space.
Life can be hard.
Did you know the devil pretends to be
a wanderer before he gets in the boat?
What?
Anyway, this is a business
relations thing, so no running away.
Maybe I'll quit my job.
There's my companion, so I'm off.
Stop, Shigure! Pay your respects
to Akito-san first.
I don't want to.
It's bound to take forever.
Shall we?
Um, if you know those people,
why not go for a drink with them next?
You must be kidding. What fun
would it be to drink with my parents?
P-P-Parents?!
Sorry, I'm afraid I do have parents.
I-I want to get a closer look at them!
Don't bother. They'll just
turn any outsiders away.
Apparently, there's a dinner tonight
for the main family's chosen guests.
You picked the worst restaurant, Mitchan.
"Main family"...
The Somas must be real elites, huh?
True. There's serious status gap
between you and Ritchan.
Oh, look, the honored family head arrives.
Mm-hmm...
Pale as a ghost, am I right?
I mean, no! I was only thinking
that he looks so young!
Not too young. Over 20, I think.
E-Excuse me?! Are you saying people
over 20 aren't young anymore?!
He's young and pretty!
Although I guess it might be rude
to call a man "pretty"...
So, where shall we drink next?
--What? Sensei!
No weird places, please, okay?!
--I did tell him to pay his respects.
--What? Sensei!
No weird places, please, okay?!
Shall I go after him?
No need.
Come, Kureno.
Don't you think you
should've abandoned Akito-san?
For Akito-san's sake...
back then and this time, too?
You don't seem too surprised.
Did you already figure out
I was free from the curse?
I wish I could say yes and sound cool,
but I'm afraid it was just a hunch.
But I feel a little better now.
I see how it is...
No wonder she wants to keep you close.
She wouldn't want people to find out,
and she'd be saddeningly desperate.
Shigure-niisan... I believe I know
how you feel about her.
And that you hate me. But--
Yes, I do hate you. I hate you a lot.
Better thank me for making that clear.
Now you can enjoy that gloomy act
of yours all you want.
How nice for you.
Niisan...
Still, I want to ask you
not to cut off Akito.
Please don't be any colder with her.
She doesn't keep me close
because she loves me.
The one she wants with
her most has always been...
"Soma"
Welcome home.
Welcome home, Akito-san.
You can stay here. Everyone keep away.
Of course.
Welcome home.
Did you have fun dining with everyone?
That outfit makes you
look even more masculine.
Why did you come? What do you want?
To apologize for not
greeting you at the restaurant.
Who was that woman with you?
Someone from work.
Slept with her yet?
That's harsh.
Wow. I thought you slept with
every woman you knew.
You're being absurd.
You slept with that woman, though.
Which woman would that be?
Ren!
How dare you... How dare you
sleep with someone like her?!
That was a long time ago.
You've already punished me
for it, too. You told me to leave.
You know I wouldn't live
in that house otherwise.
Yeah, right! You waltzed out of here
without even putting up a fight!
You wanted to go from the beginning!
You wanted to get away from here!
And from me!
That's why you slept with... with her...
Shigure, you like her more...
you want her...!
I care about you more than anyone.
That's an unwavering truth.
I... thought you forgot.
I never said I forgot.
Is that why you've been so irritable?
Why do you test me like that?!
I'm not testing you.
Don't you get it?
I only slept with her
because you slept with Kureno.
What the hell...?
What the hell?!
So it's my fault?!
I didn't do anything wrong!
Don't blame me!
Don't get the wrong idea, Kureno.
I love Akito.
I always have. I love her so much...
...that sometimes I want
to spoil her rotten...
I'm special!
The zodiac members are mine,
and I can do whatever I want with them!
It's my right!
...and sometimes I want
to crush her to a pulp.
If you don't get it, then let's not
talk about this anymore.
We're just repeating the same
discussion we always have.
Your mood is only getting worse.
I should go.
You deny your womanhood,
but you're always ready...
...to use it against me.
It's here.
Eternity is here.
I'm always thinking about you.
I missed you, before.
I'm here forever.
You just haven't noticed.
I was waiting that day...
...and I never stopped.
Isuzu Soma?
Yeah, she's in our class.
But she's on one of
her absent kicks again.
What?
I forget--is she in the hospital again?
Isn't she recuperating?
Oh, right! Someplace far away or whatever.
Your mind is a sieve.
I see... Thank you.
I don't see how Soma-san
can graduate on time.
Her family'll pay off the school.
So, do you think that girl
is Soma-san's friend?
She has friends?! No way!
You're so mean!
I've been waiting.
All this time...
...I've been right here waiting for you.
"I Hope It Snows Soon"
"I hope it snows soon."