"Ayame"
"Most Trusted" "Most Caring"
Manager?
Oh, there you are.
--Manager, what do you want for dinn--
--A question, Mine.
Yes?
If I remain cursed forever...
Will you leave me someday?
I'm the one who decides
what makes me happy.
Your Mine is not going anywhere.
She's crazy about you, Manager,
so she wants to be here forever.
Do you object?
"Shiraki Books"
What is that? You've been
looking at it a while.
Hmm? Oh. I was just thinking it might
be nice to take a trip somewhere.
A trip, eh?
That sounds good.
H-Hatori-kun, is there
someplace you want to go?
No.
President, I finished tallying everything.
President?
Thank you.
That was fast.
I worked harder than usual.
Machi.
If...
If I...
Hey, have you seen my brush?
You probably forgot it at home.
No way, I always have it with me!
Hey, Machi, have you seen it?
Not. At. All.
What about you, Yun-Yun?
Haven't seen it.
--I'm telling you,
you just left it at home.
--I have to tell her...
...that I'm not a normal human.
"Fruits Basket"
Is there some point to you
holing up in your room like this?
Do you think if you just stay there long
enough, you'll get the world you want?
That--
You're letting him leave?
I don't care anymore. He's a cold bastard.
If he doesn't want to be nice to me
when I'm suffering--really suffering--
then forget about him.
That way of thinking
won't get you anywhere.
Time will move on, and leave you behind.
So will people and emotions.
What? No way!
I'm serious! They--
Whoa, whoa, who was that?!
Come on, you know him. The Soma kid!
Wh-What?!
All by yourself? Wanna walk home together?
I'd be happy to, Momiji-kun!
He grew up! Like, all the way up!
I know, right?!
The ice cream and candy fiend...
The boy who ran around the school
with a bunny backpack...
--He's all grown up!
Oh, let's get some ice cream on the way!
--Huh?
Everyone still looks shocked
when they see me.
It's because you grew so fast,
and you're even more handsome now!
Really, I'm handsome? You mean it?
Yes, you're like a prince!
Great!
You know, I'm happy I got taller.
Don't get me wrong--being little was fun.
Plus, I could do stuff or get away with
stuff that I couldn't have otherwise...
But I'm a man, too, you know?
Oh, it's Yuki and Haru!
Yuki! Haru!
Are you on your way home?
Crazy sight, right?
Anyone would take them
for a doting couple.
Oh, Hatsuharu-san!
I'm so happy about Isuzu-san.
Oh, um, I just told Honda-san that
you found out her hospital address.
Ah, yeah. Thanks.
Me and Tohru are
on our way to get ice cream--
Hey! Let's buy a bunch and eat it
together at Shii-chan's house!
That sounds great!
Okay, then let's get
an ice cream cake, too!
An ice cream cake...?!
I guess she's never had one.
And it's definitely been classified
as a luxury item in her brain.
Uh... um!
Good... Good aft...!
Hey, you.
Could you stop intimidating Kisa?
I'm not intimidating her!
Where'd you even come from?!
I was in the bathroom.
Well, anybody who came home
to her just sitting there
--would wonder what was going on!
--U-Um!
--That's the issue here?
You should be nice to younger--
Eh, whatever. When's she coming home?
What's with that
"I'll let you win" attitude?
--U-Um!
--Anyway, did you two just barge in here?
Excuse me? Assuming we're
that rude makes you the ru--
Big Brother Shigure
was just leaving when we got here.
He said he was visiting the main estate.
Your attitude is pissing me off
more than the insults would.
Um!
G-Good afternoon!
Yeah. Good afternoon.
Well, she'll probably be home soon.
Hiro-chan!
I said hello!
Yeah, I saw.
He really is nice deep down, huh?
It seems like he's always nice
to Big Sister, after all.
Yeah...
Did you pick on Akito again today?
Don't you get tired of that?
Sheesh, why are you so mean?
I can't believe those are your
first words when you show up.
This is my house.
And it seems to me she gets more
withdrawn every time you visit her.
No way, really?!
Doesn't that seem, like, really bad?!
Knowing I'm the same age he is
makes me truly sad sometimes.
You're too old to be such a brat.
Akito is only digging in her heels
because you refuse to let on
what you're thinking.
Oh!
I'm doing that on purpose, though.
Yes, I'm aware.
How about you stop having a battle
of wills with someone younger than you?
Even to me, it sometimes looks
like you truly hate her.
Why not be a little nicer?
You say that,
but "kindness" from me is
a hastily manufactured afterthought.
It's not as good as
the real thing that you have.
For some reason I don't find it sad,
but I wonder why...
Like, I've never particularly
wanted a parent's love,
and frankly, it doesn't really
bother me that I'm possessed...
If this is what you call being
"twisted," then I must be twisted.
And the fact is,
I can't even find that sad...
Maybe that makes me very alone.
Maybe a person like me really
should have dreamed of...
But anyway, yeah! I'm not a nice person,
so it's a wash. You know?
You're going to give up
without trying, eh?
A generous kindness like yours, or a
detached kindness like Kureno-kun's...
Even assuming Akito wants that from me,
it's not going to happen.
I'm not looking to become her father.
We've got a crowd here.
What should we do for dinner?
Let's have a barbecue!
--Barbecue! Barbecue!
--Hiro, you two should call ahead
instead of just coming over.
--Barbecue! Barbecue!
--Hiro, you two should call ahead
instead of just coming over.
I do feel a little bad about that, but...
--If the person forced to make
dinner for us is fine with it,
--Kisa-san!
--If the person forced to make
dinner for us is fine with it,
I figure it's fine.
Hello, Honda-san?
Y-Yes, how may I help you?!
Welcome home.
Let's have a barbecue!
I can't imagine this house has
the equipment for barbecuing.
We're fine without equipment.
No, we're not.
But all we need is a fire
that can grill the meat, right?
Yeah.
Should burn well.
--What are you planning?!
It's what's for dinner.
Real food...
We'll get nowhere at this rate.
Let's go with curry.
Say, where is Kyo-kun?
He was here before,
so I think he's in his room.
Okay, I'll go get him!
You guys are gonna eat here, too?
It's okay, we settled on curry.
Whatever. You grew a lot, huh?
Right? Pretty soon, I might be
taller than you, and better-looking!
And then, and then...
Maybe Tohru will accept my proposal?
Do you get that if you give up,
something like that might happen?
So you shouldn't give up.
I'm gonna stop going "There's no point
in thinking about this," and giving up.
Wouldn't it sting if some
other guy took Tohru from you?
Well, look at the time!
We better go help make curry!
Come on!
It's a really strange feeling to come home
and see a soup kitchen in my yard.
--Welcome home!
Hello, children! Papa's home!
Yuki-nii, what's his deal?
He's just an idiot. Don't worry about it.
Shigure-san, if you haven't
eaten yet tonight, would...
Hi, Tohru-kun. How are you? Working hard?
Um, yes, I'm...
Maybe I really should have dreamed of you.
What?
Maybe a person like me
needs someone like you most...
...the author finds himself thinking.
Shigure-san?
I'm just playing what-ifs.
Right, I'll take a medium-large serving!
A-All right!
Tohru! Let's eat the ice cream now!
--All right!
--Time will begin marching on.
As will people and emotions.
So I want you to come soon, too.
Once upon a time, God told the animals:
"I invite you to the banquet
I shall hold tomorrow."
God in this story was you, Akito.
A special child... the chosen child.
Born to be loved.
There is no loneliness
or fear in your future.
There are only unchanging bonds.
You have been promised eternity.
No one will ever leave you--
Hatsuharu...
Don't go, Hatsuharu!
Hatsuharu!
Momiji...
Oh.
The end comes so suddenly...
Momiji...
Momiji.
Don't go.
Please.
Don't go away and leave me!
What was that?
What were all those feelings
watching me like guards
from some corner of my heart?
What about this person
could possibly tie me down?
Mo...
This person is so small,
and weak, and pitiful...
Momiji...
No. No, stop!
Those eyes... Don't look at me like that!
Don't...
You should go back to your room.
I'm sure you don't feel well.
You don't have to worry.
I won't tell anyone about this.
Go home. At least for tonight.
I'm a little confused right now, too.
I'll come talk to you tomorrow.
Hey. Have you seen Momiji today?
Huh? I haven't seen him.
Why, wasn't he in class?
He was. He came late, though.
Did something happen?
Nothing. But it's like...
Something's weird.
He's the same as always,
but something, somewhere, is different...
Good afternoon!
Honda-san.
Honda-san, have you seen Momiji?
Hmm? No, not today.
Is something the matter?
I wonder what's the matter...
Wha-What?! Wh-What in the world happened?!
Haru, behave.
Honda-san, it's okay. He was just asking.
U-Um, okay...
Kyo-kun!
What're you standing around here for?
Kyo, have you seen Momiji?
Why, something up with him?
No, nothing.
Then why ask?
Momiji?
Jeez, you're here of all places.
Tohru and them are inside
looking for you, so--
What?
Huh? Uh, nothing.
Is something different about you?
"My curse is broken."
Would it surprise you if I said that?
What? Listen, you--
Yours breaking would make Tohru
happier than mine breaking.
I'm sure she'd be happy.
You realize, don't you?
I'm the one this stings.
Shut up.
I don't wanna realize that.
It's too...
I'm sorry I sent you home alone yesterday.
I spent the whole day thinking.
Wondering why my curse
is gone... only mine.
I couldn't think of anything
that would cause it.
But I can say this:
Akito, I can't stay by your side
for rest of my life.
And you can't tie me down anymore.
Monster.
Traitor. Traitor!
If you leave here, leave me,
you've got no place to go!
Your mother and father won't just
welcome you back! No one will!
You'll never be happy!
I know.
I've become so free, and so lonely.
The curse breaking doesn't mean
I'll get the girl I want.
And the bonds that unconditionally
connected me to everyone are gone.
It's too late. I can't go back
to before things were broken.
Good morning.
Momiji-kun, is that you?
Good morning. Is this
your usual school route?
No, I thought I'd walk
a different way today.
Oh, I see.
You've grown so tall, Momiji-kun.
I hardly recognized you.
Has your daughter grown, too?
No, she's still a little kid.
We're going on a family trip
for summer break,
and she already can't contain herself!
Wow.
What about you?
Will your family take a trip, too?
Someplace far away.
Their happiness,
in a place where I'm not.
But...
But don't tell me that not having
those things means I can't be happy!
Don't just decide that!
I feel vulnerable being free,
but a happiness might exist for me!
It might be somewhere in the future,
waiting for me to catch up!
Yeah.
There'll be a trip.
With the family that I can
probably have someday.
A trip to the future.
To the world in motion.
I'm going to finally start walking...
...along my own life's path.
What about you?
How long will you stay here?
The person most afraid that
if they leave this place,
they'll have no home and no happiness...
Shut up.
Just shut up.
Get lost.
Okay.
Okay, I'll be going now.
All right. See you later!
Take care!
Will do!
"It Was So Foolish"
It was so foolish.