Even if the world doesn't need me,
I'll keep living for someone who does.
It works for me.
But my custody rights might've
been at risk for a while there!
"Custody"?
There was more craziness
after that, like moving,
but I think I bounced back
while I kept busy.
Tohru was there for me, after all!
Uh-huh...
Seriously, Tohru is so cute! Like,
cutest in the world--no, the universe!
But Katsuya Honda...
You don't want to go see him anymore?
I wonder how much time
and effort it'll take
for you kids to find your answers...
Those words sounded ridiculous to me.
Because I'd always felt like I was
only born to take other people's contempt,
and I only continued
living to hurt people.
And wasn't I right?
That's why she died...
That's why Mom died, isn't it?
Didn't she want to tell me
it was my fault, in the end?
And you, too. You smiled at me,
but don't you hate me now...?
It's not your fault, Kyo.
You did nothing wrong.
But you can't go outside.
Outside is full of bad things.
Come in the house with Mom, okay?
Let's live inside forever.
Do what your mother tells you.
I'll never forgive you.
I'll go in the house and wait for you.
You'd better get your butt inside.
Or else something
even scarier will happen.
Ta-da! This is... Tohru!
Thank you!
Are those shapes going to grill okay?
Not to worry! You can leave it to me!
Kyo! The food's almost ready!
Kyo?
Could he be asleep?
He'll show up eventually.
They showed up in my dream
to smack down that thought.
To remind me...
"Know your place. Don't fool yourself."
Because I thought maybe...
...just maybe...
...Tohru loved me back.
Stupid thought.
"Fruits Basket"
Did you slip away from your servant again
so that you can walk as you please?
Sometimes I need to go outside
and look for someone to talk to.
Right, Shigure?
That reminds me...
I hear you recruited Isuzu as
an errand girl to fetch a box for you.
You certainly have an ear to the ground.
Or perhaps she's just talkative?
Truly no good.
You're the no-good one, Ren-san.
I told you that was our secret.
Did you really?
To me, it sounded like
a suggestion to go get it from her.
Well, I'm offended.
But I'm afraid the operation failed.
This would be much easier
if you just brought it to me.
What? No, I don't want to do that.
It feels blasphemous somehow.
It is blasphemous.
No one but me has the right
to touch Akira-san.
His flesh, his blood, his soul...
I'm the only one worthy to own
anything to do with Akira-san.
I hear another marriage talk fell apart.
Can't they compromise? The doctor says
he's not long for this world anyway.
That's exactly why! I mean,
there has to be a successor.
True, no one wants "outsiders"
to fall heir to that money.
Akira-san and I met
because we were meant to.
It was destiny.
You must be so lonely,
and afraid of dying alone.
And no one else notices.
But I'm different. I see it.
Give me all of your pain, every last bit.
Because I love you.
Obviously this cannot be allowed!
You're a servant!
--We're in love.
--Silence!
Get out of here this instant.
--Never set foot on the Soma estate ag--
--Ren noticed that I was lonely.
She cried for me.
It was bliss.
Akira-san and I were
the only ones in the world.
I was the only one in Akira-san's world.
It was enough.
And yet...
Hey, they said Akito-san's
gonna be raised as a boy.
But why?
Apparently, Ren-san
decided on it a while ago,
because she said a female heir
could cause issues.
I heard she threw a fit and said
she'd abort unless everyone
considered him a boy.
She's just miffed that she's not
Akira-san's "number one" anymore.
And jealous, too.
Why won't you hold Akito, Ren?
Why bother? Everyone else
already loves that child, don't they?
Akito was born for them to love.
It's only natural.
Remember Ren-san's face that day
we went to meet Akito?
She thought, "Oh, crap."
Gure-nii... I don't get it.
Everything Gure-san says
is too complicated.
Does it mean Ren-san is bad?
It means she should be pitied.
All of the Somas should...
You poor thing.
Aren't you a "poor thing," too?
You're at Akito's mercy,
thanks to that antiquated "bonds" curse.
You don't really love
that child, you know.
You're just caught up in a fantasy.
Haven't you noticed?
You're looking at me
the same way you did then.
You want me.
Yes, I've noticed. Looking at you
gives me a rush of affection.
It lets me fantasize about whether she'd
look like you if she lived as a girl.
You're quite right.
I wanted you to take that box.
You're the right one to have it.
One person possessed by
Akira-san's ghost is enough.
--Shigure--
--Akito doesn't need that thing.
There's something wrong
with you--all of you!
Who do you suppose you have to thank
for that kid even being alive?!
Who do you think saved Akira-san?!
It's all because I was with him!
Akira-san...
Why...
Why didn't you call for me?
D-Did Akira-san die all alone?!
Quiet.
It was sudden.
There was no time to call for you.
And he was not alone at the end--
Akito-san was with him.
Akito-san safely carries
Akira-san's final wishes.
Excuse me?
--You're nothing! You're just a toy
for Akira-san to pass the time with!
--How dare you!
--You're nothing! You're just a toy
for Akira-san to pass the time with!
--How dare you!
--Now that Akira-san is gone,
you're officially unnecessary!
You're wrong.
I'm special.
I was promised eternity.
Everyone was waiting for me, too.
So I'm not unnecessary.
I know, because Father told me.
If you mock Father's words...
...then you're the unnecessary one.
Go ahead, believe that silly fantasy
of "bonds" and "eternity."
It's too stupid to last long anyway.
Eventually it'll fall apart,
and you can learn the hard way
that no one really wanted you!
Akira-san! Akira-san!
Akito? You're awake.
Mm-hmm.
I need to talk to you, Akito.
I was so happy when I met Yuki.
What?
I was the God, and he was the Rat
who stands at the top of the zodiac,
and those two roles
hadn't been reborn in so long.
Back then, I could still
show off in front of her.
Even when she said things
that hurt me, I could still...
Where did my world start to fall apart?
Yuki-kun left the estate
to go live with Shigure, I hear.
So, I take it that the Rat was
the second one to desert you?
Don't let your one-night stand
with Shigure go to your head.
I haven't been deserted.
Everyone comes back to me in the end.
Because we can't be separated.
That's the bond between us.
I'm sick of that line.
If you truly believe the zodiac
who get a taste of the outside world
will still come back to the gloomy "god"
who binds them hand and foot, then win.
Prove that nobody can break your
little dream and rub it in my face!
And if you lose...
Grovel to me and then get out.
I believed.
Akito-san, I'd like to let Kyo and...
one other person live at my house.
Would that be okay?
I believed I could win.
I believed no one could break this...
No. I wished--almost prayed.
I repeated it like a curse.
Like I'd die if I didn't say it.
I said basically the same words
over and over and over...
But it's no good anymore. They're leaving.
Leaving me behind.
Stop at once!
Someone stop her!
You know, when I woke up
this morning, my head was so clear.
I should've just done this to begin with.
Give back Akira-san!
I don't know what of Akira-san's you're
hiding here, but give it back! It's mine!
Everything of Akira-san's belongs to me!
I didn't want to lose to this woman.
I wanted to prove it however
I could and rub it in her face.
Because I...
If it you want it that badly,
I'll give you the stupid thing!
I always knew...
Don't worry, Akito.
I'm not leaving you behind.
Even if you can't see me,
I'll be by your side.
Special child...
Ren was the one I most wanted
to be happy about you...
As her man, all I could do was die...
...but at least I can leave her a child.
And our child being special
proves that Ren and I were special, right?
It's too bad we couldn't
reconcile... Ren...
You were magnificent, showing such
a dauntless attitude to that woman...
But... But the one Father loved
most wasn't me, it was--
No.
Akira-san loved you best, Akito-san.
You mustn't let yourself be fooled.
Didn't Akira-san say he'd be by your side?
You have this, and Akira-san
belongs to you alone.
Is there something inside?
Akira-san's...
...soul.
It's empty.
That's right, it's empty.
Always has been.
Because I'm the one
who's always been "Other."
Because this has been broken
from the beginning.
Hiro-chan! Hinata-chan!
Lunch is ready to--
--Hi--
--Sorry.
I'm in a complicated mood...
I wish I could just feel happy.
But I have all these mixed feelings
like anger, resentment, regret,
repentance, attachment...
Yeah.
You've lived your whole life
with those bonds, after all.
Goodbyes make us lonely.
It's no good anymore. They're really...
...falling apart.
Goodbyes keep coming.
--What's wrong?
Weren't you going to kill me?
--Ma'am!
--What's wrong?
Weren't you going to kill me?
Just shut up!
Why did you even bring a weapon in here?!
You're one to talk!
Your charge tried to kill his own parent!
And you gave him that silly box!
--The poor family head is so innocent
he believed in it, and now--
--Of course he doesn't believe in it!
--The poor family head is so innocent
he believed in it, and now--
I gave him that box to comfort him
when his heart was wasting away
after Akira-san's death!
It's like a charm.
Anyone with common sense
would know it was empty!
I told you, you mustn't give
such things to the family head!
Akito.
I was fifty-fifty.
I believed in that box,
and I didn't believe in it.
It was empty when I opened it.
But I thought, maybe there was
an invisible power.
Maybe... maybe...
So I couldn't get rid of it,
but I didn't want to look
into it anymore, so I hid it.
That's right.
I clung to it all these years.
Can you blame me?
That was my common sense!
Nobody taught me otherwise!
Nobody ever gave me
any other way to live than this one!
How am I supposed to know things
I don't know?!
How am I supposed to get it?!
Why--
You can start learning the things
you don't know or don't get now.
Let's change, Akito.
If you stay in this environment,
the Somas and the bonds will crush you.
You'll stay empty.
--So--
--Too late.
It's too late for you to say that.
"Change"? We're past that point.
Why didn't you say that in the beginning?
Why didn't you push me away
from the beginning?
Why didn't you abandon me?
--I know.
--You're changing your mind now?
I know.
I don't want that lecture now.
That "kindness" of yours that
only half-saves me or half-rejects me...
It's been killing me!
This whole time!
So take responsibility. Pay for it!
Atone with your death!
Wait--
Kureno-san!
What happened? You're bleeding!
--Never mind.
--What?!
Forget me, go after Akito. Fast!
Someone help!
It's too late now.
Now... after all this time...
Yeah, it's dead.
Ugh. I wonder if a cat
killed it or something?
Or it hit a windowpane.
You two finish cleaning yet?
Forget that, there's a dead bird out here!
Were you just tired?
Thank you.
You're welcome!
I'm going out for a bit.
Kyo-kun!
Please, there's...
something I'd like to tell you.
"I'm Disappointed in You"
I'm disappointed in you.