Good for you.
You must be happy you're such
good friends that she worries about you.
Good for you.
"Snap"
--Don't cry!
--Okay!
--I'm through with watching you
blubber like a wimp!
--She's happy. She's blushing. She's so happy.
--Haru.
--I'm through with watching you
blubber like a wimp! --She's happy. She's blushing. She's so happy.
I don't often hear you
shouting like that, Isuzu.
Shisho-san!
Did your friend's visit
put you in high spirits?
"Friend...?"
F-Friend...
They get along so well.
--Yep.
--But violence is still wrong!
Will she be recuperating here for a while?
Yes. She doesn't like the idea
of a hospital or the main estate.
She was locked up, wasn't she? By Akito.
She says she doesn't
want us to tell Honda-san.
And she's scared of having
anything more to do with Akito.
I don't want Akito
involved with her, either.
Okay.
By the way, Hatsuharu.
Where was Isuzu being held?
The Cat's place.
I see.
She was where Kyo is going.
"Fruits Basket"
I kinda think Shisho's just gonna
let Isuzu move in with him.
Don't worry, Kyo-kun,
you're his one and only!
He lives for you!
I'm not worried about it,
so no more weird phrasing!
Anyway, I figure it's a good thing.
The livelier his house,
the less lonely he'll get.
Honda-san?
Er, yes?
The anniversary of your
mom's death is coming up, right?
Can I come with you to the graveyard?
Yes, of course!
I'm going on Saturday morning with
Uo-chan and Hana-chan, so I'd love--
I... can't go with you.
Okay.
Bad luck for you, huh?
Not only did you not find
a way to break the curse,
I hear something
pretty bad happened to you.
Learn any lessons about recklessness?
Ren-san was going to tell me the way.
Yeah, about that...
She lied.
Ren-san doesn't know the way.
Smart money says she was using you
as a pawn in her feud with Akito-san.
And you just fell for it.
You're lying.
I won't tell you to trust me.
But I know Ren-san better
than you do. We're close.
Very close.
You know what?
The zodiac curse will break
on its own, eventually.
You don't have to work yourself
to death over it.
Those ties from ages past
are already fraying.
We'll be free eventually.
We're the generation
invited to the final banquet.
D-Don't just make stuff up!
When is "eventually"?
Is it years or decades from now?
That's not good enough.
It has to... It has to
break by next spring, or...
Kyo-kun will...!
Shigure-san, did you know
all along that it would break?
Nah, of course not.
But I did sense that
we might be at the end.
From what I hear,
this is the first time the whole zodiac
has been alive at once.
So the attendants were excited about it,
saying it was amazing.
But I thought something else:
"What if it's just that this is
the last banquet, so we're all attending?"
And then, what do you know,
Kureno-kun's curse broke without
him or anyone else even trying.
What?
--Wh-What does...
--I'll put it in kindergarten terms.
Kureno-kun isn't one of us anymore.
And he said it, too.
He thinks the end is near.
That tiny changes and catalysts build up,
and the whole thing moves.
Of course, as things stand,
Kyo-kun will still be locked up.
Yes, we know.
All of us know exactly what will
happen to him, in the very near future.
But we won't do or say anything.
Why not?
Because that's the Cat's role.
We zodiac members are monsters.
But when we look at him, we can think...
"Thank god, at least I'm not him."
The Cat is a gift to us:
an Other creature for us to exclude.
And Kyo knows that--
Shigure-san!
Mad at me?
But that will end, too, eventually.
It's not that I believe
Kureno-kun's story without question.
But it matches what my gut tells me.
You said "eventually" isn't good enough.
Do you want to save Kyo?
Is Kyo your--
Is Kyo her...?
What is it that's most precious to you?
That question...
I should've answered "my mother"
without even thinking, but I couldn't.
What came to mind instead was...
Why?
I swore to myself so firmly that day...
Tohru-san, is there anything
else you need to pack?
I could feel her disappearing.
She'd been there so recently, but...
She was sitting there
and smiling like always, but...
...I could feel her slowly disappearing.
Let's go, Kyoko-san.
So I swore to myself that
I'd always put Mom first in my heart.
I believed that if I kept
loving her first, they'd never fade.
Not my memories, and not our promise.
"Always together."
Because if I didn't
believe in that, I'd collapse.
And yet...
This is so wrong, but...
She's going away... far, far away.
Tohru?
Why are you crying?
I...
I... don't know what to do!
At times like that,
you should just do nothing.
It's fine to wait till you think,
"I gotta do something," before you act.
Probably.
Until then, well...
Go on and cry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I want to stay here just a little longer.
Because, eventually, I really will
have to do something...
...and I think maybe I know what
I'll let go of when the time comes.
Oh, my!
You're that boy...
I remember your orange hair!
Tohru's grandpa?
That's right.
Kyoko-san... I mean, Tohru-san.
Tohru-san lives with you.
Why are you sitting here, Gramps?
Oh, it's nothing.
I just strained my back again.
What?! Are you okay?!
I'm just waiting for my ride.
"Honda Family"
Did you come to visit
Kyoko-san's grave, too?
Thank you.
Is Kyoko--I mean, is Tohru-san doing well?
Do you always call her "Kyoko"?
Hmm? Yes, I do.
Isn't that a little messed-up?
Yes, it is. But you see...
I wanted to keep her alive.
I wanted to show her proof that
Kyoko-san existed, in any way I could.
Because she looked ready
to break forever without that.
Do you know why Tohru-san
talks the way she does?
No, I don't...
Apparently, she's copying
Katsuya--that's her father.
During Katsuya's funeral, some
no-good relatives said no-good things.
"She doesn't look a bit like Katsuya."
"Are we sure she's his?"
And, "She'll be no comfort at all."
She was so young, maybe they thought
they could say what they wanted
and she wouldn't understand.
Idiots. Children absolutely
understand what adults say.
Playing hide-and-seek, Kagura?
Shh! Pretend I'm not here, please!
I hope I'm not intruding.
Hello, come in.
Have you come to see Isuzu?
Yes, I'm on my way home
from my graveyard... visit...
Please, sit down and enjoy yourself.
Well? Are you avoiding her
because you had a fight?
It's nothing that simple.
I don't know how to face her,
and I can't get over it yet.
I know it'll show on my face.
I know I'll feel like the loser.
--And what upsets me most
is recognizing that about myself!
--Yes, that does sound complicated.
--And what upsets me most
is recognizing that about myself!
If she'd just get together with
Kyo-kun already, I could stop wavering!
She does love Kyo?
Why wouldn't she?
That's not even a question!
And anyway, I know he loves her!
Shihan? Aren't you happy?
I'm worried, that's all.
I hope she loves Kyo for who he is.
That it's not just compassion or pity...
So. Why did you come today?
Well, er, last time, I rudely ran away,
and it's been several days...
I don't mind that. But why Kyo?
Of all people... He's the Cat, you know.
Do you pity him?
The previous Cat had
a companion, you know.
It was the woman in charge
of looking after him.
She conceived his child.
She was at his deathbed.
One day, someone asked her, "How were
you able to do so much for the Cat?"
Wouldn't you feel sorry
for the poor thing?
Perhaps that's a lovely sentiment.
And perhaps it was
much better for my grandfather
than spending his days alone.
And yet...
Can this cruel, greedy
feeling really be pity?
I mean, when I say I want to protect
or free the zodiac members...
Those are just excuses!
I'm hiding my true feelings
and tricking you...
I'm a coward.
I...
I put my mother first
in my heart, but now...
I just want Kyo-kun!
I just don't want the curse,
the Somas, or anyone else
to take Kyo-kun from me!
Because Kyo-kun is what's
most precious to me!
You tell stuff like that to him!
Tohru-san took it to heart.
Katsuya was dead, and anyone could see
Kyoko-san was wasting away.
Dad went someplace far away, right?
Is Mom going there, too?
She seems sick. She doesn't talk to me.
Is she sad because I don't look like Dad?
If I turn exactly like Dad,
will she get better?
Will she stay and not leave?
Later, there was an incident
where Kyoko-san was away
from home for a long time.
That's when it started.
She copied Katsuya and...
She never finished that sentence,
but I finally know the end.
Just once, I looked in on her
because Kyoko was worried about
leaving her alone all night for work.
The Tohru I saw that night,
sitting all alone...
If that's who Tohru really is...
I remember.
She was so lonely.
I-I didn't think you were home!
Yeah. You came home early too, huh?
Yes, I heard that
it would rain this evening.
But it looks like I worried for nothing!
Hey.
What did your dad look like?
You told me you didn't remember
too clearly, but do you look alike?
W-Well, not our faces...
B-But, um, people say my polite
way of speaking is a lot like his!
Even Mom said it was... very similar...
Oh.
That probably made her happy.
I... lied. I'm not like him at all.
I'm just copying him,
because I'm not like him.
Th-The truth is... I thought of
my dad as a bad guy.
Even though I remember his kindness,
and the things he gave me.
I really do remember them, but...
But...
...I thought he might
take Mom away with him.
So I wanted to make her notice me,
and stay with me...
I wanted to keep her alive.
I didn't want her to leave me behind.
I'd do anything to feel safe, because...
I just made my dad a bad guy, because...
I'd let go of any promise out of
my own selfishness, because...
...I'm awful.
It was so foolish.
She must've thought hard about it.
She didn't want her mom to go
and leave her behind, so she thought hard.
She chased the image of
her father in her memories.
And the answer she came up with was...
"W-Welcome home."
"Did you enjoy yourself?"
"I'm glad to hear it."
--It was off the mark, it was ridiculous,
but it was what she had.
--"Oh, I see."
--It was off the mark, it was ridiculous,
but it was what she had.
--"Yes, that's fine."
--It was off the mark, it was ridiculous,
but it was what she had.
It was so foolish.
Watching her stubbornly keep at it...
Watching her do her best
to hide her loneliness...
Seeing her torture herself like that...
It was so foolish...
and it tugged at my heart.
I'm sure your mom knew all that.
But it still helped her. It did.
I hope that's true.
It is. Believe it.
I'm sorry for suddenly
acting so discouraged--
It's fine. Say whatever
you need, it's fine.
I won't be disappointed in you.
I refuse to apologize. Tohru-kun and I
communicated with our fists.
She never hit you.
I envy people who can entrust
their dreams and wishes to others.
I wonder if I can do it, too.
Because that definitely wasn't pity.
I'm not lying! I can leave this to her!
Ridiculous.
This side of you is annoying.
Comfort me!
This man is my father.
So you kept a photo? That's very you.
Tell that to him!
Ky--
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I remember.
I put this away, but...
I'll never forgive you.
Kyo-kun...?
Is something the matter, Kyo-kun?!
--Kyo-kun? Kyu-kun?
--Now I remember.
Kyo-kun?!
I'll never forgive you.
"That's Right, It's Empty"
That's right, it's empty.