--That concludes homeroom for today.
--This isn't fair--it's almost spring.
And yet it's snowing.
I don't want snow to pile up.
A clean field of white snow,
all undisturbed and perfect...
I hate that.
"Fruits Basket"
Not much time left
until graduation, huh...
Huh? You're not graduating, though, Nao.
Honestly, what a pain!
You're late!
Only because another senior asked me out!
Don't you think it's selfish
to confess love to someone
you know you have no chance with?
I'm sure they get closure from it
or whatever, and a pity party, but still!
I bet you've had lots of trouble with
that lately too, right, Yun-Yun?
All I can do is hurt them.
Your guilt sounds
karmically appropriate to me.
You hurt people, after all.
Aw, shorty, are you jealous of Yuki
for being more popular? Eh, shorty?
Enough with the "shorty"!
I know I'm a shorty, okay?!
Yeah, I'm still shorter than my sister!
Is that so wrong?
Do shorties have no right to live?!
Uh, I didn't say anything...
Are you implying that height
is what makes a man attractive?!
Not at all, Nao-chan!
It's not his height or his face.
What makes a guy attractive...
...is his bank account.
True facts.
Argh! Fine, I know, I'm a commoner guy
with commoner parents!
I'll never have a Soma-level bank account!
Listen, that's Soma money,
not my personal money, okay?
I get it!
You have a crush on someone, don't you?
And that person is pining after Yun-Yun,
so you're jealous!
Oh, hey, Nao, didn't you
call Yun-Yun your rival once?
I remember that...
I'm right, aren't I, Nao-chan?!
Is she right, Nao-chan?
Just forget it! Isn't Kuragi here yet?!
Aha! Suspicious!
I think Kuragi-san will be a while.
She's still cleaning up chalk.
When will she get sick of stunts
like that? It's so annoying.
Oi, you can't just wander in here.
Are you two in Machi's class?
Yes!
Listen to this, President!
Kuragi-san just flipped over
a new box of chalk and dumped it out!
Again?
She's really scary!
I heard she got kicked out of her house
for trying to kill her own brother!
What? I didn't know that! Tell me more!
It's kind of a recent rumor.
But I hear it's true!
It's a lie! I'll always believe in Machi!
I'll never believe
the words you just said.
Kuragi-san?
--Machi...
--She ran away!
See, it must be true.
Oh no...
I believed in you!
What, you're done believing now?!
Kimi's faith is fickle.
Don't make excuses!
You were jealous of the baby all along!
I worried that might be the case.
Let's try living apart.
It's better for you.
Yes. It's for you.
You'll be more comfortable alone.
About what they said...
it's actually pretty close to the truth.
Machi has a little brother.
I mean, he's my half-brother too.
He's way younger.
These days, he's all set
to be the successor,
but apparently Machi was jealous,
she tried to kill him, and they found out.
They set her up with her own place
because she was dangerous.
That's hard for me to believe.
Well, it's the version I heard from
the parentals, so you may be right.
--Wanna ask Machi?
--What?
You can go to Machi's place
and just ask her.
What?!
Are you-- No, I can't! She lives alone!
You'll be fine! No guy could get
an erection in that room.
Don't make this about that!
Come to think of it, there was
this one time we got a ton of snow--
Can you stop giving me whiplash
with all the subject changes?
But I just remembered.
Anyway, there was some
family gathering that day.
I snuck out because
they were all being lame.
Machi was outside already.
I watched her,
wondering what she was up to.
She was walking around
leaving footprints in the snow.
She was super intent on it.
Just round and round. Dead silent.
I wonder what that was about.
Hiya!
Sorry to barge in!
--Hey!
--Come right in, Yun-Yun! Don't be shy!
Oi, Kake...
...ru?
It's as messy as always.
Go home!
This brings back memories...
It's the Sea of Decay.
Go home!
Yun-Yun!
Here, for you.
What?
This is my fault?!
Got any better stuff?
Okay, I'm off to take out the trash.
"←Yun."
"Machi. →"
Don't do anything pervy, Yun-Yun!
I won't. I'm not you.
Did you come... all this way... to clean?
No, um...
But glass on the floor
is dangerous, you know?
Are you sure you didn't come to ask
about what my classmates said?
Do what you want.
Believe them or don't.
I don't care.
My parents didn't believe me.
No one believed me.
I'm past trying to set
the record straight.
It doesn't matter now.
Machi, do orderly things bother you?
Stuff like undisturbed snow or tidy rooms.
Is it "perfection" that you hate?
Y-Yes...
Because it scares me.
Be perfect. Always.
Have a perfect personality
and perfect grades!
Otherwise, you can't beat
that other woman's son.
I was... I was always nervous.
If I had even the tiniest flaw,
she'd be angry at me.
It felt like she was telling me
to stand still on a thin, thin tightrope.
It intimidates me. I... can't breathe...
I can't stand it.
For a while, I tried my best to meet
their expectations anyway. But...
But now... I have
a little brother, so I...
Thank goodness we finally
got the boy we wanted!
I can't tell you how relieved I am.
Frankly, Machi's a bit... well, you know.
It's like she's got no individuality.
She's boring.
I guess good grades
aren't everything, are they?
Why?
Why would you say that?
Am I boring?
I did what you told me to, though.
I thought I worked so hard for you.
Don't talk like it's my fault.
You make it sound like
I did something wrong.
Well, maybe it is my fault, though.
Maybe I raised you wrong.
No...
That's not what I wanted you to say.
That's not it.
What am I supposed to do with that?
What am I supposed to do
if I'm something you got wrong?!
Where can I go?
You've worked hard.
You worked really hard to be
the Machi you are now,
and I'm glad you're here.
You did good.
I... never thought someone
would compliment me.
I never dreamed this day would come.
I'm flawed. Warped. No good.
But...
Someone complimented me anyway.
I-I...
I worried it was too cold.
That he'd catch a cold.
So I was putting a blanket
on him, that's all...
What are you doing?!
I wasn't trying to do anything bad...
But...
Don't make excuses!
I worried that might be the case.
I couldn't make them understand.
They'd already decided how I felt.
I wasn't jealous, though!
Okay.
Machi. If this snow piles up...
...let's make footprints in it together.
It's a promise.
Sorry! I'm so sorry!
Crap! You were totally
about to kiss, weren't you?!
What?! You moron!
I should've silenced my phone!
But the snow didn't stick.
It melted overnight and disappeared.
Anyone else have an opinion?
--All right, please proceed
with that plan.
--Hey, Kimi-chan.
--All right, please proceed
with that plan.
I got a new box for you.
Wow, really? I'm so happy!
But I'm not on chalkboard duty today.
Aw, man!
...instructions, and enter quickly
when it's their turn.
Next announcement: the club activity
time limits over spring break
have been revised.
--The hard end time was originally 6pm,
but now it's 5:30pm.
--The next time it snows...
--The hard end time was originally 6pm,
but now it's 5:30pm.
...will he still remember his promise?
Will he walk with me?
I hope it snows soon.
That was the first time I ever
I wished for it to snow,
and for the snow to stay.
Kyo-kun, here you go!
R-Right...
Thanks.
"Graduation Ceremony"
I guess there's only one year left
in our high school era.
Time certainly flies.
You guys work, too!
'Scuse me?! Have you forgotten you
owe me for getting those flowers back?!
I told you, that wasn't my fault!
Watch out!
Tohru!
--Are you okay?
--Y-Yuki-kun...
Bastard.
Kyon! If anything happens to Tohru...
...we'll never forgive you.
You two started it!
I was only checking in. See you later.
Are you going back to the student council?
No, I have an appointment.
Once I graduate,
there'll be no place for me
at this school anymore.
The familiar old hallways,
shoe boxes, and classrooms
will become someone else's home.
That's what graduation means.
That's what parting means.
But...
I'm sorry I kept you waiting.
Oh, no, I'm just happy that you came!
Well, I should get right down to it...
I-I apologize; now that this moment
has come, I'm not sure what to say.
H-How awful of me.
I-I'm glad that I met you, Yuki.
I'm glad that I came to this high school.
Every day was busy, like a festival.
I got angry, I laughed,
and I caused a lot of trouble, too.
And you were always at the center of it.
I loved you.
I loved you, Yuki.
So...
So I'm praying!
Praying that you'll... that you'll find
your happiness too, Yuki.
And that if you're already happy,
you'll find even greater happiness.
I'm sure that what I experienced
here was happiness,
and so you're the one who gave it to me.
I can't give it back to you
in any other way, but...
Thank you.
Please, let him understand.
I'm not doing this to try
to make him return my feelings.
I just want to let him
know that I was happy.
Because it was fun.
Because I really am glad I met him. So...
Let him understand.
I don't deserve feelings
like those, but...
...yes.
Yes. Thank you very much.
But I--
H-Hold that thought, Yuki!
I feel quite good right now.
But you'll spoil that if you apologize.
If you apologize, I'll cry!
And these things
might be fairer than we think.
For all we know, someone might have
been pining for me all along, too--
Like former president Takei?
He is out of the question!
Honestly, Yuki, you're so...
Thank you.
"Graduation Ceremony"
We owe so much
to the kindness of our teachers
"Kaibara High School Graduation Ceremony"
Our school years have gone by so quickly
Turned into months and years
before we knew it
Now is the time of our parting
Farewell
Are you sad to leave?
You found me. I'm sorry, I wanted
to take one last look at the classroom.
I'll go now.
M-Minagawa-sempai!
Minagawa-sempai, I-I... I...
I a-always... always...
After partings come
new meetings, okay?!
After "goodbye" comes "nice to meet you"!
So...
So I'm praying that,
even after you graduate,
you'll be well and keep smiling.
Sakuragi-kun, you, too.
Be well.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Nice to meet you.
Hiro-chan, your name means
"a light on the path,"
so I named her
Hinata for "sunshine."
"Name: Hinata"
Cute, right?
Hinata-chan, this is your big brother!
He'll start middle school soon.
Come on, Hiro-chan, give her a hug.
Now's your chance!
What?! N-No, I can't hug her.
Hinata's a girl!
I've got it covered.
Mama's gonna hug you both!
"Graduation Album"
Isuzu ended up graduating
while she was still in the hospital.
My, my. And so you went
to pick up her diploma for her?
You're so nice, Kagura.
Compliments from you are meaningless.
Hey...
Is Isuzu really in the hospital?
That's what I'm told.
But nobody I've asked knows
which hospital, and she won't answer--
Kagura.
I bet your mom's advice
was not to investigate, right?
Yeah, but... somehow it feels
like she won't come back.
I'm worried.
"I'm... Home"
I'm... home.