Akito...
I'll leave some water here.
Kureno.
Do you know what this is?
No.
That's right; you wouldn't know.
What's in that box?
Father.
Yes! My husband and I and Hiro-chan
are all thrilled that it's a girl!
Hinata-chan is the family celebrity!
Shouldn't you be with her?
It's fine! Hiro-chan is staying with her.
He's already right at home
in the big brother role.
Hinata-chan might end up idolizing him!
Say, when do you think Isuzu-chan
will get released from the hospital?
Who knows...
It seems like she's in
for a long time this round.
I wanted her to see Hinata-chan...
But I hear she didn't even get
to go to her graduation.
Oh, dear.
Haru!
I heard Rin is in the hospital.
Has anyone told you her condition,
or which hospital?
Why?
Well, Honda-san is worried.
Worried? About Rin?
Yeah, they're pretty close these days.
So Rin made a friend...
Yeah... But I'm asking because
Honda-san looked uneasy.
Oh. I dunno, though.
Wait, you don't know?
Nope. Seems like nobody knows the details.
The plot thickens...
Hey, this isn't some mystery nov--
Haru, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Eh... Yeah. I guess
normally, I'd panic more.
Maybe something's wrong with me.
Maybe something's been wrong with me.
Haru...
If I learn anything, I'll tell you.
Tell Honda-san "thank you."
If it all goes wrong... comfort her.
Hiro-chan!
Kisa! You've been home already?
Yep! Now I'm on my way to your house.
What about you?
You're still in your uniform.
Yeah, I stopped by Kagura-nee's house.
I wanted to see if Rin was back.
Oh... I see...
She's not back yet, though.
You're coming to visit Hinata, right?
Mm-hmm!
I guess it's too soon for her to start
expressing her feelings well,
but I hope she'll smile soon.
I bet by then, you'll be
an even better big brother.
We'll see.
But... yeah. I want to be.
When I look at Hinata,
I realize I'm pretty stupid.
It's like, here's this person who doesn't
even know good from bad yet,
and just is the way she is.
Whereas I'm always wrapped up my vanity,
my fear... I'm so small and stupid.
I want to become someone
who can protect her.
That hits me when I see her.
So... well, that's not exactly why, but...
I have to tell you something.
Kisa, I wanted to apol--
Oops. Sorry.
Seriously, you're the size of a house,
so can't you be a little more
considerate of your surroundings?
Eh...
You two got taller.
Never mind.
Be careful on your walk.
You be careful! And if you're
looking for Rin, she's not back yet.
But maybe that's not my business.
Hey, Hiro.
Was Rin sad?
Was she hurt?
Huh? Wait, are you talking about
that time I said...?
No, I just said that because
I was in a bad mood!
But...
I do know that she was suffering.
Haru-nii...
Akito pushed Rin off
the second floor balcony.
Those injuries...
they weren't an accident.
Akito found out about her and you.
And then... and then...
What are you doing?
K-Kureno-san...
Y-You shouldn't be here. It's off-limits.
Then why are you bringing food here?
Only the Cat is allowed in this cottage.
No one else can go inside,
and normally, no one wants to.
Who's in there?
I-I can't say. I'll get in trouble.
Trouble with whom?
I can't say!
M-My father is in indebted to...
If I f-fall out of favor...
Akito...
When Akito...
Kisa.
When Akito hit you...
...that was my fault.
What?
I've always wanted
to apologize to you for that.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry to you too, Haru-nii.
Akito and Rin both told me
to keep my mouth shut.
It's okay if you're mad that I did.
Rin is trying to break the curse!
Rin is trying to free you...
from Akito and from herself.
That's why she left you.
Give me the key.
You can say I overpowered you.
This isn't right, you know.
She... She hasn't eaten for days.
She'll die at this rate!
Save her.
Tell her she can stop now.
Or she's gonna be messed up forever.
She'll just suffer alone forever!
Haru-nii?
Hiro-chan, you felt guilty
that I was hurt? All this time?
Even when I was smiling...
...you were hurting inside?
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
I'm so selfish, I never even noticed!
Wh-Why are you apologizing?!
That's not right!
I'm the one...
It was my fault...
You can stop now.
Hey, Hiro-chan, where do
you think Big Sister Isuzu is?
I don't know. But...
...I just hope she comes back healthy.
What's this about?
Hatsuharu-san! You may be a zodiac member,
but you have no right to barge in here!
Shut up. Get out of here, hag.
--How rude!
--It's fine.
It would seem Hatsuharu has
something important to speak to me about.
Very well.
Now, go right ahea--
Why did you push Rin?
Why the hell did you push her?
What are you talking about?
Me? Push Isuzu? First I've heard of it.
Who told you that story?
An oracle.
Excuse me?
You're always such a silly boy.
Enough laughing.
Why did you do it?
Were you trying to kill her?
Huh. So, you believe in oracles,
but you don't believe in me, your god.
Why would you get so angry
about Isuzu in the first place?
You've always been
kind to her, haven't you?
Is it because you feel sorry for her?
Is it pity?
It's because I love her!
And you've known that for a long time,
so don't ask just to provoke me!
Where's Rin?
You know where she is
right now, don't you?
What a worthless conversation.
Where do you get these ideas?
You've always treated Rin coldly.
You're always been
cold to her... to all girls.
You say and do cruel things
without even blinking.
If you're supposed to be "god,"
then be more--
So, you knew exactly what I was like
when you told me, "I love Rin."
You knew I hated Isuzu,
and you said it anyway.
Where is she?
Where is Rin right now?
I don't know. Stop asking.
Where did you put her?!
I said I don't know where she is!
--Stop making me
the bad guy behind every--
--We sent her to the hospital.
--Stop making me
the bad guy behind every--
Hatori-niisan took her in his car.
She wasn't fully conscious,
but don't worry.
I'm told her life isn't at risk.
Akito. You mustn't do things like that.
No matter who you are, there are
some things you just shouldn't do.
Where was she?
The Cat's...
She was locked up in the Cat's place.
You're mean. Why would
you betray me, Kureno?
Akito, it's not like that. Listen.
You're cruel!
Cut the bullshit, you little bastard!
--You lie and lie,
and he's the cruel one?!
--Hatsuharu!
--You lie and lie,
and he's the cruel one?!
Were you trying to kill her again?!
So what if I was?
It's only because you chose that girl.
You're the one who dug her grave!
Hatsuharu!
Rin.
Rin, what's wrong?
Another nightmare?
Yeah. But I'm fine.
You're here, so it's fine.
That's right. I knew.
I knew our love
might be digging Rin's grave.
I knew which direction Akito's obsession
and anger would turn in.
Deep down, I realized.
But I wanted her. Wanted to make her mine.
Even more than I wanted to protect her,
I just wanted her all to myself.
You're here, so it's fine.
It's not fine.
I'm no different than those adults.
Me being with you doesn't make it fine.
If Rin was secretly hurting
while I stuck my head in the sand...
Then it doesn't matter how much
I think I love her. It's worthless.
H-Hatsuharu...
Don't talk.
It makes me want to kill you and myself.
H-Hatsuharu...
Wait. Don't go.
Don't go, Hatsuharu!
Hatsuharu!
Hatsuharu.
Go. Don't come back.
I'm sure Isuzu wants to see you.
The first word she said...
...was your name.
Haru.
Akito...
Why does everyone want to betray me?
It's not that they want to betray you.
But everyone eventually--
Why do you betray me?!
Why? Why?!
I was born to be loved!
You were all waiting for me.
I know because... he told me...
Father... Father, help me...
Help me.
I can't find...
I'm coming in, Isuzu.
...a home to go to.
Why did you do such a thing?
Did you not realize
that taking her away without permission
was a betrayal of Akito-san?
You think I should have left her there?
Yes. Anything Akito-san wishes.
No. You're wrong--
You are the one in the wrong!
You zodiac members live for Akito-san,
and yet you commit this betrayal?
Whose side are you on?
Do you think she should win, then?!
That... That abominable, dissolute woman?
Know your place, Kureno-san.
You zodiac should merely
live and die for Akito-san.
Remember that without Akito-san,
all of you are monsters,
no better than the Cat!
Kureno...
That's right, I first came here
to see Kureno.
She was crying, and it pissed me off.
So I decided to grill him.
I planned to grab him by the collar
and punch him. And then...
Isuzu-chan, you naughty girl.
Did you sneak all the way in here?
You've been looking for something,
haven't you, Isuzu-chan?
Would you like my help?
Ren-san, do you know a way
to break the zodiac curse?
--You kn--
--If you grant my wish, I'll tell you.
What I want--
what should rightfully be mine--
is in Akito's room.
I can't get close to that room.
But perhaps you could.
Akito wouldn't have the guts
to tuck it away out of reach.
It'll be hidden by
nothing more than a door.
What... is it?
A treasure.
If I give her this, I'll learn the way.
I can free him... I can free Haru.
Oh, right.
I get it now.
Akito is like Mama, when Mama is mad.
I don't want to see your face,
or the rest of you, ever again.
I'll give you a choice:
You go into exile,
or Hatsuharu loses his eyesight.
Want to test me to see if I'm bluffing?
Don't. Don't do that.
I'll stay here.
I'll stay here till I die.
Haru, I'm sorry.
It was my chance
to learn the secret, but...
I'm no good. Just, no good.
I can't do a single thing right.
No wonder I'm not needed.
My, my, so that's what happened
to Isuzu-chan?
No wonder my wish showed
no signs of being granted.
Do you really know a way
to break the curse, though, Ma'am?
What?
Don't be silly. How would I know that?
That's what I thought.
I've always disliked her. Viscerally.
Still, I did think she'd be
a bit more useful...
But no good children are no good.
I'm here after all.
Was that all a dream?
I wish at least my last dream
were of Haru...
I want to dream of being
spoiled by his kindness.
Can't I have that, if I'm dying?
Haru?
It's Haru. I'm really dreaming of him!
I'm sorry. I couldn't do it.
I couldn't find your happiness.
I couldn't... find it...
I'm sorry!
That means your journey
is over, right Rin?
Yeah.
Then welcome home.
If your journey is over, I need you
to come home to me. Or I'll be lonely.
Haru is kind.
Well, in that case,
I'd better come home.
If I can go home to Haru,
then I'm glad. Truly.
'S a good dream.
It's not a dream.
I've been searching hard.
Everyone's worried about you.
I'm impressed you walked this far so sick.
H-Haru! I can walk by myself.
Nope.
I'm still a dumb kid,
and I thought I was worthless for
not noticing you were hurting, but...
I've grown up a little since then.
At least enough that I can carry you.
So I won't give up on you, Rin.
Walk when you can,
and let me carry you when you can't.
I'm going to carry you.
You're not a burden.
You're really not a burden.
The end... of a long journey...
H-Haru?
Yeah.
Haru...?
I'm... home.
Welcome home.
"I Mean... You Know, Right?"
I mean... you know, right?