"I'll hold another banquet."
"I'll hold banquet after banquet,
forever unchanging..."
"I may be lonely right now..."
"...but everyone is waiting for me
on the other side of that promise."
That was in the long-distant past...
The original memory,
forgotten by everyone.
The original promise.
I'll see you soon.
Soon.
"Fruits Basket"
A girl?
Akito-san is... a girl?
Is that really true?
It's true.
It's the biggest of
the Somas' many secrets.
But Akito-san behaves like a man...
And none of the others
ever treat him like... a girl...
I never dreamed she was a girl.
Akito's been raised as male since birth.
She decreed it.
Who?
Someone who almost saw you
at the main estate.
Hatori!
What are you doing? Get away!
How many times must I
tell you to keep your distance?!
Akito, it's not like that.
She was only saying hello.
That's right, I was only saying
hello to Hatori. Is that so wrong?
You leer at any zodiac man you see.
What are you even doing here?
Go back to your room!
She rarely leaves her room. She has
some... troubles, mentally and physically.
But she still looms larger
than most in Akito's mind.
Ren Soma.
Akito's mother.
She's the one who decided
to raise her daughter as male.
Neither Akito nor Ren-san
will comment on it.
All I know for certain...
...is that they hate each other.
If you don't speak more nicely
to the zodiac members,
they won't like you anymore, Akito-san.
Hatori, you poor thing.
Hatori isn't a "poor thing"!
We have a bond. We're connected
in a world that you can't reach.
You're still spouting that nonsense?
You little fool.
How many times must I tell you
that those "bonds" aren't real love?
That "eternally unchanging"
concept you cherish so much is fake.
It's just a fantasy.
I pity the zodiac members
who have to put up with it.
Akito!
Oh yeah? How about you tell me
what's "real," then?!
Parental love?
--It's not like that's perfect!
--Akito! Akito, stop!
--Lots of parents abandon their children--
including plenty of Soma parents!
--Akito!
--Lots of parents abandon their children--
including plenty of Soma parents!
--Ma'am!
--Just like you did!
You can't define what's real or fake,
what's a false image or an idol!
No one can!
No one has the right to deny
the bond between me
and the zodiac, or our eternity!
The real thing exists!
Akira-san and me...
Akira-san and me have a real bond.
I'll kill you.
--I'll kill you!
--Go right ahead!
When I die, my soul will go
to Heaven and be with Akira-san.
I don't need you!
Akito, you were born to be loved.
Everyone was waiting for you.
Ren-san says the ties that bind Akito
and the zodiac members are wrong.
She says they're unnatural. Not real.
So she's constantly clashing with Akito,
who clings to our bonds.
That day...
The morning after Ren-san conceived Akito,
I woke up in tears.
So did Shigure-niisan,
Hatori-niisan, and Ayame-niisan.
We're the only zodiac members
who know that Akito is female.
Apparently, Ritsu was
too young to sense it clearly.
But the four of us all had the same dream.
Akito, the god we hadn't seen yet,
came to us in the dream and said,
"I'll see you soon."
So we ran straight to Ren-san,
who didn't know she was pregnant yet.
As we cried, we just kept saying,
"We've been waiting for you."
It... It was like this feeling
I didn't recognize welled up in my heart,
and I sensed a me
that wasn't me, shouting.
It was the zodiac spirit.
Another self that lived
inside me. In my blood.
At the first sign of a new ego forming,
the zodiac blood begins to hound us:
"Never betray Akito."
They made a promise
to be together for eternity.
No matter how many times
they were reborn.
Now that my curse is gone,
I can see that our bond was unnatural.
Ren-san is right.
But I see something else, too.
A crying girl.
Akito, it's okay.
Calm down. It's okay.
This way, ma'am.
Akito-san.
Do you think a crybaby like you can win?
Come on, let's go back.
Why...
Why is she always so mean?
She's cruel!
Hatori!
Hatori, gimme a hug.
I can't push away a crying Akito.
And I can't see Arisa while
there's another girl I have to stay with.
I'm sorry to unsettle you
by telling you all this.
But I wanted you to know that
"Watch alone"
the same Akito who wounds others
too easily is herself deeply wounded.
I wanted to give you an idea
of why I can't leave her.
I... I should say something...
I know I should...
...but I can't make any words come out.
I'm sorry. All I ever do is hurt others.
But this is the path I chose.
The one I took of my own free will.
I'm sorry. And thank you--for everything.
I'm frozen.
Everything's frozen...
It's a chain, a spiral of sadness...
...and everything's frozen.
I couldn't find the motivation to work,
so I wanted to get some fresh air.
I'm sorry. It won't happen again.
Here I am to save the day.
Ta-da.
What? What do you mean?
Just what I said: Tohru is in my custody.
She'll be mine all night.
Hanajima-san,
your phrasing is a little sketchy...
You dare to object to
my sudden Nightgown Festival?
I think the term is "pajama party"...
But no, it's no problem.
Excellent. Goodbye.
It's no problem,
but it is a little strange.
Did something happen to Honda-san?
Who called?
Hanajima-san. She says Honda-san
is staying the night there.
You're fine with ordering out, right?
My goodness. Was she really that shocked?
Saki-chan might be pissed at me
if she doesn't bounce back...
That's a scary thought.
Oh, hey.
Maybe I should try making dinner.
Do we have a cookbook?
That's scary! Don't do it!
It's okay. I can do it
if I try harder... I think...
But maybe you can't!
Saki-chan!
Has Tohru-chan had dinner?
Is there anything she'd like to eat?
Shark fin.
That's what you want.
And you just ate, Saki-chan!
Mom, she says no dinner.
You should make her tea.
Oh, you're right! How rude of me! Tea!
Megumi?
You know what to do.
I'm on it.
The tea is ready.
Oh, thank you...
Careful, it's hot.
Right...
U-Um, Hana-chan? What brought you there?
You were crying.
It was in a voice no one but me
could hear, you were crying so loudly.
Something sad happened, didn't it?
I... Hana-chan, I'm... so confused...
My curse has already broken.
A girl?
Akito-san is...
Akito's mother.
So... I won't see Arisa.
"Kureno-san"...
"Kureno-san" is... Kureno Soma...
I wanted him to go see Uo-chan,
so... I asked him to...
But he said he can't.
Because... Because he has
someone he needs to stay with...
K-Kureno-san is a caring man who...
...puts someone else's
feelings before his own...
I couldn't say anything!
So many people have had to help me...
...but when it was my turn,
I couldn't do anything.
I was useless!
Uo-chan... Kureno-san...
You do the same thing.
You put others' feelings before your own.
I... worry about you.
If you keep taking on
people's feelings like that,
and treating them carefully...
...and carrying them on your shoulders...
I worry that one day
they'll crush you.
Look at this, Kyo-kun!
I bought a new scarf!
It even has pom poms!
I worry that if they crush you,
we'll never see your smile again.
If that happened...
If that happened,
it'd be the end of the world.
I called her.
You told me to hurry,
so I ran all the way here from work!
Did you hear us?
I heard.
So, listen...
I'm trash for making you cry.
Uo-chan, you're not "trash"!
Well, you're not "useless."
I love you, you dummy.
You can stop worrying. I'm all right.
I mean it this time.
I was right: Kureno's just like you.
You're the same kind of dumb.
So I figure...
...I just love dummies.
I don't want to make problems
for people like you.
So that's the end.
That's it.
So you loved and lost?
Why, you...
Megumi, we need to be sensitive right now.
But some things just take a long time.
Some friends and lovers, too.
So it wasn't all for nothing.
Well, duh! That's my personal creed.
All right, shall we start the party now?
Oh, I'll help!
My heart pounds as
I'm surrounded by older women.
That line again?
"Soma"
Isuzu-chan, you naughty girl.
Did you sneak all the way in here?
You've been looking for something,
haven't you, Isuzu-chan?
I know all about it.
Would you like my help?
They passed out.
Yes.
I think the chance to take a break
from her own feelings
made Arisa feel a little better.
Do you think there's any chance left?
Well, that may be
another story altogether.
Romance is tough.
Yes.
The sun always comes up again.
There's no night that doesn't end...
So I'll start again, one thing at a time.
I'm home!
Shigure-san?
I wonder if he's still... sleeping...?
What's this scarf doing here?
Could this be mine?
Wh-What...?
So it is yours?
Glad I didn't guess wrong.
It was lying all crumpled in the street.
U-Um--
I washed it,
but not all the stains came out.
If that bugs you, buy another one.
Stop it, that's not dry yet!
Told you.
Thank you! I'll never, ever drop it again!
Okay, then.
You stayed at Hanajima's last night?
Yes! Uo-chan came, too,
and we had a Nightgown Festival!
A what?
It was so much fun!
Good morning. Was it a fun party?
Good morning!
Morning!
You know, Yuki-kun's cooking last night
reminded me of just how much
I appreciate you, Tohru-kun.
It was so weird I don't even know if
it was bad--actually, it was really bad.
"Just remembered it"
I almost died!
Maybe I really can't do it...
I'd like to puzzle those
things out one at a time.
Uo-chan, Hana-chan!
Yo!
Good morning, Tohru-kun.
All those things Kureno-san told me.
"That's an Unwavering Truth"
"That's an Unwavering Truth."