♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Brother.
My soul will always be by your side
and protect you.
No!
Xiao Wu’s conscious is gone.
How can this happen?
Because she gave you all she had.
Xiao Wu.
Whoever hurts you,
I won’t let any of them go.
Martial Soul Hall!
I must make you pay for what you did!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 136]
You can’t even differentiate
your friends and enemies.
How can you be the Holy Lady?
Reflect yourself in the apse.
Don’t come out without my permission!
Yes, Your Holiness.
- Your Holiness, please calm down.
Calm down?
Elders, how can I?
Hu Liena is wrong. What about you?
You are the top elders of Martial Soul Hall,
and two Grand Soul Land Masters,
but you were tricked by a young man
and caused the Century Millennium Soul Beast
to sacrifice.
What a good job!
Forget it. You are dismissed.
Thank you for not punishing us, Your Holiness.
If I don’t lack talented people
and you’ve always been loyal...
How dare Titan Giant Ape and Azure Bull Python
ruin my plan?
When I’m free, I’ll make you into my soul ring.
But now,
Tian Dou Empire should endure some changes, too.
I feel burning hot.
Armour! Eight Spider Bone has upgraded!
This armour seems to connect all my soul bones.
My mind can control my skills immediately.
When I absorbed this Human Faced Demon Spider,
it was possessed by the Spider God.
Is that why I have changed so much?
But...
Each of these four soul bones feels different.
The one in my back is scorching hot.
The one in my right arm is gentle.
The one in my head is cold.
The one in my right leg is benevolent.
I feel sick.
Disarm!
There are conflicts among the soul bones.
I’ve never heard of this situation.
Maybe only Master can answer this question.
Strengthen the gravity!
Three times of the gravity!
As the empire’s Chief of Soul Master,
I have received an order
from His Majesty to train you.
Battle skills are important,
but your strength and determination
are more important.
Just a few days ago,
two of the Three Upper Tribes were attacked.
Qibao Amber Tribe
and the Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe
are almost wiped out.
Tian Dou Empire must be the next target.
If you don’t train hard today,
next time, you will end up with
death and destruction.
- Help!
- Help me!
- Save me!
- Help!
Xiao Gang trains the army
and carries out researches on martial soul
non-stop every day.
If this continues,
his body might not be able to take it.
There’s nothing I can do either.
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe
has been destroyed.
He’s paralyzing himself by doing this.
Watch out for your upper front!
Maybe, only Little San’s return
can make him happy.
For the past few days,
I’ve tried to gather
our tribe members everywhere
but I realized there are
only no more than a hundred people.
Their ability is average. We really can’t...
How are things of the empire going?
They are contacting Xing Lou Empire.
We have Mu Bai and Zhu Qing’s help,
and this advantages both empires share.
Joining hands shouldn’t be a problem.
Though we are trying our best,
if a war indeed takes place,
it will be a disaster for the whole continent.
[Soul Land]
Xiao Wu, we will leave here soon.
When I become a Grand Soul Land Master
and find the Decade Millennium
Grade Nine Ginseng King,
I’ll bring you back here.
You will revive.
Do you know what you are going to lose?
You have to return Sister Wu’s soul bone to her
and give her the nine soul rings
of a Grand Soul Land Master.
This means you will transfer
your martial soul into her body.
Your cultivation accumulated
in all these years will be in vain.
Forget about the martial soul
and the cultivation.
Xiao Wu, without you, all of these are meaningless.
We will meet again in 20 years.
Tang San has left.
Can he make it?
I can’t understand the feelings between them.
But, I believe Tang San will revive Sister Wu.
I hope so.
Sister Wu is so silly.
So is Tang San.
But, in a lovely way.
Now, I must return to the school
and ask Master about the Eight Spider Bone.
Xiao Wu, you must have missed Teacher Er Long, right?
- Umbrella! Umbrella!
- Boss, how much are they?
This umbrella is cheap and nice.
- Give me one, please.
- Choose whichever you like.
Move away! Move away!
Who are you? Are you tired of living?
What are you doing?
Rascal! Kill him!
There is soul power in the whistle
and his power is pretty strong.
Who’s in the car?
- How dare he offend the Fourth Prince?
- He’s in big trouble.
But, he’s so powerful. These are the royal guards,
the key warriors
for the royal family of Tian Dou Empire.
He beat them so easily.
Come on!
Damn!
Xue Beng is still so arrogant and bossy.
Stay out of it if you don’t want to die.
Leave it to me.
No, no matter how arrogant Xue Beng is,
he’s still a soul master.
He should know my rank is much higher than his.
In this situation,
he still insists to fight against me.
Is he so confident that Old Freak will help him?
Or is he doing it on purpose?
You have your own territory
and great soul power at such a young age.
Even Little Freak can’t achieve what you have now.
Who exactly are you?
Old Freak, long time no see.
Senior, he’s the one who made a mess.
You are...
Does this prove who I am?
Little Freak.
Old Freak, let’s talk elsewhere.
Ok.
It’s just a misunderstanding.
He’s my friend.
Take care of the rest here.
Old Freak.
Since when has your perception become so bad?
Stop it.
Though everything indicates
that you’re Little Freak.
But, Little Freak doesn’t look like you.
- Losers, clean this up.
- Yes, Your Highness.
Little Freak, you are indeed a monster.
You are of the bloodline of soul beasts.
Old Freak,
although my mother was born a soul beast,
when she was carrying me,
she had already become a human.
But, I never think that this would happen again.
If it weren’t for Martial Soul Hall,
our family wouldn’t have ended up like this.
This cannot be forgiven.
I didn’t know Little Freak
had gone through so much.
What are you planning to do next?
Take revenge on Martial Soul Hall?
Not now.
I’ll only attack Martial Soul Hall
when I have enough energy.
Old Freak.
Why are you still with people like Xue Beng?
Is this kind of people worth your protection?
Little Freak.
You can’t judge things by what you see.
Mostly,
you have to look into a person
to learn his nature.
Do you know why Xue Beng is so unruly?
Actually, it’s all caused by Xue Qing He.
Do you mean there’s something wrong with Xue Qing He?
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 136 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1333 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2054]
[Total scene: 51786]
[Total CGI: 26190]
[Total plan of action scene: 11104]
[Total scene model: nearly 524]
[Total character model: nearly 973]
[Total props model: 13363]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods,
who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
If you can’t find any evidence,
figure out who can benefit most from this.
You must accept this fact as soon as possible.
I’ll kill you!
Don’t be impulsive!
Impulsive?
How can I not be impulsive?
Even if I will die from it,
I will still turn the world upside down!
Enough!
You’ve been through a lot.
Find me if you need anything.
Any resource is not a problem to me.
I have decided.
Tonight, then.
Are you okay with it?
No problem.
Oh, right. Remember to keep it a secret.
Don’t worry.
[Soul Land]
[Available at 10 AM every Saturday]