♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Tang San.
You always manage to create miracles.
But...
do you think you’ll get lucky again today?
Are you fooling me?
I’d rather die for justice
than submit to evil.
The Martial Soul Hall
is my enemy for life!
[Episode 154]
Do you see the disparity between us now?
Tang San.
This is my domain.
I am the ruler.
This is the real Angel Domain.
I can feel my soul power
being cleansed and weakened again.
If we can’t break this domain,
I will die once my soul power is depleted.
Honestly,
I really appreciate you.
I will give you one last chance.
I’ve given you my answer.
Fifth Soul Skill, Blue Silver Emperor Tyrant Spear.
Arrival of Angel.
Sixth Soul Skill, Complete Emptiness.
Not bad.
Even the skill generated from
the second evolution of my Angel domain
can do nothing about
your Century Millennium Soul Skill.
But...
it’s not enough.
Fifth Soul Skill, Sacred Sword.
Such a strong energy fluctuation.
Even Complete Emptiness
can’t resist it this time, I’m afraid.
If I use Teleport,
how it will work in his domain
is still unknown.
There’s only one choice left...
Invincible Golden Shield.
Skill.
Of.
Random.
Skill of Random Hammering
should disturb my Angel Domain.
Tang San,
your hammer skill is quite powerful
but it requires constant strength gathering.
Do you think I’ll let you do that?
I’d like to see
how many times you can withstand my strike.
He stepped back for one meter?
No way.
In my domain,
even if he teleports,
not an inch can he move.
I have combined Ghostly Trace
and Skill of Random Hammering
together with the aid of Teleport.
It’s my original technique,
Skill of Random Dance.
I don’t believe
you can dodge it forever.
It’s the 49th hit.
I can’t let him wave his hammer again.
Sixth Soul Skill,
Roaring Angel.
Roaring Angel is a kind of spiritual attack.
Skill of Random Dance.
Eighty-one Strikes in One.
What strong energy fluctuations!
He made it.
I finally managed to break his Angel Domain!
Unfortunately,
my soul power has been used up.
How’s that possible?
Even we
can’t break from
Young Master’s domain easily.
Tang San is just a Soul Emperor.
How is it possible
that he greatly injured
Young Master in his domain?
Tang San,
you just keep surprising me.
Part of me wouldn’t want to kill you now.
You’re the second person
who is qualified to be my life-long enemy.
Idiot,
who allowed you to interfere?
Young Master,
I...
Listen,
even Tang San will die,
he can only die in my hands.
A fair battle
is the last respect I show him.
Yes.
I didn’t expect you
to have a bright side as well.
Everyone has their own judgment
about righteousness and evil.
Yet in reality,
the winner
is always upright
and the one that brings light.
I can’t concentrate Soul Power inside me.
Even though I managed to
break the Angel Domain,
maybe a part of his cleansing ability
has been injected into me
the moment the Angel Domain
was broken.
Tang San,
I’ll end your life with my own hands.
This is the last thing I can do for you.
I will always remember you.
Wait.
Can you tell me who exactly you are?
[Soul Land]
Although you’re only stalling time here,
I’ll answer your question anyway.
Let me show you who I really am.
That way, I believe
you can die without regrets.
He’s actually a woman?!
I’ve never seen anyone with such a gorgeous look.
My real name
is Qian Ren Xue.
I don’t care if you’re a man
or a woman.
As long as you’re from the Martial Soul Hall,
you’re my enemy.
Tang San.
Goodbye.
- Clan Chief.
- Little Freak.
What am I supposed to do?
I have no soul power left.
Xiao Wu.
No!
Your soul can’t withstand her Light Blade Entity.
Brother.
Xiao Wu.
Xiao Wu
is revived.
Xiao Wu.
Get away now!
You’re so silly.
Brother.
Xiao Wu.
I’m fine.
My Xiao Wu.
I have the Peerless Flexible Armor.
What’s going on?
You...
have emerged your soul and your noumenon?
Fifth Soul Skill, Flexible Bone Lock.
It’s bad.
Young Master is now at a disadvantage.
I was careless. I can’t move now.
Xiao Wu.
I have you suffer for me again.
It must be that you know
the state of the soul
can’t fend against Qian Ren Xue’s attack
so you emerge with your noumenon temporarily
to save me from danger.
Tang San is already a spent bullet.
Kill them!
Charge!
Shiny Gold Twirl.
Just two Great Soul Land Masters and a Soul Sect...
knowing nothing about their petty ability.
Charge!
Luo San Pao.
Farting like thundering,
sky splitting, and groundbreaking Luo San Pao.
Such a strong pressure.
Now that Young Master is heavily injured
and she’s on the verge of a breakdown,
she can’t take another hit.
Retreat!
The power of the Giant Gold Dragon
is so surprisingly horrible.
After the last fight with
the Golden Iron Triangle,
two of them have improved from Soul Saint
to Great Soul Land Master
and the other from Big Soul Master to Soul Sect.
It seems like just a minor improvement,
but the power of the Martial Soul Fusion Skill
- has been tremendously upgraded.
- Teacher.
Go.
Let our teachers take care of this.
We go and protect Emperor Xue Ye now!
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 147 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1410 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2221]
[Total scene: 55353]
[Total CGI: 27033]
[Total plan of action scene: 12052]
[Total scene model: nearly 534]
[Total character model: nearly 991]
[Total props model: 13371]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
Your Majesty.
What’s wrong with His Majesty?
He can only hang on for thirty minutes.
Only with Emperor Xue Ye’s support
can we counterattack.
The palace is heavily guarded.
We have to leave quickly
or Qibao Amber Tribe and Tang Clan
will suffer from a great loss.
Fight our way out immediately.
Is Qibao Amber Tribe going to rebel?
Let’s do this!
Allocate all our people
to lock down the palace.
We can’t let Tang San and his people
leave with Emperor Xue Ye.
[Soul Land]
[10AM every Saturday]