♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
Are you dumbfounded, kid?
I think there’s no need
for this match to go on.
Just surrender.
Your venom doesn’t work on me at all.
See you.
I’ll spare your life
because of your family.
Three pieces of soul bones.
What a strong sight.
The former pope.
Qian Xun Ji.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 101]
There’s only one champion.
So these soul bones
will belong to the champion.
I hope that all of you can do your best
and win the honor.
Please send seven members of your team to join
the individual eliminating round this morning.
The winner will enter the grand final tomorrow.
While the losing team will
have a team battle in the afternoon
to fight for the quota of the grand final.
Participants, please move to the
bleachers to prepare yourselves.
Later, you’ll draw lots for the battling sequence.
Participants who draw a bye
will undergo the second round
with the winner of the first round.
This individual match is
as important as the grand final.
If the team wins, they’ll become the top two
and have more time to prepare
for the grand final tomorrow.
Among the three teams,
Martial Soul Hall is undoubtedly
the most advantageous.
Three Soul Kings
indicate the vast gap of
three Decade Millennium Soul Rings.
Plus their Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
They’ve defeated
Tian Dou Imperial School with merely one stroke.
No one could see what happened in the red mist,
not to mention figure it out.
The only goal of their strategy is
to terrorize.
I had asked Yu Tian Heng.
However, they were totally astounded
of what skill was used.
They didn’t even exert their real strength then.
This was the most intimidating strength
of Martial Soul Hall School.
With tyrannical abilities
and rigorous plannings,
they defeated their rivals
by gradually suppressing them.
Even their rivals are at Soul King level,
they’re still a formidable team to fight against.
Not to mention Shen Feng School and us.
None of us is under the Soul King level.
Rigorous planning is also our weapon.
Besides, we possess something they don’t.
Tacit cooperation.
Please send your first member onto the ring.
In the first round,
we have to probe and observe
the other two teams’ strategies.
Jing Ling, are you willing to duel?
I’ll handle it.
How lucky I am.
Since we get the free pass, we’ll have more time
to observe them.
I hereby announce, the first round
of the individual match,
Shen Feng School versus
Martial Soul Hall School starts...
Wait.
I give up.
Give up?
Isn’t Martial Soul Hall School Team
the potential champion?
Why did they abstain in the first round?
Congratulations to Shen Feng School.
The second round,
Huo Wu Shuang from Shen Feng School
versus Jing Ling from Shrek School.
Hold on.
How dare you interrupt the match.
Please state your reason.
My reason is
Shrek School renounces the individual match
and voluntarily enters the match for loser teams.
Jing Ling, come back.
Why?
I think we have the right to renounce.
Well, this is your right.
Sorry for asking.
My apologies, Elder Yu.
Elder?
He’s the Elder of Martial Soul Hall?
I heard that even the two Grand Soul Land Masters
have outstanding credentials and achievements,
only then they’ve become the Elders these ten years.
With Grandmaster’s age and strength,
how would he have that kind of authority?
Why did she protect me?
Continue.
Martial Soul Hall School Team is a formidable team.
We’re not their match.
We renounce this match
and fight with Shrek School
for the grand final’s quota.
If that’s the case,
Martial Soul Hall School Team will
directly enter tomorrow’s grand final.
Match between Shen Feng and Shrek
will be conducted in the afternoon.
I hope you’ll be prepared
for your match. Go back now.
Martial Soul Hall would play dirty tricks
at such a dominant position.
Jing Ling’s draw was lucky,
allowing us to observe our rivals.
But Martial Soul Hall School Team
suddenly conceded.
This has led to two results.
First, members of Martial Soul Hall
would keep their full strength intact.
Second, Huo Wu Shuang would keep
his full force to fight Jing Ling.
If he defeated Jing Ling,
he’d definitely concede
when confronting with Martial Soul Hall.
This means that the two schools
have allied to deal with us.
We can’t win in the individual match.
It’s fine if we lose.
But if we win,
we would have to suffer
in the continuous battle with them.
Isn’t this too wicked?
I didn’t get it
why Martial Soul Hall agreed on
the merger of Shen Feng and Chi Huo.
Now it turns out this is what they’ve planned.
Do they really think they can hinder us?
Aren’t they too arrogant?
We have only one goal.
Shrek must win!
Do you know why we did this?
I want a showdown between us.
I’d rather give up the championship
so as to beat you.
If this is what you want,
you’ve already fallen behind.
Time will tell.
Don’t think that I’ll give in to you
even though you saved me.
I’ve paid you what I owed.
The match is starting soon.
Participants, please be ready.
[Soul Land]
Feng Xiao Tian and Tang San
represented their team to duel one-on-one.
Is Feng Xiao Tian able to
win back his victory?
Huo Wu had once defeated Tang San
in the individual match.
How will Tang San deal with them this time?
Shen Feng School stands in three rows.
It’s a firm formation for attacking and defending.
While Shrek School stands in one line.
Are they going to launch a surprise attack?
Shrek’s formation is totally
different from before.
Do they have other tricks behind?
Both teams are from Tian Dou Empire division.
[Tian Dou Empire]
They fought several times
in the preliminary and qualifying rounds.
Both teams won and lost to each other.
They’re well-matched in strength.
But only one team can enter the grand final.
Who will be the winner then?
I hereby announce
Shrek School versus Shen Feng School.
Start!
What are they doing?
What a terrifying soul power.
We’ll get hurt if we come close.
Follow the plan. Feng Xiao Tian, lift-off.
Sure.
Second Soul Skill, Double Wolves Shield Body.
Third Soul Skill, Gale Wings.
Third Soul Skill, Raining Sparks.
With Huo Wu’s Rings Fusion Skill
and the help of two
soul masters of Support Branch,
It seems that they pin all hopes
on Feng Xiao Tian and Huo Wu.
Have they managed to learn to fuse
their martial souls in such a short time?
Double Fusion Skill.
Cooperation of Huo Wu and Feng Xiao Tian
has greatly enhanced the strength of Shen Feng.
Power of fire and wind compliments each other.
It seems like Double Skills Fusion,
but they only focus their power on Feng Xiao Tian
empowering him in attacking and defending,
and to boost his power beyond a limit.
But, our kids aren’t easy to deal with.
Change.
I didn’t know that Rong Rong knows
Rings Fusion Skill.
She is the daughter of
Qibao Amber Tribe’s chief anyhow.
This skill exhausts
their soul power excessively,
so it’ll not be used casually.
This is Seven in One Martial Soul Fusion Skill?
Seven in one?
Generally speaking,
only soul masters with similar
martial souls and soul skills
are able to use this fusion skill.
Just like what Cang Hui School did previously.
But Shrek Seven Devils...
Each of them possesses
different martial souls and abilities.
But they still make it.
Although both are fusion skills,
however, this is much more difficult.
Is this the real strength of Grandmaster?
I’ve tried to learn about the theory of
different martial souls fusion skill
proposed by Grandmaster,
but I can’t figure out how it works.
Perhaps only Tang San can see through it,
besides Grandmaster in this world.
It’s Seven in One Martial Soul Fusion Skill...
But I’ve found the weakness of it.
The initiator of this fusion skill
is Ning Rong Rong.
While the foundation of this skill
is Oscar who provides substantial
soul power to Ning Rong Rong.
Hao Tian Hammer.
The time when it shocked
the entire continent was the battle
between Grand Hao Tian Master
and the former pope, Qian Xun Ji.
Today, again with the presence of Hao Tian Hammer,
what bloodshed can we foresee?
Gale Devil Wolf 36 Successive Chops.
Only two of them are done,
your fusion skill will be nothing.
So fast.
How could he accelerate
to this extent with their support?
Purple Demon Eye.
[Next Episode]
With Little San’s peculiar sight and technique,
this put Little San into a riskier position.
Why don’t I kill him now?
As much of Hao Tian Hammer’s
ability is being exposed,
Martial Soul Hall’s intend of killing
him will be more determined.
Tool Soul Form.
With the tool soul form of Hao Tian Hammer,
I have nearly 70% certainty
to compete with Martial Soul Hall School.
If Tang San uses
the tool soul form again tomorrow,
he’ll either die or be injured.
Withdraw your soul.
Dad.
Why is he here?