♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to a lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Mu Bai, it’s written in the stars.
Don’t blame yourself.
How could it be?
It’s the domain.
The tables have turned.
It won’t be good for our relationship
if we continue to fight.
Let’s sue for peace.
Nothing is impossible in this world.
Your Holiness, everything is ready.
Hurry up, report to Tribe Chief.
Yes.
Clumsy. Always drop the ball.
Plan changed. Attack.
Yes.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 130]
Intruders! Guard the fort.
Hurry up, keep up.
Godly Zhuge Crossbow, release.
What’s this?
Kill them all.
Sword Sect Chen Xin.
Seventh Soul Skill,
Snake Spear Form.
Come on!
- Go over there, follow me.
- Someone is attacking us. Hurry up.
- Over there.
Destruction. How exhilarating!
Eighth Soul Skill,
Blazing Thrill.
Leave no stone unturn. Exterminate all.
Fourth Soul Skill, Bone Jail.
I didn’t expect my dad to come
right after Brother San left.
What brings Chief Ning here at this time?
I have no idea either.
Dad, Grandpa Bone, what’s happened?
Qibao Amber Tribe
has been destroyed.
Last night, Qibao Amber Tribe was attacked.
The battle lasted for four hours.
Our loss was disastrous.
Over two thirds of our disciples perished.
The casualties are still rising.
We keep hearing of the deaths
of the disciples outside.
They got the perfect timing.
40% of our disciples were working outside
while our internal fort was empty.
If it weren’t for the night patrol
who warned everyone in time
and the hidden weapon provided by Tang San,
we might have been wiped out.
Dad, how could this happen?
Which force can be so powerful?
It couldn’t be other tribes.
Was it them?
Besides Martial Soul Hall,
who could possess such tremendous power?
They not only mobilized
their subordinate soul masters,
but also those of the Lower Four.
There were four Grand Soul Land Masters
among the attackers last night.
If it weren’t for
Uncle Bone and Uncle Sword...
Grandpa Bone, your hand...
Nothing. It’ll recover in a few days.
But Chen Xin, that old fellow...
What’s wrong with Grandpa Sword?
Uncle Sword was severely injured in the fight.
Three of the Grand Soul Land Masters
were greatly hurt by him
and were then forced to retreat.
But he lost his right arm.
Luckily, he survived.
Currently, he’s hanging on
to escort the evacuation
of the remaining disciples and supplies.
Martial Soul Hall is so cruel.
It seems that they’re determined to win.
I’m here to remind you.
Since they’ve attacked Qibao Amber Tribe,
I’m afraid your
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe...
Oh, no.
Notify your tribe immediately.
They won’t give us a chance to prepare
once they’ve started.
Therefore, I’ve decided to move
the tribe into Tian Dou City
to seek protection under the empire.
Dean Frander, Grandmaster, we’re leaving.
Rong Rong, stay at school first.
Here’s safe.
I’ll come and get you
once everything is settled.
Dad,
I can do this.
Be a good girl.
2,000 disciples.
2,000 disciples have become corpses.
Martial Soul Hall,
I won’t let you off easily.
[Soul Land]
In the battle with Qibao Amber Tribe,
a total of 10,000 soul masters were dispatched.
Including 1,000 soul masters of the Lower Four.
At least 4,000 of
our soul masters were sacrificed
and over 3,000 were injured.
Three of the four elders
were greatly hurt to different extents.
So, they had no choice
but to retreat temporarily.
Rubbish.
10,000 people were sent there
and it was a secret attack.
However, your losses doubled the opponents’.
What about the
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe?
[Blue]
Xiao Wu, it has been five years. How are you?
Finally, I’m here for you.
Master mentioned that
the center of Star Forest boasts
the most abundant soul power.
It’s suitable for the cultivation of soul beasts.
So, the stronger the soul beast is,
the closer they stay near to the center.
As long as I go straight inwards,
I can find you for sure.
Is Er Long okay?
She’s overwhelmed with sorrow.
Let her rest.
How about Mu Bai?
Except the Elephant Armoured Tribe,
the other three of the Lower Four
are all located in Xing Luo Empire.
Mu Bai and Zhu Qing went back to investigate,
and they just confirmed that
the Lower Four have already been controlled
by Martial Soul Hall.
Among the Upper Three, one has been hiding,
one destroyed, and the last one wiped out.
Every soul master is in danger.
Many individual soul masters have joined
Martial Soul Hall.
In addition to their own powerful strength,
they’ve controlled over 70% of
the soul masters across the whole continent.
Wiped out? Xiao Gang, your family...
It was too late when we reached home.
The whole tribe, over 1,800 people, died.
Only a few disciples
who were away survived.
Tian Dou Empire sent troops to help
bury the corpses immediately.
But the corpses were too many.
Our tribe was looted.
My dad, as the Tribe Chief,
died without a complete body.
The three soul bones in his body
were forcibly ripped out.
Firstly, Qibao Amber Tribe.
And then,
the Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe.
Martial Soul Hall attacked mercilessly
two times in a row.
Could their next target
be the two empires?
They’ve been dissatisfied
with their current situation
and longed to enhance their status.
Their current power
is strong enough to fight against
the two empires.
8,000 soul masters were sent to attack
the Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe.
They were not discovered by the opponent
before attacking
and successfully wiped out
all of them.
We lost 3,000 people.
Ninth Elder and their Tribe Chief
died together.
The corpse has been brought back.
Great. The Upper Three lived up to their names.
Both of them are
indeed remarkable tribes.
They cost me 7,000 people.
Powerful enough.
Teacher, don’t be angry.
Although our loss is heavy,
but we’ve finally removed
the thorn in the flesh
and threatened the two empires.
We’ll continue to accumulate power,
the two empires will surely be infiltrated by us.
We have to be careful
that they may retaliate.
Ask the Martial Soul Temple
in Tian Dou City to stay low.
Don’t act rashly.
Monitor Tian Dou Empire and the remnants
of Qibao Amber Tribe at all times.
Inform me of anything suspicious.
Retreat.
Yes, Your Holiness.
Soul Hunting Manoeuvre stops here for now.
Next, the Penetration Plan should commence.
Proceed as planned.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 130 has been completed
and broadcasted for nearly 1277 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 1929]
[Total scene: 49148]
[Total CGI: 25376]
[Total plan of action scene: 10483]
[Total scene model: nearly 508]
[Total character model: nearly 962]
[Total props model: 13352]
[Appreciate your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
[Next Episode]
Martial Soul Hall announced that
they’ll find out
who destroyed the two tribes.
Who would care about the murderers?
What’s your plan?
They may need some time to search.
Go and support them then.
The Blue Silver Plant, which has long lived
together with the powerful soul beasts,
has developed anxiety and fear.
We shouldn’t simply wait here.
Something powerful and mysterious
must have come here in the forest.
It will definitely cause a great disturbance
in the soul master world.
There will be an arduous fight.