♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Come on!
Tell me how to fix it!
From now on,
you
are the president of the Ironsmiths Society.
You bastard!
Elder Token?!
Wait!
Brother San asked you
to roll out.
[*Buzz off means roll out literally]
Fatty,
keep a close watch on their movements.
Little Ao
and Rong Rong,
you have two important missions
to complete.
[Episode 150]
Uncle Tai Tan,
what did you give to my teacher?
He hasn’t been eating
or sleeping for two days.
He’s obsessed with that blueprint.
To be honest,
I’m worried about
letting him go alone.
I’ve discussed it with Si Di.
We’ll send two Grand Iron Masters to look after him.
There’s only a fine line between a Grand Iron Master
and the God of Ironsmith.
With them
and Lou Gao, such a great artisan,
we Tang Clan will be like a tiger with added wings.
You may rest assured.
We will do whatever we can to make them feel at home.
We’re back.
Brother San,
we’re back with fruitful results this time.
This is...
Lath-like gold!
The purity is even higher than the one I got before.
This must be the Dragon Beard Needle.
This lath-like gold
can make at least a thousand Dragon Beard Needles.
It’s freezing.
Miss Ning,
may I have a look at it?
Si Long’s martial soul is Supreme Chisel.
He’s best at
identifying different types of minerals
and casting exquisite objects.
He’s got at least eighty percent of Lou Gao’s skills.
In casting communities,
he holds a high social status.
Extremely high density
with no impurities.
The essence of cold iron.
A piece of the real essence of cold iron.
It’s you again.
The core of cold iron.
No,
the essence of cold iron.
With this,
I can recreate
the unique hidden weapon of Tang Clan.
This is the hardest metal on the continent.
You can never find over five kilograms
in the whole Gengxin Town.
And this one is several hundreds of kilograms.
It’s extremely valuable.
It only took me one gold soul coin.
And that lath-like gold.
Got it also with one gold soul coin.
Miss Ning,
could you please tell me
how you found these minerals?
A soul master with the martial soul
of the Qibao Amber Pagoda
has a strong ability for treasure appraisal.
Rong Rong’s ability for treasure appraisal
is even better than Chief Ning.
These minerals she bought
were mixed in a pile of pure iron.
The boss didn’t even recognize it.
This.
And this.
This, this, and this.
Catch it.
The boss gave me this for free.
I think this stone
is the most valuable.
Could we be so lucky?
So tough.
If
the essence of cold iron is the hardest metal,
then this one
is the toughest.
The quality is even better than
the essence of cold iron.
I’ve never seen such unique metal like this.
Rong Rong,
You really got lucky this time.
If my guess is right,
this is the core of Deep Sea Silver.
If that’s so,
the Storm Pear Blossom Needle can...
I can’t say for sure.
It’s way too tough
that no fire can melt it.
It can only be hammered into shape.
Whether it’s you, me,
or even Master Lou Gao,
none of us can do that for now.
I’m afraid
my former master is the only one who can.
Peacock Plumes,
Storm Pear Blossom Needle,
and Tang’s Lotus of Buddha’s Rage.
Are we finally getting to meet again?
If we are able to make these three hidden weapons,
even if it’s the Martial Soul Hall...
Maybe, I do have a way.
But
I have to deal with it later.
I envy you, Teacher.
I can’t imagine
what great pleasure it would be
to use supreme iron
when smithing as God of  Ironsmith.
The auction is about to begin.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please.
Kid,
that thing on the blueprint
can only be made by the hardest
and the toughest material, right?
Senior, you do have a good eye.
We’ve already got the right metal.
After getting back to Tang Clan,
we’re going to count on your incredible skills.
This might be
another path to raising
the social status of ironsmiths.
I must come up with some remarkable treasures
so that the people
of the Martial Soul Hall will know
ironsmiths
can reach the same level as theirs.
I believe you will make it.
All the distinguished guests, welcome!
I am Si Di,
one of Master Lou Gao’s disciples.
I am here to announce
today’s auction has begun.
This is the very first auction item for today.
A piece of black banded iron
with ninety percent purity
and 231 kilograms of weight.
Incredible.
Yes.
Black-banded iron
is also called black iron.
Adding it into a metallic compound
can dramatically increase
the hard degree of other metals.
Such a large piece of black iron
with such high quality.
It’s the world’s most rare treasure.
The reserve price is 20,000 gold soul coins.
The bid increment is 100 gold soul coins.
Now you may call out your bids.
Twenty-three thousand.
This bidder has offered 23,000 gold soul coins.
Any more bids?
Twenty-four thousand.
Twenty-five thousand.
Twenty-six thousand.
Twenty-seven thousand.
Thirty thousand.
Thirty thousand gold soul coins calling once.
Thirty thousand gold soul coins calling twice.
Forty thousand.
This is...
Forty thousand gold soul coins calling once.
Forty thousand gold soul coins calling twice.
Forty thousand gold soul coins, last calling.
Sold.
[Soul Land]
The next item for auction
is a piece of gold with extremely high purity,
weighing 50 kilograms,
which is also a treasure rarely seen.
Starting price,
ten thousand gold soul coins.
Thirty thousand.
Who is this?
Who’s offering such a high price?
Is he here to make trouble on purpose?
He’s a bishop of the Martial Soul Hall.
Myles.
No wonder he gives the highest price at will
because he won’t pay at all.
He will have these things on credit
under the name of the Martial Soul Hall
and delay payment
until the Ironsmiths Society compromises.
That jerk.
Senior, please stay calm.
Rong Rong.
We only bid for the rare metals
in the coming session.
But when Myles bids higher,
let him take it.
Sold.
Today’s auction items
have all gone into these two people’s pockets.
Coming up
are the last two items for today’s auction.
Their creator
is my teacher,
president of the Ironsmiths Society,
the God of  Ironsmith, Lou Gao.
The God of  Ironsmith, Lou Gao,
hasn’t made any new products for a long time.
These two items are indeed precious.
They are called
Peerless Flexible Armor.
They can withstand
the Sixth Soul Skill of a Storm Attack Soul Master.
Although made of metals,
they are extremely flexible.
The most amazing thing is
that they are created with
eight different kinds of metal
melted, with a special ratio,
into a special kind of
extendable memory metal.
For now,
only the God of Ironsmiths, Lou Gao, can refine it.
Flexible metal.
This is a miracle!
He has studied it for ten whole years
and repeatedly experimented
on many kinds of rare metal.
He finally succeeded.
Given this,
he is better than me.
I promise you with my life and soul
that they are absolutely divine artifacts.
Reserve price
two hundred thousand gold soul coins for one piece.
Now you can bid.
Such kind of powerful things,
I’ll save one to enhance my ability
and give the other to Her Holiness as a tribute.
I’ll have both of them. One million gold soul coins.
I believe
it will end the bidding for this lot.
Any more bids?
Alright.
One million gold soul coins.
Sold!
That’s all for today’s auction.
Please leave the venue.
That bidder
was Myles.
He said he would go back and raise money
before he left.
He’s not going to skip the payment, is he?
We didn’t drink enough, you know?
Have some more.
How dare you say that? You can’t drink.
I’ll fuddle you today.
Look.
Run!
It’s bad, Brother San!
I was monitoring as you told me to
and found that Myles was assembling his men
to slaughter the Ironsmiths society
for the treasures.
Darn it.
Does he want other great works of my teacher?
And we have refused to join them,
so they just...
No worries.
Old friend,
we won’t
let them take away your works.
Tai Tan,
I know how strong you are.
But you can only help me defend once,
not forever.
My lord,
will there be any trouble，
robbing the Ironsmiths Society?
Remember, we are under the divine Martial Soul Hall.
It’s their honor
to give us their things.
Since they refuse to join us,
I must teach them a lesson.
Senior,
let me handle it.
Kid,
you’re going to...
A pith-dark night
is the killing night.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 150 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1431 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2266]
[Total scene: 56104]
[Total CGI: 27141]
[Total plan of action scene: 12052]
[Total scene model: nearly 544]
[Total character model: nearly 995]
[Total props model: 13374]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[The dream on Soul Land and the martial soul
illuminates our youth.]
[We are not alone with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
Gengxin Town.
Tang San.
Tell your men,
the plan is moved up.
At least a thousand soul masters
came out of the blue.
I hope that your Tang Clan
will be soul masters’ another promising option.
What can make Old Monster be in such a hurry?
Is it...?
Real trouble this time.