♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Once you’ve finished them all,
you can not only acknowledge the ancestors,
we’ll also allow your father to return to the tribe.
I’ll do it.
I’ve finally completed
what my father entrusted to me.
It’s time to return to
Tian Dou City to visit my teacher and others.
Little San, welcome back.
By the way, Rong Rong.
What did you just say about Little Ao?
I have no idea whether he’ll come.
Hulk has always had a preference for Oscar.
He’ll definitely give
the soul bone to Oscar.
Who can have the soul bone?
A dead man has no say.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 127]
Your excellent performance in the
Continental Soul Master Elite Tournament five years ago
has greatly enhanced the
reputation of Shrek School.
Tian Dou Empire has
specially allocated funds to us
for building facilities
and expanding the school.
Dad said that
Emperor Xue Ye had asked
to meet Grandmaster in person.
He appointed Grandmaster as
Imperial Chief of Soul Masters
and ennobled him.
Now, Grandmaster is responsible for guiding
the soul masters of the royals.
Emperor Xue Ye planned
to merge Tian Dou Imperial School with us.
But, Dean and Grandmaster refused it.
For those who want to enter Shrek School,
their capability is the only pass,
not their status or by the back-door.
You’re right.
Even if they are not as amazing as us,
they must be strong enough
to deserve being a freak of Shrek School.
How dare you boast like this.
I’m almost at Level 64.
Rong Rong and Zhu Qing
have just achieved Level 60.
Little San is currently
at the peak of Level 59,
and he’ll breakthrough soon.
But you’re only at Level 57.
which is the lowest amongst us.
Little freaks, you all are beyond normal.
When the Golden Generation
of Martial Soul Hall,
was at your age,
they were just at Level 50.
Thanks to the premium herbs given by Little San.
Look, they have reached Level 60.
You’re the weakest one.
You must have been idling around
for the past years.
You’ve wronged me, Teacher.
I didn’t idle around.
It’s just that they are abnormal.
Although Fatty’s soul power
is slightly inferior,
with his Evil Phoenix,
his power is no way weaker than ours.
If Dean finds out about our current strength,
he will be overjoyed.
Teacher Zhao, where is the Dean?
Qin Ming, you’re coming at the right time.
Make me some hot tea, please.
Save me the trouble of getting up.
What are you doing?
Captain, how would you do with this soul bone?
Since Oscar has obtained a soul ring,
you’re not gonna give him
the soul bone as well, are you?
Regarding the soul bone,
after Little Ao has done absorbing the ring,
we can discuss about it.
Why? Waiting for Oscar to assist you
to take away this soul bone
once he has finished absorbing the soul ring?
You...
Shut up.
You always have a preference for Oscar.
Let’s end this today.
Initiate martial soul.
Little Ao hasn’t finished yet,
I must give him more time.
Third Soul Skill, Engulfing Flames.
That’s it? Lame trick.
Fourth Soul Skill, Earthquake.
Dizzy?
When did he...
Third Soul Skill, Phoenix Blow.
The sonic attack is hidden
in the lion’s roar.
Little Ao.
Boss Fu, you’re getting lazier.
As the Dean, my task is to coordinate
the overall operation.
I don’t have to bother with the trivial matters.
Dean,
I’ve taken down these trespassers.
You should interrogate them personally.
Who dares to trespass,
I must teach them a lesson.
Bring them in.
Dean, I miss you so much.
You...
Dean, teachers. We’re back.
It’s great that you’re back.
It seems that you’ve improved a lot.
You are Little San?
I heard Xiao Gang said that
your appearance have changed greatly
after the second awakening of
Blue Silver Plant.
So it’s true.
Little San is more talented than us,
and now he has become more handsome.
Could you please give us leeway?
You’ve got Zhu Qing
and have no eyes for other pretty women.
Why do you care about this?
I’m the one who should change my appearance.
What a pity. I’m still single.
Weren’t you wooing Jiang Zhu back at the time?
She didn’t take you?
She said she saw me as her younger brother.
I heard Rong Rong has been appointed
as the next chief of Qibao Amber Tribe.
Only you are lagging behind.
How can I compare with them?
Zhu Qing is the Crown Princess of Xing Lou Empire.
Have I married you?
Mu Bai, you have been appointed
as the Crown Prince?
Boss Dai, with your current situation,
you come to Tian Dou Empire
to reunite with us, aren’t you afraid...
Without teachers’ tutelage,
and my friends’ company,
I won’t be what I’m today.
It seems that you all have
gone through a lot.
Let’s talk inside.
Little Ao.
Seventh Soul Skill, Bear Form.
Don’t let them regain
their soul power. Separate them!
Brother Hulk, don’t bother me.
I can handle this.
Be careful.
Seventh Soul Skill, Martial Soul Form.
What’s going on?
A Support Branch’s soul master
who has just reached Level 60.
How dare you talk big before me?
Oscar, I’m not sure whether you’re brave
or stupid?
What’s this?
It’s impossible to kill
two Soul Emperors by hidden weapon.
But, I may try that trick.
Time for you to die.
Everything is going to end.
Fourth Soul Skill,
Knife of Heart Piercing.
Oscar, you’re not the only one who knows
how to launch a sneak attack.
[Soul Land]
That’s how I’m temporarily
recognized by the tribe.
Uncle asked me to return once
I’ve become Great Soul Land Master
and teach me the real skill of
Hao Tian Tribe.
I didn’t expect you
has been through so much.
Losing your mom,
your dad disarming his own limbs
and being forced to separate with Xiao Wu...
Let bygones be bygones,
let’s embrace the future.
The Tribe Elders from Hao Tian Tribe
are already impressed by your talent.
The three requirements raised to you
are actually a test for you.
The three requirements test
three different abilities of yours.
Reaching Level 80 is a test for your perseverance.
Killing the Great Soul Land Master
of Martial Soul Hall
and obtaining a Decade Millennium
Soul Ring
are tests of your courage and wisdom.
In fact, they’re paving the future
of Hao Tian Tribe.
If I’m not wrong,
once you’ve accomplished
the three requirements,
Hao Tian Tribe will reemerge on the continent.
Speaking of which...
Little San will be the next chief
of this prestigious tribe.
I’ve set my own goals.
I’ve never coveted the position of
Chief Tribe of Hao Tian Tribe.
But, for the responsibility
my father left to me,
I’ll never leave behind
Hao Tian Tribe’s affairs.
Don’t worry. You have ten years more.
It may be impossible
for others to achieve,
but not for Little San.
Little San, when are you going to find Xiao Wu?
I planned to head over to Star Forest directly.
I missed you all,
so I came here first.
Afterward, I’ll find Xiao Wu directly
and practice with her.
Once she has broken through Level 60,
I’ll bring her back to visit you.
Please tell her that I miss her.
Also, no matter who she is,
I’m always her mother.
It’s good that
all of you have been doing great,
while Little Ao...
I didn’t know that
Little Ao could be so stubborn,
leaving without a word.
I wonder where he is now.
I’m worried about his safety.
He’s just a soul master of Food Branch.
Even with the help of Little San’s hidden weapon,
if he comes across a major obstacle,
I’m afraid...
Third Soul Skill,
Flying Mushroom Sausage.
There’s no way to escape.
Again.
Sixth Soul Skill, Frozen.
Almost there.
My wings have become stiff.
It’s too late...
Old tricks.
Sixth Soul Skill, Cloning Sausage.
Sixth Soul Skill, Roaring Flame.
Fifth Soul Skill, Deep Freeze.
Sixth Soul Skill, Piercing Feather.
Fourth Soul Skill, Sonic Attack.
Fifth Soul Skill, Wolf Attack.
Fifth Soul Skill, Palm of the Giant.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 127 has been completed
and broadcasted for nearly 1270 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 1914]
[Total scene: 49148]
[Total CGI: 25334]
[Total plan of action scene: 10463]
[Total scene model: nearly 507]
[Total character model: nearly 962]
[Total props model: 13352]
[Appreciate your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
I didn’t save you not for repayment.
Frankly, I give you this soul bone
with my personal intention.
Fifth Soul Skill, Palm of the Giant.
This is his promise to you.
You have to believe that he’ll succeed.
Otherwise...
What if I leave all school’s affairs to you
and I go for the match tomorrow instead?
No matter how powerful
the five little freaks are,
they’re still under my control.
Friends, don’t underestimate them.