♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind,
you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Hao Tian Tribe…
Standing tall and magnificent.
It’s worthy of its name, the top tribe of the world.
Be careful, everyone.
Don’t go, Tang San.
I’m obliged to repay my father’s debt.
I’m willing to assume
all responsibilities for my father.
What can you assume?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 124]
The pressure is denser than Uncle’s.
I can’t resist anymore.
Greetings to you, Tribe Elders.
Death God Domain.
It is.
You’ve inherited
Tang Hao’s talent though.
What’s so great about the talent?
If there’s another one
behaving like Tang Hao,
the tribe will collapse, I’m afraid.
Kneel down, bastard.
Return to the tribe this time,
I am to atone for my father and
to help the tribe regain its glory.
Please accord me to acknowledge
my ancestors, Tribe Chief and Tribe Elders.
Absurd. Never even think about it
after what your father have done.
What’s worst is that you’re a bastard of him and the evil beast.
Mind your words, Seventh Brother.
Who are you calling bastard?
You, exactly. If it wasn’t for Tang Hao,
my son wouldn’t have been killed by
Martial Soul Hall.
Tang Hao has been reckless since young,
he never considers the safety of
the entire family something important.
He’s indeed a troublemaker.
Nonsense. Brother Hao is not.
He doesn’t deserve to be
the disciple of Hao Tian Tribe.
Tang Hao has to be expelled from the tribe
to save us all.
You’re right. We can’t afford
to offend Martial Soul Hall.
Tang Hao has to be expelled. Expel him!
No. No way!
Hand over Tang Hao.
Does he dare to duel with the Tribe Elders?
I’m sorry, Seventh Elder.
I apologise to you on behalf of my father.
However, your real enemy
should be Martial Soul Hall,
not Father or me.
It’s Father’s fault to get the tribe into trouble.
And I’ve apologized to you for that.
But, you’ve humiliated my mom.
I must get the justice back.
Seventh Elder, I challenge you.
I’ll never regret even if I die.
My advice to you is to be tough.
Is he insane?
How dare you, a junior, challenge me?
It seems that Elder Brother wants to
take this chance to test Tang San again.
Don’t you dare?
Brat...
It’s good for young people
to have pride, but not arrogance.
You despise the tribe,
we won’t let you off easily.
Where’s Tang Hu?
Second Uncle.
Have a fight with him.
Although Hao Tian Tribe had gone into hiding,
but we never allow provocation.
Be careful, Tang San. Although I’m the
strongest amongst the third generation,
Tang Hu isn’t no way inferior than me.
Elder, if I win,
am I eligible to challenge
Seventh Elder?
Yes.
Tang Hu, if you lose,
I’ll lock you up for a year.
Tang Hu, Soul Emperor Level 64
from Storm Attack Branch.
Tang San, Soul King Level 59
from Controlling Branch.
He is on Level 59?
Such a cocky young man.
How dare he bluff before the Elders?
Previously, Tang Hao
has been considered as
the rare talent of Hao Tian Tribe.
His son is more outstanding than him.
Start.
Since Tang Hu has one more
soul ring than Tang San,
I don’t think he can make up the gap
with just a Death God Domain.
Blue Silver Plant? Such a lame martial soul?
How ridiculous!
He wants to join the tribe
without the martial soul of
Hao Tian Hammer?
Seventh Brother.
If I’m not wrong, he must have twin martial souls.
Yes. A rare twin martial souls.
Twin martial souls plus Death God Domain,
he does have that in him to be arrogant.
Continue.
Watch out. The fourth soul skill.
Blue Silver Cage.
He’s so powerful.
The third soul skill.
Vigorous Strike.
This strike weighs more than a ton.
Why is the cage not broken?
His soul power is much higher than mine.
Besides, he’s only using
the third soul skill.
It’s only a matter of time for him to break
Blue Silver Cage.
Then I’ll let you have a taste of...
What’s this?
As the colour of the martial soul is changing,
it’s clearly that the power is soaring.
It’s the mutating of the martial soul
caused by the innate domain.
No, it isn’t a mutated martial soul.
[Soul Land]
Since Little San has inherited
Ah Yin’s Blue Silver Emperor,
he must have carried on the uniqueness of it.
Fifth soul skill...
Such destructive pressure.
I can’t let him perform this soul skill.
Fifth Soul Skill,
Man and Hammer Union.
Tang San has taken a long time to accumulate
power for this skill.
Since it requires such a longer time to do so,
why does he have to use this skill then?
There’re only
two possible reasons for this.
Firstly, this skill must be
extremely powerful.
It’s strong enough to resist a head-on strike
and simultaneously take down the rival.
And secondly...
It’s over. Random Air Hammer Skill.
This shows that he wasn’t raised in the tribe.
How dare he encounter directly
at such a critical moment?
Second Soul Skill.
Parasite.
And secondly...
he purposely extends the time of
accumulating power...
to induce his rival to think that there’s a flaw.
I must win this duel.
Sixth soul skill...
Third Soul Skill,
Constraint of Spider Web.
Other soul skills of mine
don’t take time to accumulate power.
How could it be?
With Tang Hu’s ability,
he should be able
to break through the control.
What makes Tang Hu
unable to resist is poison, actually.
Tang San merely attacks
his rival discretely every time.
Penetrating the poison into his rival bit by bit
is hardly noticeable.
Fifth Soul Skill,
Blue Silver Emperor Tyrant Spear.
Can’t break it.
I could only take this blow.
This strike is so powerful.
If it was me, could I take it?
I’ve lost.
Thank you for letting me win.
I wonder if I could challenge
Seventh Elder now?
No matter what soul skills I’m gonna use,
I’ll use only 30% of my strength.
I’m less consumed than you think.
Besides, I’ll be using my soul bone.
Please use 10% more.
Soul bone?
Not necessary.
If you think I’m taking advantage of you,
I’ll choose the battle location then.
Agree?
Sure.
On the iron chain bridge then.
Seventh Elder, if you lose,
I hope you take back
your words which insult my mom
and agree upon my acknowledgment
towards the ancestors. Deal?
But if you lose,
you’ll be imprisoned here forever
as a sinner of Hao Tian Tribe.
Seventh Elder,
this’s not for you to decide.
What do you think, Tribe Chief?
If Tang San wins the battle,
please stop obstructing him.
But if he lose...
What?
he’ll have to leave the tribe.
He can never use Hao Tian Hammer
for the rest of his life.
Isn’t this too easy?
Imprisoning him here forever
means that he’ll end up here.
Are you willing to see
such a gifted person falls?
No matter what, in his veins
flows the blood of Hao Tian Tribe.
Nothing can ever change this fact.
Well, I agree.
If Tang San wins over
Seventh Elder,
I have three additional requests.
Of course, I’ll tell him
after he acknowledges the ancestors.
He can decide whether to agree or not.
Although there’re conflicting opinions
between my uncle and the Tribe Elders,
but it seems like they’re all working
for the tribe’s sake.
Well, if so. Please proceed.
Next, there’s something about Tang Hao
that I’d like to invite all Tribe Elders to witness.
I refuse to hear anything about him.
Tribe Elders, only this news...
you all must listen.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 124 has been completed
and broadcasted for nearly 1249 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 1869]
[Total scene: 47895]
[Total CGI: 24937]
[Total plan of action scene: 10180]
[Total scene model: nearly 506]
[Total character model: nearly 957]
[Total props model: 13348]
[Appreciate your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
[Next Episode]
After reborning,
I still can’t escape from the same fate.
But in this life,
I’ll take control of my own destiny.