♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind,
you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Who could have such tremendous power?
Destruction is so exhilarating.
Qibao Amber Tribe
has been destroyed.
They got the timing perfectly.
Leave no stone unturn.
Exterminate all.
Martial Soul Hall not only mobilized
their subordinate soul masters,
but also those from the Lower Four.
Next, we should commence the Penetration Plan.
Proceed as planned.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 131]
Martial Soul Hall announced that
they’d find the culprits
who destroyed the two tribes.
Simultaneously, they suggested that
every existing tribe
be given a year to get prepared.
After that,
under the supervision of Martial Soul Hall,
the Seven Great Tribes will be re-elected
based on their strength.
Everyone knows who is behind the massacre.
A thief crying “stop thief”!
Even though we know
Martial Soul Hall is behind this,
who dares to question them
without evidence?
Furthermore,
they’ve proposed the re-election of
the Seven Great Tribes.
It is so advantageous to be one of it.
This event will bring a catastrophic turmoil
to the soul masters’ community.
Who will care about the murderers anymore?
We can’t await our doom.
Xiao Gang, what’s your plan?
I’ll do everything I can
to destroy Martial Soul Hall.
You’re dismissed.
Yes.
Nana,
Xie Yue and others
have gone there for a long time.
Any news from them?
Star Forest is the largest forest of soul beasts
on the entire continent.
They may need some time to search.
Go and support them then.
Yes, Your Holiness.
I’m close to the living area of
Decade Millennium Soul Beasts.
I shall stop by for a rest.
Blue Silver Plant, which has lived together with
the powerful soul beasts for a long time,
is nervous and fearful.
There must be something
powerful and mysterious in the forest.
Or...
humans.
With my current spirit power
merging with the surrounding Blue Silver Plant,
I can clearly perceive everything
within five kilometers.
If I focus all my spirit power
on one direction,
I can sense up to 1,500 meters.
At least 20 Soul Saints are here.
Which tribe could have such powerful members?
It’s Martial Soul Hall.
What are they doing here?
Grand Chrysanthemum Master,
the Elder of Martial Soul Hall
and also another Grand Soul Land Master,
is leading the team.
Their target must be huge.
Have they found out about Xiao Wu?
No.
I’ll never let them harm Xiao Wu.
My Blue Silver Domain
hasn’t found a trace of Xiao Wu for now.
It means she’s not nearby.
But they are probably searching for Xiao Wu.
What should I do now?
No matter that I secretly stalk them;
bypass them and search for Xiao Wu quietly,
or even challenge them,
I don’t stand a chance of success
against such a powerful team.
There’s only one way now.
Perhaps they have sensed my spirit power.
What comes next
is an arduous fight.
Who’s there?
His aura is filled with aggressiveness.
This person is very dangerous.
Take him down.
Such strong power!
Darn it. Take my strike!
Sixth Soul Skill,
Gear Blade Armour.
This is...
[Soul Land]
You’re
from Hao Tian Tribe.
Why are you here?
Here in Star Forest,
what can I do
besides hunting soul beasts?
Hunting by yourself?
I reckon that
you’re approaching us intentionally.
Spit it out!
What’s your intention?
I...
admit that I approached you on purpose.
Seeing that you have so many members,
I wanted to collaborate
with you to hunt soul beasts.
If you wanted to collaborate,
why did you harm us?
Without some tests,
how can I know
whether you’re worth my time or not?
It seems
there’s no need to do so.
Do you think
you can leave now?
It seems that
you want me to stay.
Just now, I sensed
a strong spirit power approaching.
Then,
you appeared.
So?
[Hao Tian Tribe]
Hao Tian Tribe
has gone into hiding.
Their disciples rarely wander around
in the soul master’s community.
And now,
we’re undertaking a crucial task.
Please tell me
do you
happen to be here
or not?
What if I tell you
I’m not from Hao Tian Tribe?
They’ve dispatched two Grand Soul Land Masters.
Martial Soul Hall is coming for Xiao Wu.
With such a powerful team,
I’m afraid even Titan Giant Ape,
a Century Millennium Soul Beast,
can hardly...
Well.
Great minds think alike.
Tang Yin?
Nana, you’re finally here.
Hu Liena. Why is she here?
Nana, do you know him?
He’s my friend.
Tang Yin, are you coming here
to hunt soul beast?
Yes. I’m reaching Level 60 soon.
You’re awesome.
You almost reach my brother’s level.
Why are you hunting alone?
It’s too dangerous.
Who else would help me other than myself?
You have me.
No. I mean we’re friends.
I don’t care who you are.
Since Martial Soul Hall
is carrying out a task in Star Forest,
any suspicious person
must be taken down.
Yan!
Is Star Forest Martial Soul Hall’s property?
Are you challenging Martial Soul Hall?
You’re from Martial Soul Hall,
but I’m not.
I’m just an individual soul master.
You’re challenging me, not the other way around.
Hu Liena is my friend, but you’re not.
Since no one welcomes me here...
Yan, if you don’t stop now,
I will fight against you.
Nana, he disdained Martial Soul Hall.
I can’t let him get away with that.
Should he disturb our target after he leaves,
the consequence is disastrous.
I’ve said, he’s my friend.
Nana...
Brat, I won’t let you get away easily.
Yan acted too rashly, please don’t mind him.
Why don’t you come to our camp
since we haven’t met each other for a year?
We could talk about
our thoughts on Death God Domain.
I’ve been treated as an enemy
before I enter your camp.
If I do, I will be accused of stealing information.
Nana, did you say that he had Death God Domain too?
Why don’t you introduce him to us?
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 131 has been completed
and broadcasted for nearly 1298 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 1975]
[Total scene: 50151]
[Total CGI: 25631]
[Total plan of action scene: 10586]
[Total scene model: nearly 513]
[Total character model: nearly 964]
[Total props model: 13355]
[Appreciate your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
[Next Episode]
Silly girl, as long as I’m alive,
I’ll never let them harm you.
I miss you so much.
Meeting you again,
I have no more regrets.
Persuade him to join Martial Soul Hall.
This is one of the reasons I let him stay.
Besides,
it’s for your sake.
It has been five years, finally...
I haven’t seen you for so long.
You’ve changed a lot.
You too.
Is your heart filled with agony
underneath your silence?
What have you been through?
You two look good together.