♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Shrek School is known as
the best school in Tian Dou.
It is enormous.
We want to move in here too.
Nonsense!
Xiao Tian and I have been together for a long time.
I’m here to learn about
your fascinating skills personally.
Let’s do it then.
I want to see
what skills he has
to fight the three of us simultaneously.
Tang San.
I’ve trained so hard in the past five years,
but I still can’t surpass you.
It seems like we’re destined to part with Shrek School.
I’ll ask Grandpa Bone for help.
I’d like to see who dares make trouble here again.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 148]
Rong Rong.
If Senior Grand Bone Master is invited
to protect our school,
we can travel with this opportunity.
We have less than a year left
before the Seven Great Tribes Re-Selection Contest.
We must have a batch of ready-made weapons,
so we can have the power
to fight the Martial Soul Hall.
Tang Clan needs a great amount of metal for
the manufacture of hidden weapons.
The Tribe of Strength has enough common metal.
But rare metal are very scarce.
I’ve discussed it with Elder Tai Tan.
We have to visit the Capital of Metal,
Gengxin Town, as soon as possible.
Yes! It’s good that Old Rhino is here.
We can leave the mess to him.
I’ll free myself from
the annoying errands this time.
You’ll only be at ease
when Senior Niu Gao is the one in charge of
the construction of Tang Clan.
You might not be willing to
entrust the job to another person.
Yes. You’re right.
Talking about buildings,
I don’t think we can find another person
who is better than Old Rhino.
If he’s in charge of it,
the construction of Tang Clan
might be almost done when we’re back.
Xiao Wu! We’re here.
Welcome to the Capital of Metal.
We’re at the right place.
Gengxin Town is the place
with the most smithies and ironsmiths.
Many ironsmiths from other towns
come here purposely to take
the smithing assessment.
If they pass the advanced smithing assessment,
they can stay here.
[Smithy]
Although the two empires don’t value ironsmiths much,
military gears and weapons,
[Gengxin North]
farm equipment, buildings, and furniture
are all works of ironsmiths’.
The more superb an ironsmith is,
the more valuable his works are.
Elder Tai Tan, do ironsmiths have
different rankings too?
Yes.
Normally, there are seven ranks
for ironsmiths.
From the lowest to the highest, they are
Beginner Ironsmith,
Intermediate Ironsmith, Advance Ironsmith,
Iron Master, Great Iron Master, Grand Iron Master,
and the God of Ironsmith.
What is your ranking then?
Silly boy. Do you call that a question?
Elder Tai Tan is the Vice President
of the Ironsmiths Society.
He’s certainly the God of Ironsmith.
Elder, how many Gods of Ironsmith
are there in this continent?
Three. The current President of
the Ironsmiths Society,
me...
and your father.
Don’t overthink it.
Master has such a brilliant son
to pass on his legacy.
He can finally live in peace.
- Never miss out these!
- Chief, if there’s a chance, please bring me to him.
[North Street of Gengxin Town]
This Bright Silver Armor is created in person
by a disciple of the current President of
the Ironsmiths Society,
the king of the God of Ironsmith, Lou Gao.
The one and only! Selling at a discount!
Does the disciple of Lou Gao need
to promote his product on a street market?
Lou Gao?
Lou Gao is the President of
the Ironsmiths Society.
It’s not wrong to say that he’s
the king of the God of Ironsmith.
After your father retired,
he and I are equally competent in iron casting.
Let’s go and have a look.
This Bright Silver Armor is created in person
by the disciple of the king of
the God of Ironsmith, Lou Gao.
Hey! Have a look!
The one and only! Selling at a discount!
Everyone! Please have a look!
This is
created by Lou Gao’s disciple.
- Rubbish!
- This is created by Lou Gao’s disciple in person.
Indeed, the armor looks firm.
But, each plate is very thin.
It doesn’t work at all.
Old man! Who is the rubbish here?
I said that this armor is rubbish.
So is the ironsmith who made this.
Old man!
My teacher is the disciple of Senior Lou Gao,
the current President
of the Ironsmiths Society.
How dare you say that the armor made
by my teacher is rubbish?
You’re insulting the God of Ironsmith.
Don’t you dare to leave
before explaining yourself!
Okay, I’ll explain it to you.
I don’t care about your teacher.
Even if Lou Gao is here
and says that he made this armor,
I’ll still call it rubbish.
This man is wrong.
You’re not convinced, right?
Okay, I shall explain to you in detail.
This armor was made
with the method of creating a chain armor.
You can have a look closely.
Every plate is different in size insignificantly.
It looks nice from the outside.
Actually, it’s way too thin.
Bright Silver Armor?
The metal plates are coated
with a layer of silver.
It’s not much stronger than a piece of paper.
My armor
is for decoration,
not for wars.
It features the thin plates.
It’s light-weighted so
you won’t feel tired from wearing it.
An accessory. Do you know what accessory means?
Then, what about
the different sizes of the plates?
Well...
This is the beauty of uniqueness.
This is taught by my master, Lou Gao,
the God of Ironsmith. You know nothing!
Lou Gao did once create
a Bright Silver Armor.
But, this is a lame fake.
Every plate of the Bright Silver Armor
that is created by Lou Gao
is made by refined pure silver.
The plates are thin,
but they protect the user well.
It is an accessory with good practicability.
Rubbish is already an understatement.
Oh, there’s a good show to watch now.
Liar!
This man is ruining
the reputation of ironsmiths.
Yes. He must be punished.
Don’t cheat around with his title next time.
Or else, you won’t survive here in Gengxin Town.
You...!
Go to hell!
[Soul Land]
Who’s causing trouble here?
Brother-in-law, it’s him.
I was selling my latest products,
but this old man came and made a scene.
He not only criticized my new armor,
but also insulted the God of Ironsmith, Lou Gao.
Ouch!
Arrest him now!
No wonder he dared to
fool aound with Lou Gao’s title.
I see. Someone backs you up.
Take him!
Master Tai Tan.
It’s really you!
Welcome back. I am...
Si Long.
Good boy.
You’re getting stronger.
Master Si Long is bowing to him.
Is he one of the three Gods of Ironsmith?
I didn’t expect that
Senior Tai Tan is of such a high status
in the Capital of Metal.
Seems like I can’t stay low key.
Is the liar indeed Lou Gao’s disciple?
If I’m not wrong,
he was bribed by the Martial Soul Hall
to defame my teacher, Master Lou Gao.
Bishop Myles. This is the case.
How dare he cause trouble on the territory
of Main Hall of the Martial Soul Hall!
He’s asking for trouble.
Keep a close eye on them.
Yes.
Are you being suppressed
by the Martial Soul Hall too?
Not only that. They have gone too far!
You’ve suffered a lot in recent years.
Chief.
Let’s get in the carriage.
After meeting Lou Gao,
I’ll show you around Gengxin Town.
Chief?
Even Master Tai Tan calls him that.
He must be an unusual man.
Is Master Tai Tan here
to accompany him to purchase things?
Here we are.
Please come down.
This is the headquarter of
the Ironsmith Society?
It’s been a long while.
Nothing seems to have changed.
Let’s go.
Let’s meet our old friend.
There are five floors in the building.
The first floor is the trading area.
Relatively,
the goods sold in the headquarter
are more expensive than that out there,
but all the products are verified by the society.
They are guaranteed.
The second floor is the advanced trading area.
Whoever owns a shop here
is experienced and capable.
The products being sold here
are more advanced than those
on the first floor.
The third floor
is where ironsmiths register for an assessment.
The registration is routine.
Nothing is worth a visit.
The fourth floor is for
VIP customers and auctions.
We don’t have auctions in the daytime,
so it’s not open.
There’s one tomorrow night. It will be open then.
Alright.
We shall come again tomorrow night.
Chief.
We shall go straight to the fifth floor
to meet Lou Gao.
Okay.
Here it is. The fifth floor.
This is the office of the Ironsmith Society.
The fifth floor is a secret casting area
exclusively to the high-ranked ironsmiths.
Every ironsmith with the title of
the Grand Iron Master or higher
has their personal space here.
What is Lou Gao experimenting these days?
Didn’t I say?
Don’t disturb me!
Teacher, it’s me.
Sorry to disturb you.
But, Vice President Tai Tan is here.
Tai Tan.
You’re alive! Old chap!
Lou Gao. You damn fatty is a few years older than me.
You’re still alive.
How can I die?
This...
is the top God of Ironsmith in the world?
Let me take a good look at you.
Brother San, your father is one of
the three Gods of Ironsmith.
Is he like this too?
You’re here at the right time.
Come here.
Let me show you a treasure.
I’ve studied it for many days.
The one who has made this
is surely a genius.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 148 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 13682 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2236]
[Total scene: 55581]
[Total CGI: 27046]
[Total plan of action scene: 12052]
[Total scene model: nearly 542]
[Total character model: nearly 995]
[Total props model: 8507]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[The dream on Soul Land and the martial soul
illuminates our youth.]
[We are not alone with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
I’ve spent a huge amount of money
to get this from the Martial Soul Hall.
You know too.
Myles is a bishop of the Martial Soul Hall.
The peerless hidden weapon.
You brat!
I’m the President of the Ironsmiths Society.
So what?
Si Long.
Where did you get these two girls?
[Soul Land]
[Available at 10 AM every Saturday]