♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
How can this happen?
Last time, Captain endured longer time
while competing with Tang San.
But he’s defeated very quickly this time.
You’d have known that
the benefits of this tournament.
It’s a chance to make you famous.
It also decides the ownership
of the three soul bones.
The more Hao Tian Hammer’s
ability is exposed,
the more determined
Martial Soul Hall wants to kill him.
This puts Little San into a riskier position.
Xiao Gang,
you still surprised me a lot.
Back then, did
our teacher tear us apart?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 103]
The Martial Soul Fusion Skill
of Xie Yue and Hu Liena
can resist our
Seven in One Fusion Skill temporarily.
Once our formation is destroyed by the other five,
we’ll be totally defeated.
Little San, what do you think?
To defeat the opponents,
I’ve come up with two ways.
One of it is to use the tool soul form again,
disregard of my spirit depletion.
But this might be targeted by the opponents.
The winning probability will be around 50%.
The tool soul form should
never be used again tomorrow,
as well as the Seven in One Fusion Skill.
All of you must keep in mind.
Once your skill has been known by the opponents,
you would have to change.
Once there’s a change,
the opponents’ pace will be disrupted.
And we can regain the initiative to fight.
Another way is
to break the opponents’ Martial Soul Fusion Skill,
making them lose the abilities to fight.
Then, we concentrate our powers
to clear the remaining five of the opponents.
Do you have the way to break the
Martial Soul Fusion Skill?
Martial Soul Fusion Skill is
incomparable to the common fusion skill.
Once it’s completed,
its power will be enormous.
And there’ll be no defects at all.
If both Soul Kings of the opponent fuse,
their strength to fight
can be increased to about Level 70.
I’ll settle them.
If all of you can hold enough time for me,
I believe that I can do it.
It’s Shrek. They’re here!
They’re here!
Tang San.
Tang San, you’re the man who defeated us.
You must win!
Shrek, it’s your showtime.
Little Freak, be extra careful.
Kids, this is your last battle before graduation.
Honestly, it’s my pleasure to cultivate all of you
into the great geniuses.
- I’m very proud.
- How about Oscar?
Nothing lasts forever.
Must win!
Shrek School couldn’t keep assisting your growth.
Your future path relies on your own.
Don’t you worry, Dean.
We’ll obtain the champion
that we promised you.
Just go on as the plan. Try your best.
If you can’t make it,
just put your safety as a priority.
Xiao Gang is right.
I’ve told you that
I won’t let you graduate
unless you obtain the champion.
But I change my mind now.
What I want is neither
the victory nor the champion,
I just want all of you
to be safe and sound.
Whether you win or lose, you’re still my pride.
I’ll never allow anyone of you to be injured or died.
Don’t you worry, Dean.
We hate to die.
Moreover,
three alluring soul bones await us.
Let’s go.
Yes.
Shrek!
Must win!
I’d show them what’s being called as
the genuine strength.
The disparity of soul power
between us is insurmountable.
Even the soul master at the lowest level among us
is similar to their captain’s level.
I’d like to see what makes them qualified to win.
Little San.
Don’t worry. I’m fine.
This is foundation strengthening, Long Zhi Leaf.
The healing speed will be boosted after taking it,
and stimulate the rapid recovery of soul power.
It also makes our minds more focused.
So we can maintain our optimum state in the battle.
And the rest will be left to all of you.
Shrek, must win!
Must win?
I’ll settle Tang San.
The Pope and the Elders are watching us.
We must win this tournament.
And it must be a perfect victory.
I’ll never give them any chance.
Who are we?
Champion!
We’re here to defeat the champion.
[Soul Land]
Continental Soul Master Elite Tournament.
The grand final is about to start.
Both teams, please be ready.
Team of Shrek School
enters the grand final
by obtaining the first place in Tian Dou.
Throughout the finals,
they’ve defeated many
strong opponents successively.
They’ve proved to us that
they’re eligible for the grand final.
Martial Soul Hall School
has always been the champion
for the past grand finals.
Xie Yue, Yan and Hu Liena are
the youngest generations who obtained
Badge of Purple Record in history.
They’re known as the Golden Generation
of Martial Soul Hall School.
Xie Yue’s martial soul,
Moon Blade is extremely peculiar.
Ordinary people who use it
are more likely to hurt themselves.
But he can use it deftly,
doubling the powerful attack
of the martial soul itself.
It’s really terrifying!
[Xie Yue, Martial Soul Hall School]
Hu Liena’s martial soul, Devil Fox.
She has been known as Sky Fox all along.
It’s said that Sky Fox
has the ability to fly over the sky.
How amazing is Hu Liena’s strength?
Let’s look forward to it.
[Hu Liena, Martial Soul Hall School]
[Tang San, Shrek School]
[Dai Mu Bai, Shrek School]
[Zhu Zhu Qing, Shrek School]
This person can use the flame as well.
Is his beast soul having a flame attribute
which is the same as Fatty’s?
It’s not easy. Flame Lord.
Since he dares to name himself
as the Flame Lord,
his ability must have exceeded
the scope of flame attribute.
[Yan, Marital Soul Hall School]
These three are extraordinary.
They’re indeed the
Golden Generation of Martial Soul Hall.
Bibi Dong, they’re the ones that you chose.
The two War Soul Sects
from Storm Attack Branch,
Sun Chuan Tao,
and Li Kai.
[Li Kai, Martial Soul Hall School]
In the previous battle,
they didn’t reveal their real strength.
[Ma Hong Jun, Shrek Schook]
Will Shrek spur them on today?
[Xiao Wu, Shrek School]
Zhang Ping, War Soul Sect of Keen Attack Branch,
Xu Yu, Tool Soul Sect of Support Branch.
They didn’t reveal their strength.
How will they perform their strength today?
[Ning Rong Rong, Shrek School]
[Oscar, Shrek School]
Xiao Gang, you’ve changed the formation as expected.
There’ll be only one winner.
Who will be the champion in the end?
I announce that
the battle between Martial Soul
Hall School and Shrek School
begins now.
Second Soul Skill, Fox Charm.
Even the best charm skill needs its triggers of
hearing, sight, taste, smell,
tactile and sensation.
It’s released through one of the six.
Hu Liena from Martial Soul Hall team
relies on sight and hearing mainly.
So let’s do it in this way tomorrow.
Second Soul Skill, Charm.
Unexpectedly, they counter the charm with charm.
The one with stronger strength
would have an advantage over the other.
Xiao Wu!
Although Xiao Wu is injured,
she has undoubtedly broken
Hu Liena’s initiated skill.
Xiao Wu.
Fourth Soul Skill,
Bright Static Moon.
Martial Soul Fusion Skill, Genie Mesmerize.
The Martial Soul Fusion Skill of
Xie Yue and Hu Liena
can trap someone,
suppressing their multiple abilities.
Can Little San cope with it?
Yu Tian Heng has already realized
that he couldn’t win in that battle.
But he still took the risk to battle
to force them using their trump in advance.
As expected,
the outsiders couldn’t see
what’s happening in the red mist.
You can’t see it either?
This red mist is extremely weird.
I think
only those whose soul power
and spirit power at its peak
could figure out its mystery.
This is Genie Mesmerize.
I’ve never heard of
the form of Martial Soul Fusion Skill
will appear in a humanoid figure.
Did they fuse in such quick manner before this?
It’s the skill of the
soul master of Support Branch,
making them complete the fusion in an instant.
Why didn’t Shrek Seven Devils interrupt
their Martial Soul Fusion Skill?
Is the current situation
also a part of Grandmaster’s plan?
If so, why did he do so?
[Next Episode]
This thick red mist
mixes with power containing
a sense of ruthlessness and hallucination.
Don’t act rashly.
Before Seven in One
Martial Soul Fusion Skill is exerted,
they’re engulfed by the red mist.
The world’s first martial soul of Support Branch
is really threatening.
I’ll settle you first.
How could be this possible?
You’re right. Unless you can fly.
Then, we’ll fly.
Taste it, Tang San.
Once Xie Yue uses the skill,
it means you have no way to stay alive.