♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind,
you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Little Ao.
We can’t be together
because I’m not a soul master
from Attack Branch.
Rong Rong, will you wait for me?
Ten years. Wait me for ten years.
Scan everything on earth,
eradicate all injustice.
Purple God Light.
All complete.
The 81st hammering.
Next, use this to practice.
Wooden hammer is influenced by
both buoyancy and water impulse.
So, it needs precise strength
comparing to forging hammer.
He’ll surprise us in the near future
and the soul masters’ community as well.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 111]
Victory belongs to Shrek.
Same dream again.
Nana, we’re going to
Death Valley for training.
Have you done packing?
Death Valley?
I can’t accept it.
I can’t accept.
The 81st hammering.
Accomplished.
Combining Hao Tian Hammer and
secret weapon of Tang Clan
together with my spirit power
directing at the rivals,
it’s impossible for them to escape it.
Unless their spirit power transcends mine
or they possess
the ability like teleport.
Months ago, I’ve unsealed his soul power
for the training on Hao Tian Hammer.
Under the condition without soul ring,
Little San has trained his Hao Tian Hammer
to the utmost level.
Your soul power has reached Level 52.
The improvement of my soul power
is getting slower
after breaking through
Level 50 last year.
Even the Hao Tian Hammer
is getting hard to practice.
It’s a watershed
between Level 50 to 60.
Back then, I used 5 years to accomplish.
But I’ve set your goal for 4 years.
Is this Dad’s expectation of me?
Dad.
Training of Skill of Random Hammering
ends today.
Little San, what do you think about
your combat capability?
Still lacking far behind.
Do you know where you’re lacking?
Theoretically,
Grandmaster’s tutelage is profound.
But, you lack the essence of combating.
The essence?
Heinous spirit.
Purple Demon Eye.
Heinous spirit turns substantial.
Master once told me that
when a person’s strength
has reached a terrifying level
he’s able to do this.
Feel it?
This is heinous spirit.
It helps you to display your strength
to the greatest extent.
Even when confronting rivals
far more formidable than yourself,
you’ll never give in either.
Heinous spirit itself
is not terrifying,
but the possessor
who has experienced countless deaths.
A person who doesn’t fear
death nor his rivals.
Dad, how could I possess it?
Later, I’ll bring you to a place where
you can cultivate this spirit.
Slaughter City?
Your Holiness, I’m willing to risk
for Martial Soul Hall.
You might not be able to return
if you go there for training.
Isn’t Death Valley better?
No, Your Holiness.
Though Death Valley is dangerous,
I knew you’ve sent Lord Yue Guan
to protect us secretly.
As such, I can’t truly experience death,
and never able
to transcend over Tang San.
It has been two years,
yet you can’t forget that failure.
If I forget the failure,
how could I be worthy of your tutelage?
I hope you won’t send anyone to protect me
on the journey to Slaughter City.
Please allow me to grow independently.
Fine, I approve it.
Whether as the Pope of Martial Soul Hall
or as your teacher,
I hope
you’ll return alive.
I will, Teacher.
Absorb it before you leave.
This is too precious, Teacher.
This precious thing must be used
to prove its high value.
[Soul Land]
After absorbing the Skull Bone,
my soul power has advanced a great deal.
Should you encounter Tang San alone,
never fight with him.
I’ll settle him one day.
And his father as well.
Our plan will definitely be hindered,
if we don’t settle Tang Hao.
Yes, Teacher.
Tang San, the humiliation you caused me,
I want you to repay with your life.
Before cultivating the heinous spirit,
you must obtain
the fifth soul ring first.
Yes.
Finally, I can obtain
the fifth soul ring.
Sit.
Sit down, release
the Blue Silver Plant and feel it.
This is familiar.
King, My Great King, is it you?
King?
You’ve finally come to me,
thank Heaven.
Are you calling me?
Who are you?
Why are you calling me King?
On this continent, except you,
I’m the oldest Blue Silver Plant
Your blood is more noble than mine.
Hence, you’re
the Emperor of Blue Silver Plant.
I’m not your King. I’m a human
who possess Blue Silver Plant
as my martial soul.
No, I won’t mistake it.
The aura around you is
the Empress of Blue Silver Plant.
If your martial soul is an ordinary
Blue Silver Plant,
do you think you can reach this level?
You’re possessing the royal blood
of the Blue Silver.
Old Freak once mentioned that
my Blue Silver Plant is uncommon.
There’re two conditions of
Twin Martial Souls.
Firstly,
the nature of parents’ martial souls
has great variance.
Secondly,
the quality of
parents’ martial souls is very close.
Meaning to say,
the quality of your mother’s
martial soul, Blue Silver Plant
is very close to
your father’s martial soul.
All Blue Silver lines are your people.
Haven’t you felt
their calls towards you?
Calls?
Every Blue Silver Emperor in this world
is from the same origin.
Only when
the last Blue Silver Emperor died,
the next emperor will appear.
Although you’re a human,
but, you’re the only one who possesses
the royal blood of Blue Silver Emperor.
I always thought that my strength
originates from my special practice.
This is our mistake.
Because your royal blood hasn’t awaken.
My martial soul has once awaken,
is it going to awake again?
My Great King.
how could ordinary people awaken
your noble blood?
As your loyal subject,
we’ll always protect you.
Do you wish to shelter
your subjects forever?
I do.
It has been twenty years,
I haven’t felt the king’s aura.
King, please feel the loyalty
of your subjects.
Mom.
My Great King, please rest assure.
The real Blue Silver Emperor
has finally awaken.
[Next Episode]
Give me two shots of Netherworld.
No, Dad.
Your injury is severe.
If you don’t take good care,
possibly you’ll...
Don’t bother about me.
How could I?
If you die,
how about me?
Cut that crap.
I hate cowardice.
Ah Yin.
Mom.
This is
the real form of my Blue Silver Plant.
Yes, King.
Its name is...