♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Continental Soul Master
Elite Tournament,
The champion goes to
Shrek School.
It seems like
this’s an unavoidable bloody fight.
Seize that girl.
Hold on.
Why are you seizing my disciple?
Do you want to know the reason?
Why don’t you ask your disciple then?
If I’m not mistaken,
You’re the one that we missed out back then.
What did you say?
I want to revenge for mum.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 107]
Silly girl, nothing to worry about.
Regardless of whether
you’re a human being or a soul beast,
you’re always my sister
and my beloved one.
The relationship between Brother San
and Xiao Wu has transcended life.
Brother.
To seize her, step over my body first.
Xiao Gang, don’t let our tragedy happen again.
I’ll never allow the same tragedy to repeat.
Mother.
Er Long, I won’t allow it since I’m here.
Xiao Gang.
do you really want to go against me
for a soul beast?
Seven Devils unite as one in life and death.
In life and death.
Rong Rong.
And us too.
Well said. I’ll fulfill your wish.
Kids, it’s not your turn yet to stand before us
since we are here.
If you can go back alive,
remember to give all money
that I kept in the back room of my study
to Zhao Wu Ji.
Ask him to manage Shrek School well.
Boss Fu, you...
Dean is eager for money,
but he values relationships more.
Today, Shrek stays together in life and death.
Moon and Sun Brilliance Intertwine.
Don’t forget I’m part of Shrek School.
Old Freak.
Martial Soul Hall has no enemies.
But, it might be hard to make it this time.
Their target is Little Freak and Xiao Wu.
If both of them are taken away, the rest will be safe.
I can’t move.
Century Millennium Soul Ring.
Is this the real power of
Century Millennium Soul Ring?
This...
That’s Mom’s soul ring.
Shrek fears nothing.
Bibi Dong, Shrek will never give in.
Your Holiness.
No mercy for
those who resist.
Get them.
Luo San Pao.
Cocky.
Too bad, we’re oppressed completely.
Is that all you have?
Martial Soul Hall, why do I fear you?
Old Venom Freak, get ready to die.
Xiao Wu, run.
Run? Where to?
Sixth Soul Skill, Bloodsucking Spider Thorns
Xiao Wu, run!
Mom.
Run!
Run?
[Soul Land]
Xiao Wu.
Mom, I’m sorry.
Bring this along and stay alive.
Don’t worry, you both will reunite very soon.
I must fight more time for Xiao Wu.
Eighth Soul Skill, Streamers Strike.
Invincible Golden Shield.
Golden Shield?
What a strong energy flux.
Could it be...
Futile struggle.
Under Invincible Golden Shield,
you can’t stop me
and never ever get my soul ring and soul bone.
Kill yourself?
Ask my permission first.
Sixth Soul Skill, Immortal Strike.
Unfortunately,
my sixth soul skill can defeat any physical defence.
Twin Martial Souls.
It’s over.
Xiao Wu, you must live on.
I’ll never escape again.
Brother, please stay alive, promise me.
I’m Xiao Wu, the “Wu” from dance.
Can I not call you Brother?
I promise to never leave Brother,
even if I die.
Brother, please remember,
if you die, I’ll die with you.
No!
Darn it.
Xiao Wu!
Mother, let me protect you this time.
No, run!
You’re as stupid as your mom.
Don’t you ever think of using that skill.
Old Ghost, stop her.
Never let them fuse together.
Too naive.
What if many people want to kill me one day
and you’re not able to fight against them?
Let them step over my dead body first.
♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
This is...
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond, conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your solitary braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
One little chrysanthemum and
one little ghost.
How dare you hurt my son?
Scram!
Tang Hao.
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance,
I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond, conflicts and war never stops ♪
Martial Soul Hall, I’m back.
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your solitary braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ Looking beyond, conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind,
you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your solitary braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[Next Episode]
Martial Soul Hall,
what you have owed me,
I want you to repay one day.
If Tang Hao didn’t present today,
perhaps none of us could leave here.
Let them leave.
Get out of Martial Soul Hall now.
I should lock you up
and kill you
when Tang San needs you.
You’re the first man to comb my hair
and the only one.
Forever.