♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[Previous Episode]
Ah Yin confessed to me that
she was a Century Millennium Soul Beast,
Blue Silver Emperor.
I thought
we’d be living happily ever after.
Martial Soul Hall
found out Ah Yin’s identity.
Stop her, everyone.
Farewell, my love.
Those people from Martial Soul Hall
went to Hao Tian Tribe again.
Elder Brother was forced to remove me
and close down the tribe.
I want you to help to rebuild the tribe.
Dad, I’ll definitely make it.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 122]
Open it.
After I tell you everything,
you may return to the tribe.
I want you to help rebuild the tribe.
This is the feeling of life.
Among the six soul bones,
the right leg bone ranks close to the last.
However, the quality of this soul bone
surpasses the other two.
This feeling of life
can only be produced by
Century Millennium Soul Beast.
This is what your mom left to you.
Absorb the soul bone
that your mom left to you.
Dad.
I think she’d be very happy to see this.
Is Mom urging me?
Little San.
Thank you, Mom.
Seeing you being so independent,
I’m happy for you.
Take care of yourself and your dad.
Please hand
the other two soul bones over to your uncle
once you return to the tribe.
You’ve greatly changed.
As for your physique,
you’d definitely rank top three
in the entire continent.
Dad, how about the training of
the twin martial souls?
After your Blue Silver Emperor
reaches the ninth ring,
you can obtain soul rings
for your Hao Tian Hammer as you wish.
As long as your body can take it,
I think you keep training for it.
Understood.
I was too strict to you in the past.
You may come back every year
to visit me and your mom.
I won’t leave here again.
Neither will I hurting myself.
Dad,
if the external factors
can accelerate the growth,
would it help shorten
Mom’s time for training?
To possess wisdom,
she has to train for 10,000 years.
And it takes century millennium years
to transform into human again.
I won’t have the chance to see that.
No, Dad.
I know a place
that can help plants
grow thousands of times faster.
Perhaps there’s a chance
for Mom to recover.
Thousands of times faster? Really?
Yes.
After discussing with
the Elders of the Elder Hall,
there’re three major decisions
to be announced.
Firstly, as the Pope,
I’ve confirmed my successor
and it has been approved by the Elder Hall.
From today onwards,
I confer the Holy Lady, Hu Liena
as the first successor to the Pope.
She’s about to reach
Level 60 at such a young age.
This has never happened
in the history of Martial Soul Hall.
Nana is no doubt more gifted than me.
She has been the most hardworking one
amongst the three of us.
Although Nana is my successor,
she’s got all the honor with her own effort.
I believe that you’ve heard that
she has obtained the Death God Domain.
Secondly, according to
our years of investigation,
the Century Millennium Soul Beast that
appeared in the Soul Master Contest
is currently at Star Dou Forest.
Da Ming, why do you come out at this time?
Sister Wu,
I hate to see you being so lonely.
You’ve been like this
for the past five years.
Is the human world that good?
No, it’s not the human world that I miss,
but my human friends.
Da Ming, Er Ming, don’t worry about me.
I’m alright.
Sister Wu.
Previously, those humans we met
in the forest has escaped.
Whether you have the desire
to go back to the human world or not,
don’t leave Star Lake recently.
Big Brother and I can better protect you here.
Just let them come.
Back then, if we had been here,
your mother wouldn’t have...
Sister Wu, I’m sorry.
I didn’t mean to make you sad on purpose.
It’s okay,
it has already been many years.
Besides, I’ve found those
who killed my mom.
One day,
I’ll kill them with my own hands
to avenge her.
Yue Guan, Gui Mei, you two lead a group of
20 cardinals of above Level 70
as well as Xie Yue and Yan
to search the Star Dou Forest.
She must be captured alive and
brought back to me.
Yes.
Tang San, Shrek School.
I want you to experience the extreme pain.
[Soul Land]
Well, stop worrying about me.
Sister Wu, is the human world interesting?
Tell us about your story in that world.
Brother, how are you?
I wonder when I could see you again.
Don’t worry. I’ll keep on training.
After entering the mature period,
I’ll definitely go and find you.
Dad, this is Ice Fire Mouth Spring.
Ah Yin’s very happy.
It seems like we’re at the right place.
Yes, let Mom rest here then.
Little San, don’t force it.
It’s okay if your mom
can’t recover faster.
Don’t hurt her due to maladjustment.
Mom, are you worried about me?
Little San, stop.
Your mom likes here very much.
Dad, this place is not suitable for humans.
It may harm you
if you stay here for a long time.
As long as your mom is fine,
it doesn’t matter.
No.
Mom finally has the hope of recovery,
how can you let anything happen to you?
Dad, I have an idea.
Thirdly, I’ve decided to start the
Soul Hunting Manoeuvre.
Simultaneously, cleanse the Seven Great Tribes.
Soul Hunting Manoeuvre?
After enduring for twenty years,
the Pope has finally decided to take action.
Your Holiness, please reconsider it.
Silence.
Regarding this matter,
I’ve discussed with the Elders
and we’ve decided that
Soul Hunting Manoeuvre will begin in a month.
The main force will be sent by
The Sacred Temple
and every Martial Soul Temple
and Main Hall
must follow
The Sacred Temple’s order strictly.
No mistake is allowed.
I’ll be in charge of this operation.
If anything goes wrong,
I won’t let you go off easily.
Yes. Your Holiness.
I want the Seven Great Tribes to know
who is the true master
of this continent.
Dad, eat it
so you can stay by Mom’s side here.
The concoction of this pill is my blood
which can blend with
two premium herbs.
It can save you from later worries.
You may set off in a moment.
I’m here. You don’t need to worry.
Dad, when can I go and find Xiao Wu?
After reaching Level 60
and obtaining the soul ring.
By then,
probably she has entered the mature period.
But before this,
avoid showing yourself in Martial Soul Hall.
Very soon, I’ll reach Level 60 which is a bottle neck.
I can meet her by that time.
Before you go looking for her,
make a trip back to the tribe first.
Accomplish what I’ve told you.
I believe you’ll do it well.
Remember, you’re my only son.
Dad, be rest assured. I know what to do.
Hao Tian Tribe was
once the most prestigious tribe.
How can it end up like this?
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 122 has been completed
and broadcasted for nearly 1228 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 1839]
[Total scene: 47218]
[Total CGI: 24742]
[Total plan of action scene: 10016]
[Total scene model: nearly 501]
[Total character model: nearly 935]
[Total props model: 13343]
[Appreciate your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
[Next Episode]
How does he know my name?
Could it be...
Tribe Chief ordered us
to bring you directly to him.
We’re not going to show you around.
Frankly,
I’ve never thought that it was his fault.
Now, the situation
in the tribe is complex.
The team leading by your uncle...
These are what Dad asked me to bring here.
Stay by your mom’s side...
Expel him from the tribe.
Eradicate his martial soul.