♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Do you want to compete with our tribe in speed?
Your steps are wonderful.
I hope that
you can join Tang Clan.
Kid.
You’re very ambitious.
So close.
I can’t dodge him
just by Ghostly Trace.
It seems like I need to be more serious
to capture you.
This young man is not simple.
He founded Tang Clan
and is planning to fight the Martial Soul Hall.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 144]
Tang San is doomed to lose.
Seventh soul skill, martial soul form!
If a martial soul form is released,
the soul master’s body will become bigger
in order to endure more soul power.
Why did Master Bai reduce in size?
What do you know?
Grandpa is compressing his soul power
forcefully
in order to gain an extreme speed.
Tang San.
I didn’t want to bully a junior
with my martial soul form.
Why don’t you show me how well you can defend
with your secret weapon?
Alright.
Senior, be careful.
You should be careful instead.
He disappeared?
No way.
Blue Silver Domain!
God Killer Domain!
Fairly well, Tang San.
Let me try this skill!
Eighth Soul Skill, Swirling Swift!
He split into seven forms.
Which is his real form?
Every clone
can be my real form.
Even the strongest Grand Soul Land Master
can’t catch up with the extreme speed of
Grandpa’s clones.
Tang San actually...
You haven’t seen the real strength
of Brother San.
Purple Demon Eye!
The key to win
is to find his real form.
Even if your Brother San is impressive,
that’s his capability.
What does that have to do with you?
Now’s the time!
You’re the one!
What?
They penetrate through them.
That’s bad.
I think you’re just his attendant.
Whatever.
How would you know
about our relationship?
Xiang!
Brother San!
Master Bai!
There are only 15 minutes left.
Tang San!
You have no way to escape now!
Century Millennium Soul Ring?
What is that?
This soul skill is so mysterious.
I can’t touch Tang San at all.
I didn’t use my soul skill.
Can it be...
Xiao Wu?
Xiao Wu.
It turns out that your soul has been
accompanying me.
Senior Bai He.
I surrender.
Your sixth soul skill is so strong.
Why did you surrender?
That was a form of my sixth soul skill.
Nothingness.
It allows me to avoid every physical attack
and weaken every energetic attack,
but that has nothing to do with speed.
I lost.
No.
Since I used my eighth soul skill
to increase my speed and the range of control,
you can also use any skill to
avoid being touched.
This is fair.
If we move on,
I will lose.
Enough.
Stop being humble.
You’ve been friends through this game.
Let’s treat it as a draw.
As for Tang Clan...
Come.
Old White Bird.
This...
I’ve heard about your situation from them.
I didn’t know that you’re Tang Hao’s son.
Today, I’ve seen
you and Tang Clan’s capabilities too.
But...
Come!
Old White Bird.
Doesn’t the Tribe of Agility
hope to become stronger?
With Tang Clan’s secret weapons,
you have nothing to be afraid of.
I understand.
You have good intentions.
But, in these years,
Old Goat has been supporting me.
I need to consider his feelings.
Judging from Old Goat’s temper
and his resentment against Hao Tian Tribe,
I’m afraid that he won’t accept Tang Clan.
Senior.
If the Tribe of Destruction is
willing to join Tang Clan,
will the Tribe of Agility join too?
[Soul Land]
But Old Goat is more stubborn than both of them.
I know him the best.
He’s arrogant and obstinate.
If he wasn’t like that,
the Tribe of Destruction
wouldn’t have experienced
such a big loss.
It’s not easy
to persuade him.
Leave it to me.
If I succeed,
those Four Tribes may reunite.
Old Goat is reaching tomorrow.
Let’s drink
today!
Come.
Brother San.
Just now, that was...
Xiao Wu’s soul.
I will never use it again.
At least I’m sure that
Xiao Wu is always by my side.
This is enough.
As long as she actually exists,
I will definitely revive her.
Let’s drink!
This brat!
You!
One more bowl!
Hey!
Miss Bai.
What’s wrong?
Today,
you did well too.
I shouldn’t have said that
you’re an attendant of Tang San.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I’ve never expected that a pretty lady
would apologize to me one day.
I didn’t mean that.
But noble girls wouldn’t
look at me right in the face normally.
Not to mention an apology.
How am I a noble girl?
People of our tribe have been living in poverty
for so many years.
We can only rely on other tribes.
Grandpa has to let go of his dignity
and beg others.
But I heard that
all the Four Tribes refused
the subsidies for their soul masters
offered by the Martial Soul Hall.
Who would accept their help?
If it wasn’t for the Martial Soul Hall,
we wouldn’t end up like this.
One day,
I will revitalize our tribe.
I’ll show all the soul masters
how mighty our Tribe of Agility is!
Do you think that
I’m not capable enough
and without self-knowledge
by saying these?
I just
thought of a few of my brothers.
Do you mean
Tang San
and...?
I,
Brother San
and another five friends.
We experienced a lot of things together.
They are like you too.
They have goals.
They have the courage and
determination to reach their goals too.
What about you?
Me?
I have no ambition.
I’ll be glad as long as I can live happily
without worrying about my livings.
But...
If it is for the people that I care about,
I will throw myself in like them.
I’m sorry.
I will never do that again.
Today,
thank you for saving me.
But it doesn’t mean anything else.
You’d better get rid of all your bad intentions.
Or else,
I will hit you whenever I see you!
You’re the most hardworking young man
that I’ve seen.
You’re overpraising me, Senior.
I’m just used to getting up early to practice.
Little San.
Can I call you this
privately?
Of course.
You’re the senior.
Actually,
your grandma is my biological sister.
Considering our relationship,
you should call me Granduncle.
My sister died at a young age.
We raised
her kids,
including your father.
Granduncle.
The case back then...
I know.
Your father would never offend
the Martial Soul Hall
out of impulse.
So, we didn’t really blame him.
But it doesn’t mean that
Old Goat will be convinced
because of their old friendship.
What kind of person
is Senior Yang Wu Di?
His skill
is the strongest among us, the four leaders.
Neither Old Gorilla’s power,
nor Old Rhino defense,
nor my agility
can defeat his destruction.
Besides, they have
their pharmaceutical techniques.
Pharmaceutical techniques?
Drugs?
Granduncle.
You mean that...
Old Goat is into drug production.
to the point where he forgets to sleep and eat.
Your strength now
can’t be compared to his.
To convince him,
you have to start with drugs.
This is
an heirloom of the Tribe of Agility.
I’ve been hiding it
from Old Goat.
Take it.
It might help you.
Crystal Bloody Dragon?
It grows from the eighth grade
and evolves for ten thousand years.
This is
a 5,000-year-old
Crystal Bloody Dragon Ginseng.
Five thousand years later,
it will evolve into the ninth grade.
Such premium herb
is rare.
It’s a priceless treasure.
Granduncle.
I can’t take this.
Little San.
This is a gift from your granduncle.
The future of the Tribe of Agility
depends on you.
I believe that you won’t disappoint me.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 144 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 13682 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2160]
[Total scene: 53862]
[Total CGI: 26632]
[Total plan of action scene: 11543]
[Total scene model: nearly 533]
[Total character model: nearly 989]
[Total props model: 13368]
[We appreciate
your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next Episode]
Brother San.
People from the Tribe of Destruction is here.
If the four of our tribes join in hands,
there will be about a thousand soul masters.
He’s Tang Hao’s son.
Xiao Wu.
Old Goat is angry.
How many more skills are you hiding from us?
Brother San.
Or else,
don’t blame me for killing you!
[Soul Land]
[Available at 10 AM every Saturday]