♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
There’s only one champion.
So these soul bones
will belong to the champion.
Hold on.
Shrek School renounces the individual match.
We renounce this match
and fight with Shrek School
for the grand final’s quota.
Don’t think that I’ll give in to you
even though you saved me.
I’ve paid for what I owed you.
This is Seven in One Fusion Skill.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 102]
Gale Devil Wolf 36 Successive Chops.
How can this happen?
Last time, Captain endured longer time
while competing with Tang San.
But he is defeated very quickly this time.
Damn. If we did manage to hinder Tang San last time,
this wouldn’t happen today.
Both were fusion skills.
Six teammates were working
together to support Little San.
But there were only three
behind Feng Xiao Tian.
The great difference
between the total soul power
made Little San have an overwhelming advantage.
Apart from that, Feng Xiao Tian
did the biggest mistake of
using the Gale Devil Wolf
36 Successive Chops again.
This is his most powerful ability.
It exerted enormous pressure to Little San last time.
Why shouldn’t he use it again?
The previous experience did
trigger Little San to conduct
an in-depth investigation.
He realized
Gale Devil Wolf 36 Successive Chops
has a similar defect as Random Air Hammer Skill,
in which
its power can’t exert at all
once it’s interrupted at initial of its exertion.
The successive chops and increases of power
are the most terrifying strengths of the skill.
While Feng Xiao Tian was accelerating,
Hao Tian Hammer was
thrown accurately by Little San on him.
It was just in time that Feng Xiao Tian
hadn’t fully exerted his power yet.
With Little San’s peculiar sight and technique,
he must have known
Feng Xiao Tian’s motion track.
He managed to shot at his wings,
instead of his chest.
This saved Feng Xiao Tian’s life. But...
this put Little San into a riskier position.
As much of Hao Tian Hammer’s
ability is being exposed,
Martial Soul Hall’s intention of killing
him will be more determined.
The size of the hammer is bigger than Little San’s body.
Yet, he can still hold it steadily.
The atmosphere changed.
Brother San seems to have fused
with Hao Tian Hammer as one already.
Tool soul form!
No. This is impossible.
He’s just at his Level 43.
How can he perform the
tool soul form of above Level 70?
Although the Seven in One Fusion Skill
that I taught them
is not as great as
the Martial Soul Fusion Skill,
it can gather everyone’s powers
to exert as one.
By the time, Little San’s soul power
is the result of superimposed
soul power of seven persons.
Plus the superimposed increase of
Qibao Amber Pagoda,
Little San’s soul power
is even more advanced
to Level 70 and above.
This is why
Little San can break the soul power gap
of 30 levels incredibly
and being able to control
the tool soul form.
The seventh soul skill of beast soul master
must be the martial soul form,
transforming himself as the martial soul itself.
It has enormous explosive power.
Its strength is increased by infinite times.
However, the seventh soul skill of tool soul master
is the tool soul form,
transforming himself as
the tool martial soul itself.
It makes the tool martial soul’s power
rise to an extreme.
If the tool martial soul itself is very powerful,
the explosive power of tool martial soul form
will be more terrifying than it.
They have not given up yet.
They’re indeed the respectable
opponents for the kids.
Hao Tian Hammer. Random Air Hammer Skill.
They’ve already defeated the opponents.
But Little San still want to use Random Air Hammer Skill?
I’m afraid that the whole auditorium
will be destroyed in one blow.
This astonishing power is...
The world’s first tool martial soul,
Hao Tian Hammer.
Stop!
Dad!
Restrain your power.
Withdraw your soul.
No. How come he’s here?
It should be Master.
This is tool soul form.
It’s not only the soul power,
I feel myself to be fused with
Hao Tian Hammer as one.
So that the genuine
martial soul form can be used.
Restrain.
Fortunately, without Master’s reminding in time,
I might have lost control
and my soul might be drained as well.
I announced that the winner
of this round is Shrek School.
Great!
Tomorrow’s final round
will be kicked off in between
Martial Soul Hall School and Shrek School.
Master, thanks to you.
Unexpectedly,
you can even use the tool soul form
of Hao Tian Hammer.
It’s exactly the world’s first tool martial soul.
It’s my mistake.
The kids have been exhausted for today.
Let’s head back to have some minor
adjustments and plan for the next.
All right.
[Soul Land]
Although everyone seems to be fine,
the soul power has actually depleted greatly,
especially Little San.
He has used the tool soul form.
His soul power might have been drained.
Little San, will your soul power
recover to its optimum state
for tomorrow’s final round?
I have foundation strengthening medicines.
It’s not a problem for the soul power to recover.
Plans can’t keep up with the changes.
I’ve made a false forecast.
Grandmaster, we’ve defeated
Shen Feng School in this round.
This can be said as a perfect victory.
Right.
Seven in One Fusion Skill was delivered
by Grandmaster to us before the match
and Little San was asked to give the command
to defeat the opponents in the fastest speed.
The tactic was well executed, wasn’t it?
If I knew in advance that
Little San can use tool soul form,
it would be a different tactic for today.
By having tool soul form of Hao Tian Hammer,
I have nearly 70% certainty
to compete with Martial Soul Hall School.
But revealing it in prior now
would make things worse.
Is it possible for them
to figure out our Seven in One
Fusion Skill by just one night?
Others than that, the opponent team tomorrow
is supported by Martial Soul Hall.
There are countless talents
and the Grand Soul Land Masters
in Martial Soul Hall.
They can always come up
with the countermeasures.
Did you understand what I’ve told you just now?
Understood, Your Holiness.
If Tang San uses the tool soul form again tomorrow,
he’ll either died or injured.
It’s unnecessary to care about it.
You only need to focus on
the Seven in One Fusion Skill.
Destroy it as what I’ve told just now.
By your genuine strength,
they’re impossible to be your opponents.
Yes.
You’d have known that
the benefits of this tournament.
It’s a chance to make you famous.
It also decides
the ownership of the three soul bones.
There are Qibao Amber Tribe
and many Advanced Soul Master Schools
paying attention to this.
Martial Soul Hall couldn’t break the promise.
Moreover,
Little San couldn’t perform the tool soul form
again for the time being.
Otherwise, he’ll be suffered
from unforeseen trauma.
It may affect his future as well.
Tool soul form and martial soul form
have the same effects of different natures,
or even more powerful.
The most terrifying part of the tool soul form
is to fuse the soul master himself with
tool martial soul itself as one.
It will use up the spirit power.
Spirit power?
It’s different from soul power.
The spirit power can only be
supplied by soul master himself.
With the current strength of Little San,
his spirit is still far from a stable state.
If he keeps it on,
his spirit will suffer from severe trauma.
For the minor trauma, he’ll lose memory
and become unresponsive.
For the severe trauma,
he’ll become unconscious at all.
This comes as a reward,
as well as the pressure for all of you.
If you’re defeated,
I’ll send you all to Disorienting Grand Canyon
for three-year cultivation.
Disorienting Grand Canyon, a sinister place
where only ghosts can survive.
We must win this tournament.
All right. You can go down now.
Yes.
Your Holiness, are you worrying?
Although they have the advantage over today,
in fact
the victory is still inclined to our side.
I’m not worried on Shrek Seven Devils.
They’re indeed talented,
but they’re still very young.
Their personal potentials
have not been fully explored yet.
Except Tang San, the others are
still ineligible to cause harm.
But their Grandmaster is distinct.
I’ve known him for many years.
I’ve never met someone
as wise as him in my lifetime.
The Seven in One Fusion Skill of
martial souls of different attributes
is the proof.
I admit that I’m incapable of
doing such a meticulous plan.
Are you worrying that
he’ll have any unusual plan
which may lead
to variables for tomorrow?
Why don’t I kill him now?
Even if Grand Venom Master is protecting them,
I still have 80% certainty
to kill him in one stroke.
Grandmaster, what should we do tomorrow?
Even if we can maintain
our optimum state for the battle,
the opponents’ soul powers
are much higher than ours.
They also have their Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
It’ll be really difficult for us to defeat them.
The difficulty is not absolute.
You’d start cultivating now.
I’ll carefully figure out
the tactics for tomorrow.
If you were that sure,
Tang San wouldn’t have arrived here alive.
Have you forgotten what our teacher
taught you in those years?
The effort is needed even for
the very tiny and easy matter.
Underestimating the enemy
is the greatest fear of the strategist.
Yes, Your Holiness.
If an Honourary Elder is being killed
casually in the Martial Soul Hall,
it’ll be a shame to Martial Soul Hall.
Moreover, he is from
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe.
Please remember, without my order,
nobody is allowed to act against him hereafter.
Yes.
It’s late now. You may leave first.
Xiao Gang, you still surprised me a lot.
Did our teacher really tear us apart back then?
All I can do is to protect you.
But I couldn’t care so much
for the others.
[Next Episode]
Kids,
this is your last battle before graduation.
Honestly,
it’s my pleasure to cultivate all of you
into the great geniuses.
Nothing lasts forever.
Your future path
relies on your own.
I’ve told all of you that
I won’t let you graduate
unless you obtain the champion.
But I change my mind now.
I’ll never allow anyone of you
to be injured or died.
What I want is neither the victory
nor the champion,
I just want all of you to be safe and sound.