♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind,
you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Mum.
Wake up, my son.
This is the original form of
Blue Silver Plant?
Yes, King.
Its name is
Blue Silver Emperor.
Let’s go.
We should move to the next training place.
No place for trash here.
Go back to your mother’s wing, brat.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 113]
Kill them all.
But, Dad...
Compassion to enemies,
is cruelty to yourself.
Everyone who survives to be here
depends on terminating others.
I’ll kill you first.
It’s a test. To enter Slaughter City.
Kill him.
Two black soul rings?
Soul King?
Fourth Soul Skill.
Blue Silver Spike Formation.
The sharpness is not lesser than
Eight Spider Bone.
Is this the power of Blue Silver Emperor?
You shouldn’t let anyone live.
Remember, after entering Slaughter City,
you can only depend on yourself.
Defeat all who threatens you.
Win the champion of Hell Slaughter Arena
and come back alive.
This is your training.
Slaughter City?
Dad, I’ll make it.
It’s nothing down there. Could it be?
This should be
the entrance of Slaughter City.
Spirit power
can’t pierce through this tunnel.
Welcome to Slaughter City.
This...
This is the capital of Hell,
a place where...
A place where...
you can obtain everything you desire.
Brother.
At the cost of your life.
Purple Demon Eye.
Stop there.
I’m Scott, the Dread Knight.
You’ve broken the rules.
Defeat me
is your pass to enter Slaughter City.
As you wish.
Can’t use soul skill?
That’s why Dad sealed
my soul power to train.
You’ve passed.
9528.
I’m here, Slaughter City.
A place where soul skill is forbidden.
Welcome to Slaughter City.
[Soul Land]
I’m your guide.
You’re under rookies protection
within 24 hours.
I’ll answer any questions you have.
After 24 hours,
you’ll become
an official member of Slaughter City
How did Slaughter City come about?
It has existed for thousands of years.
It’s a domain by a robust soul master
after he broke through the Level 100.
You can initiate martial soul here.
But soul skill is ineffective.
Soul power too?
You can use it as the source of power.
What about the rules?
The rule is no rules.
I’d say that
here is the paradise for crime.
Paradise for crime?
Yes. You’re forbidden
to leave once entered.
Let me out! I want to get out of here.
I don’t want to kill anymore, let me go.
There’re fools around.
The mighty Slaughter King
controls everything here.
Besides, the enforcement team is
formed from the Great Soul Land Masters
and they’re allowed to use soul skills.
Leaving without permission?
That’s impossible.
Is there any way out?
Only one way.
Win the champion of Hell Slaughter Arena,
challenge and pass through Hell Road,
you can leave here then.
Whoever triumphs the challenge
will be bestowed as Death God.
Death God?
But, only eight Death Gods
appeared over the past thousand years.
What?
Road to Hell, to Netherland.
Road of no return.
Here’s a rookie.
New shots of Netherland
is ready to be served.
She is the emissary of Slaughter King.
What’s wrong with them?
Currently, you’re at the outer city
of Slaughter City.
Not the real Slaughter City.
Some of them are
losers from Slaughter Arena.
They need to contribute
two shots of Netherland every month
to seek protection from Slaughter King.
Only the inner city
is not governed by any rules.
Bring me to Hell Slaughter Arena.
Are you sure?
I am.
Follow me.
A gang of thugs.
Hu Liena.
She has changed.
She’s immersed with sinister vibes
rather than charm whom she was.
What a strong heinous spirit.
She saved me?
Thank you.
You’re new?
My appearance has changed.
She didn’t recognise me.
You don’t look like a degenerate.
This place is dangerous.
You’d better be careful.
It seems like you’re a rookie,
but you don’t need my protection.
Anyway, don’t approach her.
Why?
She’s terribly strong.
Although she was here just a year,
however, she has won 16 times
on the Hell Slaughter Arena.
This result will qualify her
in the top 100.
Just 16 wins is able to rank top 100?
Do you think it’s same as
the battle in Soul Arena?
It’s quite horrifying
to maintain the result of 16 wins.
Thanks for your information.
Let’s go. Hell Slaughter Arena
is at the front.
The heart of Slaughter City.
[Next Episode]
Every time Death God appears
will cause countless deaths and injuries.
In case...
Can’t use the Hao Tian Hammer in time,
hidden weapon can’t pierce through
their armour as well.
This is our strategy.
This is the determination act.
In the past thousand years,
you’re the third from Hao Tian Tribe
to enter Slaughter City.
In Slaughter City,
friendship never exist here.