♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped by wind ♪
♪ Missed the farewell to my lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
This again.
Sixth Soul Skill, Dragon Killer Sword!
Actually,
I didn’t hate you that much.
Hurry, hurry.
Let’s go. Go.
So,
this is the Chief from the Tribe of Defense.
I am Tang San.
My father is Tang Hao.
As your father’s subordinates,
we were abandoned by him.
We have had enough suffering
thanks to Hao Tian Tribe!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 142]
He’s doomed.
It’s impossible for you to defend my fist
with 70% of my soul power.
Blue Silver Domain. God Killer Domain.
Activate.
What?
He deserves to be the Chief,
as he knows how to
offset an attack behind him
by using forward power.
Brilliant.
Master San stands still at the moment.
But why does he still punch at the same place?
No,
he has changed the way he punches.
I see.
This is...
I must stop him now.
Not only did Chief waver fist to defend him,
but also
to distract him
so as to gather strength.
Random Air Hammer Skill.
I can’t hold it off any longer.
So, is this Tang Hao’s son?
Random Air Hammer Skill.
Eighty-one
Strikes
in
One!
Old Rhino,
use your Martial Soul right now!
That is the only way.
What happened?
There was an earthquake.
Kid,
you won.
I used my Martial Soul just now.
I lost.
No need to wait for half an hour.
My word counts.
From now on,
we, the Tribe of Defense,
will no longer
hold grudges against
you and your father.
If you hadn’t been careless,
I wouldn’t have had the chance
to gather my strength, Senior.
Alright.
I did lose.
Am I such a person
that wouldn’t admit defeat?
You can stay.
I think you are indeed such a person.
You lost to this young man
at your strongest point, defensing.
You owe him some sort of a gesture.
What do you want?
Do you want me to
surrender to him with my tribe?
Not necessary.
But,
recently, Chief and I are about to
establish a clan named Tang Clan.
Are you in?
Knock it off.
Have you not had enough for Hao Tian Tribe?
Are we gonna suffer again?
Old Rhino,
I know what you are concerned about.
But, do you know
why I am in?
Why?
What I value
is his strength.
Did you know
the Soul Master Contest five years ago?
Of course I did.
Some boys from my tribe
joined the competition as well.
But they didn’t do well.
You are not as good as me in this field.
Tai Long is one of the members
of the champion team.
Great.
Boy,
you did a good job.
I heard that
the contest
is the most classic one
over the past few decades.
I am only a substitute.
I wasn’t even on the court
for the last match.
We defeated the Golden Generation
of Martial Soul Hall
thanks to Master San.
I was also one of the main players.
Tai Long,
why don’t you praise me?
Yes.
Fatty was also one of the main players.
He is much powerful than me.
Let’s go.
Now you get what I mean, right?
People from Martial Soul Hall
are also jealous of him.
He has a bright future.
But
I am afraid that
the whole world of soul masters will be reshuffled
in the near future.
I have to consider my tribe.
Dad.
Uncle Tai Tan.
Here comes the Chief of Elephant Armoured Tribe,
Huyan Zhen.
Why is he here?
Brother Niu,
how is it going?
Thanks to you, I am good.
Heavenly Elephant,
to what do I owe this pleasure?
I can see this dude is so strong.
Who is he?
He is my brother,
Tai Tan.
So he is from the Tribe of Strength,
Brother Tai Tan.
Perfect timing.
- Saved my trip to Tian Dou City.
- Do you see that he comes with a lot of people?
He’s here with so many skillful men.
Is he...
Just cut to the chase.
Okay.
Brother Niu,
you may have received
a letter from the Martial Soul Hall.
I am sure
you know the Upper Three exist
in name only nowadays.
The Martial Soul Hall has enacted a law.
A year later,
they will re-select the Seven Great Tribes.
What’s that got to do with us?
To be honest,
I want to be elected as
one of the Upper Three.
Well,
that’s why I’m here today.
I hope that you can support me.
What?
[Soul Land]
We can unite to work on it.
No one can
defend us.
As long as you agree,
then you will be the Deputy Chief
of Elephant Armoured Tribe.
What do you think?
Does he mean they can unite?
It sounds like a nice deal,
but actually,
the Tribe of Defense will be annexed by him.
Don’t you forget
who pushed us
like homeless dogs.
Brother,
don’t you even understand
the strength of Martial Soul Hall?
You can ask for anything you want.
They can satisfy you,
even if I can’t.
Huyan Zhen.
You are free to be their running dog.
I’m not interested.
Niu Gao.
I called you Brother
because I was trying to be nice.
Qibao Amber Tribe
and Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe
have come to a bad end.
Didn’t you see that?
Hao Tian Tribe did let us down,
but we, the Four Tribes,
have developed
relying on its power.
It is better to die with honor
than to live in infamy.
Kill me
if you can.
So,
I paid you respect but you rejected it.
Huyan Zhen.
I’d recommend you to call more people here
if you want to fight with me.
It’s enough for me to
fight with you and your tribe,
but the God of Strength, Tai Tan, is here too.
Okay.
Niu Gao.
I’ll see you soon.
I hope you will be as brave as you are today
when we meet again.
The bastards of Martial Soul Hall.
What do they want?
They are intimating you.
Not many people
like Senior Niu
are not afraid of them.
A year later,
as long as the Seven Tribes Re-selection Contest
are successfully held,
the new Seven Tribes
will be controlled by them.
He can see through.
I think
the Martial Soul Hall
will fight against
the two empires openly
when that contest is over.
What’s worse,
once the war begins,
that will be disadvantageous
for the two empires.
Old Gorilla introduced
your awesome weapon to me
in private.
Godly Zhuge Crossbow.
May I have a look?
Is this it?
How could it be a deterrent to them?
Wanna show me?
No problem.
My house
is indestructible.
Feel free to try.
This...
My house...
Old Rhino.
You didn’t expect that, right?
Don’t underestimate it.
In the attack,
Qibao Amber Tribe managed to survive
thanks to hundreds of hidden weapons like this one.
That battle...
Indeed, this is remarkable.
If we can mass-produce it
for war,
we may stand a chance to fight
with the Martial Soul Hall.
Senior Niu Gao,
I sincerely invite you
to join Tang Clan.
I know you still can’t forget
Hao Tian Tribe once abandoned you,
but I can guarantee you
Tang Clan
will never be taken over by Hao Tian Tribe.
It’s the right timing
for Chief to persuade him to join us.
Huyan Zhen violated
Old Rhino’s bottom line.
As a tribe chief,
he cares about his tribe’s life and death.
In the past few years,
we are separated into two different empires.
I miss the days
when we dined together every day.
Old Rhino,
would you make a bet
with me this time?
They are going too far.
Alright.
Old Gorilla,
I’m in.
Tang San.
Don’t forget what you said today.
My brother,
welcome on board.
Senior Niu,
Let’s go.
Let’s go for a drink
and have fun.
Let’s go.
Let’s drink all night
like we used to.
Speaking of the past,
it would be better
if Old White Bird and Old Goat are here with us.
Let’s drink
for three days.
Now that Tang Clan is so promising,
how about inviting Old White Bird?
He has a difficult time
with his Tribe of Agility.
That guy hates to be called that.
Don’t get him mad.
But
we can think about how to set him up.
They get close so fast
to discuss
how to invite Grandpa Bai.
Isn’t it better to invite more people to join us?
Please.
Here.
We are in the same clan now.
Suit yourself.
Let’s drink together.
There you go.
That’s what a young man is supposed to be.
Here.
One more.
You guys,
why didn’t you wait for me
to enjoy the good wine with you?
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[Episode 142 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1375 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2145]
[Total scene: 53594]
[Total CGI: 26562]
[Total plan of action scene: 11543]
[Total scene model: nearly 531]
[Total character model: nearly 983]
[Total props model: 13366]
[We appreciate
your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolor ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
girl is
so cool!
Ouch.
I am Bai Chen Xiang from the Tribe of Agility,
please have a friendly match.
I wonder who he is.
She moves much faster than I expect.
Her move is appealing.
Miss Bai,
thank you for indulging me.
Enough.
Boy.
How dare you!
But if you are overconfident,
you’re only asking for trouble.
[Soul Land]
[Available at 10 AM every Saturday]