♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to a lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
It seems like
you all have gone through a lot these years.
Since Oscar has obtained a soul ring,
you won’t give him
the soul bone as well, will you?
Losing your mom,
your dad cutting his limbs
and you’ve been forced to separate with Xiao Wu.
Little Ao hasn’t finished absorbing the ring yet,
I must give him more time.
Let’s make an end today.
I wonder where he is now.
I’m worried about his safety.
He’s just a soul master of Food Branch.
Fifth Soul Skill, Palm of the Giant.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 128]
Little Ao.
Little Ao has left to become
a different soul master of Food Branch.
This is his promise to you.
You have to believe that he’ll succeed.
Speaking of which,
you’re the icon of Shrek School.
Perhaps you should
make some contribution to our school.
Dean, how are you going to exploit us?
[Shrek School]
Shocking! Five of the Shrek Seven Devils
have come back!
Tomorrow, they will
have a showcase of skills
against the Dean Frander, and Teacher Zhao.
You will witness
the presentation of the amazing skills.
Spread this news.
Who do you think will win?
- The Dean, of course.
- Boss, well...
The five of them fighting together
has a high chance to win.
Er Long.
I told you to arrange an exhibition match.
What were you thinking?
Look what you’ve done.
Don’t you know how abnormal they are?
What’s more, I’m the Dean!
How could I expose my skills easily?
What if I leave
all school’s affairs to you
and I go for the match tomorrow instead?
Well...
You’ve been idling these days,
not doing any work at all.
You should make some contribution.
Give your students a performance,
show them your strength.
Mu Bai and Zhu Qing’s Martial Soul
Fusion Skill alone is hard enough to handle.
Not to mention
the attack from the other three.
I might drop a brick if I fail.
You’re not doing this alone.
Wu Ji and I are not taking turns?
Of course not. I’ve planned that
you two against them five together.
I know how powerful they are.
You’re my boss,
how could I let you make a gaffe?
Great. Two persons.
No matter how powerful
the five little freaks are,
they’re still under my control.
Boss, don’t underestimate them.
Never estimate those little freaks
by common sense.
Even if they’re geniuses among geniuses,
you can’t underestimate your big brother.
If Wu Ji and I can’t defeat the five of them,
we should retire then.
Really?
By the way, Er Long.
Have you collected ticket fees
from the students?
Boss, are you very short of money?
I remember the empire
has just allocated funds to us.
It’s just a habit.
Well, follow your plan then.
Fifth Soul Skill, Palm of the Giant.
What’s going on...
How could you use Hulk’s soul skill?
Take them down
since their soul power has been exhausted.
Do you dare to belittle
a soul master of Food Branch now?
Little San, Xiao Wu.
Brother Dai, Zhu Qing.
Fatty.
Rong Rong.
Finally, I can meet you.
Finally, I can protect you.
Little Ao.
[Soul Land]
Congrates, Little Ao. Your wish has finally come true.
Thanks for your help, Brother Hulk.
We’re buddies, don’t mention it.
Tell me about your sixth soul skill.
My sixth soul skill is Cloning Sausage.
The effect is cloning.
It must be made
with the blood of a soul master.
That’s why you could copy
my Snow Demon Bear.
If the soul power of the blood’s owner
is higher than mine,
I could display 70% of the power
of the soul skill equals to my level.
Otherwise, 80% of the power
from the blood owner’s skills.
It can last three minutes.
It will consume
much of your soul power while using it, right?
Yes, it consumes all my soul power
even just to present
70% of the power of another person’s soul skill.
Besides, with my current ability,
using the Cloning Sausage once
will take away one-third of my soul power
That’s why you fainted
since you’ve been severely injured.
Little Ao,
I’ve never seen such an excellent
soul master of Food Branch like you.
You’re truly a genius.
A real genius
is born with supreme glory.
As for me, I’ve spent my entire life
approaching that light.
Absorb the soul bone. I’ll protect you.
Brother, what are you doing?
I’m contented enough, obtaining the soul ring.
You deserve this soul bone.
The effect is maximized when one absorbs
the soul ring and the soul bone
of the same beast.
I’m sure you know this.
Besides, you’ve saved my life.
I didn’t save you not for repayment.
Frankly, I give you this soul bone
with my personal intention.
Think about it.
With your current achievement,
you’ll probably reach the legendary level of
Grand Soul Land Master of Food Branch.
Since you call me Brother,
I’ll rely on you later on.
Brother.
Rong Rong, wait for me.
Teachers, please take care of your students.
Don’t enter the match area.
Otherwise, you might get hurt at your own risk.
Little San, put on your mask.
Why, Master?
You impressed Martial Soul Hall greatly.
Although your appearance and vibes
have totally changed,
it’d be better not to expose yourself.
All of you should put on a mask as well.
It’s better to remain mysterious.
Seniors. Nice to meet you.
Five years ago,
your seniors
triumphed Soul Master Tournament
for our school.
The exhibition match today
is not for you to enjoy,
but to let you know
the strength of the graduates
from Shrek School.
Little freaks, announce your skill level.
Dai Mu Bai, Soul Emperor of Level 63,
from Storm Attack Branch.
Tang San, Soul King of Level 59,
from Controlling Branch.
Ma Hong Jun, Soul King of Level 57,
from Storm Attack Branch,
Ning Rong Rong, Soul Emperor
of Level 60, from Supporting Branch.
Zhu Zhu Qing, Soul Emperor of Level 60,
from Keen Attack Branch.
Shrek.
Well, please maintain silence.
For the coming match,
as long as the Shrek Five Devils can
withstand the attack from Teacher Zhao and me
for the time of
three sticks of incense,
they’ll win.
Teacher Liu, prepare the incense.
Boss, shall we go easy on them?
Have you forgotten how miserable
you were when Tang San first came?
Fight sensibly will do.
You’ll be the main force on the ground,
I’ll distract them in the air.
You’re using me as
the meat shield again?
Boss, how can you be so cruel.
Don’t worry.
I’ll support you fully from the air.
Just feel free to attack.
Zhao Wu Ji, Great Soul Land Master
of Level 81, from Storm Attack Branch.
Frander, Great Soul Land Master
of Level 83, from Keen Attack Branch.
Start now.
Buddies, it’s our turn.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 128 has been completed
and broadcasted for nearly 1277 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 1929]
[Total scene: 49148]
[Total CGI: 25376]
[Total plan of action scene: 10483]
[Total scene model: nearly 508]
[Total character model: nearly 962]
[Total props model: 13352]
[Appreciate your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
[Next Episode]
It’s written in the stars.
No.
I’ll terminate this damn destiny.
Everything is ready.
Start when the sky turns black.
Failure is not an option.
My current capability
is beyond what you saw today.
After all, they wouldn’t dare
to turn against the two empires.
You never do anything right.
Next, defeat them one by one.
If I get stronger earlier...
This day
has finally come.
[New episode available at 10 a.m. every Saturday]