♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Just a few days ago,
two out of Three Upper Tribes were gone.
Qibao Amber Tribe
and the Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe
are almost destroyed.
Tian Dou Empire must be their next target.
If you don’t train hard today,
next time, you will end up with
death and destruction.
Prick!
The relationship between them
is something I don’t understand.
Without you, everything is meaningless.
Be it my martial soul
or my cultivation.
I’ll definitely meet again in 20 years.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 137]
Emperor Xue Ye had four sons.
Xue Qing He is the eldest
and Xue Beng is the youngest.
The best out of the four wasn’t Xue Qing He,
but Second Prince.
But, Second Prince died when he was 12.
The next year, Third Prince died, too.
Was the death of these two princes
related to Xue Qing He?
No one could confirm without any evidence.
But, two days before Second Prince died,
Emperor Xue Ye just discussed about
crowning a prince with
a few high-ranked officials.
Most of the officials suggested Second Prince.
Was it done by someone behind Xue Qing He?
Actually, both of the princes died from poison.
But, all of the four princes stayed in the palace
at that time.
Their daily life was taken care of
by Emperor Xue Ye’s trusted followers.
Outsiders couldn’t get close to them
and wouldn’t have the chance to poison them.
Hence, the death of the two princes
became a cold case.
After that,
Emperor Xue Ye ordered Prince Xue Xing
to investigate this case.
Prince Xue Xing found out that
the two princes weren’t poisoned by drugs,
but the Poison of Martial Soul of a soul master.
But, this can’t prove that
it’s related to the Crown Prince, Xue Qing He.
If we don’t have any evidence,
we have to look for the most benefited one.
Second and Third Prince died.
Fourth Prince was too young.
Who would be the most benefited one?
If it was done by an outsider,
why did he let the eldest son live?
Not long ago,
Prince Xue Xing asked me
to check on Emperor Xue Ye.
I found out that Emperor Xue Ye was poisoned
by a mixed poison.
It was caused by a spice.
And Xue Qing He is the only one
who is using this spice in the palace.
He’s definitely not a simple man…
Then, why are you following Xue Beng?
Aren’t you afraid that
Xue Qing He will harm him if you do so?
Xue Qing He is meticulous,
but Xue Beng is not as simple as you think.
He avoids training purposely
to stop improving his soul power.
He pretends to be arrogant and bossy.
It’s the only way for him to live.
That’s why he…
Does Emperor Xue Ye know about
the mixed poison and Xue Qing He?
I only told him that he was poisoned
and asked him to maintain his conditions.
But, I gave him a medicine to relieve the poison.
No matter what,
this is a fight within the royal family.
Old Freak, you shouldn’t get involved in it.
I don’t care about the matters of the royal family.
But, the stability of Tian Dou Empire
will benefit us from fighting Martial Soul Hall.
You just came back. You don’t know
about the other two incidents yet, right?
What incidents?
Qibao Amber Tribe
and the Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe
were attacked by Martial Soul Hall.
Wha... What?
More than two thirds of the disciples
of the Qibao Amber Tribe died.
They moved to Tian Dou City.
But, the Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe
almost got extinct.
Only a few members away from the tribe survived.
You must accept this fact as soon as possible,
because I’m afraid that these are not all of
what Martial Soul Hall is planning to do…
Martial Soul Hall is so cruel.
Old Freak, please look into the matter
of the royal family.
I need to rush back to my school to meet my teacher.
Master…
Little San.
This is...
Master. Teacher Er Long.
Let’s talk in a quiet place.
What? Do you mean this rabbit is Xiao Wu?
It’s all my fault. I didn’t protect her well.
Martial Soul Hall! Bibi Dong! I’ll kill you!
Teacher Er Long, don’t be angry.
Angry? How can I not be angry?
Tang San, if you’re a man,
follow me to Martial Soul Hall!
Even if I die,
I’ll turn their world upside down!
Enough!
Things have already happened.
Do you want to make Little San to die along with you?
We can’t blame you on Xiao Wu’s incidence.
You tried your best.
What you need to do now
is to improve your skills
and become a Grand Soul Land Master
as soon as possible,
so you can revive her.
Do you understand?
We have to plan carefully
for our revenge on Martial Soul Hall…
Master…
Xiao Gang! Xiao Gang…
Master!
- How are you feeling, Xiao Gang?
- Master!
[Soul Land]
Damn it! Martial Soul Hall…
Little San, I’m sorry for your suffering.
Dean, I’m okay.
I’m okay with anything as long as Xiao Wu can be revived.
What are you planning to do here this time?
I’m planning to do some training
and create some useful hidden weapons.
Rong Rong and Hong Jun
are training in the school.
You can train with them.
Come to me if you need anything.
Now, Tian Dou Empire fully supports us.
We can get access to all kinds of resources.
Dean, thank you.
Alright. You should be tired from your journey,
have a rest first.
The power we have is far from enough
to fight against Martial Soul Hall.
Oh, right! With these,
I might be able to defeat Martial Soul Hall.
Fatty, you have improved a lot.
Brother San!
Fatty, I’m thinking of setting up a clan.
I hope you can help me.
Setting up a clan? Brother San, are you joking?
Isn’t Martial Soul Hall re-selecting
the Seven Great Tribes one year later?
We shall bring some trouble to them.
Trouble? I like it.
Brother San, don’t worry. I’ll definitely help you.
Brother San, what kind of clan are you going to set up?
Shall I give you some ideas?
We have to get a cool name no matter what.
I have already decided on the name of the clan.
I’ll call it
Tang Clan.
Tang Clan? Why does it sound strange?
Tang Clan. I can only miss you in this way now.
Brother San, you’re setting up a clan by your own.
Won’t Hao Tian Tribe be pissed off?
Though I have been readmitted to Hao Tian Tribe,
it is shut down already.
There won’t be any conflicts
between Tang Clan and Hao Tian Tribe.
In the future, we can rely on each other.
Brother San, you’re really an ambitious man.
Anyway, I’ll follow you.
Now, there are only two members in Tang Clan.
You’ll be the Chief. I’ll be the Deputy Chief.
Is that okay?
If you want to be the Deputy Chief, do it then.
I have already thought about the detail plan
of setting up the clan.
I’ll commence with my plan
after discussing it with Master.
No problem.
Rong Rong!
Rong Rong, how’s Qibao Amber Tribe?
How can it be?
Dad brought the tribe
to stay in our school for a short while.
Then, they moved to the palace
after being invited by Emperor Xue Ye.
Rong Rong, I have something
to discuss with Uncle Ning.
Can you bring him here?
Okay, I’ll look for my dad now.
Let’s meet tonight. Is that okay?
No problem. Thank you, then.
Not at all. “Thank you” is not for us.
Oh, right. Remember to keep it a secret.
Don’t worry.
Hey, you!
You sounded so affectionate.
If someone heard it,
they would thought that
you two has a special relation.
Fatty! Stop saying nonsense in front of Xiao Wu.
I’m leaving.
I’ll look for the Master.
Someone’s here!
A man from Martial Soul Hall?
This sound is…
Who are you?
What about you?
Why do you have
the Twenty-Four Moonlight Bridges?
Why were you with Ning Rong Rong?
This voice sounds familiar.
Why do you care about my relationship
with Rong Rong?
Rong Rong. Sounds so affectionate.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 137 has been completed
and broadcasted for nearly 1340 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2069]
[Total scene: 52040]
[Total CGI: 26190]
[Total plan of action scene: 11104]
[Total scene model: nearly 524]
[Total character model: nearly 973]
[Total props model: 13363]
[Appreciate your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods,
who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never change ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
No matter how sad I am,
I wouldn’t want Xiao Wu to get hurt.
Now, I can’t see Xiao Wu anymore.
You have already known
what happened to Qibao Amber Tribe, right?
Who is Rong Rong to you?
All theses things are too complicated.
These days, I have been immersed in hatred.
What Senior Dugu Bo knows
might not be the whole story.
Xue Qing He is not that simple.
A soul master with a better skill in using poison
than the Grand Venom Master
might exist.
I don’t like you
because you’re disfigured.
I’d rather become extremely ugly.
[Soul Land]
[Available at 10 AM every Saturday]