♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind,
you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
The 81st Hammering.
Feel it?
This is heinous spirit.
Go to Slaughter City for practice,
you might not be able to return.
Absorb it before you leave.
The real Blue Silver Emperor
has finally awaken.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 112]
Let’s begin.
Mom.
Mum.
Wake up, my son.
The real Blue Silver Emperor
has finally awaken.
Ah Yin...
This is the original form of
Blue Silver Plant?
Yes, King.
Its name is
Blue Silver Emperor.
This soul ring is the product of
the awakening of Blue Silver Emperor.
Yes. This soul ring comes from you.
According to human,
it equivalents to soul ring from
a 25 millennium soul beast.
And it’s the optimum limit you can endure.
It evolves along with your endurance.
Ah Yin.
Dad.
Let’s go.
[Soul Land]
How could Dad’s injuries worsen?
Was it that day?
I’ll fight you till the end.
Little San, withdraw.
The old wounds will be alright.
No, Dad.
You’re seriously injured.
If you don’t take good care,
possibly you’ll...
Don’t bother about me.
Now, your task is
to grow stronger as fast as possible
like what I’ve told you.
Do you want to be like me
who is not able to protect my lover?
How can I not care about you, Dad?
I’m your son.
You’re my precious one too.
If you die, what about me?
I’m not dead yet.
Moreover, there’s no way to cure.
Luckily, I’m able
to control my injuries until now.
I can cure you.
Even the Grand Soul Land Master
from Healing Branch can’t. Can you?
The healing skill of
those healing type soul masters
can only cure the symptom.
While my soul power is able
to cure the injuries.
But, I can’t heal you completely
at this moment.
Unless my soul power approaches yours,
I’m sure I can heal you.
It’s a matter of the future.
Stand up, I dislike weakness.
Dad, please promise me one thing.
From now on, never fight with others.
Especially those who are as strong as you.
Otherwise, if your injuries relapse...
Cut that crap.
We should proceed to the next place.
Dad.
What are you doing?
Dad, if Mom is still alive.
She wouldn’t want you
to disregard your health.
Please promise me, for Mom and me.
Let’s go. I promise you.
Netherland. Please give me
a shot of Netherland...
One more.
What’s your order?
Give me two shots of Netherland.
Are you sure?
One moment, please.
Here they are.
Dad, what’s this?
It has a strong bloody smell.
Drink it.
Netherland.
Extracted from one’s soul energy
after killing.
What?
Where does this brat come from?
Get out of here.
No place for a trash.
Go back to your mother’s wing, brat.
Kill them all.
[Next Episode]
After entering Slaughter City,
you can only depend on yourself.
In this place,
you can obtain everything you desire.
Welcome to Slaughter City.
Defeat me
is your pass to enter Slaughter City.
The mighty Slaughter King
controls everything here.
Is there any way out?
Leave here without permission?
Vain hope.