♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Absorb the soul bone
that your mom left for you.
Thank you, Mom.
I won’t have the chance to see that.
Perhaps there’s a chance for Mom to reinstate.
Do you mean it?
Thirdly, I’ve decided to start the
Soul Hunting Manoeuvre.
Simultaneously, cleanse the Seven Great Tribes.
Brother, how are you?
I wonder when I could see you again.
I can go find Xiao Wu at that time.
Before you go looking for her,
make a trip back to the tribe first.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 123]
Please leave. Outsiders are not welcomed.
I’m not an outsider.
I’m going home.
Going home?
We don’t have such a patrician like you here.
Can this prove it?
Which family are you from?
My aunt is Tang Yue Hua.
She asked me to come back.
You’re Tang San?
How does he know my name?
Yes, I am.
Follow us.
These mountains are strange,
most of which are stiff.
They can
resist the attacks
by ten times more attackers than the defenders.
It’s an ideal attack and defense point.
Both Hao Tian Tribe and Tang Clan
are using natural barriers.
It seems similar to the Tang Clan.
Could that be
the Hao Tian Tribe?
This thousand-meters long iron chain
must be the first barrier
before entering the tribe.
Once they can’t resist the enemy’s attack,
they can retreat to the second mountain
and chop it off
so, they will have time to buffer
and the second mountain will be the new barrier.
Due to the low temperature,
the frozen iron chain has turned
brittle and slippery. Be careful.
Ok.
The temperature is getting lower.
Soul masters who are under Level 40
can’t pass through it.
This brat has lightning speed.
This mountain is
more than 2,000 meters high.
Temperature, fog, wind, and iron chain.
Any slight change may cause
intense mental tension.
One might fall due to carelessness.
Even a Grand Soul Land Master
can’t survive from the fall.
The speed and direction of fog flow
seem to have changed.
Purple Demon Eye.
Be careful, everyone.
I focused too much on the iron chain
that I missed it.
There’s no way to dodge it. Purple God Light.
It’s too late.
Elder Brother!
Tang Tian, Tang Yu!
First Soul Skill, Intertwine.
Darn it. The limit of
Blue Silver Emperor is 120 meters.
Tang Tian!
I’ll send you up first. I’ll save him.
Don’t go, Tang San.
Tang San...
It’s my fault.
He can fly?
This brat really surprises us.
Thanks, Brother.
Elder Brother, your fist is powerful.
Cut your crap.
It’s your bone that hurts my hand.
Thank you.
My aunt sent you here, right?
Yes. Was the martial soul
you used just now one of the two you possess,
Blue Silver Plant?
Yes.
How come you can fly?
My mom left me a Century Millennium Soul Bone.
It has flying ability.
It’s my first time using it.
The second aunt spoke so highly so you.
I didn’t believe her then,
but now I do.
There’s the last mountain left.
Standing still and magnificent.
[Hao Tian Tribe]
It’s worthy of its name, the top tribe.
How do we enter?
It requires at least two tribe members
to open it simultaneously.
That explains why there isn’t any guard here.
Tribe Chief ordered
to bring you directly to him.
So, we’re not going to show you around.
Everything is stone made.
The fortifications are quite strong.
Tribe Chief, we’ve got Tang San here.
Come in.
[Soul Land]
Little San.
Aunt.
Yes.
This must be my uncle.
He looks even stronger than Dad.
Purple Demon Eye.
Death God Domain.
He’s extremely powerful.
Transferring the soul power into pressure
via his fingertip
and controlling it precisely at the same time.
The pressure Tribe Chief is releasing
bounced me away
and targets on Tang San alone.
Why doesn’t it affect him at all?
What is that white vibe?
What strong pressure. Is he testing me?
Blue Silver Domain.
Greetings to you, Tribe Chief.
Is he a human?
He only kneels down
under such robust pressure.
He can even talk.
I’ve activated my two domains.
But I still can’t breath
under the oppression.
It seems that he’s forced to kneel down,
but in fact, he has found
the weakest area of the pressure
and is reducing the pressure by doing so.
Stand up.
What are you doing?
The son is obliged to repay the father’s debt.
Tribe Chief, I’m willing to assume
all the responsibilities for my father.
Do you think you can do that?
I don’t know if I can,
but I will serve the tribe with my life
and do everything I can for it.
How can he let a child carry his duty for him?
Tang Hao...
Tribe Chief, my father is not escaping from his duty.
He said that he felt too ashamed
to return to the tribe.
How is he doing?
He’s fine. He’s accompanying my mom
every day
and going to spend
the rest of his life like this.
Accompanying your mom?
After she died,
she turned into the Blue Silver Plant.
She...
Well...
Perhaps this is the best for him.
Tribe Chief,
this is what Father asked me to bring here.
He said this is the only thing
he could do for the tribe.
Brother Hao...
Father said if he didn’t do this,
he couldn’t stay with Mom in peace.
Tribe Chief, you don’t have to...
Call me Uncle.
Uncle.
To be honest,
I’ve never thought that he was wrong.
If Ah Yin had chosen me,
I would have done the exact same thing as he did.
Uncle.
No matter what others say hereafter,
I don’t wish to see
his past become your burden.
Serving the tribe is your responsibility,
because you’re part of it.
Thank you, Uncle.
Yue Hua, hold a ceremony tomorrow
to acknowledge him back to the tribe.
Please arrange it.
What about those tribe elders?
Rather than notify them privately,
it’d be better make it public.
It has been some time since
Hao Tian Tribe last held a grand ceremony.
This young man must
have some connection.
- I heard that the Five Elders...
- Maybe they refuse to see him.
He’s coming.
He looks mundane.
He looks so weak.
How dare he come to our tribe?
There are four generations of
immediate family in the tribe.
We belong to the third generation,
about 200 people in total.
Only part of them come today.
The others are training at the front yard.
Now, the situation in the tribe is complex.
Viewing from your father’s point,
the tribe has separated into two parties.
The one led by your uncle
reckons that it wasn’t your dad’s fault,
but the overbearing Martial Soul Hall,
while the other, which is led by
the tribe elders from the first generation,
thinks that the conflict was caused
by the matrimony of your dad and the soul beast.
Besides, he infuriated your grandpa
on his deathbed, which is unforgivable.
Our tribe is hiding all because of him.
How dare he come back?
Aunt, do you mean that
the tribe elders will prevent me
from coming back?
All the tribe elders are powerful.
They are tough and stubborn personality, and...
The worst result will be that
you are expelled from the tribe
and your martial soul eradicated.
Since you allow me to come back,
you have figured out a countermeasure, right?
My advice to you is
to be tough.
One’s power speaks for him here.
Why is it so cold suddenly?
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 123 has been completed
and broadcasted for nearly 1242 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 1854]
[Total scene: 47521]
[Total CGI: 24833]
[Total plan of action scene: 10016]
[Total scene model: nearly 506]
[Total character model: nearly 957]
[Total props model: 13348]
[Appreciate your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
[Next Episode]
I refuse to hear
anything about this man.
Only this news
you all must listen to, Tribe Elders.
We’ll let you try then.
It’s over.
Random Air Hammer Skill.
His soul power is way higher than mine.
Besides, he’s only using
the third soul skill.
But
Tang San only discretely gives
his opponent small cuts every time.
Releasing the poison bit by bit
is the way least likely to be noticed.