♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Welcome to the Capital of Metal.
Don’t you cheat around with his title anymore.
Or else...
forget about living your life in Gengxin Town.
How dare he cause trouble
at Martial Soul Main Hall’s territory?
Seems like they’re tired of living.
Teacher.
Vice President Tai Tan is here.
You’re here at the right time.
Come!
Let me show you a treasure.
The one who made this
must be a genius.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 149]
Let me show you this.
It’s a casting furnace made solely of Black Iron.
You’ve never seen this, right?
I spent a huge amount of money
to get this from the Martial Soul Hall.
Ironsmiths might get a higher status
because of it.
But when I was disassembling it,
I accidentally broke some of its components.
The man who made this
is definitely a genius!
Tai Tan, are you overwhelmed by this?
Why aren’t you talking?
The thing on these blueprints
looks so similar to the Godly Zhuge Crossbow.
Is it...?
He’s indeed the God of Ironsmith in this world.
Senior Lou Gao.
This is called the Godly Zhuge Crossbow.
I think the genius you just mentioned
is me.
Where did you come from, boy?
What did you say?
You...
Well...
This is great!
Senior Lou Gao! What are you doing?
Brat! Why are you avoiding me?
Come here!
Come on!
Tell me how to fix it!
And...
how did you invent it?
I sold this Godly Zhuge Crossbow
to the Qibao Amber Tribe.
Seems like the Martial Soul Hall
snatched many
Godly Zhuge Crossbows when they attacked
the Qibao Amber Tribe.
I purposely made a system in
the Godly Zhuge Crossbow
to prevent disassembly.
Once a person disassembles it,
some gear will be triggered
to destroy the key components.
This is to prevent others from copying it.
I saw your blueprint.
Although it’s very close to
the actual design,
without the key part,
it’s useless.
Then, how can I fix it?
Senior.
I’m sorry to disappoint you.
I can’t help you.
What?
You! Brat!
You’re Tai Tan’s disciple, right?
I’m the President of the Ironsmith Society.
Senior, you’re the God of Ironsmith.
If I fix the Godly Zhuge Crossbow
in front of you,
you can definitely figure out how it works.
This is a secret of Tang Clan.
What is Tang Clan?
Brat! You’re very arrogant!
Tai Tan, why aren’t you stopping him?
There’s nothing I can do.
This is not my disciple
but the Chief of our clan.
I’ve joined Tang Clan.
Tai Tan.
Even if you can’t be the leader of
the Tribe of Strength,
you can return to the Ironsmith Society.
Old Brother.
Actually... If you were me,
you would join Tang Clan, too.
Although this Godly Zhuge Crossbow is not bad,
it’s just a normal
hidden weapon in Tang Clan.
Oh, right!
We call these things “hidden weapons”.
Besides our key members,
we will never reveal our secrets to anyone else.
This...
It’s easy. I’ll join Tang Clan.
Given my casting skills,
I can be a key member, right?
Si Long!
Get over here!
Teacher.
From now onwards,
you
are the President of the Ironsmith Society.
Teacher, are you joking?
Do I look like I’m joking?
I’ll leave my works
to you and your brothers.
When I’m not around at the Ironsmith Society,
you should be united.
If you’re faced with problems that you can’t solve,
send a man to the Tribe of Strength
to look for Tai Tan.
I think this is
the simplest handover ceremony in history.
Lou Gao.
Are you serious?
One will never succeed without taking a risk.
I must join Tang Clan!
Brat!
Do you dare to accept me?
Yes.
Of course.
Since you’re willing to join Tang Clan,
from now onward, you’ll be the same as Senior Tai Tan,
an Elder of Tang Clan.
Then, may I know
the method of making
this Godly Zhuge Crossbow?
Don’t worry.
I will never tell an outsider.
I won’t reveal it when I’m in Tang Clan.
After I master the skill,
can’t I withdraw from Tang Clan?
Godly Zhuge Crossbow
is no match for you, Senior.
With your status, you should work on
the best hidden weapon of our clan instead.
You have a even better hidden weapon?
Once we succeed in making it,
you’ll be the founder.
We will craft your name
on these peerless hidden weapons.
Peerless hidden weapons?
Senior.
Please take a look at this blueprint first.
Great!
Si Long.
I’ll leave other things to you.
Yes, Teacher.
Senior.
We’ll go and buy some things first.
Go!
Getting Lou Gao into our clan
is a great help.
Although Senior Lou Gao is cunning,
he might be a great contributor to Tang Clan.
The Storm Pear Blossom Needle,
the Peacock Plumes and
the Tang’s Lotus of Buddha’s Rage.
We might be able to see them again.
I’ll treat you to lunch first.
We’ll shop for the metal later. What do you think?
You know us well.
I have a list here.
I’ll leave this errand to you.
Vice President Tai Tan.
Are you serious?
Ten tons of iron ore.
Five tons of pure silver.
Five tons of tungsten.
I never see anyone
buying these precious metals
in tons.
Don’t forget to give us a discount.
[Soul Land]
Grand Master Si Long, you’re here?
Give me the usual room.
Yes.
I’m sorry.
Grand Master Si Long.
That room is reserved today.
May I take you to another room?
I have important guests today.
I know.
But...
But what?
But we’ve reserved the room.
He...
can’t afford to offend us.
Grand Master Si Long.
You know it too.
Myles is the Bishop of the Martial Soul Hall.
He’s the local despot.
We can’t offend him.
Why is he here?
I heard that he never gets along
with the Ironsmiths Society.
Is he here to pick a fight again?
Lower your voice!
It’s Bishop Myles.
Grand Master Si Long.
Do you want me to offer you our room?
What do you mean?
I pity you, being at Level 70,
but you’re just a useless tool soul master.
Si Long.
As long as you can persuade Lou Gao
to merge the Ironsmiths Society
with the Martial Soul Hall,
I’ll offer you my room.
Myles.
Next door is the headquarter of the Ironsmiths Society.
You should choose the right time
to make your statement!
So what?
Even the governor has to bow to me.
Si Long.
Where did you get these two ladies?
Good dogs don’t stand in the way.
Get out!
So pretty.
You bastard!
At a level higher than a Great Soul Land Master.
He is...?
Elder... Elder Token!
Buzz off.
Let’s go!
Wait a minute!
Brother San asked you to roll out.
[*Buzz off means roll out literally]
Aren’t you leading us in?
Honorable guests.
Please come in.
They have the Elder Token of
the Martial Soul Hall.
Who are those people?
Please.
You people are from the Martial Soul Hall?
Don’t worry.
We are definitely the enemies of
the Martial Soul Hall.
The Elder Token...
My teacher got this in a coincidence.
Before we left,
he handed the token to me specifically.
So we can travel around this continent
without being bothered.
We should have chased them
and give those bastards a lesson!
If you punish them,
the Martial Soul Hall will blame it
on the Ironsmiths Society.
By then,
the Society will be in big trouble.
Senior Si Long.
The relationship between the Ironsmiths Society
and the Martial Soul Hall
looks very bad.
The Ironsmiths Society has little value
to the Martial Soul Hall.
We’re useless to them,
but they are not willing to let us go.
Myles, that bastard,
wants to take over the Ironsmiths Society
to earn himself some extra money.
He always sends people here to make trouble.
They have injured many of our people.
Where is the Martial Soul Main Hall
in Gengxin Town?
At the east of the town.
Myles was offended today.
He won’t let it go.
Fatty.
Keep an eye on them later.
But, remember,
don’t act on impulse.
Don’t worry. Leave it to me.
Senior Si Long.
Please prepare what we need as soon as possible.
Please arrange for us to attend
the auction held by the Ironsmiths Society
tomorrow too.
Little Ao. Rong Rong.
I have two important tasks
for you.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 149 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1424 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2251]
[Total scene: 55877]
[Total CGI: 27065]
[Total plan of action scene: 12052]
[Total scene model: nearly 543]
[Total character model: nearly 995]
[Total props model: 13372]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[The dream on Soul Land and the martial soul
illuminates our youth.]
[We are not alone with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
We’re in trouble! Brother San!
I spied on them as you said.
And I found that Myles
had been gathering his people.
These two are definitely treasures.
Leave it to me.
Brat.
Are you thinking of...?
[Next episode]
[Soul Land]
[Available at 10 AM every Saturday]