♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet I’ll be brave and fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking up,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Looking back,
you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give in ♪
[This animation is based on the novel of Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
It’s neidan.
Be careful. It’s going to
take us down with it.
To Kill or to be killed,
what’s your choice?
Ten-Headed Burning Sun Serpent.
I almost ended up death in there.
Your destination is Slaughter City.
Three to go.
Tang Yin, do you want to die?
Just hang in there. If I’m not wrong,
we’re almost out.
I can’t resist it anymore.
Insensate me.
Please bring me out.
Do it. Hurry up.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 118]
The exit is about 2 kilometers away,
200 meters up on the cave top.
It seems that the only way is to jump up
and then climb to the exit.
The limit of Blue Silver Emperor
is 120 meters.
It’s 100 meters away from there.
What should I do?
I can’t wake her up.
If she loses control and attacks me,
I’ll stand no chance.
How could it be...
It seems like it absorbs
the soul power from Netherland.
There’s no way out.
Am I going to end up here?
Little San, although I’m strict to you,
I know you’ll come out alive.
Dad must be waiting for me.
Give it a try.
The limit of Flying Godly Claw
is 30 meters.
If I combine it with Blue Silver Plant,
there’ll be around 70 meters left...
This is the only chance.
The newly evolved Eight Spider Bone,
I’ll bet everything on it.
I can’t reach it.
Is it because of her weight?
Will I die here?
No. Purple God Light.
I’ll never forget
the critical challenges
I’ve taken these two years.
Collapse, Slaughter City.
It’s cold. Is it the domain
with the condensed heinous spirit?
Why are there so many strange lines on it?
Is this the Death God Domain?
Can you feel it?
We have the same Death God Domain.
She has no heinous spirit.
We’ve saved each other once.
Are we even now?
But I still want to thank you
for not abandoning me.
Why are there so many burns on his body, while mine...
Never mind.
We worked together and did our parts.
Anything else?
I...
If nothing, I should get going.
Well, he has no other intention
other than saving my life.
I’m done. You may leave.
Tang Yin.
Little San.
I knew it. Dad’s waiting for me.
Dad.
You’ve been doing great for the past two years.
Let’s go.
You must have lived a hard life these years.
Dad, do you have the Death God Domain as well?
Are you aware of how it works?
Robust vibes.
You’re right. Robust vibes.
Remember,
the innate domain of martial soul is not
restricted by your twin one.
How do you know?
Because there was someone
who did it before.
Bibi Dong, the Pope?
I’m willing to pass through Hell Road
with the Emissary of Hell.
Calm down. If I’m not wrong,
we’re almost out.
Tie the rope to your tail.
Those who collaborated to challenge
Hell Road had their own intentions.
I’m Tang Yin.
Tang Yin, why am I from Martial Soul Hall
while you’re from Hao Tian Tribe?
Elder Gui. Elder Ju.
[Soul Land]
He’s so handsome.
His refined features.
His gallant manner.
All these can’t be concealed by
his gross icy heinous spirit.
It’s ok. Don’t mind them.
I’m used to it these two years.
Wow, he looks attractive
even from the back.
Both of them are handsome.
- Hurry up.
- Brother, wait for me.
- Follow me. Come on.
- Wait for me.
Watch out.
It’s been 20 years.
Dad.
Is it time for you to tell me the past now?
You haven’t met my requirements.
No? How should I do that?
Your robust vibes are too evident.
You need to learn how to conceal it
among the soul masters.
When can I...
This is Moon Pavilion.
Yes.
I’m sorry. Please stop there.
Scruffily dressed visitors are not allowed
in the Moon Pavilion.
Go away.
Such powerful vibes.
You’re right.
Tell Yue Hua
that the obscure full moon
marks the arrival of old acquaintance.
A visit from an old acquaintance?
Please wait a moment.
Manager Oudy, he’s looking for the Madam.
Moon Pavilion only welcomes
elegant guests. Please see them out.
You’re too superficial. Get lost.
How dare you!
Don’t kill. Don’t damage this place.
Merely two Soul Sects above Level 40...
Little San.
Their arms are broken inch by inch. You...
I’ve already been easy on them.
Moon Pavilion won’t endure your brutality.
This is impossible.
Last warning to you. Leave now.
King of Haunted Vine?
Haunted Vine Spike.
How come my martial soul is immobilised?
It’s like being oppressed.
Is this your limit to control it?
Blue Silver Emperor could suppress
any martial soul from plant by its aura.
It’s not easy to cultivate
soft vines to such needle-like form.
Such a pity.
Death God Domain.
What skills are you using?
Don’t you understand?
Check this out carefully.
Little San’s heinous spirit is out of control.
Little San, stop it. It’s enough.
First Soul Skill.
Intertwine.
Little San.
Dad.
Feel it with your heart.
Is this... the domain?
Spreading the power of domain via the rhythm.
What a powerful skill!
Although it’s not as oppressive as
the Death God Domain,
its gentle and elegant power
has made people follow with it unconsciously.
Yet her soul power couldn’t be noticed.
Is she the Grand Soul Land Master
who can conceal her strength completely?
What happened?
[Since the commencement of animating
Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[118 episodes has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1207 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 1779]
[Total scene: 46104]
[Total CGI: 24480]
[Total plan of action scene: 9892]
[Total scene model: Nearly 495]
[Total character model: Nearly 931]
[Total props model: 13324]
[Appreciate your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
[Next Episode]
What’s going on?
Is she the owner of Moon Pavilion?
No wonder her temperament is so extraordinary.
She’s comparable to Bibi Dong.
It’s me,
Yue Hua.
Is it really you?
How did you...
You must go back with me.
Go back?
I’m no longer part of Hao Tian Tribe.
You can’t imagine how miserable he is.
Stop it.
The moment when Ah Yin died,
my heart had died too.
Besides,
he’s the son of Ah Yin and me.
Your son?