♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Seems like my guess was right.
There’s a high possibility that
you will obtain a special skill.
Soul Bone Fusion Skill.
I’m afraid the one behind is
the Martial Soul Hall.
Seems like Xue Qing He is anything but simple.
Hao Tian Hammer!
Blue Silver Plant?
Little San!
Who do you think Rong Rong is?
Do you think that Rong Rong would dislike you
because of your scarred face?
No matter how sad I am,
I can’t meet Xiao Wu now.
It will be too late to regret
after you lose her.
I understand now.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 139]
Chief Ning. Rong Rong.
I’m back.
Uncle Ning.
I have an important matter
to discuss with the Qibao Amber Tribe.
But, I don’t want to involve the Tian Dou Empire.
Is it okay?
Little San, just get to the point.
- Domain?
It can isolate sound.
Outsiders can’t hear our conversation.
Whenever we meet,
you always bring me a big surprise.
Same for this time.
You are much prettier, yet I’m uglier.
No. You have become more mature.
Now, I feel more secure with you.
Rong Rong, I’ve been missing you these five years.
No matter how much I struggled,
as long as I thought of your face,
I would gain courage.
This time, I will definitely get
Chief Ning’s consent this time.
I’ll never leave you.
Alright.
Where are Little San and Chief Ning?
It’s all your fault. They will make fun of me.
Just let them be.
Uncle Ning, that’s a deal.
Today onward, Tang Clan
will rely on your support.
This is mutually beneficial cooperation.
When Tang Clan is settled down,
I’ll send you the resources
that you need secretly.
Ask Rong Rong to drop me a message
if you need anything.
We have to meet less frequently later
to keep a low profile.
Don’t worry.
Chief Ning.
Silly guy, why did you leave?
Though we have rules of our tribe,
don’t you think
I’ll consider my daughter’s happiness?
Do you
agree with me and Rong Rong being together?
Just a reminder.
Rong Rong is my only daughter.
Do you understand?
Don’t worry.
I have the ability to protect Rong Rong now.
I’ll protect her with my life.
Chief Ning, if Little Ao mistreats Rong Rong,
we won’t forgive him.
Oscar, Rong Rong is the little princess of
Qibao Amber Tribe.
I always treat her as my granddaughter.
You said you could protect her now.
Show us how much you’ve improved
in the last five years.
Little San, lend me a drop of your blood.
Sixth Soul Skill! Cloning Sausage!
Little San, the effect from your blood is so strong.
Come on. Show us your sixth skill.
I need an opponent.
Fatty, we haven’t seen for so many years.
Let’s have fun!
Little Ao, are you serious?
You want to have a fight with me?
I’ll be easy on you because of Rong Rong.
No thanks. Bring it on!
A Food Series Soul Master
tries to fight a Storm Attack Soul Master
in a combat approach?
So powerful.
Little Ao has experienced many crises.
His physical fitness has already surpassed
an average Food Series Soul Master’s.
Little Ao can duplicate Brother San’s soul skill!
But, a Controlling Soul Master
lacks explosive force the most!
Fatty is getting serious, too.
Fourth Soul Skill, Phoenix Strike!
Though the Blue Silver Emperor can defend
ice and fire,
it can’t block the Phoenix Flame of
a Bursting Phoenix.
Fiery Right Arm Soul Bone Skill!
Bursting Phoenix!
[Soul Land]
Smells so nice!
Though Fatty has powerful explosive force,
his attack range is limited.
Little Ao is aiming on this weakness.
Flight Mushroom Sausage is coming to an end!
That was Little Ao’s Mirror Clone.
Nice.
He distracted him with his Mirror Clone first,
so that he could accumulate energy for
the Blue Silver Emperor Tyrant Spear.
Fifth Soul Skill,
Blue Silver Emperor Tyrant Spear!
Fifth Soul Skill, Phoenix Meteor Shower!
It’s nighttime, you’re so noisy!
Again?
You can even duplicate the Twin Martial Souls?
[Ah!]
Little San, your Hao Tian Hammer is too heavy.
Little Ao, you’re so freaking strong now.
I almost died here.
What did you experience in the past five years?
You’ll know when you find the one
you want to protect the most.
It’s okay.
It’s just that I’ve consumed too much soul power.
Your soul ring and soul bone
are from the same soul beast, right?
Yes. Whoever consumes the Cloning Sausage
within three minutes,
can exert 70% of the power of
the blood provider.
After creating my Mirror Clone,
the power can be increased to 80%.
Oscar, you have a choice now.
Little San is planning to set up
a new clan called Tang Clan.
But, I hope that you can join our Qibao Amber Tribe.
As long as you follow me back,
I’ll agree with you being with Rong Rong.
Dad.
Girl.
Qibao Amber Tribe needs a talent like Oscar.
Let him work for our tribe.
There will be less obstacles between you, too.
Why did you work so hard for so many years?
Promise Uncle Ning now.
This is your best chance.
I’m sorry,
Chief Ning.
I can’t promise you.
Little Ao.
I love Rong Rong.
I’m willing to love her with everything I have.
But, Tang San is a good brother of mine.
Now, he needs my help.
If I leave,
I won’t forgive myself.
What about Rong Rong?
I won’t give up on Rong Rong either.
No matter how long it will take,
I’ll definitely persuade you in my own way.
Little Ao is right.
Dad, we, the Shrek Seven Devils, are one.
Brother San is setting up Tang Clan
to revive Xiao Wu and take revenge
on Martial Soul Hall.
How can we stand aside?
Oscar.
Though your answer is very tricky,
I must admit that
this is the answer that I was waiting for.
Chief Ning, you...
Why are you still calling me Chief Ning?
Call him your father-in-law!
Father-in-law!
It’s too early for that.
Call me Uncle Ning, like Little San.
Uncle Ning.
Rong Rong! Rong Rong!
Xiao Wu, Tang Clan has just gained much assistance.
But, it’s still far from enough for us
to reach our goal.
Time to meet my old friend.
Young Master.
Senior.
Martial Soul Hall is too cruel.
They not only made Master
wandering for half of his life,
but also attacked you over and over again.
Master, I’ve been waiting for you to come back.
But, you…
Senior.
My father can finally live peacefully
with my mother.
It’s a relief to him.
I’m here to discuss something with you.
Young Master, please.
I won’t refuse
as long as it’s within my capability.
I’m planning to set up a clan, named Tang Clan.
I hope you
and Tribe of Strength can support me.
When Hao Tian Tribe is back,
will it be merged with Tang Clan?
If yes... Sorry, I have to refuse.
Tribe of Strength won’t be
a subsidiary of Hao Tian Tribe again.
Don’t worry.
Since I’m building up a power of my own,
I won’t merge with Hao Tian Tribe.
That’s great.
You are indeed ambitious
with sharp perceptions.
I’m in.
Master San, I’ll follow you, too!
Today onward,
Senior Tai Tan will be
a Chief Elder of Tang Clan.
We have to conclude on the location of
Tang Clan as soon as possible.
Let’s do it in my mansion.
Lord, you can renovate as you wish.
I’ll fully support you.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 139 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1354 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2099]
[Total scene: 52700]
[Total CGI: 26323]
[Total plan of action scene: 11293]
[Total scene model: nearly 527]
[Total character model: nearly 977]
[Total props model: 13365]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods,
who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
It’s on the way.
Dad.
There’s deadly poison on the gear.
Why are you...?
What is this?
So lethal.
It can take one’s life right away.
No wonder.
This is the Peacock Plumes.
Senior.
I need a batch of iron smiths.
They must be trustworthy.
Can you help me find them?
Have Hao Tian Tribe
and Tang Hao
ever considered us?
[Soul Land]
[Available at 10 AM every Saturday]