♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
This is the decisive stroke.
Little freak.
I can’t be defeated.
What exactly is my real strength?
Do you know it?
Your flame couldn’t resist mine.
No one can escape from Batwing Rebound.
Xie Yue, you’re defeated at last.
He made it.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 106]
While soaking up the poison,
my Eight Spider Bone is
recovering simultaneously.
Even Dugu Bo can’t dissolve the poison,
Tang San must be killed
if he refuses to serve under me.
Nana.
Your Holiness, their poisons have been dissolved.
Great.
Although the poison has been removed,
they will be seriously ill from the after-effects.
I’m afraid you have to behave for some time.
What’s wrong?
Purple Demon Eye.
These powerful soul masters
seem to gaze at Xiao Wu.
Are they...
My appreciation, Chief Ning.
That’s nothing. Don’t mention it.
Next is the award ceremony.
Let’s welcome Her Holiness
to present the award.
Continental Soul Master Elite Tournament,
The champion goes to
Shrek School.
Congratulations,
talented and young soul masters.
The representative of Shrek School,
please accept the reward.
Little San, this honor belongs to you.
Although I’m the captain,
but you’ve done so much for the championship.
All of us know it.
You’ve always been the soul of Shrek Seven Devils.
He’s right, Little San.
Come on, Little San. Don’t shrug off.
Just go, Little San.
OK.
You’re brilliant, even more than what I thought.
So,
do you wish to join Martial Soul Hall?
One who refuses
will be erased off without hesitation.
Perhaps this is the last chance she offered.
Thanks for your offer, Your Holiness.
However, I have a plan for my life.
I don’t want any restrictions.
If that’s the case,
I wish you the greatest achievements in the future
and to enter Tian Dou Hall one day.
If without the tyranny of Martial Soul Hall,
the presence of these soul bones
would have set off a bloody fight.
The three pieces of soul bones
are proof of our team’s effort.
All of us are eligible to possess them.
I give up.
Me too.
None of them suits me.
I’m a soul master from Food Branch.
These soul bones have
no significant effect on my strength.
Well...
Fast-Moving Chasing Left Leg
suits a soul master from
Keen Attack Branch the most.
It belongs to Zhu Qing for sure.
Thank you, Grandmaster.
While Burst Burning Flame Right Arm
suits fire-attributive soul master
from Storm Attack Branch.
Fatty, this is yours.
Thank you, Grandmaster.
This Spiritual Cohesion Wisdom Skull...
If I take the last piece,
Rong Rong would have nothing.
I give up...
No. Brother San, it should go to you.
You’ve done so much
for the championship.
Our Qibao Amber Tribe
wouldn’t be lack of soul bones.
Just accept it.
You’ll become the real soul of our team
when you possess it.
Little San, give Rong Rong
the soul bone you’ve been keeping.
That suits her better.
This soul bone is under jewel category.
It suits soul masters from
Support Branch and Illusion type.
Hence, it’s not suitable for you.
Rong Rong, this left-armed soul bone
is mainly for illusion.
It’s better than
Spiritual Cohesion Wisdom Skull for you.
Thank you, Brother San and Grandmaster.
Dad.
What’s wrong?
It seems like
this is an unavoidable bloody fight.
[Soul Land]
Have you distributed them?
Once you’ve done,
the competition is concluded successfully.
Gui Mei, Yue Guan. Seize that girl.
Sword Sect Chen Xin.
Darn it.
Your Holiness,
can’t you do it after figuring it out?
Chief Ning, please behave yourself.
If you hinder us,
Qibao Amber Tribe will be
the enemy of Martial Soul Hall.
Hold on.
I’m one of the Elder of Martial Soul Hall.
I have the right to know the truth.
Your Holiness, you can seize her if you want.
But please clarify first.
Why are you seizing my disciple?
Do you want to know the reason?
Why don’t you ask your disciple then?
If she’s just a student of Shrek School,
why would I seize her?
But if she’s a soul beast in the human form,
I’d have ample reasons to capture her.
What did you say?
- What?
- Xiao Wu, this can’t be real, right?
Soul beast in the human form?
My Xiao Wu is...
Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet
has concealed her soul beast’s scent.
If not, I’d have seen through her
and never allowed her to come
to Martial Soul Hall.
Xiao Wu.
If I’m not mistaken,
You’re the one that we missed out back then.
I never expect you’ll come here yourself.
I want to revenge for Mom.
Xiao Wu, what’s going on?
Brother, stop asking.
Xiao Wu is not a human being.
Brother, you...
Say nothing. I understand.
To be honest, I knew it a long time ago.
You’ve already known it...
When my Purple Demon Eye
upgraded to Surreal level,
I had seen through you.
Mother, I’m sorry.
My child, no need to feel sorry.
No matter who you are,
you’re always my precious daughter.
Mother.
No matter who she is,
I only know Xiao Wu is part of Shrek.
She’s our precious member too.
Xiao Wu, don’t be afraid. We’re here.
Right. Shrek Seven Devils are one.
Xiao Wu, we’ll stand by your side forever.
All of you...
Stop worrying then.
Brother, but we...
Silly girl, nothing to worry about.
Regardless of whether
you’re a human being or a soul beast,
you’re always my sister
and my beloved one.
Brother.
To seize her, step over my body first.
Xiao Gang, don’t let our tragedy happen again.
I’ll never allow the same tragedy to repeat.
Er Long, I won’t allow it since I’m here.
Master.
Seven Devils unite as one in life and death.
In life and death.
Well said. I’ll fulfill your wish.
[Next Episode]
Xiao Gang,
do you really want to go against me
for a soul beast?
No mercy for those who resist.
Century Millennium Soul Ring.
That’s Mom’s soul ring.
Kids, it’s not your turn yet to stand before us
since we are here.
Cocky.
Xiao Wu, move away.
Brother, please stay alive, promise me.
Mother, let me protect you this time.
No!