♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
To fight with the Martial Soul Hall,
we must collaborate with all parties
which are opposed to them.
Destroying the Martial Soul Hall
can’t be done within a short time,
we should make a long-term plan, Your Majesty.
Welcome to the Star Forest.
Xiao Wu...
The King of Forest, Titan Giant Ape.
Amongst all the Grand Soul Land Masters,
Tang Hao is the only one
who has defeated the Titan Giant Ape.
It has been five years. Finally...
[Soul Land]
[Episode 133]
Martial Soul Hall,
let’s put an end to this today.
Stay put, everyone.
Ju Hua Guan, try to resist this giant.
I’ll capture that rabbit first.
Leave here once I get her.
Martial Soul Form.
Spirits Attack!
Gravity Press.
Martial Soul Form...
Old Ghost!
Die!
Elder Ghost! Elder Ju!
This is...
Emperor of Forest! Azure Bull Python!
Ju Hua Guan!
Er Ming, stop them.
Oh, no.
Bipolar Static Field.
How come...
Run.
We could only trap
these two beasts for a short while.
You all leave immediately
after capturing the rabbit.
Hurry up!
Do it now!
Go!
Blue Silver Plant?
Tang San!
Tang Yin is... No...
Brother...
Darn it. Tang San tricked us.
Xiao Wu.
Brother.
Let’s go.
Why?
Get them!
Brother, I miss you so much.
I have no regrets after seeing you again.
Silly girl, as long as I’m still alive,
I won’t let them hurt you.
The further outward we go,
the more soul beasts there will be.
Brother, that side is safer.
These five Soul Saints of the
Keen Attack Branch are of lightning speed.
I’m afraid they may catch up with us soon.
You and I will teach them a lesson then.
Xiao Wu, later, I can eliminate two of them.
However, I need time to regain my strength.
After the attack, you need to carry me to escape.
Run as fast as you can. Got it?
[Soul Land]
Ghostly Trace.
They’re too speedy.
We could only attack them head on.
They’re really fast. We need to get out of here.
Fifth Soul Skill, Thunder Flash.
Got you.
Purple God Light.
Fifth Soul Skill,
Soft Bone Lock.
I’m immobilised.
Once you’re trapped by my fifth soul skill,
unless your soul power doubles mine
or my soul power has depleted,
otherwise, it’s impossible to get rid of it.
Xiao Wu!
Third Soul Skill, Teleport.
Is my soul power reaching the limit?
Fourth Soul Skill, Invincible Golden Shield.
Nana.
Tang San is Tang Yin.
Nana, what’s wrong with you?
Only nine Soul Saints are left out of twenty.
Darn it.
They’re not far. Go get them.
How come my spirit power fail to notice it?
A Human Faced Demon Spiders over
a decade millennium can make itself invisible.
Even the spirit power can be shielded by it.
I’m afraid it’s over 30,000 years old.
Invincible Golden Shield.
We’re running out of time.
We must force it to appear and slaughter it.
Purple God Light.
Over there.
They are right ahead.
Brother.
Keep running. Why don’t you run now?
It’s too late.
Brother.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[133 episodes have been completed
and broadcasted for nearly 1312 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2005]
[Total scene: 50898]
[Total CGI: 25862]
[Total plan of action scene: 10905]
[Total scene model: nearly 518]
[Total character model: nearly 965]
[Total props model: 13355]
[Appreciate your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
[Next Episode]
I wish I could live with you,
just like the old days.
But...
No.
Not bad.
Third strike!
It turns out...
Give up. Don’t bother to fight back.
I heard, back then, Tang San’s mother was also...
Tang San.
Don’t you care about your life?
If so,
they’ll have to kill me first.
[10 AM, Every Saturday]