♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Kid.
I lost.
From today on,
there is no more grudge
between you,
your father
and Tribe of Defense.
If both of our tribes team up,
who can defend
against us?
It is high-sounding,
but I’m afraid
that he’s planning
to take over the Tribe of Defense.
I would rather die in honor
than live in disgrace!
The mansion of the Tribe of Defense
is indestructible.
This...
Brother!
Welcome to Tang Clan.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 143]
Come!
Since we’re members of the same clan,
make yourself at home.
Let’s drink together!
Senior.
I really can’t drink much.
I’m afraid that I can only drink a bowl with you.
Alright!
I won’t force you.
I lost to you in the battle.
I can finally regain my dignity
in this banquet.
Both of you.
Why didn’t you wait for me
when you had good wine?
Old White Bird.
I didn’t expect that you would arrive early.
He’s the Chief of the Tribe of Agility,
Grandpa Bai He.
And she is his granddaughter, Bai Chen Xiang.
Old Rhino.
Old Gorilla.
You drank without me.
You have to punish yourselves
with three glasses of wine later.
Old White Bird.
Just tell us if you want to drink.
Don’t make excuses.
Hello, Grandpas.
Hello.
Xiang becomes prettier.
Come.
Let’s talk inside.
I saw Huyan Zhen
on my way here.
Old Rhino.
Did he come to look for you?
Huyan Zhen
came to persuade our tribe
on behalf of the Martial Soul Hall.
I rejected him.
But, I’m worried that they will take revenge.
So, I’ve decided
to move our tribe to Tian Dou City
and work with Old Gorilla.
Old White Bird.
We can’t help you in the future.
It’s been many years.
Had it not been for your help,
our Tribe of Agility
would have already ceased to exist.
It’s a shame.
Even now,
our tribe still...
Old White Bird.
Let me introduce a person to you.
My little brother
is a genius in the casting industry.
He created some weapons.
I think
they suit your tribe.
Never underestimate this thing.
It’s called the Godly Zhuge Crossbow.
Back then, Qibao Amber Tribe
managed to survive extermination,
thanks to a hundred of this kind of weapon.
Yes.
It’s very powerful.
It can destroy the defense soul skill
of a soul master who is below Level 40.
Really?
I’ve tried it.
He wasn’t exaggerating.
Grandpa Niu.
Was it the one
that penetrated your door?
You’re right.
So amazing?
What is its effective attack range?
Within 50 meters.
It does suit our tribe.
It can make up for our disadvantage in attacking.
Great.
I’ll buy this.
How much is it?
I want 200 of them.
Since you’re a friend of Senior Tai Tan,
I’ll take
120 gold soul coins then.
Alright.
There are 100 gold soul coins.
For the remaining 20 gold soul coins,
I’ll pay you
when the Tribe of Destruction arrives.
Senior.
I think that you’ve misunderstood me.
I meant
120 gold soul coins for one.
What did you say?
Are you fooling me?
Why don’t you rob someone?
Senior, please calm down.
We, Tang Clan, never cheat
when we do business.
I can guarantee
that this price is almost the same as the cost.
If you want,
you can buy one to protect yourself.
Though we failed to make a deal,
we can still maintain a good relationship.
I’ll give this Godly Zhuge Crossbow
to you to commemorate our first meeting.
This...
I can’t accept anything while doing nothing.
I can’t take it.
What about this?
I always look up to the Tribe of Agility
for your astonishing speed.
Why don’t I
have a battle with Miss Bai?
If I win,
I get these 100 gold soul coins.
If I lose,
I’ll pass this Godly Zhuge Crossbow
to you as the stake.
How is it?
You’re competing with our tribe in speed?
This...
Alright!
I’ll compete with you.
How shall we compete?
Within half an hour,
we’ll compete in this living room.
If you can touch any part of my body,
you win.
If not,
I win.
Alright.
Tribe of Agility,
Bai Chen Xiang.
Come on.
Tang Clan,
Tang San.
Tang Clan?
Old White Bird.
This young man
is not simple.
He founded Tang Clan
and is planning to fight the Martial Soul Hall.
Old Gorilla and I have already joined him.
Look.
Let me have a look at how good he is first.
I’ll start now.
Please.
Ghostly Trace.
It was close.
Her speed is scarier than I imagined.
He actually managed to dodge.
His steps are agile and unpredictable.
No wonder he suggested this battle.
But,
your steps
are not enough.
Her action
is so beautiful.
Sharp-tailed Swift Soul Skill?
Sharp-tailed Swifts
are the fastest birds in flight.
No wonder I’ve heard that the Tribe of Agility
focuses fully on their agility
during their training.
Xiang is using her Martial Soul.
Can the Chief win?
Look at Old White Bird’s face.
He was relaxed at first.
But he’s anxious now.
So,
what do you think?
Why is it burning so fast?
Third Soul Skill, Flight.
It’s useless.
Purple Demon Eye restrains speed.
First Soul Skill, Delusion.
Delusion?
She even has such a soul skill?
This happens every time.
It looks like I’m going to touch him,
but he always dodges it as he has predicted it.
Didn’t expect that Brother San’s
Blue Silver Emperor Right Thighbone
not only contains the additional skill,
but also allows him to speed up.
I’m not watching! I’m dizzy.
Brother San will win anyway.
Tang San! You can’t escape this time!
[Soul Land]
Time’s up!
You cheated!
How can half an hour be so short?
Even if you’re given another half an hour,
you still can’t touch a single strand
of Brother San’s hair.
The outcome will still be the same!
You...
He’s right.
We lost.
I admit defeat.
Miss Bai.
Thank you.
If you’re competent,
let’s compete in the long-distance speed.
Enough.
As he’s competing
with our Tribe of Agility in speed,
he may certainly choose the way to compete.
You didn’t train hard.
How dare you complain?
It’s not scary to fail.
But you have to realize the reason
of your failure.
Ouch!
It hurts!
This girl
has a temper.
Your steps are wonderful.
I’m convinced that we’ve lost.
I used my tricks.
Looking solely at the speed,
no one can compete with your tribe.
What’s the use of it?
Among the four single attribute tribes,
Tribe of Agility is the most useless one.
You just didn’t get a good chance
to showcase your skills.
Senior.
Why don’t we compete again?
If you lose,
I hope
that you can join Tang Clan.
Tang Clan
will provide you with all the equipment
and the resources you need.
And we won’t
give any orders to you.
What do you think?
Kid.
You’re very ambitious.
Chief.
I’m not judging you.
It’s okay for a young man to be confident.
But, if you’re too arrogant,
you’ll suffer.
No one can triumph
over Old White Bird’s speed.
If I lose,
I’m willing to provide you
with the full set of secret weapons for free,
including a Godly Zhuge Crossbow,
two sets of Soundless Arrow,
a Tight Flowery Crossbow,
a Malicious Attack,
and two Leg Crossbows.
Chief.
This set costs at least 500 gold soul coins.
There are more than 200 people
in the Tribe of Agility.
That would be 100,000.
Senior, what do you think?
Alright.
I’ll bet with you.
If I lose,
the Tribe of Agility will join Tang Clan.
But, I have to remind you first.
If Tang Clan is somehow related
to the Martial Soul Hall
later,
we’ll quit immediately.
There’s only one possibility
that Tang Clan is related
to the Martial Soul Hall,
which is the latter’s destruction.
Senior.
Let’s get started.
Still half an hour.
Same conditions.
This room is too narrow.
We shall go out and compete instead.
Alright. Please.
Get set!
First soul bone skill of Soft Bone Rabbit.
Go!
It was close.
I can’t dodge him
just by Ghostly Trace.
Teleport?
No wonder you were confident.
It’s interesting.
I want to see
how many times you can teleport.
Be careful!
After my breakthrough in power,
the soul bone skill, Teleport,
is enhanced too.
I can use it continuously
with just a small amount of soul power.
This is too fast.
Brother San only managed to dodge him
by changing his direction of teleport non-stop.
This is only the speed
under Old White Bird’s
martial soul amplification.
If he uses his soul skills...
This is the speed of the Tribe of Agility
at the level of the Great Soul Land Master.
I’ve used my Purple Demon Eye and spirit power
to the greatest extent,
but I barely managed to catch up with him.
You didn’t spend much of your soul power
despite 100 times of teleport.
Kid, you’re very good.
Looks like I need to be more serious
to get you.
Tang San is going to lose!
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 143 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1382 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2160]
[Total scene: 53862]
[Total CGI: 26632]
[Total plan of action scene: 11543]
[Total scene model: nearly 533]
[Total character model: nearly 989]
[Total props model: 13368]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
I shouldn’t have said
that you were an attendant of Tang San.
You’re actually Tang Hao’s son.
He’s arrogant and obstinate.
One day,
I will revitalize our tribe.
I’ll show the soul master world
how good our Tribe of Agility is.
I’m glad as long as I can live happily
and not worry about my living.
If you want to persuade him,
you must make use of the drugs.
I’ll never use
Xiao Wu’s soul again.
No! Xiao Wu?
[Soul Land]
[Available at 10 AM every Saturday]