♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind,
you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Although everyone knows
Martial Soul Hall is the murderer,
who would dare to suspect them
without evidence?
I’ll forsake my life
if I fail to destroy Martial Soul Hall.
Xie Yue and others have been there
for a long time.
Any news from them?
Now you may go to support them.
Later, there will be an arduous fight.
This person is very dangerous.
Take him down.
Sixth Soul Skill, Gear Blade Armour.
Brat, I won’t let you off easily.
Yan, if you don’t stop now,
I will fight against you.
Nana, why don’t you introduce him to us?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 132]
Nana, you mentioned
he has Death God Domain too?
Why don’t you introduce him to us?
Brother, he’s Tang Yin
who saved me at the Hell Road.
So, it was you. I should thank you.
You are Nana’s lifesaver.
We were only helping each other.
I need to find a place to rest. I’ll leave now.
You can’t leave.
Yan was right about one thing.
If you leave and
disturbed our target,
all of our efforts will be in vain.
Even I couldn’t bear the consequences.
So, you meant I have to stay here.
Grandpa Ghost, he won’t.
Maybe I’ll ask him to leave Star Forest first.
Nana, you’re not as smart as before.
Won’t our target
appear outside the forest?
Whichever way he takes
will possibly disturb our target.
Not letting you go
doesn’t mean that we’ll harm you.
Your spirit power is useful to us.
As repayment,
I’ll help you hunt the soul beast that suits you.
Please do consider.
Tang Yin...
Do I have other alternatives?
They’re too arrogant.
Does Martial Soul Hall
want to rule the entire continent?
Do they think Tian Dou Empire
has no guts to fight them?
Calm down, Your Majesty.
Now we have to come out with
a plan to deal with them.
Apart from a majority of soul masters,
some of the kingdoms and duchies of our empire
are also under the control of Martial Soul Hall.
Please don’t act rashly, Your Majesty.
The defense of the palace
has been greatly improved.
How could I not be impulsive?
Chief Ning is loyal to the empire,
but he was almost killed by Martial Soul Hall.
And also Grandmaster...
If I don’t take any actions,
how am I going to face the deceased?
Your Majesty, you should remain calm.
Your forbearance can help us the most.
With my mighty armies,
do you think I’m scared of them?
It’s not about fear. We just can’t.
Martial Soul Hall has at least
20,000 powerful soul masters
and more than ten Grand Soul Land Masters.
Perhaps they can’t compete with
your armies in quantity.
But they have the support of Guardian Knights
and many small countries.
We don’t have enough soul masters
and we lack capable leaders.
That’s why we have to endure.
Any suggestions, Grandmaster?
To fight with Martial Soul Hall,
we must collaborate with all parties
who are opposed to them.
Do you mean collaborating with Xing Luo Empire?
But Tian Dou has feuded with Xing Luo
for ages, I’m afraid...
Your Majesty, there’s no eternal enemy
in this world, but eternal benefit.
Xing Luo Empire would also be afraid of
their strength and artifice.
Collaboration is inevitable.
Besides...
Martial Soul Hall has started their plan.
As for us, we’re still short of competent people.
So, we must recruit
more individual soul masters to join us.
Destroying Martial Soul Hall
can’t be done within a short period.
Please make a long-term plan, Your Majesty.
I see what you mean.
Grandmaster, any suggestions on
recruiting soul masters?
My tribe has been wiped out
so I’m so distracted now.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
But please be rest assured.
I’ll train our soul masters as much as I can
so that they’ll be prepared for the battle
as soon as possible.
Without further ado, let’s discuss it now.
Hao Tian Tribe...
Grandpa Ghost,
is this why you let Tang Yin stay?
Yes. Nana,
find out the reason why he left the tribe.
Maybe he can help us
snoop into Hao Tian Tribe’s internal affairs.
Grandpa Ghost,
we’ve already known where Hao Tian Tribe is.
Why do we need him?
Girl, you’re blinded by your emotions.
Hao Tian Tribe
is one of the reasons why I let him stay.
Besides, it’s for your sake.
Grandpa Ghost, don’t say that...
If you really want to be with him,
his identity
is an inevitable problem that you can’t avoid.
Persuade him to join Martial Soul Hall.
You are such a good match.
Brat, mark my words.
If you dare to get close to Nana,
I’ll kill you.
Do you think you can?
You...
[Soul Land]
It’s late, rest early.
I won’t let you off easily.
Come in.
Eat something.
I’m so sorry for troubling you.
After we finish the task,
you may leave whenever you want.
You’re here to convince me to
join Martial Soul Hall.
I won’t do anything futile.
You’re a smart one.
However, I’m curious
what Martial Soul Hall is going to do
by gathering so many people in Star Forest?
We’re going to hunt a powerful soul beast.
We will possibly encounter some trouble,
so we come in a big group, just in case.
A Decade Millenium Soul Beast?
Yes.
It’s Xiao Wu.
I must snoop for more information from her.
Where’s Nana?
It’s been a while. You’ve changed a lot.
Although you were as cold as ever
when we met last night,
your personality has changed.
You’re maturer and more sophisticated now.
So are you.
Teacher spent a lot of time and effort
to help me control my heinous spirit.
Speaking of which,
obviously you’re much more talented than I am.
Not really.
After leaving Slaughter City,
I failed to control my heinous spirit.
and turned the tribe upside down.
That’s why I was expelled from Hao Tian Tribe.
So, under your calmness,
you’re filled with agony.
Tang Yin, what have you been through?
I won’t ask about your tribe’s anymore.
If you don’t have anywhere else to go,
come to Martial Soul Hall with me.
Teacher will definitely appreciate you.
Martial Soul Hall and Hao Tian Tribe
are antagonistic.
They won’t accept a person from Hao Tian Tribe.
It depends on whether you can impress my teacher.
Let’s set off.
The target is at the center of Star Forest.
Nana has tested him yesterday.
He’s trustable.
The plan went well.
First, pretend to expose
my Blue Silver Domain to attract them.
Then, gain their trust by acting as
an expelled disciple of Hao Tian Tribe.
Next,
it’s time to use the Blue Silver Domain.
We’re getting closer to the center of the forest.
This...
Tang Yin, what’s wrong?
He must be backlashed.
The aura...
It’s the aura of two
Decade Millenium Soul Beasts. Xiao Wu...
Xiao Wu must be around here nearby.
Welcome to Start Forest.
Xiao Wu. It has been five years. Finally...
I must find a chance to save Xiao Wu.
You have looked for me for a long time, right?
You’ve found me now.
Why don’t you dare to come?
King of Forest, Titan Giant Ape.
Amongst all Grand Soul Land Masters,
Tang Hao is the only one
who defeated Titan Giant Ape.
It’s Xiao Wu. How come Xiao Wu is with it?
Was it protecting Xiao Wu that time?
This is bad.
Martial Soul Hall, let’s put an end to this today.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 132 has been completed
and broadcasted for nearly 1277 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 1929]
[Total scene: 49148]
[Total CGI: 25376]
[Total plan of action scene: 10483]
[Total scene model: nearly 508]
[Total character model: nearly 962]
[Total props model: 13352]
[Appreciate your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
[Next Episode]
This is...
Tang San?
Tang Yin is...
Why?
Brother, I miss you so much.
I have no regrets anymore
after seeing you.
Silly girl, as long as I’m still alive,
I’ll never let them hurt you.