♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind,
you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
The real threats
normally exist at the outer side of
Slaughter Arena.
I want to enroll.
Hao Tian Hammer?
Friendship never exists in Slaughter City.
The journey of slaughtering,
begins.
Only one will win among ten.
Don’t need your protection.
Fight!
The eighth hidden weapon of Tang Clan,
Phoenix Guides Nine Chicks.
The descend of a Death God
will plunges hell into misery.
Do you think he can accomplish 100 matches
and challenge Hell Road?
If I’m not wrong,
the entrance of Hell Road
must be in the Hell Slaughter Arena.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 115]
The heinous spirit inside me
is getting harder to control.
I must be in complete control
in order to take down the 100th match
and challenge Hell Road.
Who is it?
It’s me.
Anything?
There’s no limit in participants
to challenge Hell Road.
I want to team up with you.
Hell Road?
Why do you choose me?
Because we’re not the real degenerates.
You’re here for training, right?
Is there any problem?
If you’re here for training, you must
win at Hell Road to get out of here.
Hell Road toxicated with heinous spirit,
it’s truly menacing.
We should team up,
otherwise both of us will perish.
Why should I trust you?
I’d like to remind you,
this is Slaughter City.
I know you’re from Hao Tian Tribe.
To show my sincerity,
I’ll tell you my origin.
I’m Hu Liena, from Martial Soul Hall.
My teacher
is the Pope of Martial Soul Hall.
I see, you’re the disciple of the Pope.
But you should be aware of
the conflicts between
Martial Soul Hall and Hao Tian Tribe.
Collaborating will brings us benefits.
I can reveal one more secret to you.
If one’s able to pass through Hell Road,
he’ll be recognised by one special domain,
namely, the Death God Domain.
It absorbs one’s heinous spirit
and tags on his own martial soul.
Death God Domain?
Is this the reason why
Father asked me to come here for?
Besides, it’ll enhance
according to the growth of
one’s heinous spirit.
How are you so clear about it?
Because I know someone
who possesses this domain.
Could it be...
I’ve told you everything. Your reply?
The 100th match of Asura King
is beginning soon.
The soul power of nine of them
is above Level 80.
I can’t believe they’ll collaborate.
If they lose,
their soul power will belong to Asura King.
They have high possibility to win.
That guy had won 49 matched
just around one year plus.
His winning rating is just below
Asura King and Emissary of Hell.
While the others had won 40 matches.
Asura King might not be able
to handle them.
Nine of the Great Soul Land Masters
collaborated?
As expected,
the 100th match is strenuous.
Terminate Asura King and
let’s challenge the Hell Road together.
He’s just merely a Soul King,
how could he fight against nine of us?
Fight!
Got him.
He is protected by
a strong heinous spirit.
Settle him quickly. Stop him
from condensing his heinous spirit.
Phoenix Guides Nine Chicks.
Be careful. The hidden weapon
is controlled by his heinous spirit.
Quickly dodge!
So, the strategy you meant
was to manipulate us for your gain.
Only I can defeat Asura King.
Even Hao Tian Hammer can’t resist this,
Meteor Continuous Hammer.
Meteor Hammer, which is formed from
the condensation of soul power?
I wonder how you can counter it.
[Soul Land]
Heinous spirit becomes tangible.
Heinous spirit…
Asura King, 100 matches.
It has been decades that Slaughter City
never emerges a strong one.
I never expect both Emissary of Hell
and Asura King have succeeded.
Congratulations to young Asura King.
Slaughter King.
- I’ve seen this aura on Dad...
- Slaughter King.
He must be the Grand Soul Land Master.
Emissary of Hell, please.
This...
My mind will be calm
only if I drink it.
It’s poisonous.
Poisonous?
The air in Slaughter City
contains chronic toxin
that will excite one’s mind.
It’ll be worst if you consume
Netherland Shot which is also poisonous.
Could it be...
This toxin must be related to Hell Road.
It entices people to consume
to boost their soul power.
You’re not deeply poisoned.
Stop before you get worse. Take this.
Eat it if you trust me.
The toxin inside you will be excreted
within three days.
If you don’t...
I do. Please trust me too.
Because we have to get out of here alive.
I’ve bared my heart to you.
But I’ve no idea who you are.
What’s your name?
But I can’t tell you I’m Tang San...
My name is
Tang Yin.
Today, we have two invincibles.
Are you intimidated by their
formidable strength and heinous spirit?
Yes!
Asura King and Emissary of Hell,
I hereby bestowed upon you
the title of Death God.
And hire you as my alien minister,
whose level is just below me.
From now on,
you can enter Slaughter City freely.
Bestowed as Death God
without challenging Hell Road?
Looks like
he doesn’t want us to obtain
the Death God Domain.
No need.
I’m willing to pass through
Hell Road on my own
to become Death God.
Perhaps you’re not aware of
the horror of Hell Road.
Emissary of Hell,
I hope you’d understand
you only have one life.
Mighty Slaughter King,
isn’t it funny for you
to talk about life with me?
How about you?
I appreciate your kind intention.
Please open the entrance of Hell Road.
I’ll pass through Hell Road
with Emissary of Hell.
Both of you are collaborating?
Have you forgotten your origin?
Rather than both of us die at Hell Road,
why don’t we go out of here alive
and become the real Death Gods?
Please follow Slaughter City’s rule,
Slaughter King.
If so, it will be a good journey
to have company at Hell Road.
No one has ever seen
the opening of Hell Road
besides Death God and Slaughter King...
They’d be honored to be the sacrifice
of the opening of Hell Road.
Those who’ve seen it have...
What’s that?
Even my spirit power can’t endure it...
Wish you good luck.
[Next Episode]
This is Hell Road?
I wonder what’s down there?
Do you feel it’s getting
hotter and hotter?
Those who collaborated
to challenge Hell Road
do have their own agendas.
When confronting with an invincible,
if you can’t let him surrender to you,
it’d be better to let him sleep forever.
Are you trying to harm me?
We’re in trouble now.
It’s too insidious.
Tang Yin!
Where’s the vital point?