♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
We’re coming back fully loaded.
Peacock Plumes.
Storm Pear Blossom Needle.
Tang’s Lotus of Buddha’s Rage.
If we can successfully make
these three types of hidden weapons,
even the Martial Soul Hall...
The auction is about to begin.
Everyone,
please.
He studied for ten whole years,
and has actually succeeded.
Oh, no, Brother San!
But I found Myles
gathering his troops,
saying he’s going to attack the Society
and kill to steal the treasure!
A pith-dark night
is the killing night.
[Episode 151]
We didn’t drink enough, I’m telling you.
Let’s drink some more.
You can’t even drink, but you keep saying that.
I’m definitely going to get you drunk today.
Look.
Run!
Who are you?
How dare you block my path!
You two,
go and take a look.
What is it?
Look.
Even though Xiao Wu is unconscious,
she can still sense
the blood on my body,
instinctively keeping distance from me.
The Martial Soul Main Hall and its people
were destroyed overnight.
Nothing like this has ever happened
on the Douluo Continent.
This is called upholding justice.
But Brother San,
why did we have to give the money
I brought back from the Martial Soul Main Hall
to the Ironsmiths Society?
That is money from the people of Gengxin Town.
They should give it back to the people.
Also because of this,
the Ironsmiths Society
agreed to sell us
the auction items at half price.
Including the two magical weapons.
Rong Rong.
Let us see how strong
the item’s defense is.
Master Si Di said
that this flexible armor
can withstand any frontal attack
from a soul master less than Level 60.
This is truly a rare treasure.
Little Ao.
This one is for men.
You wear it.
Brother San.
Xiao Wu needs it more than I do.
Besides, Senior Lou Gao
promised to keep making this kind of armor for us.
I’ll ask him
for another one then.
We should call him Elder Lou Gao
now that he’s a part of Tang Clan.
Elder Lou Gao.
Are you alright?
Chief.
What was the metal
you found
that could make
the Storm Pear Blossom Needle?
Is it the Essence of Cold Iron?
Tai Tan and I already looked into it.
In order to make the Storm Pear Blossom Needle,
we need at least two kilograms
of the Essence of Cold Iron.
But there’s not enough
in the whole Gengxin Town.
How did you find it?
Those ores were mixed in with the pure iron.
The owner didn’t recognize them.
But soul masters with the Qibao Amber Pagoda
as their martial soul
have a strong ability for treasure appraisal.
But to make the Storm Pear Blossom Needle,
the Essence of Cold Iron is hard enough
but not tenacious enough.
Why don’t we use the core of Deep Sea Silver instead?
Chief.
I am more than 60% certain
that we can make this peerless hidden weapon.
Senior.
I understand how you feel.
But the core of Deep Sea Silver
can’t be melted by any kind of flame.
It must be hammered by hand.
However, with the power we have right now,
it’ll be difficult to cast it.
My old master might be the only one
who can do it.
Let me
take care of this problem.
Elder Lou Gao.
I will find a suitable partner for you.
With the Essence of Cold Iron,
I will be able to make another
unique hidden weapon of Tang Clan,
Lotus of Buddha’s Rage.
If Elder Lou Gao
can also create the Storm Pear Blossom Needle,
then these two hidden weapons
will be a huge boost
for Tang Clan.
The Seven Clans Re-Selection Contest
is just around the corner.
We must accelerate
the development of Tang Clan.
[Soul Land]
[Tang Clan]
Clan Chief.
Three Elders.
How did you know we were back?
Clan Chief.
Don’t forget the Tribe of Agility’s talent.
There are people of my clan
watching throughout Tian Dou City.
Any changes
will be reported right away.
It’s not your clan or my clan.
From now on,
we are all part of the Tang Clan.
Tang Clan is officially established.
Talking about other clans
is indeed not appropriate.
Our trip to Gengxin Town
was very fruitful.
Most importantly,
we brought back
a top-tier craftsman.
This is Elder Lou Gao,
the former president of the Ironsmiths Society.
He is now
also an Elder of Tang Clan.
Clan Chief.
Let’s talk while walking.
Here.
Take a look
at what we’ve done while you were gone.
This is so big!
I’m surprised that you, Old Rhino
has already built the clan.
Tang Clan is currently built
to hold 1,500 people.
As the clan grows,
we can keep expanding.
Clan Chief.
Tang Clan buildings
are currently divided into five sections.
The east, south, west, and north
are the four tribes’ quarters.
The Chief’s Mansion is in the middle.
All of the buildings
have been strengthened
and have places to fire hidden weapons.
Once the clan is attacked,
all soul masters
can get to the battle positions immediately.
The Tribe of Defense
really is the top architect.
You’ve finished building a huge complex
in such short time.
It’s a pity we didn’t redesign and build
the outer walls.
Or else, I’m confident
we could make Tang Clan into a fortress.
Elder Niu Gao.
You’ve done an amazing job already.
Based on the current state
of the soul masters’ world,
we don’t need to publicize Tang Clan for now.
The four single attribute tribes
are all the foundations of Tang Clan.
From now on,
I will need all of your help and effort
to grow and expand Tang Clan.
Clan Chief.
No need to be polite with us.
We need you to lead the way
in the future development of the clan.
I have a suggestion
that I’d like to discuss with all of you.
I’d like to change the names of
the four single attribute tribes,
and also give each elder a specific role.
Clan Chief.
Please give us more details.
My plan
is to change the four tribes into four halls.
Each elder will be the leader of one hall.
The Tribe of Destruction
will now be the Hall of Medicine,
responsible for making medicine
and the clan’s defense.
Hall of Strength
will be responsible for making hidden weapons.
Hall of Defense
will lead the clan’s defense and construction.
Hall of Agility
will focus on intelligence and scouting.
Elder Lou Gao
will be responsible for making
all hidden weapons for the clan.
I believe
that among all hidden weapons we make,
the ones engraved with two words “Lou Gao”
will be the top tier.
Alright.
That’s the plan.
Also,
we will add a Hall of Martial Arts
for fighting against enemies.
Ma Hong Jun will lead it.
Logistics and finance
will be managed by Oscar and Ning Rong Rong.
Lastly,
I think it’s time to tell everyone
her identity.
Xiao Wu.
My love.
She is a Century Millennium Soul Beast
like my mother.
She sacrificed herself
to save me.
Thankfully, with the help of two celestial goods,
she has become human again.
But her soul
has emerged with my sixth soul ring
during the sacrifice.
Besides Xiao Wu, everyone else here
will are all members of the Hall of Discussion.
Any important matters of the clan
will be discussed and voted
by all of us.
Everyone will have one vote.
Elders,
do you have any suggestions?
Chief, your plans are well-organized.
My only opinion
is that you have too little power.
I suggest
giving our chief two votes.
Just consider it Xiao Wu’s vote.
At the same time,
the Clan Chief can veto any decision.
Now that the structure
and responsibilities are clear,
we can start to operate the clan soon.
By then,
even if the Martial Soul Hall
finds out about Tang Clan,
they won’t be able to attack us easily.
Speaking of the Martial Soul Hall...
Clan Chief,
our people
found that
over a thousand soul masters
has come into the city recently.
That many?
It seems like something big
is going to happen.
Let’s do this.
Little Ao.
You and Rong Rong
go back to the Qibao Amber Tribe
to visit Uncle Ning.
Fatty and I
will go back to our school.
Gengxin Town.
Tang San.
Send my orders.
We will execute the plan earlier.
Among the soldiers on horseback,
nobody was dressed like a royal.
Why do them dare to charge through the street?
Are they on an emergency mission?
Fatty.
Let’s walk faster.
We’ll check up on the school first.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 151 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1438 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2281]
[Total scene: 56372]
[Total CGI: 27165]
[Total plan of action scene: 12052]
[Total scene model: nearly 546]
[Total character model: nearly 995]
[Total props model: 13374]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[The dream on Soul Land and the martial soul
illuminates our youth.]
[We are not alone with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
Little Freak.
Come to the palace with me.
If you can’t do anything,
then Tian Dou Empire is really doomed.
It turns out Tang Yin is Tang San.
Attack.
You monster!
No need to resist.