♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
I will definitely obtain consent
from Chief Ning this time.
I’ll never leave you.
What did you experience in the past five years?
You’ll know when you find someone
whom you want to protect the most.
Why did you leave?
I’m willing to love her with everything I have.
You have a choice now.
But, Tang San is a good brother of mine.
Now, he needs my help.
If I leave,
I won’t be able to forgive myself.
Silly boy.
Chief Ning.
Why are you still calling me Chief Ning?
Call him your father-in-law!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 140]
Tribe of Strength
has been standing for many years.
It’s more than suitable for it to be
the foundation of Tang Clan.
Senior, thank you for your kindness.
Why are you still calling me Senior?
Call me Elder.
I should call you Chief now..
Please get up. You may forgo the formalities.
Chief, I’ll go out tomorrow.
Tai Nuo will be in charge of
the early preparation of Tang Clan.
Are you going on a long journey?
Among the subordinates of Hao Tian Tribe,
the Tribe of Defense, Tribe of Agility,
Tribe of Destruction
and my Tribe of Strength
are the top four single attribute tribes.
Since Hao Tian Tribe is closed,
we survive on our own
and promised to meet every two years.
I see.
Recently, Martial Soul Hall is being too active
and the Seven Great Tribes will
be re-selected one year later.
Indeed, you shall meet for a discussion.
Elder, may I go with you?
It’s alright that you go with me,
but the other three tribes have been weaken a lot
by the punishment from Martial Soul Hall,
for which they’re holding grudges
with Hao Tian Tribe.
If you hope to get their support,
I’m afraid that you’ll be disappointed.
Hao Tian Tribe indeed let them down.
Well... Please let me go with you.
I’d like to do something for them.
Chief, you’re indeed considerate.
Tomorrow morning, we will set off to
Long Xing Town in Xing Luo Empire
to visit the Tribe of Defense.
Elder, I need a batch of ironsmiths.
They must be trustable.
And, they must be the top ironsmiths
who are good at casting.
Can you help me find them?
Chief, don’t you know what we,
the Tribe of Strength, do?
Each of the top four tribes
has different advantages.
We, the Tribe of Strength, are good at casting.
Our specialties are our strength and tolerance.
Tribe of Defense we’re visiting this time
is good at building houses.
Their specialty is more on defense.
Tribe of Agility is good at inspection.
They are the best scouts.
Tribe of Destruction is good at making medicine.
Their specialty is the ruthless attack.
Though these four tribes
haven’t recovered fully,
there are almost a thousand people in total.
I see...
Chief, why are you looking for ironsmiths?
Are you making weapons?
Life is so hard.
I’ve just escaped from Tian Dou Empire
and came to Xing Luo...
We can’t even earn more than we did in Tian Dou.
These are all I’ve got.
I don’t have much either.
I have...
I... I have...
Fart!
Calm down!
I heard that the top four single attribute tribes
are gathering soon.
They will gather
at Tribe of Defense’s place this year.
Maybe we can...
Be careful! It’s poisoned!
Elder, you...
Did you just break the Godly Zhuge Crossbow?
I’m the Vice President of
the Continental Ironsmiths Society
When it comes to the skill of casting,
if I declare myself as the second best,
no one will dare to declare himself as the best.
Even my master isn’t better than me
in controlling the fire.
But... disassembling the Godly Zhuge Crossbow
will trigger it.
The poison on the gear is highly toxic.
How did you...
This is a unique palm skill
of Tribe of Strength.
Iron Hammering Palm.
With it,
our palms wouldn’t be injured during casting.
It can isolate most of the poisons, too.
The design of the Godly Zhuge Crossbow
is ingenious.
It’s of uniform texture and
sufficient resilience.
Chief, don’t worry.
You can leave the mass manufacturing
of Godly Zhuge Crossbow to us.
Thank you, Elder.
After we’re done,
we can make a deal with
both Tian Dou Empire and Xing Luo Empire.
Not long ago, I came into an agreement
with Qibao Amber Tribe.
Tang Clan will exchange weapons
with Qibao Amber Tribe for their supplies.
In that case,
Tang Clan will have
enough money for its establishment.
It will also help us a lot
in defeating Martial Soul Hall.
Chief, you’re far more careful than others.
This weapon is amazing.
Why don’t we make more?
I’m thinking about it, too.
With our skill now,
there’s another type of weapon
that we can make.
It can at least break the defense of a Soul Saint,
including the martial soul form.
What exactly is that thing so lethal?
When the weapon is launched,
it will be like a peacock flaunting its tail.
It will take a person’s life instantaneously
when he is dazzled,
for which it gets the name “Peacock Plumes”.
Peacock Plumes is a one-feet-long cylinder.
On it, there are two buttons.
One is for reloading
and the other button is for shooting.
There are a total of 12 types, 365 hidden weapons,
in a Peacock Plumes.
Each of the 12 types
has a different function, penetration,
explosion, poisoning and so on.
The strongest ones are Needle of Destruction
and Needle of Seven Kills.
They can take a person’s life immediately.
This is the Peacock Plumes.
Chief, hurry and tell me...
Master San. Grandpa.
You’ve been discussing along the way.
We still have to visit
the Tribe of Defense tomorrow.
Aren’t you resting for a while?
We’re not tired.
You can sleep first if you’re tired.
Here, Chief. Let me have a look...
OK.
[Soul Land]
The lobbyists from the Martial Soul Hall
are on their way.
Dad, are we really going to be
a affiliated tribe to Martial Soul Hall?
Working with the Martial Soul Hall
is like asking a tiger for its skin.
However, as the Chief of Tribe of Defense,
I have no choice...
Dad...
Hao Tian Tribe... Tang Hao.
When you were fighting the Pope,
did you even consider us?
Chief, this blueprint is ingenious.
Did you draw it yourself?
No, I saw it from a book by chance.
This kind of weapon is called
“hidden weapons” in that book.
My purpose in establishing Tang Clan in Soul Land
is to develop these hidden weapons.
I’ll contribute
what I’ve learned to Tang Clan
and bring Tang Clan to its peak.
Chief, you’re young but your experiences
are abnormal.
Chief, you said that you need one more thing
to create the Peacock Plume. What is that?
This thing is called “Black Iron”.
Black Iron? What... What is that?
This... I don’t know what exactly it is called, either.
It’s slightly heavier than normal iron.
If a weapon is created with pure Black Iron,
it can defeat most metal weapons.
You mean Black Banded Iron, right?
It is much more expensive than gold.
It’s the king of metal.
Yes. It’s the Black Banded Iron.
It’s hard to find Black Banded Iron.
We have to go to the capital of metal,
Geng Xin Town.
The headquarter of
Continental Ironsmiths Society is there too.
Whatever you want, the society
can meet your need.
What about the core of Deep Sea Silver?
What... What is this?
The Peacock Plume that I mentioned last time
ranks third in the top three long-lost
machinery types of hidden weapons.
The first and the second
are the Angered Buddha’s Lotus
and the Storm Pear Blossom Needle respectively.
Angered Buddha’s Lotus is the strongest
multi-attack hidden weapon.
Unlike the Storm Pear Blossom Needle
and the Peacock Plumes,
its biggest specialty
is its highly concentrated gunpowder.
So it can explode violently in an instant.
It looks like a normal lotus
but its attack range is wide
and it is very powerful.
It can even scare a Grand Soul Land Master.
It’s touted as the supreme hidden weapon.
I once developed a Angered Buddha’s Lotus,
but unfortunately...
I came with nothing and I’ll go with nothing.
This Angered Buddha’s Lotus is the last gift
that I leave for our clan.
Though the Storm Pear Blossom Needle
ranks second in machinery type of hidden weapons,
judging its sole attack power,
it’s no worse than the Angered Buddha’s Lotus.
Twenty-seven hidden weapons
can be triggered at the same time.
No one can dodge it.
Injuries are inevitable once it’s triggered.
Amazing! It’s really marvelous!
To produce the Storm Pear Blossom Needle,
we need the core of Deep Sea Silver.
Deep Sea Mica
is a kind of metal ten times more expensive
than the Black Iron.
As for its core, it is so precious.
Chief, when we reach Geng Xin Town,
we can ask the president of the society, Lou Gao.
He will be quite interested in it.
Here, after looking at your blueprints,
I have a few suggestions in upgrading
the Godly Zhuge Crossbow.
No, your plan is not good.
Rascal, how is it not good?
They’ve been talking about
hidden weapons the whole trip.
Aren’t they tired?
This old man and the young man.
Why are they so crazy about hidden weapons?
Halt!
I’m from Xing Luo Empire.
I’m telling you.
Anyone who wants to enter Long Xing Town
has to hand out his soul guiding tool.
Elder.
Bu Le, don’t you recognize me?
It’s been a long time, you’re still so wretched.
Fatty, how do you know my name?
Don’t you remember
the taste of Sister Wu’s Eight Flinging?
Shit. It’s you.
You made me lie in bed for half a month.
You even hung me up in the plaza.
[Confession: My name is Bu Le. I’m a scoundrel
but I swear I’ll be good from now on.]
It is a shame.
I’ve looked for you for so long.
Can’t believe you come and find us today.
Brother San, you don’t have to help me.
I can settle it by myself.
Fatty, can you do it?
They are just a Soul King and two Soul Emperors.
I’ll hit their teeth off today
to wipe off my humiliation.
Be careful then.
Fatty, you’re over-confident.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 140 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1361 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2114]
[Total scene: 52948]
[Total CGI: 26361]
[Total plan of action scene: 11293]
[Total scene model: nearly 528]
[Total character model: nearly 977]
[Total props model: 13365]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
[Youth becomes vibrant with your presence.]
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods,
who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
Fifth Soul Skill!
Formless Attack!
Hurry... Hurry up and run!
This is...
the leader of the Tribe of Defense.
Who is this guy?
I’m Tang San.
My father is Tang Hao.
Isn’t the harm
that Hao Tian Tribe brought to us enough?
What?
What do you mean by that?
Young man.
You’re absolutely madcap!
[Soul Land]
[Available at 10 AM every Saturday]