♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind,
you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Kill them all.
I’ll kill you first.
Defeat me,
is your pass to enter Slaughter City.
Slaughter City,
a place where soul skill is forbidden.
I’m here.
Welcome to Slaughter City.
Here is a paradise for crime.
Besides,
you’re forbidden to leave once entered.
Hu Liena.
This place is dangerous.
You’d better be careful.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 114]
I want to enroll.
Take this. This way, please.
The competition has ended. 5177 won.
35 wins in total.
What is he doing?
Only one wins among ten.
The winner can absorb losers’ soul power.
This’s the rule of Slaughter Arena.
How to win the championship?
Participate in 100 matches,
you’ll be the champion.
But, the current top one
merely took part in 67 matches.
Every match you win
allows you one more year
to enjoy yourself here.
Your group has filled with
10 participants.
Next match is your turn.
Are you sure...
I’ve decided.
Well, your life’s in your own hands.
Wish you luck.
My advice to you,
friendship never exists in Slaughter City.
Journey of slaughter, begins now.
Hao Tian Hammer?
He is from Hao Tian Tribe.
That’s why he’s similar to Tang San.
Over the past thousand years,
you’re the third from Hao Tian Tribe
to enter Slaughter City.
The competition has ended. 9528 won.
You may leave.
I’m familiar with Slaughter City.
No need your protection.
You’re too naive. In Slaughter City,
the real threats don’t come
from Slaughter Arena.
Suit yourself.
Competition starts now.
Competition ends.
9528 won. 17 wins in total.
9528 won. 67 wins in total.
9528! 9528 excellent!
I really can’t see through him.
Why is she here?
I heard that she watched every competition
which involved 9528.
Are you sure?
Look at her serious face.
It seems she’s analysing 9528.
It’s terrible to be her target.
No one is more terrifying than
Emissary of Hell.
Next participant,
9528 please be on stage.
Competition starts now.
Fight!
Nine of them are
at least Soul Saint and above.
Ghostly Trace.
I sacrificed both my limbs
for this competition
and fixed with two robotic limbs
just to counter your attack.
What?
Cut your crap.
Don’t let him use the hammer.
Can’t use Hao Tian Hammer in time,
hidden weapon can’t pierce through
their armour as well. What can I do?
Well, it’s not a problem
if failed to pierce through the armour.
Amass soul power on this arrow.
Its great impact will
throw you to some distance.
You too, fall.
How come they’re not falling?
This’s our strategy.
This is the determination act.
[Soul Land]
Can 9528 win this time?
I hope someone can kill him.
Constantly struggling at the edge of death
is the truth of battling.
The eighth hidden weapon of Tang Clan.
Phoenix Guides Nine Chicks.
Only strength is the strongest strategy.
Although my soul power only
improved one level this year,
however, my strength is beyond
threefold enhancement.
Competition ends.
9528 won. 68 wins in total.
9528! 9528 superb!
- He’s as horrible as the Asura.
- Asura King!
He’s the first one ever
to win 67 matches within a year.
I don’t dare to join the match.
Who dares? I heard that once
there were hundreds of people
collaborating to attack him
after his match.
Although he was severely injured
by those people,
he crushed them in the end.
Fought hundreds of men by himself?
He’s truly a Asura King.
Who do you think will win
if Emissary of Hell fight with him?
Emissary of Hell?
That lady won 72 matches
just within two years?
What’s wrong with me?
Why would I worry for him?
Brother was once
the most outstanding one I had seen
until I met him...
Don’t be cocksure. Asura King’s
waiting for you at the Slaughter Arena.
It’s her?
The descend of a Death God
will plunges hell into misery.
Asura King won another match.
I know.
All techniques of Asura King
are extremely powerful.
Even the Grand Soul Land Master
can’t kill him without using soul skill.
Do you think he can
hit 100 matches and challenge Hell Road?
It’s a matter of time
to hit 100 matches,
but, as for Hell Road,
I’m afraid he can’t.
I was told that
he was sent by the most terrifying one
of the two existing Death Gods.
While the Emissary of Hell
was sent by the other one.
Each time a Death God appears,
there would be disastrous harm
to Slaughter City.
Just in case,
why don’t we let
Emissary of Hell to battle Asura King?
They will be...
Fool.
We can’t afford to offend
any of the Death Gods.
Go, keep an eye on them.
Emissary of Hell has completed
the 99th match.
She just came here for around two years.
Asura King only came for a year.
He has won more than 90 matches.
What if both of them meet in the match...
Are you new?
Slaughter Arena stipulates that
participant with 50 victories and above
won’t meet in the match.
As expected,
if winner absorb all soul power,
his or her strength should be
increased by leaps and bounds.
In every competition,
it may seem like the winner absorbs
all the soul power of losers,
in actual fact, it was all absorbed
by Slaughter Arena.
If I’m not wrong,
the entrance of Hell Road is
in the Hell Slaughter Arena.
Netherlands shot is a good thing.
It calms our thoughts and
enhances our soul power too.
But it’s exorbitant.
It can only be exchanged with
the victory of Slaughter Arena.
Asura King!
I’m sure Emissary of Hell and
Asura King won’t worry about this.
It seems like Asura King
has completed 99 matches.
Perhaps Emissary of Hell wants
to challenge Hell Road with him,
that’s why she doesn’t
go for the last match.
She has finally got him.
He’s the first one
to achieve 99 wins in two years.
[Next Episode]
It’s me.
You’re here for training,
right?
I know you’re from Hao Tian Tribe.
To show my sincerity,
I’ll tell you about my origin.
When one passed through Hell Road,
he or she will be recognised
by a domain.
Absorb others’ heinous spirit.
Besides, everyone I met...
Talking about life with me,
isn’t this ironic?
My mighty Slaughter King.