♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Death is knocking on your door.
Stop struggling.
I said I’d protect you with my life.
You must escape from here.
Brother!
Brother.
Do you think I will live without you?
I don’t want you to die.
I want you to be alive.
When I’m gone,
take good care of yourself.
Farewell, my love.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 135]
Xiao Wu.
Sister Wu’s breathe is getting weaker.
Please don’t leave me.
Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet
can help one to reborn
and protect its owner. Perhaps...
It has sublimated. We still have hope.
Xiao Wu, can you hear me?
Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet
is starting to work,
it may take some time to take effect.
Sister Wu sacrificed her soul.
Even if she can wake up, I’m afraid...
Martial Soul Hall,
I will have you pay with your blood.
It has been seven days.
You can’t keep going on like this
without eating or sleeping.
If Sister Wu knows, she will be worried.
Sister Wu awakes.
It’s great! Xiao Wu isn’t dead.
She is still alive.
Xiao Wu.
There is no trace of soul in her.
Why?
Brother.
Xiao Wu, I knew it.
That’s just a bad dream, right?
Xiao Wu.
No, Xiao Wu.
All of my attributes have greatly improved,
as well as my spirit power.
Is it because Xiao Wu gave her soul to me?
Brother, your soul power
has ascended to Level 65.
That’s great!
You must be the most powerful
Soul Emperor on the entire continent now.
I don’t want any of these.
I only hope that you’re still alive.
Xiao Wu.
In the future, you will become
a Soul Saint, a Great Soul Land Master,
and even a Grand Soul Land Master.
Brother, my soul will always stay by your side
to take care of you and protect you.
No!
Xiao Wu’s conscious is gone.
How come?
Because she gave her everything to you.
It is useless crying here.
If you are a real man,
you should revive her.
Do you have any methods to save her?
[Soul Land]
I don’t, but you do.
Sister Wu died for you,
only you could revive her.
She sacrificed her life for you
as well as her soul.
She used the most ultimate way of sacrificing,
which is only harmful to herself.
The rabbit in your arms is
Sister Wu’s original shape.
However, she has lost her soul and
her decade millennium cultivation.
This body is the only thing she has left.
What should I do to save her?
Luckily, that flower
has given her great vitality.
You still have a chance now.
As long as you can do it, she will revive.
Despite the coming hell and high water,
I will definitely do it with all my might.
Sister Wu, you didn’t misjudge him.
He is worthy of your sacrifice.
Big Brother and I had thought about it,
there is only one way to save Sister Wu.
There are three preconditions for it to work.
Firstly, you have to find three kinds of herbs.
What are they?
First, the Sacred Soul Plant
which can arouse her soul.
It must be decade millennium years old or above.
Big Brother and I will find it for you.
The second one is a precious herb
which can help her to reborn
and remold her human form.
The Decade-Millennium
Ginseng King of the Ninth Grade.
Ice Fire Mouth Spring boasts
countless premium herbs.
Yet I have never seen anything like that.
The third one is a treasure that aids
the reunification of the soul and the body,
the neidan of an ancient soul beast.
You should find it yourself.
Ancient soul beast?
Got it.
This...
This is the neidan of
the Ten-Headed Burning Sun Serpent.
I got it when I was in Slaughter City.
Does this one work?
No problem.
Now, we only lack the Decade-Millennium
Ginseng King of Ninth Grade.
Big Brother and I saw one before.
Judging from its current cultivation,
it is most probably in the north.
You may search for it
in those famous forests in the north.
The Ginseng King is equivalent to
a Century Millennium Soul Beast.
I might not be able to fight against it
even if I have found it.
But,
I will find it.
No matter what, I will bring it back.
Remember, you must ensure
it’s still alive when it gets here.
It won’t work
if it loses its vigor.
However,
these are not what you should do now
since you have other preconditions to meet.
Xiao Wu, I know how to bring you back to life.
I will definitely make it.
But before that...
Blue Silver Domain.
The poison left by
the Eight Spider Bone is still lingering.
You have no way to escape!
Human Faced Demon Spider.
Xiao Wu, whoever hurts you,
I will never let off
every single one of them easily.
First Soul Skill, Intertwine.
Spider God Possession.
It is a Human Faced Demon Spider’s special state
when it’s in life-threatening danger.
Under this state,
its attack power will be improved tremendously.
Every second the spider maintains
in this special state,
it drains one year of its cultivation.
First Soul Skill of Flexible Bunny,
Teleport.
Fifth Soul Skill,
Blue Silver Emperor Tyrant Spear.
Second Soul Skill of Flexible Bunny,
Invincible Golden Shield.
Xiao Wu, you have saved me again.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 135 has been completed
and broadcasted for nearly 1326 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2039]
[Total scene: 51541]
[Total CGI: 26140]
[Total plan of action scene: 11104]
[Total scene model: nearly 520]
[Total character model: nearly 971]
[Total props model: 13362]
[Appreciate your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods,
who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never change ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
[Next Episode]
Hence, the death of the two princes
has become a mystery case without clues.
Although my mom is a soul beast,
when she was carrying me,
she had already transformed into a human.
If it weren’t for the Martial Soul Hall,
my entire family
wouldn’t have suffered all these.
I’ve never expected that
Little Freak has gone through so much.
Senior,
this man is suspicious.
Take him down right away.
Even if he was Little Freak,
he wouldn’t be so outstanding.
You...
You are...
[Soul Land]
[Available at 10 AM every Saturday]