♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind,
you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
If you’ve decided
to take on your dad’s responsibilities,
you need to learn more
and be stronger.
You’ll know it soon.
What you need the most
for studying at Moon Pavilion
is to control your behaviour precisely.
From now on,
time for harp class
will gradually increase.
Before the convocation,
I’ll pick one of
the best students among you
to represent the class
to perform at the graduation ceremony.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 120]
Thanks for coming, distinguished guests.
The convocation will commence shortly.
Let’s welcome the graduates.
I wonder what Madam Yue’s background is.
Most of the noblemen
in Tian Dou City are here.
I don’t get any information about her.
Even the royals have to show respect to her
and those princes and princesses
come here to study.
How come the representative
isn’t Princess Xue Ke?
Who is this young man?
[Please Keep Me In Your Heart]
No wonder my sister
praised him in front of me.
His mind is calm and pure.
It’s not easy to do that.
But, he feels familiar...
Is he from the hiding Hao Tian Tribe,
the same as Aunt Yue Hua?
You’re doing great today.
You portrayed great calmness in your entirety.
I’ve already known Father’s intention for me.
I need to train my mind
in both Moon Pavilion and Slaughter City.
Your soul power has reached Level 57.
Your mind wasn’t calm till now.
This is the crucial step to be invincible.
Thank you.
Aunt Yue Hua.
Brother Xue?
Xue...
Few people know my identity.
Although Brother Xue
is the disciple of Uncle Ning,
it’d be better to verify something with Dad first.
Now isn’t the time yet.
Your Highness Crown Prince.
Aunt Yue Hua, that’s too much for me.
Please don’t call me Aunt. Am I that old?
My brother is too outspoken.
You’re not old at all.
You’re like my sister.
This is the Crown Prince
of Tian Dou Empire.
Prince Xue Qing He.
This is my nephew, Tang Yin.
Tang Yin.
Your Highness Crown Prince.
I’ve heard my sister said that
another talented man is studying here
in the Moon Pavilion.
You’re indeed as good as she said.
Tang Yin, may I discuss
about the harp with you
when you’re free?
I want to join too.
I’d like to seek guidance from Tang Yin.
Perhaps I’ll have to let you down.
If possible,
I’ll definitely visit you when I return.
I’ll wait for you then.
Xue Ke really falls for you.
Just now, she came to ask me
what level of noble status
a commoner have to obtain
in order to marry a princess.
Aunt, I won’t consider this at all.
Is there someone in your heart?
It has been five years.
Xiao Wu, how are you?
[Soul Land]
There was a time that
I gave it all for love as well.
But later I found that
it wasn’t worth it at all.
Aunt.
Promise me.
Don’t do anything out of emotions rashly.
Your safety is your priority. Ok?
You may set off tomorrow.
After meeting with your dad,
he’ll bring you back to the tribe
to pay your respect to the ancestors.
I’ll wait for you at the tribe as well.
Aunt, please take care.
You’re back.
Dad...
It’s good that you’re back.
I’ve been waiting for you.
Who has caused you
such severe injuries?
Have you forgotten
what your aunt has taught you for this year?
Sober up. Beside myself,
no one can hurt me to such extent.
One year ago, when I came back here,
I chopped off my right arm and my left leg.
You’ve been curious about my past, right?
Follow me.
Little San, kneel down here.
Ah Yin, I’ve brought our son to visit you.
He’s a lot like you.
He’s more outstanding than me.
Do you see that?
So the royal blood of
the Blue Silver imperial lineage
comes from my mom.
My dad’s lover
was a Century Millennium Soul Beast too.
Why did it never come to my mind?
Could it be? Ah Yin...
Can you really come back to life?
Ah Yin.
Mom...
This feels the same
as when I first saw your mom.
Back then,
I was older than you are now.
With our outstanding talent
and tedious training,
my elder brother and I were entitled as
the Double Star of Hao Tian.
My brother and I
had a great relationship.
Most of my skills were cultivated
under his tutelage.
One year, our dad sent us out for training.
We helped people in need and saved normal people.
Not long after,
we gained our reputation
in the community of soul masters.
Look.
- It’s the Double Star of Hao Tian.
- It’s them. They’re awesome.
It’s really the Double Star of Hao Tian.
One day, a kid was captured by a soul beast.
That soul beast was extremely fierce.
Elder Brother and I
had a hard fight with it.
And finally we saved the kid.
After saving the kid,
we were treated warmly by the villagers.
On the same day, I met Ah Yin.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 120 has been completed
and broadcasted for nearly 1221 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 1809]
[Total scene: 46646]
[Total CGI: 24543]
[Total plan of action scene: 9892]
[Total scene model: nearly 500]
[Total character model: nearly 934]
[Total props model: 13338]
[Appreciating your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul.]
[We’re not alone with you by our side.]
[Next Episode]
Do you know
although it was the first time I met her,
yet she had all my heart.
However, both Elder Brother and I
fell in love with this beautiful woman.
Elder Brother gave up in the end
and returned to be the head of the tribe.
Hao Tian Tribe
went into hiding since then.
The enmity to the Martial Soul Hall
must be revenge.
When I settle all the matters,
you may return to the tribe.
I want you to help rebuild it.
I’ll definitely make it.