♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to my lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
He’s really a little freak.
Confronting with the Grand Soul Land Master,
everyone has to go all out.
Yin, I know you’re worrying about Little San.
So am I.
But, as our son,
there’s something he has to face.
He’s able to dodge briskly?!
Enough.
You’ve broken your promise in the duel.
Since I’ve lost,
I’ll do to what I’ve promised.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 126]
Well, I take back the words I’ve said.
A bet is a bet.
I concede your acknowledgment to our ancestors.
Stop staring at me.
A bet is a bet. Don’t you understand?
Our words do count.
Can I pay respect to my grandpa too?
Well...
No.
Because of your father’s wrongdoing,
you’re not allowed to do so yet.
But you said that
you’d pay for what
your father had done wrong.
Serve the tribe.
Am I right?
Yes. What should I do to be allowed
to pay respect to my grandpa?
You have to do three things for the tribe.
Once you’ve done them all,
you can not only acknowledge the ancestors,
we’ll allow your father
to return to the tribe
and pay respect to the ancestors
together with you.
Pardon?
Leaving the tribe
is the eternal pain of Father’s.
If...
I’ll do it.
The deadline for completing
these three things is ten years.
First, breakthrough Level 80 of soul power.
I can do it.
Second, bring back the head of
a Grand Soul Land Masters from Martial Soul Hall.
Third, obtain a Decade Millennium Soul Ring
for your eighth soul ring period.
Among the learned Grand Soul Land Masters,
only Father and Bibi Dong have obtained
a Decade Millennium Soul Ring.
And Dad inherits his from Mom.
It’s almost a mission impossible.
Don’t you want to regain
the glory of the tribe?
I can promise you now,
if you achieve them all in ten years,
the soul bones returned by your father will be yours,
and you’ll be the next Tribe Chief too.
Only by taking this position,
you can truly lead the tribe
to regain its glory.
I’ll succeed.
For Dad and for Hao Tian Tribe.
Hence, Dad’s entrustment
is finally completed.
It’s time to return to
Tian Dou City to visit my teacher and others.
I wonder how they are doing.
- Ah! The lesson was hard.
- Agree. It’s really hard...
It has been five years.
I’m curious how they are doing?
You’ll find out when you see them.
Are Little San and Xiao Wu doing well?
It’s a pity that
they don’t know about
the promise of regathering in five years.
On this vast continent,
when can we meet again?
Heaven helps the worthy one.
Little San and Xiao Wu will be alright.
What are you doing here?
Is Dean Flander and Grandmaster in?
I’ve no idea whether they’re in,
but the school’s rules state that
outsiders are not allowed to enter.
If you’re trying to pull some strings
to be admitted here,
please go home.
Junior, you’re doing your job well,
But I don’t think
I need further training.
Please report to the Dean that
Dai Mu Bai and Zhu Zhu Qing are back.
If you’re Dai Mu Bai, then I can be Tang San.
Stop pretending.
You’re the 23rd batch of people
trying to enter the college
by pretending as the seniors.
Here you go.
It seems that we indeed
have impressed our school.
You should leave now if you know better.
Otherwise, I won’t let you off easily.
How dare you be so rude to Boss Dai.
You are bold.
Fatty, you’ve grown fatter.
Boss Dai, you’re as violent as usual.
I was going to hug Zhu Qing.
Nice acting.
Much better than the last batches.
Do I have to learn anymore?
Fatty, you’re much cockier
after five years.
Rong Rong has become prettier.
Although Little Ao is from the Food Branch,
if you dare to touch her,
he won’t let you off easily.
Where’s Little Ao, Rong Rong?
Little Ao...
Who made Rong Rong so sad?
Who are you?
I first awakened my Blue Silver’s royal blood,
and then went through the trials
in the Slaughter City and the Moon Pavilion,
My appearance and my aura
have changed greatly.
That’s why they can’t recognise me.
Why do you have Little San’s
Twenty-Four Moonlight Bridges with you?
What have you done to Little San?
Take him down.
Listen to me.
First Soul Skill,
White Tiger Protection Barrier.
Listen to me, Mu Bai.
Shut your mouth.
Fatty.
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
Phoenix Firing Line.
The prop is pretty realistic.
- Pardon? Prop?
- Zhu Qing, Fatty, surround him.
Third Soul Skill,
Flying Phoenix.
Boss Dai, he can fly too.
My turn.
Jiubao Boosts! Second, Speed!
Listen to me, please.
You can’t escape.
[Soul Land]
Welcome back, Little San.
You guys pulled a prank on me.
Fatty, is this prop realistic?
Brother San, my fault.
Little San.
How do you know about our gathering?
I came back to the school once,
but I only managed to meet with our Master.
And our Master told me about it.
By the way, Rong Rong.
What did you say of Little Ao?
Little Ao.
I have no idea whether he’s coming.
Rong Rong.
Little Ao, please come back.
I don’t want you to be strong.
I want you back.
As long as you come back to me,
no matter how strict the tribe rules are,
I’ll never leave you.
It has been five years.
I’ve never heard from Little Ao again.
I can’t imagine what he has been through,
I’m afraid that he’s...
Although Little Ao looks playful,
he has high esteem.
For you,
he has always shown
endless courage and hard work.
Let’s hope that
the ten-year promise
is a good thing for him.
Say no more.
Rong Rong can’t take it anymore.
Rong Rong, stop crying.
You have to trust Little Ao.
Just wait for him.
What can I do besides waiting?
I truly regret it.
Why didn’t I fight firmly back at the time
and let Little Ao endure this alone.
He’s just a soul master from the Food Branch.
He can’t even obtain a soul ring by himself.
Great job, Captain.
It’s my responsibility.
Little Ao, this place is dangerous.
Hurry up. Give it the last strike
and absorb the soul ring.
Thank you, Brother Hulk.
A 20,000-year-old
Mirror Image Beast.
Hopefully, you could give me
the skill I desire.
Who dares to pretend
to be our little freaks
and want to fight?
Let me have a look.
Teacher Zhao.
So, it’s really you the little freaks.
The real Shrek Seven Devils...
Good. Very good. Let’s go inside.
It’s cold.
I can’t understand
why Oscar, a soul master from the Support Branch,
needs to obtain his soul ring
in Icebound Forest.
Couldn’t he just go to a random forest
to kill a Decade Millennium Soul Beast?
Hulk is Level 76
and he’s also the captain.
Both Oscar and he helped us
obtain the soul rings we desired.
We’ve no reason to complain about it now.
What about the captain?
His level is just slightly higher than mine.
He rubs me the wrong way.
It has been five years.
I’ve known Little Ao for five years.
He never gives up his pursuit.
Who can expect that
a soul master from the Support Branch
would like to have...
What?
This...
Soul Bone.
Soul bones are rarely spotted
on the entire continent.
I can’t believe to see it here.
Hulk has always preferred Oscar.
He’ll definitely give
the soul bone to Oscar.
Who can own the soul bone?
A dead man has no say.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 126 has been completed
and broadcasted for nearly 1263 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 1899]
[Total scene: 48698]
[Total CGI: 25157]
[Total plan of action scene: 10234]
[Total scene model: nearly 507]
[Total character model: nearly 961]
[Total props model: 13349]
[Appreciate your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
[Next Episode]
He’s just a soul master from the Food Branch
Little San, when are you going to find Xiao Wu?
I’ll bring her back.
For the responsibility Dad left to me...
This is the promise he gave you.
You have to believe he can do it.
Let’s put this to an end.
Rong Rong.
Who dares to trespass?
They’d better watch out.