♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond, conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Tang Hao?
The Sacred Temple?
how dare you be rude!
The imperious one.
This is the real Hao Tian Form.
How dare you?
What Martial Soul Hall has owed me,
I want you to repay all one day.
Let them leave.
Get off from Martial Soul City now.
Shrek is always your home.
Let’s meet at Shrek again.
Let’s keep the five-year promise
whether rain or shine.
Does it matter whether being a human
or a beast?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 109]
Be a real man,
you have to go forward.
Once you possess the ability to protect her,
then find her.
Little San.
Do you blame me for leaving you for eight years?
I do not.
Why?
Because you’re my father.
My life was given by you.
Children never have the right
to blame their parents.
Is this the feeling of paternal love?
I know you have lots of questions for me.
The voice you heard of
when you were using Tool Soul Form was mine.
Stop, withdraw your strength and soul.
There are many things
you don’t need to know now.
Since you can’t afford to know them.
From now on, I’ll arrange your training.
Once you’ve reached my requirement,
I’ll reveal all you need to know.
Couldn’t I follow Master anymore?
Grandmaster is undoubtedly a great teacher.
But, there’re things he can’t teach.
Dad, are you injured?
Nothing.
It’s just old injuries.
Besides, regarding Xiao Wu.
Are you curious that
as a Century Millennium Soul Beast,
why Xiao Wu is not strong in particular?
Yes.
Since soul beasts are born, they start to practice.
They’re classified into
decade, century, millennium,
decade millennium,
and century millennium.
When soul beasts reach
the level of century millennium,
they’re the same as the Grand Soul Land Master.
But, at this point in time,
they’re facing two choices.
One is to maintain their life as usual.
But they can only live not more than 1,000 years.
After 1,000 years, they’ll die.
While the other choice is more adventurous,
that is changing form.
Changing form?
Yes, changing into a human form.
Because among all living beings,
human is the most potent species.
After turning into a human,
they need to start from scratch.
If they would be able to reach Level 100,
they will be immortal,
as a God.
Don’t soul beasts tend to transform?
In fact, their practice is much harder than us.
The transformation is irreversible.
Also, they need to engage
with humans during their practice.
Otherwise, they can’t improve.
Even though their practice is faster than
common people.
And they don’t need to hunt for soul rings.
Only when they exceed Level 60,
they will enter the mature period
and become human.
When stunned by Titan Giant Ape,
some soul beasts were with me.
So, I killed one of them
since it was suitable for me.
Now I get it.
Currently, Xiao Wu is in the infancy period
of transformation.
I’ve told you what you wanted to know, you...
Dad, was Mom killed by Martial Soul Hall?
You’ll know the truth once you’re stronger
and achieve my set target.
You have no way out against Martial Soul Hall.
Make yourself stronger,
otherwise, you can only live in the dark.
Go and rest.
Tomorrow, I’ll bring you somewhere
to start your training.
[Shrek School]
[Soul Land]
Oscar.
You’re such a young and talented
food branch soul master,
who is precious to Qibao Amber Tribe.
Do not hesitate to raise any need,
we’ll foster you as much as we can.
I should have told Little Ao
about the tribe’s rules clearly.
But he’s working so hard every day, I...
Who is it?
Rong Rong, it’s me.
Rong Rong, it’s late. Why aren’t you resting?
I’ll sleep soon.
Just ended training?
Yeah. I’m lucky that
Uncle Ning values me highly.
He let me join the inner sect.
Only those direct disciples of the tribe
or great soul masters from outside can join.
I can’t lose to them.
You’ve been working hard...
Rong Rong, what’s wrong?
I just finished the training.
I’ve made you some desserts.
Have a taste.
I’ll make more if you like it.
Rest early. I’m leaving now.
Little Ao!
Why are you so good to me?
Rong Rong, you’re my loved one.
Of course, I’m treating you well, why shouldn’t I?
Rong Rong, don’t cry.
What’s wrong?
Tell me. As long as I can help, I’ll definitely do it.
Do you know we can’t be together?
What did you say?
Little Ao, let’s end here.
Why?
Rong Rong, do you know?
Back then, I just wanted a safe and happy life.
I cared for nothing
until I met you.
The first time I met you,
I couldn’t help liking you.
But, your arrogance and dominance
kept reminding me that
you’re a precious lady.
I’m only a common soul master.
However, you’ve changed gradually.
You’re gentle and lovely now.
It got into my heart deeply.
That day I realized you like me,
do you know how I feel?
I’ll never trade this feeling
even with a hundred pieces of soul bones.
In order to be with you,
I’ve staked my life to practice
regardless of sufferings or loneliness.
Your smile is worth everything to me.
I realized I’ve fallen for you.
Whenever you were in danger,
I felt blessed
to protect you.
Stop. Little Ao, I...
Even if you say nothing, I knew it.
We can’t be together.
You’ll become the chief of
Qibao Amber Tribe in the future.
No matter how hard I strive,
I’ll never stand shoulder to shoulder with you.
I’m too foolish.
Little Ao.
Wow, how beautiful!
Surrounded by mountains and woods,
filled with animals.
Has your attached soul bone recovered?
It has, after this half-month journey.
In these two years,
here’s the place, you’ll be living and training.
Two years?
Are you aware of what’s your biggest flaw?
It’s lacking power boosting.
My martial soul is mainly on control,
but lack of power.
It’s quite problematic
when encountering rival like Xie Yue.
Right. You have good controlling power.
Even if it’s flawed,
it’s the problem of Blue Silver Plant.
Don’t worry.
It’ll be enhanced
when you get the fifth soul ring.
Ah.
You’ll know afterwards.
The training starts now.
Firstly, absorb the soul bone
you got from Martial Soul Hall.
This soul bone
must be prepared for the outstanding lady
among the three soul masters.
You mean Hu Liena?
Isn’t Xie Yue the leader of Golden Generation?
No. Hu Liena is the leader of Genie Mesmerize.
Bibi Dong fosters her as the next pope.
I know it now.
Luckily, my Purple Demon Eye is
able to resist Genie Mesmerize.
Otherwise...
Start. Fuse with it.
Feel it wholeheartedly.
Such a wonderful sense of transparency.
Worthy of being Spiritual Cohesion Wisdom Skull.
My spirit power is well coherent.
I can feel everything outside clearly
even with my eyes closed.
[Next Episode]
Training starts now.
You can see the summit which is 200 meters high?
Little San’s spirit power
has reached nearly to the level of
the Great Soul Land Master.
- Little Ao!
- I know I don’t deserve you.
Are you leaving?
Why should I stay here?
But you’ve sealed my soul power.
How can I practice then?
You’ll know if you try.