♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Please allow me
to acknowledge my ancestors.
Absurd.
Never even think of returning to the tribe
after what your father has done.
It’s Father’s fault to involve the tribe.
And I’ve apologised for that.
But, you’ve humiliated my mom.
I must get the justice back.
You despise the tribe,
we won’t let you off easily.
I wonder if I could challenge
Seventh Elder now?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 125]
That year, Tang Hao left the tribe
and brought away the two soul bones
given to him by the tribe.
Now, he ordered Tang San
to acknowledge the ancestors
and bring back the two soul bones.
I reckon this can prove his remorse.
Removing soul bones from a living man?
After all, he’s the son
of the last Tribe Chief.
It seems that
he hasn’t forgotten about the tribe.
These soul bones are the most precious
treasures of the tribe.
I hereby hand them over to you for safekeeping.
When the next Tribe Chief is confirmed
or whoever makes outstanding contribution
to the tribe,
these two soul bones
will be awarded to that person.
The same cliff,
the same oppression by
the Tribe Elder last-named Tang.
I’ve never expected that in my second life,
I still can’t escape from the same fate.
But in this life,
I’ll take control of my own destiny.
Seventh Elder,
whoever leaves between the mountains loses.
Agree?
I rank the seventh.
My title is Lie Yang.
The Grand Soul Land Master?
There are only
two Grand Soul Land Master Hao Tian Tribe, no?
We’ve been practicing
for the past 20 years.
Naturally, we have made breakthroughs.
Why? Are you scared?
No. It’s my pleasure to challenge you,
Grand Soul Land Master Lie Yang.
Tang San, Soul King Level 59
from the Controlling Branch.
You know he has an attached soul bone, don’t you?
This is one of
the three soul bones he has.
Three pieces?
He’s indeed a little freak.
After a decade, a new prodigy emerges.
Watch out.
Death God Domain.
Confronting with
a Grand Soul Land Master,
everyone has to go all out.
Third Soul Skill,
Clear Burning Sun.
I can clearly feel that the power of
Hao Tian Hammer is soaring.
I can’t fight recklessly right now.
It’s hard to resist
the continuous attacks from
the Grand Soul Land Master.
I must break this deadlock.
Ghostly Trace.
Ah Yin, I know you’re worrying about Little San.
So am I.
But, as our son,
there’s something he must face.
First Soul Skill, Intertwine.
Third Soul Skill,
Constraint of Spider Web.
Blue Silver Domain.
The spiderweb not only can not restrain me,
it’ll be hindered by the iron chain bridge as well.
Nice trick.
Combination of soul skills and
the manipulation of hidden weapons.
My body has become heavy.
Is it because of the gravity control?
Sixth Soul Skill,
Martial Soul Clone.
Now any skill that Seventh Elder
performs through the Hao Tian Hammer
can double the power.
Fifth Soul Skill,
Gravity Control.
This is bad.
Second Soul Skill,
Hammer Soul Control.
That’s fast.
Blue Silver Domain.
Death God Domain.
Not merely soul skills but also
the gap of actual combat experience.
Tang San can’t resist it.
He’s a good opponent worth fighting with.
Ghostly Trace.
Good.
Even Seventh Brother can’t target him.
This way, his attacks are all in vain
however powerful they are.
Oppressed to such extent by my Hao Tian Hammer,
he’s still able to dodge briskly
without a trace of fatigue.
After opening up the Eight Meridians,
my body recovers faster than it used to.
Seventh Brother has used more than 40% of his soul power,
is he eager to win?
After all, Tang San has surprised us a lot.
The seventh soul skill is
much more powerful.
This means that Little San has to deal with
two Tool Soul Form.
In this situation,
he can’t stand the attack from Seventh Elder.
Seventh Elder is not only superior
in terms of soul skills,
his soul power is even stronger.
The exertion of his power is continuous.
Consumption is not his concern,
but mine.
[Soul Land]
Seventh Elder.
Is that brat going to surrender?
Well, then. I will tell them I used more soul power than I actually did.
This way, I get to display my strength
as well as accomplish
Second Elder’s order to end this in a tie.
Purple God Light.
No.
Seventh Soul Skill,
Tool Soul Form.
It’s a spontaneous defense
invoked by accident.
Seventh Elder has exerted
all of his soul power.
It’s over, little freak.
Fifth Soul Skill,
Blue Silver Emperor Tyrant Spear.
Fifth Soul Skill, Impregnable Defense.
Lame trick.
Blue Silver Domain.
I’m frozen under this power...
Little San...
Uncle, I’m alright. No worries.
Brother Hao,
you’ve raised him into a little freak.
Are you alright, Little San?
The Tool Soul Form was weakened by
the Blue Silver Emperor Tyrant Spear.
And most of the impact was endured by
the Eight Spider Bone.
I’m only slightly injured.
Seventh Uncle lost out big this time.
Second Uncle, please restrain him later.
Stop his impulsiveness.
Where’s that brat?
Has he been broken by me?
How did he get up here?
Did you save him, Tribe Chief?
He got up by himself.
That’s out of the question.
Under the full attack of Tool Soul Form,
he must have been injured severely.
Face it.
We’ve witnessed it.
If I’m not wrong,
he has the ability of flying.
- He didn’t use it in the duel.
- But...
Enough. You broke your promise in the duel.
You’ve lost.
What’s going on?
My soul skill has been forcibly cut off.
It’s due to the domain resulted from the
scattering of Blue Silver Tyrant Spear.
No way.
I must get off from this deadlock.
A bet is a bet. Since I’ve lost,
I’ll do as I promised him.
Dismiss, everyone.
Return to your practice.
Yes.
Yue Hua,
you can prepare for the ceremony now.
Thank you for your approval, Tribe Elders.
It’s not that we approve it,
but Tang San himself earned it.
I have never seen
such an outstanding young man.
I hope he won’t go off track in the future.
Don’t make his father’s mistake.
Tribe Elders, Hao Tian Tribe
has gone into hiding for years.
Is it time to lift the ban?
Tribe Chief, do you mean...
It has been 20 years.
It’s time for Hao Tian Hammer
to reemerge in the soul masters’ world.
You have repeatedly request me
to lift the ban, no?
I think now it’s time.
I don’t agree.
I reckon,
we should continue
to stay low for a while.
Because of Little San?
Yes. Hao Tian Tribe needs a leader
who can lead the tribe to forge ahead.
We’ve grown old and so have you.
But it’s a different case for him.
He’s so talented.
We must not neglect him
due to the reemergence of the tribe.
He needs training and guidance.
The tribe should stay put
to provide him with better training.
Second Uncle, have you forgiven
Brother Hao?
No, don’t you remember
the three requests I mentioned before?
If he can accomplish all of them,
it means that he’s qualified
to be your successor.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 125 has been completed
and broadcasted for nearly 1256 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 1884]
[Total scene: 48355]
[Total CGI: 25113]
[Total plan of action scene: 10180]
[Total scene model: nearly 506]
[Total character model: nearly 957]
[Total props model: 13349]
[Appreciate your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
[Next Episode]
It has been five years.
I wonder how they are doing.
You should leave here if you know better.
Otherwise, I won’t let you off easily.
Who dares to pretend
to be our little freaks?
With my capability, do I have to
learn anymore?
After five years, you’re much cockier.
It seems that we really
impressed our school.
Who are you?
What have you done to Little San?
Take him down.
You have no way to escape.