♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to the lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Today’s exhibition match
isn’t for you to enjoy,
but to let you know
the strength
of these graduates from Shrek School.
By the way, Er Long.
Have you collected ticket fees
from our students?
As the grand dean,
how could I expose my skills easily?
You’ve really set me up.
You’ll be the main force on the ground,
I’ll distract them in the air.
No matter how great
the five little freaks are,
they’re still under my control.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 129]
Begin.
Fifth Soul Skill, Gravity Squeeze.
Restricting all of them?
Next, I’ll attack them one by one.
From now on, Dai Mu Bai is
the crown prince of Xing Luo Empire
and Zhu Zhu Qing is the crown princess.
If I had become stronger earlier,
Second Brother wouldn’t have died.
Mu Bai, it’s written in the stars.
Don’t blame yourself.
It isn’t, Zhu Qing.
I’ll defeat this damn destiny.
I want to be stronger,
strong enough to protect you
and more people.
I’ll stay by your side.
Go!
Fourth Soul Skill,
White Tiger Meteor Strike.
The pressure is gone.
Jiubao Boosts! Third, Soul!
Blue Silver Cage.
Second Soul Skill, Supreme Palm.
How is that possible?
It’s the domain.
The tables have turned.
It’s not that simple.
Oh, no.
Sixth Soul Skill, Owl Protection.
Purple God Light.
Now, Fatty!
Fifth Soul Skill,
Phoenix Meteor Strike.
It’s too late.
Dean, a letter from Hong Jun.
Teacher, I’ve obtained
the fifth soul ring.
But I won’t tell you what the skill is.
Have a guess.
I want to give you a surprise
when I come back.
Little brat, trying to prank me?
Anyway, he doesn’t disappoint me.
Hong Jun is gifted.
As long as he is
diligent and practices hard,
he’ll definitely make great achievements
in the future.
That’s right.
Look at who his teacher is.
Good lad.
Teacher, please don’t blame me.
The Fire Phoenix has reborn.
Attack Teacher Zhao with full strength.
Jiubao Boosts!
Fifth, Attack! Sixth, Amplify!
What amplification did Rong Rong
provide Mu Bai and Zhu Qing with?
Rong Rong’s fifth soul skill
amplifies the attack power.
What amplification did Rong Rong
provide Mu Bai and Zhu Qing with?
Rong Rong’s fifth soul skill
amplifies the attack power.
While the sixth amplifies attributes.
Sixth Soul Skill,
White Tiger Annihilation.
Shield of Acala.
An instant breakthrough?
Attribute Amplification? What’s that?
Attribute Amplification is
the kind of support to enhance
the strongest attribute of the receivers.
This means their current soul power,
agility and the power to attack
are all boosted by 70%.
Nether Slash.
Oh gosh, these brats
are truly fighting hard.
There are two incense sticks left.
Boss Fu, good luck.
No way!
You can fly, Little San?
Nothing is impossible in this world.
Look, Dean.
We all have used so much soul power.
It won’t be good for our relationship
if we continue to fight.
Let’s settle for a draw. What do you think?
You can turn Teacher Zhao
into a roasted bear,
you’ve truly improved a lot.
Well, let’s end it here.
Dean Frander, please stop.
We concede.
Since you have defeated Teacher Zhao,
your strength is pretty good.
That’s it for today’s exhibition match.
Shrek!
- They’re so handsome!
- Shrek!
You’re so handsome!
Not you, Fatty. Stay away.
Shrek!
These little brats
have improved a lot.
You’re right. They’re relentless.
Look at my wounds. Look here.
But doesn’t this also mean that
we taught them well?
[Soul Land]
Your Holiness, everything is ready.
Start when the sky turns black.
Failure is not an option.
Yes.
This day has finally come.
I wonder how Rong Rong is doing?
Uncle Bone, Rong Rong has grown up.
She’ll take good care of herself.
Don’t worry.
Catch it.
These kids are
truly the golden generation
of the soul master community.
Little freaks,
what’s your plan later?
Teacher.
I’ve been wandering around
for the past few years.
If you’re willing to take me in,
I’ll stay here then.
[Information of Participants]
If you want me to teach something,
I can do that.
You still have some conscience.
Stay here then.
Not an issue for us.
This fellow obviously has
his intention to stay.
Dean, be careful.
Really?
Don’t listen to Boss Dai, Teacher.
I’m staying to keep you company.
Others might not know you, but not me.
After we all leave,
Fatty will be
the only one of the Shrek Seven Devils here.
He’ll become the focus
of the whole school.
By that time, it’ll be easy for him
to hook up with some pretty girls.
Am I right, Fatty?
Nonsense, I’m a decent man.
Zhu Qing and I will stay
for a few more days
before going back to Xing Luo Empire.
I’m going back to the tribe.
It’s so late at night.
yet some disciples are still practicing.
They’ve been working so hard
under Rong Rong’s lead.
It seems that our tribe is thriving.
Recently, Tribe Chief
has been strict in patrolling.
It’s tiring.
I feel something is behind us.
Nothing.
I’ll take a look.
What about you, Little San?
Firstly, I’ll go find Xiao Wu.
Then get the sixth soul ring.
As for the rest,
I’ll think of it when I find Xiao Wu.
If you have nowhere to go,
come back then.
This school always welcome you all
with open arms.
Even Martial Soul Hall would have to
think it over if they want to harm us.
After all,
they don’t dare to turn against the two empires.
Little San, when are you leaving?
Tomorrow, early in the morning, Master.
I’m worried about Xiao Wu.
We’ve been parted for five years,
I wonder how she’s doing.
Hopefully, every one of the Shrek Seven Devils
could get together next time.
Little San, although your current soul power
is lower than mine,
your strength is still better than mine.
Hope that you’ll surpass Little Ao and me
in the next gathering.
You’d better work hard.
My current strength is
beyond what you’ve seen today.
I really look forward to seeing you all
become Grand Soul Land Masters.
What’s wrong, Rong Rong?
I don’t know why my head
suddenly hurt.
I’m alright.
Report to Tribe Chief. Hurry up.
Yes.
Stupid. Always drop the ball.
Change of plan. Attack.
Yes.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 129 has been completed
and broadcasted for nearly 1284 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 1944]
[Total scene: 49513]
[Total CGI: 25493]
[Total plan of action scene: 10586]
[Total scene model: nearly 513]
[Total character model: nearly 962]
[Total props model: 13355]
[Appreciate your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
[Next Episode]
Enemy attacks! Guard the fort.
Kill them all.
Follow me, hurry up.
Destruction is really exciting.
What brings you here
at this time, Chief Ning?
What’s wrong with Grandpa Sword?
Martial Soul Hall...
I won’t let you off easily.
Where’s the Blue Lightning
Tyrant Dragon Tribe?
Could their next target be...