♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your solitary braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
No mercy for those who resist.
Brother.
Today, Shrek stays together in life and death.
Xiao Wu, run.
- Mom.
- Run.
My sixth soul skill defeats all physical defence.
- Mom, let me protect you this time.
- Run.
You’re as stupid as your mom.
Cocky.
Martial Soul Hall.
I’m back.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 108]
Dad.
Lord Hao Tian?
Worthy of being The Grand Hao Tian Master.
Tang Hao, how dare you be rude
before The Sacred Temple.
The Sacred Temple? The imperious one.
Look carefully, this is the real Hao Tian Form.
How dare you, Tang Hao.
Martial Soul Form.
I’ll fight you till the end.
The power Hao Tian Hammer is overwhelming.
What Martial Soul Hall has owed me,
I want you to repay all one day.
Grandmaster, Frander.
No words can express my appreciation
to thank you for tutoring my son.
I’ll never forget.
He took away Little San and Xiao Wu.
Tang Hao only suffered slight injury
from the attack of Martial Soul Hall.
He crushed the crucial statue of Martial Soul Hall.
The Pope is not his target,
but The Sacred Temple,
which is a symbol of Martial Soul Hall.
Qibao Form.
He took away the Century Millennium Soul Beast.
Your Holiness...
No need to chase Tang Hao. He’s too robust.
I’ve been practising these years
and finally reaching the level of
the Grand Soul Land Master.
But, when we are confronting with Tang Hao,
he’s just too oppressive.
This bastard is too rampant.
Your Holiness, it concerns
the dignity of Martial Soul Hall.
If we can tackle Tang Hao easily,
how could he live until now?
It’s not the time yet.
How about them?
Let them leave Martial Soul Hall now.
Let’s go.
Tang Hao, we’ll settle our hatred one day.
Little San’s dad is awesome.
I’ve decided to make him my role model.
If it wasn’t Tang Hao’s presence,
perhaps none of us could have left.
Chief Ning, you may bring back Rong Rong.
Kids have graduated since the competition ended.
You’ve seen it yourself,
we’ve offended Martial Soul Hall.
We expect to face a harder time in future.
It’s time to go back since she’s graduated.
Dean Frander.
Qibao Amber Tribe is always your friend.
Chief Ning.
May I join Qibao Amber Tribe?
Of course. We greatly welcome you.
I was going to tell Oscar about
the tribe’s rules after the competition.
Each of you is very welcome
to join Qibao Amber Tribe.
Thank you, Chief Ning.
Zhu Qing and I are from Xing Luo Empire.
We want to return home
since we’ve been away for years.
How about you?
Count me out as well.
I like freedom like Brother San.
I plan to hang around on the continent.
Afterwards, I’ll go back to school to help out.
I’ve never expected you brat...
Worthy being my disciple.
All of you are great.
You’ll be successful wherever you go.
Qibao Amber Tribe always
welcomes you with open arms.
Please don’t be sad to say farewell.
It’s hard for me to say goodbye.
In those days we were practising,
I always thought it was too long and tedious.
In fact, it’s the greatest moment to be with you all.
Same here. I can’t believe we’re parting now.
Little Freaks.
Although you have your own life and future,
Shrek is always your home.
Dean.
Sadly, Little San and Xiao Wu aren’t here.
I’m curious about how they are now.
They’re safe
to stay with The Grand Hao Tian Master.
[Soul Land]
Good girl.
Mom.
Brother!
This is Brother San’s father?
You’re awake?
Thank you.
That’s fine. As a soul master,
I should lock you up
and kill you
when Tang San needs you.
Give him your soul ring and soul bone.
But, as a father,
I would make another choice.
Is it because of my relationship with Little San?
Girl, do you know
Tang San’s mother is the same as you.
She’s a Century Millennium Soul Beast too.
You should go now.
Little San will get into trouble if you stay with him.
Do you oppose us being together?
No. Why would I?
Didn’t I make the same choice back then?
But, when his mother and I were together,
my soul power has transcended Level 70.
Both of your levels are too low.
At least, his father isn’t opposing.
Go, return to the place you should be.
That’s the safest place for you.
Back then, I thought I was strong enough.
But our ending was still a tragedy.
I don’t wish to see
the same tragedy happens to my child.
I wonder
when we will see them after this farewell.
How about we make a five-year promise?
Let’s meet at Shrek
after five years, okay?
Good idea.
Great. Let’s keep this promise whether rain or shine.
Take good care of yourselves.
Don’t forget to practice even after you graduated.
Well, it’s time to say goodbye.
Let’s leave Martial Soul City now.
Dean Frander, we’ll take our leave first.
Take care, Fatty.
Can I leave after he wakes up?
Will he let you go by then?
Go. Here isn’t far from Star Dou Forest.
You’re the first man who combs my hair
and the only one.
Forever.
Does it matter being a human or a beast?
Instead, a beast’s feeling is more sincere.
Dad.
I finally meet him.
Sit down.
Don’t look around. She’s gone.
Gone? Why?
Because she has to.
Let me ask you a question.
Are you able to protect her
with your current strength?
I...
[Next Episode]
Changing form?
Forming into human
is a tough journey.
Death is unavoidable.
Dealing with Martial Soul Hall,
there’s no way to escape.
You can only live in the dark forever.
What’s going on?
We can’t be together.
Little Ao.
Something behind the waterfall
is responding to my spirit power.