♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
The Martial Soul Main Hall and its people
were destroyed overnight.
Nothing like this has ever happened
in the Douluo Continent.
This is called carrying out justice for god.
The Seven Clans Re-selection Contest
is around the corner.
We must accelerate
the development of Tang Clan.
Clan Chief.
Take a look
at what we’ve done while you were gone.
You finished all these constructions
in such a short time.
I have a suggestion.
I’d like to change the four tribes
into four halls.
Each elder will be a leader of one hall.
Send my orders.
We will execute the plan earlier.
[Episode 152]
Is that all you can do?
Sorry, my lord.
He’s so handsome.
Boss Fu.
You’re being irresponsible again?
There are so few students this year,
and you’re not going to do anything?
It’s not that I don’t want to.
The Martial Soul Hall
recently reorganized multiple
Advanced Soul Master Schools.
Many young soul masters have joined them.
If it wasn’t for our existing popularity,
the situation would be even worse.
After soul masters finish studying,
they still need to find a career.
-Teacher!
-they still need to find a career.
Hong Jun.
Little San.
You came back just in time.
We are talking about soul masters.
How is Tang Clan going?
Everything is ready.
The clan is ready to start operating.
Next,
after we produce a number of
our hidden weapons,
the clan
will be officially established.
If you need any help from the school,
just say so.
The graduation exam is in half a month.
At that time, I will pick some talented students
with good nature and refer them to you
to join Tang Clan.
I hope your Tang Clan
will be a new option for soul masters in the future.
The teachers
have been doing preparations to help us.
Teacher.
Thank you.
Oh right, Dean.
While we were gone,
did anything happen
at Shrek School?
How is the School of Four Elements?
Don’t worry.
Everything is well with Shrek School.
The School of Four Elements
has also joined our school as well.
If we’re talking about power,
Shrek School
is definitely the top
over the continent.
What?
The School of Four Elements
joined Shrek School?
is nothing to be afraid of.
I mean,
are we afraid that they will harm our interest
in Tian Dou City?
But it’s also because
they’re dealing with a profiteer like you.
Will an evil businessman be disadvantaged
when negotiating conditions with them?
The School of Four Elements
was scared by Grand Bone Master
and Grand Venom Master.
[Unfair Treaty]
They definitely wouldn’t disagree
with two Grand Soul Land Masters.
Senior Dugu Bo was here?
He came for you.
It seemed urgent.
He probably ran into some trouble
and left without staying for long.
What would make that Old Freak be in such a rush?
Could it be...
Not too long ago,
Prince Xue Xing asked me to diagnose
and treat Emperor Xue Ye.
I found
that Emperor Xue Ye was poisoned
with a mixed poison.
The cause
was a type of spice in his food.
In the palace,
only Xue Qing He uses that spice.
The Ning family’s little girl
said that Little Freak is back!
Frander.
Is he here?
Little Freak.
Emperor Xue Ye is about to die.
What?
Old Freak.
Didn’t you tell me last time
that Emperor Xue Ye’s poison
was under control?
I did have it under control then.
But who would’ve thought
that he would become
suddenly poisoned again,
and the situation is even worse this time.
What antidote did you use?
I used Jade Phosphor Serpent King Venom,
attacking his poison with more poison
to neutralize the mixed poison.
I then used medicine to nurse his health.
But every time I neutralized it,
there would be new poison not long after.
I’ve calculated it carefully.
After neutralizing seven times,
he will die once he is poisoned again.
How many times have you neutralized it already?
Six.
The time between each relapse
is also getting shorter.
If Emperor Xue Ye
is not poisoned with a simple mixed poison,
but a more complicated one,
then we’ll be in big trouble.
Hurry and come with me to the palace.
If you can’t even do anything,
then Tian Dou Empire is really doomed!
Wait.
We need to find someone first
and take him along.
What?
You know someone else that’s good at using poison?
Let’s go.
I’ll tell you on the way.
Teacher.
Dean.
We’ll leave first.
Fatty.
You stay here
and wait for Rong Rong and Little Ao.
If things really change in Tian Dou Empire,
then our plan
also has to be changed.
All of the symptoms you described
are signs of multiple mixed poisons.
If we can’t find the root of the cause,
we won’t be able to find a cure.
It seems like this person’s knowledge of poison
is no less than mine.
Can you make an antidote?
As long as we can find the root of the poison,
I am fairly confident.
That’s great.
[Soul Land]
Out of the way.
We have urgent matters to report to His Majesty.
His Majesty is resting.
The Crown Prince has ordered
that no one is allowed to enter.
Anyone who disobeys
will be killed.
Do you not see the gold medal in my hand?
This is the Crown Prince’s gold medal.
How is this possible?
The situation has changed.
The Crown Prince has changed his mind.
Hurry and let us in.
Have you seen those royal guards before?
No.
Teacher didn’t tell me
about the royal soul masters being redeployed.
The entire palace
must be locked down by Xue Qing He.
Old Freak is so frightened.
These two people must have a higher level
of soul power than him.
It turns out Tang Yin is Tang San.
I made a mistake
when we were in the Moon Pavilion.
Brother Tang San.
Why didn’t let them tell me you were here?
I could’ve welcomed you.
Xue Ke keeps talking about you.
Greetings, Crown Prince.
Crown Prince.
Greetings.
Thank you for your kindness,
Crown Prince.
I was invited
by Senior Dugu Bo
to treat His Majesty.
Will you let us in first
to treat His Majesty?
No need to worry about my father, brother.
It’s not easy for you to come to the palace.
Let me treat you to a meal
and we can have a chat.
It seems like
all the guards here
are from the Martial Soul Hall.
Right, Crown Prince?
Tang San.
What nonsense is that?
This is the Tian Dou Empire Palace.
Why would people
from the Martial Soul Hall be here?
Crown Prince.
You still slipped up.
The two people next to you
must be Grand Soul Land Masters, right?
Why aren’t they with Emperor Xue Ye, protecting him,
but with you instead?
Besides, there are only a limited number
of Grand Masters in the entire continent.
Besides the Martial Soul Hall,
who has this kind of power?
Second,
did you really replace all the royal guards
with soul masters
just to protect His Majesty?
If so, why didn’t you tell the Chief of Soul Masters,
who is also my teacher?
Third,
you knew my real identity as soon as you saw me.
But you didn’t question
the medal I had at all.
I’m positive that you are close
with the Martial Soul Hall.
You learned from them that Tang Yin is Tang San.
Crown Prince.
I think
my thought is mostly correct.
No wonder you’re the core of the Shrek Seven Devils.
You could guess all that
from just a few clues.
But how can you prove you right?
That’s easy.
As long as you let us see His Majesty,
everything will prove itself.
But
you won’t let us
ruin your plan, will you?
Very good.
You guessed correctly.
I did borrow power
from the Martial Soul Hall this time.
But the palace is under internal
and external threats
and I have no other choice.
Tang San.
Stay in the palace and help me.
Gold,
beautiful women,
nobility,
even soul rings,
and soul bones, I can give you everything.
I need you to help me build Tian Dou Empire.
Xue Qing He.
Do you think that I would follow
a traitor who kills his own father and ruler?
Tang San.
You’re so smart.
But don’t you understand?
You have revealed all my plans.
I definitely won’t let you go.
Why bother?
People like you
naturally won’t understand
what I’m doing.
When a person’s moral and conscience
both perish,
then
that person is no longer a human.
Instead, they’re a beast like you!
Attack.
Little San is in trouble.
Shrek School is going to rebel.
Kill them all!
Surround the side hall.
Capture everyone of the Qibao Amber Tribe!
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 152 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1445 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2296]
[Total scene: 56607]
[Total CGI: 27178]
[Total plan of action scene: 12052]
[Total scene model: nearly 552]
[Total character model: nearly 995]
[Total props model: 13375]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
Tang San.
Even if you fire off the signal flare,
no one will come to rescue you.
As long as you surrender,
I can accept this condition.
I’m going to give you one last chance.
Are you going to surrender
or to be destroyed?
Dugu Bo!
Hurry and become my nourishment!
But I need to live.
As long as you seek revenge for me
and destroy the Martial Soul Hall,
submitting myself to you
is not a problem.
Great.