♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond, conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Training starts now.
Couldn’t I follow Master any more?
Of course not.
Even if you say nothing,
I know
we can’t be together.
Be a real man.
You have to go forward.
Once you possess the ability to protect her,
go and find her.
Start now.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 110]
Besides the soul bone is rare to obtain,
the main reason why a soul bone
is more precious than soul ring
is due to the infinity of one’s
soul power to absorb it.
Even if the soul master is only at Level 1,
he or she is able to absorb
a Century Millennium Soul Bone.
There’s spirit power emitting from Little San’s body.
Nothing can escape from
the power of spirit within 100 metres.
Child.
Focus on your spirit power,
don’t release it or you’ll lose control.
Fortunately.
Something behind the waterfall
is responding to my spirit power.
My eyes are hurt.
Little San.
Everything has changed.
Both Purple Demon Eye and
Spiritual Cohesion Wisdom Skull,
these two strong elements meet
and complement each other.
How’s it?
Snow on the summit is spectacular.
Purple Demon Eye is only one step away from
the final stage, Boundless.
You can see the summit 200 meters high?
Little San, can you tell me what’s the glow
in your eyes?
Scan everything on earth and
eradicate all injustice.
Purple God Light.
We can start training now.
Judging from the emission,
Purple God Light is a piercing attack.
It is centralised and extremely destructive.
My spirit power is substantially
consumed when attacking,
but my soul power does not.
As expected, spirit power’s consumption
is slower when no attack is launched.
It seems like this skill is
mainly driven by spirit power.
The more the emission of spirit power,
the stronger the attack force.
These light particles are my spirit power.
It has improved at least 100 times than before.
Eight Spider Bone empowers my combat capability,
while Wisdom Skull enhances
spirit power by leaps and bound.
Little San’s spirit power
has nearly reached the level
of Great Soul Land Master.
Little Ao.
Are you leaving?
I know I don’t deserve you.
Why should I stay here?
No. I love you.
What did you say?
Initially, I didn’t care about you.
But, I realised
you’ve devoted all for me.
Everything you’ve done
has engraved deeply in my heart.
I should’ve told you the truth earlier.
But I had no courage to say it out.
I don’t want to hurt you or leave you.
Perhaps this is love.
Tell me, why we can’t be together?
Because of the tribe’s rules.
Every tribe’s disciple is
a soul master from Support Branch.
We can’t escape from
the truth of being lack of attack.
As a result, the tribe stipulates that
a disciple’s spouse
must be from Attack Branch.
I’m the only daughter of my dad
and as the future chief.
Hence, I have no right to change this rule.
We can’t be together
because I’m not from Attack Branch.
Sorry, Little Ao. I’m truly sorry.
[Soul Land]
I’ve sealed your soul power temporarily
for training.
There’s a boulder under the waterfall.
Stand on it to practice the hammering I taught you.
Skill of Random Hammering.
When you’re able to accomplish 81 hammerings
flawless and completely.
The first training session will be over.
It has been four days,
I still can’t stand on the boulder,
not to mention the hammering practice.
The current of the waterfall is forceful.
If without the forging hammer, I’m afraid...
The rock has been pounded all year round.
Those smooth areas are eroded by water.
I’d be able to stand firmly on the rock
if I avoid those areas.
Ghostly Trace.
With the feature of Ghostly Trace,
the impact of currents is resisted.
Since you’ve stood still on the rock,
begin to practice your soul power then.
How can I practice
since you’ve sealed my soul power?
You’ll know when you try it.
I see.
Even if I can’t use Xuan Tian Strike,
it doesn’t affect the practice.
Ever since the farewell of the finals,
I was thinking,
when my partners were
oppressed by Martial Soul Hall,
I just stared helplessly
and under other’s protection?
Now, I finally have a clear goal.
Qibao Amber Tribe hopes their disciples
can be sheltered under protection.
I know I’m a soul master
from Food Branch.
I don’t have the ability to do so.
But it doesn’t mean it’ll be impossible for me.
Rong Rong, will you wait for me?
Ten years. Wait for me for ten years.
If I don’t come back after ten years,
you may marry others.
I’ll definitely come back to you when I succeed.
It’s your greatest period after ten years.
I’ll definitely succeed if I didn’t die.
Silly girl.
You’ll be together when he comes back.
Perhaps Oscar is not as intelligent as Tang San.
However, his insistence can never be doubted.
He’ll surprise us shortly.
and the soul masters’ world as well.
Just let him venture.
I’ve done. The 81st hammering.
It took me half a year to accomplish
all 81 hammerings.
Little San only spent three months...
You’ve done great.
But, you should do better.
Next, use this to train.
If the handle breaks, make one yourself.
What’s going on?
Though wooden hammer is light,
it received greater resistance in water
than forging hammer.
I should adjust my centre of gravity.
As expected. Skill of Random Hammering.
Comparing with forging hammer,
wooden hammer is influenced by
both buoyancy and water impulse.
So, it needs to be more precise
on the strength than forging hammer.
Batwing Rebound.
[Next Episode]
I set the goal for you for four years.
Our plan will be hindered
if we can’t settle Tang Hao.
Evil aura is materialised.
Tang San.
The humiliation you caused to me,
I want you to repay with your life.
Purple God Light.
I hope you’ll come back alive.