♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
I want to team up with you.
If one’s able
to pass through Hell Road,
he’ll be recognised by one special domain.
Death God Domain?
Is this the reason why
father asked me to come here for?
Eat it if you trust me.
I do. Please trust me too.
I hereby specially bestowed upon you
the title of Death God.
Looks like he doesn’t want us to obtain
the Death God Domain.
Please open the entrance of Hell Road.
I’ll pass through Hell Road
with Emissary of Hell.
Wish you good luck.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 116]
The heinous spirit is invigorating.
This is Hell Road?
I wonder what’s down there?
It’s Netherland Shot.
No. I’d rather say
it’s Netherland stockpile
due to its massive volume.
I think it’s the cemetery of losers
in Slaughter City over the years.
Perhaps Hell Road
is the core of Slaughter City.
Or
it’s the energy source of Slaughter City.
If this place collapsed,
it’ll bring disastrous catastrophe
to the whole Slaughter City.
Speaking of which,
Slaughter City should
have collapsed earlier.
However, Martial Soul Hall
acquiesces with Slaughter City’s evil,
Is sheltering those degenerates
your real intention?
I knew Hao Tian Tribe has
prejudice against Martial Soul Hall.
But I’ve no rights
to decide on those matters.
It’s better to settle the obstacle
we’re facing now.
Go up. Netherland is poisonous.
Possibly rare beasts exist down there.
Don’t you have the antidote
to cure poison?
I think the downside path is more secure.
There’s no antidote that can
prevent every poison.
It’s better to go up.
For the sake of our safety.
You prefer the front or rear?
Let’s go.
Don’t you feel
it’s getting hotter and hotter?
If I’m not wrong,
it’s because we’re approaching
Netherland down there.
How could it be?
I didn’t feel any gradient.
At first, we’re 1000 metres
higher than Netherland.
But, now it has decreased to 900 metres.
If the temperature keeps increasing,
the last part of the path
would have been sunk by Netherland.
And it should be
the most challenging path.
[You’ve harmed me.]
You’ve harmed me.
There’re many dead bodies here.
This must have been carved by him
before he died.
It seemed that they died of distrust.
Those who collaborated to challenge
Hell Road had their own agendas.
Is not surprising.
You don’t trust me?
There’s a sound.
Sound? What is it?
They’re here.
Bats.
Those bats are hesitant to launch attack.
They seem to be intelligent.
Let’s try them out.
Amazing speed and keenness.
They must have been mutated.
Unless our speed
surpass their limit of reaction,
otherwise, it’s hard to defeat them.
I can’t control the heinous spirit...
Blue Silver Domain.
Thank you.
Domain? How come he had it?
It’s innate domain.
It awakens me instantly,
and also limits the speed of
those bats completely.
Tang Yin, how many secrets do you have?
They’ve retreated
to the offside of the circle.
I obtained Blue Silver Domain
after the second awakening.
It enhances my spirit power
as well as oppresses rivals’ strength.
It’s more effective
when collaborating with hidden weapon.
However, it’s limited in attack range
due to the absence of mechanism.
I must bring the bats over.
Go.
Run forward. Bring them all together.
Tang Yin!
Expand.
Purple Demon Eye.
Retaliating strategy
in such a short period.
Tang Yin, you’re really a smart partner.
A strong opponent too.
Our attack can only
force them to retreat temporarily.
We should run forward quickly.
The collaboration between
Sura King and Emissary of Hell
is as incredible as expected.
It has just started though.
We’re in trouble now.
Their boss has come
after repulsing those sidekicks.
[Soul Land]
Soul Bone Skill.
Coquettish Genie.
It’s destroying the path.
Follow me.
The path will vanish if we don’t move.
Forward, hurry up.
Go.
No supporting leverage.
Tang Yin...
Tang Yin!
What to do?
When confronting with an invincible,
if you can’t let him surrender to you,
it’d be better to let him sleep forever.
Now...
How come it can regenerate?
Hao Tian Hammer.
Thank you.
I never foresee its ability
to regenerate and clone.
It’s too insidious.
It’s destroying the path again.
I’ll do it.
So fast. How could a soul master
from controlling branch has such speed?
Could it be soul bone?
Thanks to the attached soul bone
and skull bone given by Teacher,
it really helps to enhance
my combat strength.
It’s accumulating its power.
Perhaps it’s going
to launch another formidable skill.
The path has been destroyed
and only a little part of it is left.
Don’t give it a chance
to launch any attack.
We have to find its weakness.
Current terrain is suppressive for us.
Hence, we can’t attack simultaneously.
Tie the rope at your tail.
Then...
Wonder where’s the weakness?
Be careful. It’ll grow stronger
after every regeneration.
Tang Yin!
Wisdom Skull.
I got it.
Purple God Light.
Striking the three heads simultaneously
is the only way to halt
its ability to regenerate.
And this is its weakness too.
Do you want to take a rest?
Well. We’re quite exhausted.
And we still don’t know
what we’ll face later.
From what I know,
there’re three trials on Hell Road.
Each one is impregnable than the last one.
Just now, we’ve passed through
the first one.
Her fox tail is not merely a martial soul.
It’s likely to be an attacked soul bone.
The golden generation of
Martial Soul Hall is really formidable.
[Next Episode]
This is just a beginning.
The moment they enter Hell Road,
they’ve become its prey.
The sound and form...
Could it be...
Tang Yin, what should we do?
I’ll divert its attention,
and you wait for a chance to attack it.
But, are we able to dodge
on this narrow path?
Watch out!
Tang Yin, don’t you want your life?
Kill or to be killed,
what’s your choice?
He can’t persist anymore.