♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Luckily, Xiao Wu didn’t finish the final move of Eight Flinging.
That’s the critical strike flying through
the air and rotate in 180 degrees.
That would nearly kill him.
Xiao Wu.
Please go easy on him.
Do you know how much I miss you?
Why were you so silly to save me
by sacrificing yourself?
Finally home.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 147]
Why are they here?
I wonder who is here.
I was wondering who were here.
What?
Are you being a sore loser
and came here to fight us again today?
We, the Four Elements School
have been invited by the royal family
of the Tian Dou Empire
to move to Tian Dou City.
We came to greet you today.
Clearly, you guys barged in
by hurting the guarding students.
If you’re not happy about it,
ask the Shrek Seven Devils to come out
and fight us again.
What a pity!
Dai Mu Bai and Zhu Zhu Qing are now in Xing Luo,
and no one knows where Tang San is.
You still haven’t forgotten my Brother San?
Nonsense!
Xiao Tian and I are together already.
As for you,
Xiao Wu.
Tang San was so nice to you.
How can you betray him
and choose that boy instead?
Brother Feng.
It’s been a long time.
You are...
My appearance has changed.
No wonder you don’t recognize me.
I’m Tang San.
What?
No wonder.
All of us know how close
you and Xiao Wu have been.
Xiao Wu is...
Xiao Wu.
Little San.
Xiao Wu is....
She has her human form back,
but not her soul.
She only has a few basic reflexes.
Brother San.
Don’t be too sad.
This is a good start.
What did you all
come here for?
I’ll be honest with you.
Shrek School
is the number one school in Tian Dou
and has alot of land.
We want to move in,
so we came to negotiate with you.
It’s a pity.
Dean Frander and others aren’t here.
Negotiate?
You keep provoking us,
just so we would come out, right?
That’s right.
We wanted to see how much you had improved.
Moreover, we’d like to talk about land
and buy some space to practice with you.
We have a lot of land,
but we don’t have enough space
for the Four Elements Schools.
Why don’t you go to Tian Dou Imperial School?
We don’t want those wealthy dandies
to affect our school’s culture.
Sounds great and all,
but not a chance.
Of course.
If you want to merge into our school,
we won’t reject.
Stupid Fatty!
You!
Tang San.
I lost to you five years ago.
Today, shall we represent our schools
and bet again?
Brother Feng.
Are you in charge?
After we combined into the Four Elements School
Xiao Tian has been appointed Deputy Dean.
He does have the right to represent the school.
How about this?
I will challenge
the three of you on my own.
If I lose,
you can punish me as you wish.
If I win,
please stop
from trying to mess with our school.
You’re that confident in yourself?
So arrogant!
Xiao Tian
Let’s do it then.
I want to see
what skills he has
to fight the three of us simultaneously.
Feng Xiao Tian and the others are truly talented
and they have fought together for many years.
What solutions does Little San have?
Don’t worry about Brother San.
Xiao Wu.
Stay with Rong Rong for a bit.
I will be back soon,
okay?
Come here, Xiao Wu.
Come here.
During the Soul Master Competition five years ago,
Tang San created too many miracles.
We can’t let him create another one against us.
Ok.
Level 54, Control Branch, War Soul King.
Level 53, Storm Attack Branch, War Soul King.
Level 61, Keen Attack Branch, War Soul Emperor.
Please.
[Typhoon Canyon]
Brother Feng is already a Soul Emperor?
No wonder you are the Deputy Dean.
Are you going to surrender already?
Hurry and show your martial soul.
This is...
One hundred thousand years?
Level 66, Control Branch, War Soul Emperor.
Please.
Third Soul Skill, Dragon’s Rage!
His Blue Silver Plant
is more tougher than before.
Hurry!
Fifth Soul Skill.
Hurricane Blade!
Shooting Stars of Fire!
The wind is helping the fire
and the fire growing with the wind.
They’ve created a new Double Fusion Skill!
It’s useless.
Brother San’s Blue Silver Emperor is immune to fire.
What?
Tang San.
You are immune to fire,
but you can’t dodge wind.
Let’s fight head-on.
That is my intention.
God Killer Attacks.
Xiao Tian!
Xiao Tian.
Are you okay?
If I can’t avoid it,
then I’ll stop the wind.
Good for you, Tang San.
I have to use that skill.
Fifth Soul Skill.
Fire Dragon!
His fifth soul skill again?
He used a large amount of soul power.
Second Soul Skill.
- They want...
- Double Wolf Guard.
Third Soul Skill.
Gale Wings!
This is...
Gale Devil Wolf 36 Successive Chops?
It turns out you wanted to delay time
so that he can accumulate his power.
Do you think you can stop me like this?
Fourth Soul Skill.
Blue Silver Spike Formation.
Damn it, this skill is of dizzying effect.
Fifth Soul Skill.
Blue Silver Emperor Tyrant Spear!
Xiao Tian.
Be careful.
Thirty-three.
Thirty-four.
Thirty-five.
He’s about to finish gathering the power.
Tang San.
The speed is even faster.
This skill has advanced a long time ago.
It’s now called
Gale Devil Wolf 54 Successive Chops!
Brother San!
Forty.
Forty-one.
Forty-two.
The power of the Gale Wings
seems to have been sealed.
Teleport.
This time, I can’t lose again!
Xiao Tian.
Do you still want to continue?
Do you want to feel the power
of my Random Air Hammer Skill?
Three versus one,
yet we still lost.
Shrek is the best.
- Shrek is the best.
- Shrek will always win.
Tang San.
I’ve worked hard to train for five years,
but I still can’t beat you.
It seems that I won’t
be better than you in this lifetime.
Xiao Tian.
Don’t be too pessimistic.
It’s only been five years.
We can train for another 10 years,
20 years.
No matter where you go,
I will always be with you.
If Xiao Wu can return to normal
I am willing to give up my power.
The power of a soul master is important.
But for me,
she is more important.
Tang San.
Do we still get to discuss
moving our school in here?
You’ve already lost the bet.
What more do you want?
Brother Feng.
If I guessed correctly,
you’re changing your school locations
because of Martial Soul Hall, right?
Tang San.
Dealing things with you
is quite painful.
That’s right.
Those bastards in from Martial Soul Hall
keep trying to force us to join forces.
We have no choice
but to move to Tian Dou City.
Based on your performance today,
it seems like you won’t give up
your lead position.
I’m afraid there might be
conflicts among us in the future.
After all,
your school has more students,
and is overall
more powerful than Shrek.
We just...
It seems like
we’re destined to part with Shrek School.
When you fight against
the Martial Soul Hall in the future,
don’t forget us.
Goodbye.
What should we do?
Wait until the teachers come back?
The Four Elements School
might be our ally in the future.
But right now,
Shrek School needs to maintain
its dominant position.
We’ll wait for the Dean to decide when he gets back.
Then the Four Elements School
is about to suffer.
Certainly.
When it comes to scamming...
I mean,
when it comes to financial smarts,
no one can beat our Dean.
You guys did make the trip worthwhile.
All of a sudden, there’s a Tang Clan
with a thousand soul masters.
It won’t be long
before you surpass
the Qibao Amber Tribe.
Tang Clan was built upon the Four Tribes.
Unless it’s a soul master we wholeheartedly trust,
we won’t accept
any newcomers.
Also, besides us and Uncle Ning,
we must keep
all important matters
a secret.
Tang Clan will operate
under the name of Tribe of Strength for now.
Ok.
Little San.
When are we moving in?
Let’s decide when the teachers are back.
Shrek School is also our home.
We can’t let others come and bully us.
I’ll ask Grandpa Bone for help.
I’d like to see who dares to make trouble here again.
Rong Rong.
If you can get Senior Grand Bone Master
to come and support us,
we can take this opportunity
to go on a long trip.
This time
we need you, the fortune god of Tang Clan.
No problem.
My dad has already given me the first fund
to support the Tang Clan.
Brother San.
Where are we going?
For Tang Clan to create hidden weapons,
we need large amounts of metal.
Tribe of Strength
has a lot of normal metal.
But we lack precious metal.
Elder Tai Tan and I decided
that we needed to visit the Capital of Metal,
Gengxin Town.
Elder Tai Tan has been talking about
the hidden weapons this entire way.
The re-selection meeting of the Seven Great Tribes
is in less than a year.
We have to make some weapons beforehand
so that we can have the power
to fight against the Martial Soul Hall.
No matter what,
we need to create some problems
for them this time.
Rong Rong.
What are you doing?
Seek reinforcement, of course.
Once Grandpa Bone is here,
we can leave.
That’s right, Little Ao.
Are there any changes
in Tian Dou City during our absence?
Tian Dou City is still peaceful on the surface.
I heard Uncle Ning said that
it was quite intense in the royal family.
Emperor Xue Ye is seriously ill,
and no royal physicians knows what to do.
Maybe,
something big is about to happen.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 147 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1410 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2221]
[Total scene: 55353]
[Total CGI: 27033]
[Total plan of action scene: 12052]
[Total scene model: nearly 534]
[Total character model: nearly 991]
[Total props model: 13371]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolor ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
There is less than one year
before the Seven Clans Re-selection Contest.
Elder Tai Tan and I decided
that we have to go to the Capital of Metal.
I am the disciple of the top craftsman, Lou Gao.
Chairman of the Ironsmiths Society.
Trash.
Who is making trouble here?
Welcome to the Capital of Metal.
Teacher.
It’s me.
Didn’t I tell you?
No one is allowed to disturb me.
[Soul Land]
[10 AM every Saturday]