♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped by wind ♪
♪ Missed the farewell to my lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
I believe that
Xiao Wu must be right.
The Crystal Bloody Dragon Ginseng
could be greatly beneficial to her.
We, the Four Tribes, could team up to
fight against the Martial Soul Hall.
It seems that
we are aiming at the same thing.
So is this immature kid going to be
our tribe chief?
Let’s see how you
would tear me up, Senior Yang Wudi.
I have got to take my chances now.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 146]
What is this?
It’s Xiao Wu again.
I have tried so hard to suppress it.
But with my current mind power,
I can’t control Xiao Wu’s impulsive soul now.
He pissed Xiao Wu off.
The first move of Eight Flinging
is already this cruel.
Here comes the eighth one.
That’s too horrible.
Xiao Wu.
Please go easy on him.
Luckily, Xiao Wu didn’t finish
the final move of Eight Flinging.
That’s the critical strike flying through
the air and rotate in 1080 degrees.
That would nearly kill him.
Xiao Wu
Don’t worry.
I am alright now.
How’s that possible?
He has actually
heal himself?
That’s because of the second skill
of Blue Silver Emperor Right Thighbone.
Burned in wildfires yet born again
when spring breeze blows.
I see.
You two go and check if Old Goat is okay.
Leave the Chief to me.
Why did Wu point to the Lucky Almighty Pouch?
Senior.
I’m a little tired.
I have to go back and rest.
Please tell Senior Yang Wudi
I wish to talk to him
when he wakes up later.
I am glad that you are okay.
Go and take a rest.
Brother San.
The door is this way.
Oh.
Brother San.
Do you need help?
I thought Xiao Wu...
You’re right, Old Gorilla.
Where’s Tang San?
As he got impaled by the Soul Breaking Spear,
he may suffer from sequelae
if he doesn’t get proper treatment.
What do you mean?
What happened to him?
Is he dead?
No.
I didn’t mean to hurt him.
Alright, Old Gorilla and Old Rhino
stop misleading Old Goat now.
Tang San is fine.
He is much stronger than we thought.
as he could even heal himself.
Heal himself?
I lost to the last bit.
What did that little brat ask for?
No, he asked me to tell you
to rest first
and he would talk to you later.
It seems that
I really need rest.
This fight
has stopped Old Goat from being stubborn,
but it has also cost him his confidence.
Well, in some ways
it could be a good thing.
Our four single-attribute tribes
are literally reunited this time.
Old White Bird,
I notice something.
Actually, you are the most cunning one.
You were putting on an act yesterday,
but in fact,
you have agreed already
when you knew who he was.
Save all your words.
I am so happy to
see my grandson succeed.
I didn’t know who he was
when I first saw him.
Now I’m starting to dream about
the future of Tang Clan.
Another dream.
Brother San.
Are you feeling better?
Fatty.
What time is it now?
It’s night already.
Brother San,
have some food.
The Chief from the Tribe of Destruction
is waiting for your conditions.
Fatty.
You go there first.
I...
I will catch you in a second.
Ok.
Xiao Wu.
You have finally come back to life.
That’s perfect.
Xiao Wu.
Do you know how much I miss you?
Why were you so silly to save me
by sacrificing yourself?
If I hadn’t known there was
a chance to bring you back to life,
I might have died with you.
Xiao Wu.
I’m sorry.
I’m too excited.
I held you too tight, didn’t I?
Xiao Wu.
What...
What’s wrong with you?
[Soul Land]
Big Brother and I had thought about it,
there is only one way to save Sister Wu.
It must be met with three requirements.
They are...
Sacred Soul Plant,
Decade Millennium Grade Nine Ginseng King,
and Ancient Spirit Animal Neidan.
This 5,000 Millennium Crystal Bloody Dragon Ginseng
is almost as good as the Ginseng King.
But it is not enough
for Xiao Wu’s resurrection,
but for the recreation of her body.
Xiao Wu.
I would work hard to practice
to help you get your soul back.
Come.
Come with me.
Alright?
Xiao Wu?
Sorry to keep you all waiting.
Who is she?
She is Xiao Wu,
my lover.
She can’t pay respects to you all
because she has lost her conscious
when she saved me.
Seniors, please forgive her.
Senior Yang Wudi.
I guess you haven’t forgotten the bet we made
this morning, right?
Of course I haven’t.
I, Yang Wudi, always keep my words.
What I want is simple.
I only hope that you can
accept a gift from me.
Ok.
Give it to me.
Old White Bird.
What is so funny?
Are you doing something behind me?
That’s Fragrant Silk Woven Flower.
What is this?
Little San.
Where’s the Crystal Bloody Dragon Ginseng I gave you?
Granduncle.
Xiao Wu ate it.
What?
You...
You are willing to give it to me?
Yes,
spiritual objects choose their own masters.
It may bring out the best effect with you.
I also know a little something about herbs,
- so I hope I can learn more from you in the future.
- Alright.
From now on,
I will work under you.
Why didn’t you show me early?
I didn’t have to fight with you and lose.
I have looked for it for a life time.
I didn’t expect that
I would get it this way.
My Fragrant Silk Woven Flower, with you,
there will be no poison that I can’t create.
Is this one more valuable
than my Crystal Bloody Dragon Ginseng?
Old White Bird,
you did conspire with him against me,
didn’t you?
Alright, forget about it.
Your piece may be more valuable,
but, as for me,
this one is priceless.
Now that I have it,
I don’t need to worry
about getting poisoned
when refining any medicine.
Its fragrance could lead to
variations of many medicines.
I could even sacrifice myself to get it.
So,
you kinda get what you both want.
That’s to say,
you are going to join Tang Clan as well, right?
Yes! Yes!
[Old Goat is super thick-skinned.]
I am gonna go back tomorrow
and take my people here to gobble up your food.
This is bad.
Old Goat is obsessed with that thing.
Tang San,
good job.
Do you still call him that?
We are all now part of Tang Clan.
All of you are my seniors,
and you all would be the Elders of Tang Clan too.
Indeed, it’s not proper to call me that any more.
Why don’t you
call me Little San?
Alright,
that’s it.
We will set off
by tomorrow morning.
Huyan Zhen won’t be able to find us
even if he wants to take revenge on us.
We are arriving at Shrek School.
Finally home.
Hey.
Brother San.
You are pretty good at
braiding her hair.
Xiao Wu is overly dependent on me,
so I can’t allow anyone else to do that.
Go.
Let’s go and visit the teachers.
Okay.
If they knew Xiao Wu has come back to life,
they would be very happy.
Brother San.
Elder Tai Tan said
it will take about three months to build Tang Clan.
So are we going to relax
and have some fun
during this period of time?
Of course.
Practice more and raise yourself to Level 60.
Then I’ll accompany you
to the soul beast forest for fun.
Except for Xiao Wu
you are the only one who hasn’t reached Level 60.
We are different.
You are all focused on practicing
since you have had your lover.
What about you
wakening my martial soul for a second time?
I wish I can be half as handsome as you.
Work hard to practice
and be stronger.
Do you think there won’t be a girl
who adores you after that?
Brother San is right.
I must work hard to practice
and impress Miss Bai.
Miss Bai?
It’s noon.
Class should be dismissed.
Where are they?
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[Episode 146 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1326 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2039]
[Total scene: 51541]
[Total CGI: 26140]
[Total plan of action scene: 11104]
[Total scene model: nearly 520]
[Total character model: nearly 971]
[Total props model: 13362]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolor ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
Are there any changes
in Tian Dou City during our absence?
I heard Uncle Ning said that
it was quite intense
in the royal family.
Emperor Xue Ye is seriously ill,
and no royal physicians knows what to do.
Maybe
something big is about to happen.
Are you going to keep doing this?
Tang San.
It’s quite painful
to deal with you.
I came here for negotiation this time.
Clearly, you guys barged in
by hurting the guarding students.
Let’s fight again
if you are not convinced.
Please
don’t disturb our school anymore.
[Soul Land]
[Available at 10 AM every Saturday]