♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
They’re coming.
Shrek, it’s your showtime.
Who are we?
Champion!
We’re here
to defeat the champion.
In the previous match,
they didn’t reveal their real strength.
Will Shrek spur them on today?
There’s only one winner.
Who will be the champion in the end?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 104]
What’s wrong? The sky has turned dark.
Not the sky, but our sight.
My body feels heavy and I can’t use my soul power.
Purple Demon Eye.
This is what Senior Dugu mentioned
the effect of Genie Mesmerize.
Within its controlled area,
our senses fade 50%,
soul power is suppressed by 50%,
and all movements are lagged by 50%.
Don’t act rashly.
This thick red mist
mixes with power containing
a sense of ruthlessness and hallucination.
Thus, people lose their sight
and minds within their clutches.
They aim to cripple rivals’ strength
and then disrupt their minds?
No wonder Tian Dou Imperial School
was defeated within seconds.
Master is right.
This Martial Soul Fusion Skill is
par to the seventh soul skill
of ordinary soul masters.
Before Seven in One
Martial Soul Fusion Skill is exerted,
they’re engulfed by the red mist.
Shrek School has nothing to worry about.
It’s too bad
to be trapped in the
Martial Soul Fusion Skill of their rivals.
Shrek Seven Devils’ soul power is inferior
to their opponents
Under such an adverse situation,
how are they able to fight?
Xuan Yu Hand.
How do you know the direction of my attack?
Impossible. Ordinary soul masters
can’t identify directions in this red mist.
It’s impossible to escape when they’re trapped.
How strong Little Freak’s mental power is.
He can actually view in the red mist.
This must beyond Xie Yue’s expectation.
And Little San could reverse the situation
with his ability.
Do you think
you can escape from
our Martial Soul Fusian Skill?
This red mist perpetuates from
the center of Genie Mesmerize.
Genie Mesmerize stopped attacking me
when you’re out of it.
It speeds up
to bring the red mist along to spread it.
You’re right. Unless you can fly.
Otherwise, don’t think you can escape.
It’s impossible.
The world’s first martial soul of Support Branch
is really threatening.
I’ll settle you first.
Then, we’ll fly.
How could this happen?
Flight Mushroom Sausage had been used before.
Perhaps Martial Soul Hall thought
it was Little San’s flight ability.
So they have missed out Little Ao.
If there’s a focus in the vision,
the blind spot appears as well.
Neglecting a soul master from food branch
is their biggest mistake ever.
They did break out by flying.
By now, it’s useless
to hunt the six of them.
They may use the same way to escape.
Even though Martial Soul Fusion Skill is great,
but it depletes our soul power too.
For now,
the best way would be
depending on our members to settle them.
Boss Dai, please settle yourselves.
Do you think you can win
by escaping from Genie Mesmerize?
Don’t overestimate yourselves.
Shrek can never be comparable with
Martial Soul Hall Team
even without two of us.
You can never defeat two Soul Kings
when you’re just at Level 43.
This is
Soul bone?
I never thought that Tang San
could hide his soul bone
throughout the whole tournament.
It looks like
a soul bone from a spider-typed soul beast.
How could this Soul Sect possess a soul bone?
The soul bone grows from his back.
Is it a torso bone?
It seems that we can’t settle him in a quick fight.
Although Tang San’s soul power
is weaker than us,
however, the presence of soul bone
will minimize this gap.
The Eight Spider Bone’s amplification
empowers me to retaliate the red mist.
The effect of Eight Spider Bone
on strength, agility, and toxicity
is robust.
I might be able to fight against them.
Advancing me with speed?
I saw you.
I must go near them.
Blue Silver Plant.
After absorbing two Human Faced Demon Spiders
and tempering by both
Octa Dark Frost and Fiery Soft Apricot,
Eight Spider Bone has become extremely tough.
But they had broken it.
The attack of Moon Blade
is beyond my expectation.
The current situation
is different from what we perceived,
Martial Soul Hall will win anyway.
The moment we kill Tang San,
is the moment of victory.
Second Soul Skill, Rock of Granite.
Third Soul Skill,
White Tiger Vajra Transformation.
Third Soul Skill, Light of Support.
First Soul Skill, Nether Spikes,
[Soul Land]
What an immense defence.
Rock of Granite.
He’s a double-attribute soul master
of fire and earth.
Third Soul Skill, Holy Ring.
Straight line.
Fourth Soul Skill, Invincible Golden Shield.
Her tactical consciousness is dominating.
Darn it. One more.
Third Soul Skill, Teleport.
Brother Tao!
First Soul Skill, Phoenix Firing Line.
First Soul Skill, Intertwine.
Ghostly Trace.
What a tough guy.
First Soul Skill, Intertwine.
Watch out, Mu Bai.
Little San’s signal.
What is happening in the red mist?
It’s Moon Blade.
Right now.
My moves are slowing down
and my body is freezing.
Fourth Soul Skill, Churning Lava.
Mu Bai!
Leave me and stay away.
Fourth Soul Skill, Blue Silver Cage.
Tang San, your soul power is weaker than mine.
How confident are you
to use the laborious fourth soul skill?
Hao Tian Hammer.
First Soul Skill, Arched Body,
The weakest point of human
is at the lumbar spine.
Brother taught me this.
Third Soul Skill, Teleport.
We have got you.
Fourth Soul Skill, Phoenix Strike.
Oh, no.
Sun Chuan Tao has lost.
Dai Mu Bai is also free from control.
It seems Shrek has got the upper hand.
But the situation in the red mist is unknown.
Can Tang San resist the attack of Genie Mesmerize?
Even if I’m able to take the first Moon Blade,
but not the second one.
Maybe...
Xuan Yu Hand.
Tang San, let’s see how you’re going
to take the second Moon Blade.
How could be this possible? A coincidence?
Hidden Weapons of Tang Clan,
Kill Two Birds with One Stone.
In this world,
except me, no one knows this.
With a precise estimation of the strength
and angle of Hao Tian Hammer’s attack,
everything is within my control.
This is the essence of
Kill Two Birds with One Stone.
If it’s not a coincidence,
His ability has gone far beyond my expectation.
But
I still have that stroke.
Tang San, you’re honored to fail
under my soul skill creation.
Feng Xiao Tian was
as arrogant as you when he used
Gale Devil Wolf
36 Successive Chops on me.
How dare you put Feng Xiao Tian on par with me?
My soul skill is flawless.
Tang San, taste it.
Full Moon.
Xie Yue had used this skill
to defeat his teacher at Level 68.
Tang San, once Xie Yue uses the skill,
it means you have no way to stay alive.
Fourth Soul Skill, Blue Silver Cage.
It’s a matter of time for Moon Blade
to break Blue Silver Cage.
What’s more, this Full Moon.
What?
Break it instantly?
It’s powerful.
Xie Yue depletes his soul power
for Full Moon after using fusion skill,
this must be the final strike.
After this,
both of us
will deplete our soul power.
This is the decisive strike.
[Next Episode]
I’ll never die here.
Brother!
Fifth Soul Skill,
Sand Storm Raging Fire.
What exactly is my real strength?
Do you know it?
That’s...
This is your soul skill creation?
Tang San.
Are you ready to lose?