♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Ah Yin, I’ve brought our son to visit you.
Mom.
This feeling
was the same as I first saw your mom.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 121]
There is a kid targeted by a soul beast.
Over there.
The kid is trapped there.
Don’t attack impulsively,
otherwise the kid may get hurt.
Oh, no.
Do you know, your mom was pretty,
but she was more attractive with her fresh vibes.
She was as pure as a fairy.
So I fell for her
the first time I met her.
My name is Ah Yin,
which is ‘silver’ from the word “Blue Silver Plant”.
I planned to deflate the Double Star of Hao Tian.
But I’ve never expected the Blue Silver Plant
to be so powerful.
That surprised me.
Later, we became sworn brothers and sister.
Ah Yin was the youngest and
ranked the third among us.
We called her Ah Yin or Little San.
This is where your name derives.
Both my elder brother and I
fell for Ah Yin, the pretty lady.
Elder Brother dropped out in the end
and returned to the tribe.
On the same night,
Ah Yin confessed to me that
she was a Century Millennium Soul Beast,
Blue Silver Emperor.
However, my love for her surpassed everything.
I didn’t care about her identity at all!
As long as she could enter the mature period,
she would become a human.
So, I expressed my love to her.
Only then did I know that
she had always loved me.
She was worried that
Elder Brother might be upset,
so she didn’t take any action.
Since then, we got together.
I thought we could live happily ever after.
As we were going to return to the tribe,
people from Martial Soul Hall
found out about Ah Yin’s identity...
We managed to get rid of them,
so they went to Hao Tian Tribe.
Your grandpa was already very sick then
so the news let to his death.
Elder Brother succeeded as
the chief of the tribe.
However, he struggled among the powers.
The day that you were born
was destined to be a special day.
That day, my soul power reached Level 90.
And your mom
finally reached the mature period
of transforming into human.
Simultaneously,
people from Martial Soul Hall came to us...
Are you willing to sacrifice?
Do you know you will vanish forever for using it?
Ah Yin, no. Please go with them.
Don’t sacrifice.
Stop her, everyone.
Blue Silver Plant has never had a home.
After so many ordeals, I’ve finally met you.
Farewell, my love.
Ah Yin!
No.
A Grand Soul Land Master who
has a Century Millennium Soul Ring.
Go,
before he
has completely adapted to the soul ring.
[Soul Land]
Ring Blasting?
Martial Soul Hall!
The Ninth Soul Skill.
Chrysanthemum strewing to the ground.
Demon of Hell.
Petals piercing through bodies.
The Strike of Ling Tian.
He has repelled the attacks
from Old Ghost and me instantly...
He has completely adapted to
the Century Millennium Soul Ring.
The Ninth Soul Skill.
Glory of
Angel.
Sumeru Hammer.
No.
Leave now.
Tang Hao,
Martial Soul Hall will remember this.
The buck stops here.
You can come for me anytime.
Grand Hao Tian Master.
I could kill Qian Xun Ji at that time.
But I couldn’t drag the tribe down.
There was one person of Martial Soul Hall
that could make Hao Tian Tribe scruple.
After I left, I planted the seeds here
and stayed at the nearby
Soul Saint Village with you.
Later, Qian Xun Ji died from the incurable injury.
People from Martial Soul Hall
went to Hao Tian Tribe again.
Elder Brother was forced to expel me
and close down the tribe.
Hao Tian Tribe
went into hiding since then.
And you know what happened later on.
If I hadn’t found hope in you,
perhaps
I would have muddled my life aimlessly.
You’re much better than I expected.
Dad.
Don’t feel sad for me.
I’ve survived the toughest moments.
I used my soul power to drive the thrombus
into a leg and an arm
and chopped them off to heal all injuries.
Isn’t the soul bone inseparable
from the body after fusion?
For a Grand Soul Land Master,
as long as he wants to,
the soul bone on his limbs
can be separated.
But the cost is significant.
Hence, my soul power
has dropped to Level 75.
Dad, I can help you cure the injuries.
You don’t have to...
This is my debt to the tribe.
Back then,
the two pieces of soul bone
I received from the tribe
were fused into these severed arm and leg.
I didn’t become the tribe chief,
and I let my dad down.
I’ve been feeling guilty for years.
If I had a chance to start over,
I’d still choose your mom
yet I’d protect the tribe as well.
After I settle everything,
you may return to the tribe
and pay respect to
your late grandpa on my behalf.
Qian Xun Ji is dead.
But I still have to take revenge
on the Martial Soul Hall.
I want you to help rebuild the tribe.
Dad, I’ll definitely make it.
Open it.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 121 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1228 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 1824]
[Total scene: 46957]
[Total CGI: 24653]
[Total plan of action scene: 10016]
[Total scene model: nearly 500]
[Total character model: nearly 934]
[Total props model: 13339]
[Appreciate your continuous
support and love,]
[we will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land
illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
[Next Episode]
The Century Millennium Soul Beast
that appeared in the Soul Master Contest
is currently in Star Dou Forest.
Tang San,
I want you to experience
the extreme pain.
That is...