♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind,
you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previously on Soul Land]
The exit is about two kilometres away.
How could it be?
This is the only chance.
Is it the domain condensed with heinous spirit?
We’ve handed over
our lives to each other successively.
Are we even now?
Moon Pavilion?
Your reckless behavior is unbearable here.
Is this all you can do?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 119]
What happened?
Madam Yue.
She’s the owner of Moon Pavilion?
Her temperament is outstanding,
comparable to Bibi Dong.
Madam Yue, here they are.
Is it really you?
Yes, Yue Hua.
How come you’ve become so haggard?
Is this the son of yours and hers?
Why do you avoid me? I’m your aunt.
Aunt, I’m sorry for what happened just now.
It is Brother’s fault
for not bringing you to me earlier.
Follow me.
Is your name Tang San?
Yes.
You’ve never forgotten her,
just as our Elder Brother.
Is he well?
You know him.
He keeps everything in his heart.
Last time, I went back home
and accidentally saw him
looking at the portrait of
us three when we were young.
You have to go back with me this time.
Go back? I’m no longer
a member of Hao Tian Tribe.
Yue Hua, I let the tribe down.
But I’ve never regretted what I did.
Don’t you want to visit Elder Brother?
A prestigious tribe has to hide.
You’ve no idea how miserable he is.
The moment Ah Yin died,
my heart has died too.
I’m of no help for the tribe.
As for apology, Elder Brother
would know even if I don’t say it.
But you’re the youngest
Grand Soul Land Master...
Aunt, it isn’t that
Dad is not willing to help,
but his body has...
Enough, Little San.
Yue Hua, he has just come back
from Slaughter City.
Only you can help him.
Find me in the valley one year later.
Remember, what you should be afraid of
is not a robust enemy
but a depraving heart.
Second Brother...
Yue Hua, please tell Elder Brother that
Little San is my repayment to the tribe.
Besides, he’s my son with Ah Yin.
Our only son.
Do you know why he asked you to stay here
for a year?
Moon Pavilion is an academy that teaches
court etiquette in Tian Dou Empire.
We specialize in noble etiquette and music.
Later on, you’ll learn all these with me
until I’m satisfied with your performance.
What Dad asked me to learn are useless for combat.
But I need to practice more now.
And become stronger the sooner the better.
Otherwise, how could I be able
to counter Martial Soul Hall?
It’s not enough to have powerful strength.
Like your dad, he’s powerful,
but his heart is full of sadness.
How to use language and arts,
how to survive amongst the powers,
and how to protect yourself
without relying on strength...
If your dad had everything that I’m good at,
the tragedy wouldn’t have happened.
If you decide to take on
your dad’s responsibilities,
you need to learn more and be stronger.
Ok.
Does Father want me to learn what Aunt is good at?
But,
can these hands play an elegant piece of music
aside from combating?
Silly boy.
You’ve passed through Hell Road
at such a young age,
I know you’re outstanding.
But, you haven’t mastered
all the potentials you possess.
Do you mean the Death God Domain?
This’s my innate domain.
Noble Circle.
My current soul power is Level 9.
Is your martial soul mutated?
You might think
I’m the most useless in Hao Tian Tribe.
But an authentic invincible person
should learn to control
everything he possess first,
especially the emotions and the vibes.
Can learning etiquette and music
really help me control my heinous spirit?
You’ll find out soon.
What you need the most
for studying at Moon Pavilion is
controlling your behavior precisely.
I got it.
Well, go back and rest.
You’ll meet with
many demanding classmates tomorrow.
They’re all from noble families
who are good at scheming.
This is your new classmate, Tang Yin.
You’ll be studying together
for the coming year.
Is he going to learn
a three-year course within a year
and graduate?
From now on,
the time for harp class
will gradually increase.
Before the graduation ceremony,
I’ll pick one of
the best students among you
to perform on behalf of the class.
[Soul Land]
The graduate representative must be
Princess Xue Ke without doubt.
She’s the sister of the crown prince
who is born with elegant vibes.
She wins only because of her royal blood.
If I wasn’t in the same badge with her,
I’ll surely qualify for the position
as I’m the elder daughter of duke.
He knows nothing about music.
Which family would’ve raised
such an uncultivated person?
Is he just a commoner?
[Theories of Music]
[Solo Piece of Harp]
[Information of Candidates]
Today we’ll practice
how to invite others to dance at the prom.
Tang Yin,
you should know your identity as a commoner.
Never try to favor the rich and the powers.
Tang Yin,
I don’t want any rumours
that could tarnish my image.
I hope you understand.
Go and invite others.
I reckon that
those who are not from a noble family,
are disqualified to study in Moon Pavilion.
Oh, no. If Little San’s heinous spirit
is out of control again...
What are you smirking at?
Etiquette teaches me to be restrained,
while music calms me.
You should be
more self-disciplined and nobler than me
since you’ve studied longer.
But, it seems otherwise.
What does a commoner like you
know what nobility means?
Even a commoner like me knows that
nobility doesn’t engraved on your skin
nor run in your blood.
It’s a medal you earn with your behavior.
Lineage is not a must for a hero.
We’ve studied together for some time.
We know how excellent Tang Yin is.
Less than a year,
Tang Yin’s harp skill
has reached a superb level.
And his deportment,
his gallant manner is
so different from others.
I hope you remember
the base of etiquette is respect.
Let’s continue.
Brother, can you attend my graduation ceremony?
Tang Yin, the person I told you before,
has replaced me
as the representative of the graduates.
But I’m not upset
because his talent will surely shock you as well.
How charming you are
to make my proud sister admire you?
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 119 has been completed
and broadcasted for nearly 1214 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 1794]
[Total scene: 46409]
[Total CGI: 24493]
[Total plan of action scene: 9892]
[Total scene model: nearly 499]
[Total character model: nearly 931]
[Total props model: 13329]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on going.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul.]
[We’re not alone with your presence.]
[Next Episode]
No wonder sister
praised him in front of me.
He’s not simple.
How come the representative
not Princess Xue Ke?
You’re doing great today.
Thank you, Aunt.
I’ve already understood Father’s intention.
Dad...
Who hurt you to such extend?
It has been five years.
Xiao Wu, how are you?
[Soul Land]
[10 a.m. Every Saturday]