♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Emperor Xue Ye is poisoned by a mixed poison.
And Xue Qing He is the only one
who uses this spice in the palace.
Martial Soul Hall!
Even if I die,
I’ll turn their world upside down!
Enough!
-Teacher…
-Gang…
This power is far from enough
to beat Martial Soul Hall.
Fatty, I’m thinking of setting up a clan.
Let’s call it the Tang Clan.
Someone’s here!
Who are you?
What about you?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 138]
Who are you?
What about you?
Why were you with Ning Rong Rong?
What does my relationship with Rong Rong
have to do with you?
Rong Rong? Sounds so affectionate.
Godly Zhuge Crossbow!
The Century Millenium Soul Ring!
Intertwine!
Sixth Soul Skill! Cloning Sausage!
A food series soul master?
Red Flames!
His power is very strong!
Fourth Soul Skill!
Blue Silver Cage!
Mirror Skull! Duplicate!
He has a duplicate!
Hao Tian Hammer!
Hao Tian Hammer? Blue Silver Plant?
Little San?
Little Ao, it’s you!
Little Ao!
You’re back alive. That’s great!
Why did you become like this?
Let’s go! Follow me back to school.
I’ll explain it to you.
Wait a minute. I can’t go back to school.
Let’s talk in another place first.
Take your hat off.
Since you’re back,
why didn’t you return to school?
You should have known about what happened
to Qibao Amber Tribe, right?
You held grudge against me just now
because I was out with Rong Rong?
You were jealous?
Look at me now. How can I meet Rong Rong?
I’m satisfied enough
to see her secretly.
Because of that scar?
Do you know that Rong Rong suffers a lot
because of you these years?
What kind of people do you think Rong Rong is?
Do you think Rong Rong would dislike you
because of your scarred face?
Little San, you don’t understand.
Rong Rong is prettier than she was five years ago.
I wasn’t good enough for her.
Now, I become like this.
How can I go and meet her?
You might be sad because of your inferiority.
But, no matter how sad I am,
I can’t see my Xiao Wu now.
Little San, what do you mean?
Enjoy.
This is Xiao Wu. My Xiao Wu.
What... What happened?
What’s the point of being handsome?
If I have a choice,
I rather become extremely ugly
for Xiao Wu’s well-being.
That day, after Xiao Wu and I were saved by my father,
my father asked Xiao Wu to leave me for awhile.
Then, he brought me to the waterfall
to trained my hammer skills.
Now, you know how I got
my Century Millenium Soul Ring?
If I have a choice, I just want Xiao Wu back.
Little Ao, cherish the people around you.
It will be too late to regret
when you lose her.
Little San, I’m sorry.
I didn’t expect that you and Xiao Wu would...
Don’t apologize to me.
You should apologize to Rong Rong.
I understand now.
Let’s go! I’ll follow you back now.
No matter what happen in the future,
I will never leave her.
I’ll be happy even if
I can only protect her by her side.
Xiao Wu, did you see it?
Rong Rong and Little Ao can finally be together.
You would be happy for them too, right?
We will be together, too.
I promise you.
Little San...
Let me touch for awhile.
Just awhile.
Did you stick this scar on?
Let me touch for a while.
Just a while.
Did you just put a scar sticker?
Master.
Brother San, you’re awake.
Don’t worry. You’re alright.
It might be because you have been
too sad these days
and too anxious for your training.
And you didn’t rest well.
Master.
It might also be caused by
the Eight Spider Bone that I obtained.
Oh! Let me have a look.
Master, it wasn’t like this last time.
At that time, my other three soul bones
changed as well.
They were extended into an armor
and combined with this armor.
My power was enhanced a lot.
I understand now. Looks like I was right.
There’s a high possibility
that you will obtain that special skill.
Soul Bone Fusion Skill.
[Soul Land]
Soul Bone Fusion Skill?
Master, you’ve never told me about this before.
Because I didn’t expect
that you would have the chance
to get to know the Soul Bone Fusion Skill
in your whole life.
I didn’t expect that you would be so blessed.
What exactly is the Soul Bone Fusion Skill?
Soul Bone Fusion Skill
is an additional skill produced by
the fusion of all your soul bones.
It’s very strong.
Almost no one has reached this field.
Now, among all the soul masters,
there’s only one person
who might have this skill.
How many soul bones does a person need
to obtain this skill?
Normally, you need to gather all six soul bones.
And they must come from
the same kind of soul beasts.
Then, you’ll have one out of a thousand chance
to obtain this skill.
This is nearly impossible to achieve.
But, Brother San only has four soul bones now.
So, Little San’s situation now might be
a sign of the Soul Bone Fusion Skill.
But, my soul bones were not produced by
one type of soul beast.
If I’m not wrong,
it’s because of your Eight Spider Bone.
As an attached soul bone,
it has evolved several times
and developed a new function.
It connects all your soul bones like a bridge.
Therefore,
whether you can obtain
the Soul Bone Fusion Skill
depends on the soul bones you obtain
in the future.
Grandmaster, who’s the one you said that might have
this skill?
In history,
there’s a set of inherited soul bones
only in the Martial Soul Hall.
I’ve never heard that anyone
has fully fused the six soul bones.
But, I think someone is capable of it,
which is Bibi Dong.
Bibi Dong!
Little San, don’t grieve over Xiao Wu.
Since there’s a possibility
that she can be revived,
we will make it some day.
What’s your plan this time?
Master, given the situation now,
Martial Soul Hall aims at
conquering the whole continent, I’m afraid.
We won’t stand any chance to
change the situation with what we’ve got now.
You chose to rely on Tian Dou Empire.
But, I’m not doing that.
Then, what are you planning to do?
It is indeed viable to take advantage of
the power of Tian Dou Empire.
But, the domestic situation of
the royal family is too complicated.
Previously, I met Senior Dugu Bo.
I’ve thought a lot over his words.
You... should be careful, too.
Their relationships are too complicated.
What Senior Dugu Bo knows
might not be everything.
I was too immersed in hatred these days.
I didn’t think carefully.
Seems like Xue Qing He is quite scheming.
I’m afraid that Chief Ning is also kept in the dark.
But...
Is there a soul master
better at using poison than the Grand Venom Master?
I don’t know either.
Maybe...
There’s indeed such a person.
But, such a great soul master
is working under Xue Qing He.
This means this soul master
is supported by someone powerful.
Can it be Xing Lou Empire?
No. The worst scenario is the Martial Soul Hall.
Master.
I don’t think Xue Beng
is any better than Xue Qing He.
Considering that, we should focus on ourselves.
I’ll set up a clan.
But, I need some support and protection of a power
to develop it.
Do you want me to help you?
Now, Emperor Xue Ye trusts you.
You can’t leave.
I’ll do everything I can to help you.
Tell me your plan in detail.
Brother San, I’m back.
It’s really hard to believe
martial soul can change a person completely.
Hello, Uncle Ning. Long time no see.
This is...
Chief Ning. Rong Rong.
I’m back.
Rong Rong, give me ten years. Ten years later,
if I’m not dead, I will definitely make it.
Why do you treat me so well?
Rong Rong, I love you the most.
Besides you, who should I take care of?
Do you know? We can’t be together.
Oscar, you like me, don’t you?
Come back!
I don’t want you to become stronger.
I only want you to come back!
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 138 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1347 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2084]
[Total scene: 52368]
[Total CGI: 26259]
[Total plan of action scene: 11189]
[Total scene model: nearly 525]
[Total character model: nearly 974]
[Total props model: 13365]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods,
who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
Master.
I’ve been waiting for you.
But, you...
I’m planning to set up a clan.
Tribe of Strength
is unwilling to be
a subsidiary of Hao Tian Tribe anymore.
Uncle Ning.
I have something important...
I only have one daughter,
Rong Rong.
I’m sorry.
I can’t promise you.
If I leave,
I’ll never forgive myself.
What about Rong Rong?
Then, let’s see
how you’ve improved these five years.
[Soul Land]
[Available at 10 AM every Saturday]