♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
A place like Slaughter City
should have collapsed earlier.
We’re in trouble.
Blue Silver Domain.
This is just the start.
It’s destroying the path.
Tang Yin, how many secrets do you have?
The boss finally comes
after all those sidekicks.
It’s accumulating its power.
Perhaps it’s going to launch another formidable skill.
We must find its weakness.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 117]
The moment they entered Hell Road,
they’ve become its prey.
The two existing Death Gods
fought hard with it.
Only eight people have passed over the past 1000 years.
I wonder whether
Asura King and Emissary of Hell can succeed?
Let’s go.
Do you want to rest for a few more minutes?
It’s hot.
I can feel my energy draining off.
Blue Silver Domain.
It has cooled down.
Tang Yin’s innate domain enables him
to maintain full combat strength
under any circumstances.
Hao Tian Tribe is really
a great place for nurturing talents.
Tang Yin...
I’m fine.
Serpent?
Watch out. The red maze must be poisonous.
Are we able to dodge on this narrow path?
Tang Yin, what shall we do?
The sound, form, and poisonous fire.
Could it be the ancient beast,
Ten-Headed Burning Sun Serpent?
There’re nine crystals
glowing with reddish radiance.
Perhaps these are its weakness.
This smell... It’s alcohol.
As long as it’s snake venom,
it can be suppressed by realgar.
The venomous flame is approaching.
It’s incredible to resist the fire with wind,
and yet he seems so calm.
I’ll divert its attention,
and you wait for a chance to attack.
Soul bone skill.
Coquettish Genie.
I can’t pierce through it.
The flowing flame is like an impregnable armor.
Forty-two, forty-three,
forty-four, forty-five...
There’s a flaw here.
Watch out!
Seven more to go.
Destroy all of them when it’s off-guard.
Your Holiness,
Xie Yue and Yan will be back
from Death Valley today.
It has been two years.
Have they made any progress?
Your Holiness, both of them
are approaching the Level 60.
Great.
I’ll send someone to fetch them.
Gui Mei, Yue Guan.
Your destination is Slaughter City.
Yes.
You must come back alive.
[Soul Land]
Three left.
Carry on.
It’s neidan.
Oh, no. It’s going to bring us down with it.
The pressure is strong.
Don’t we have other alternatives?
Darn it.
So powerful!
Tang Yin!
The powerful neidan of the serpent
turns the earth pale.
I almost lost my life there.
Little San, how would you handle this?
If the connection between
the body and the neidan is cut off,
- we still have a chance.
- Tang Yin, you will die for it!
Skill of Random Hammering.
Nine by Nine Consolidate to One.
This neidan can invalidate any venom,
and restrain all snakes as well.
Tang Yin!
What’s wrong with you?
Blue Silver Domain.
The longer we stay, the harder
we can control the inner heinous spirit.
Dash for it.
Calm down. Let’s speed up and walk through this.
Tang Yin, I can’t make it.
Just hang in there. If I’m not wrong,
we’re almost there.
Calm down.
Will they be like the two people before?
[You’ve harmed me.]
Kill or to be killed,
what’s your choice, Asura King?
Calm yourself.
Too bad. If Hu Liena goes ballistic,
she’ll attack me.
I might win if I resist with all force,
but I’ll be injured instead.
Is killing her the only way?
Tang Yin, I can’t resist anymore.
Insensate me before I go ballistic.
Please bring me out.
Hurry up. Do it.
Even Hu Liena can’t stick to the end.
So, the most threatening obstacle here
is not from the external,
but the evil in our heart.
Luckily, I have Blue Silver Domain
and Wisdom Skull.
The base of Slaughter City
is Yomigaeri, formed by the mixture
of degenerates’ souls and toxins.
Although I can’t resolve it,
however...
This Bloody Swan Kiss
will stimulate the toxins by many folds,
strong enough to make Yomigaeri
a venomous toxins without antidote.
Slaughter City, Slaughter King,
I hope you’ll like my present.
It’s the exit!
[It’s been 1200 days from the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017]
[to the completion of episode 117.]
[Total minute of the animation: 1764]
[Total scene: 45634]
[Total CGI: 24377]
[Total plan of action scene: 9823]
[Total scene model: nearly 493]
[Total character model: nearly 931]
[Total props model: 13323]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will keep working on it.]
[Dream of Soul Land. Illuminates our martial soul.]
[Our youth vibrates with yours.]
[Next Episode]
I’m sure you’ll be able to come out alive.
Dad must be waiting for me.
We’ve handed over our lives to each other.
I’ll never forget
the critical challenges of these two years.
There’s no way out.
Will I end up here?
Collapse.
Slaughter City.
When the full moon turns obscure,
it denotes the arrival of old acquaintance.
Last warning.
This is the only chance.