♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Martial Soul Hall,
let’s make an end today.
Bipolar Static Field.
- Run.
- Leave right after capturing the rabbit.
Hurry up!
Tang Yin is...
- Why?
- Chase after them.
San Wu will teach them a lesson then.
Human Faced Demon Spider
over a decade millennium
can shield the spirit power.
I’m afraid its age has exceeded
thirty thousand years.
They are at the front.
We’re too late.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 134]
You’re at the end of your tether.
Stop struggling.
Brother.
Fight now!
Martial Soul Form!
What’s that glow?
He has ascended to Level 60.
My soul power has depleted.
Titan Giant Ape and Azure Bull Python
are being trapped by Grand Ghost Master
and Grand Chrysanthemum Master.
To get rid of them,
the only breakthrough point is...
the sky.
- He has broken through.
- Let’s do this together.
Fourth Soul Skill, Invincible Golden...
I can’t move.
Brother.
Xiao Wu, leave first!
No!
Attack him.
If your level hadn’t ascended,
you wouldn’t have been able to
take the first three attacks.
You have no way to escape, Tang San.
Ah Yin, do you feel that too?
Little San,
are you facing the same destiny as I mine?
No!
He’s using his leg to attack.
Is there nothing else you can do?
Tang San!
Are you giving up your life, Tang Yin?
Soul bone!
Xiao Wu, this is a flying soul bone skill. Run now.
Brother.
Brother!
What if many people try to kill me one day
and they’re too powerful for you to fight against?
Let them step over my dead body first.
Xiao Wu, I said I’d protect you with my life.
You must escape from here.
Tang Yin.
He killed himself to extract the soul bone?
Nana.
Brother, I’m sorry. This time...
I won’t let your plan succeed.
What’s going on?
That direction...
Could it be...
What happened just now?
I heard that
when a Century Millennium Soul Beast perishes,
it will create a strong magnetic field.
No way! The Century Millennium Soul Ring...
We have no chance anymore.
Is she going to sacrifice herself?
- It happened to Tang San’s mother too...
- It’s different.
This Flexible Bunny
has used a more deadly way.
She sacrifices not only her life,
but also her soul.
Pardon? Sacrificing her soul?
She has assimilated her soul into the ring
and handed herself over to Tang San.
Under such situation,
regardless of Tang San’s strength
or whether he has reached the level
which needs the soul ring,
the fusion of him and this soul ring
will definitely succeed.
Tang San is different from Tang Hao,
he is far from being a Grand Soul Land Master.
It’s impossible to absorb
the Century Millennium Soul Ring by himself.
How about Xiao Wu?
She will never be reborn again.
Sister Wu,
is this worth it?
It is.
♪ We still have to part ♪
♪ I’m not brave enough to keep you
so I have to say goodbye ♪
Brother, you’re so silly.
♪ In the lost forest, who is crying? ♪
Do you think I’ll live alone when you’re gone?
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
I don’t want you to die.
I want you to be alive.
♪ I risk everything to look for your trace ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ The world in your eyes is shapeless ♪
I really hope to live together with you.
As we did in the past.
But,
it’s impossible now.
Take care of yourself after I’m gone.
Otherwise, I’ll be sad.
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme sadness ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one I dream to comb my hair for ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
For Tang San,
Xiao Wu’s willing to sacrifice herself
to a soul ring.
For Xiao Wu,
Tang San is willing to die
to extract the soul bone.
I see. So, in his heart,
he has had a perfect lover.
♪ Over the sleepless nights ♪
♪ Who is sighing out there ♪
♪ I am still languishing after you ♪
♪ Wistfully missing the four seasons
we have spent together ♪
♪ The sceneries are somberer ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise ♪
♪ I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ It is unforgettable ♪
Farewell, my love.
♪ Hand in hand
we breach the hindrance of destiny ♪
♪ Loving you till eternity ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
Brother.
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one I dream to comb my hair for ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ to envisage our future ♪
♪ Hold my hands ♪
♪ To recall our heartbroken emotions ♪
No...
Xiao Wu...
[We appreciate your accompany with
Soul Land all the way.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]