♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Grandpa is compressing
his soul power forcefully
in order to gain an extreme speed.
He split into seven forms.
Which is his real form?
Why don’t you use your secret weapon
and see if you can stop me?
Xiang!
What are you doing?
But, noble girls wouldn’t
even look at me normally.
One day,
I will revitalize our tribe.
You’d better get rid of all your bad intentions.
Or else, I will hit you whenever I see you!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 145]
In order to help me win Senior Yang Wu Di’s favor,
Granduncle handed me this treasure.
Xiao Wu?
Xiao Wu.
It’s not that I’m not willing to let you eat it.
But, looking at your condition now,
you should take
Decade Millennium Grade Nine Ginseng King.
Crystal Bloody Dragon Ginseng’s effect
is too strong.
I’m afraid you can’t take it.
No!
Xiao Wu!
Xiao Wu.
Can your body
handle this Crystal Bloody Dragon Ginseng?
Looking at Xiao Wu’s expression just now,
this Crystal Bloody Dragon Ginseng
might help her a lot.
In that case,
her revival is more likely to take place.
She must be absorbing the medicinal effect.
Xiao Wu’s choice
must be correct.
Brother San.
Come in.
The Tribe of Destruction is here.
Elder Tai Tan wants to see you.
Xiao Wu.
You might need to suffer for a while.
Brother San.
Perhaps the Chief from the Tribe of Destruction
is not easy to deal with.
He didn’t even want to speak.
As if everyone owed him money.
Be careful of your words.
We shall go and have a look first.
No.
Let me tell you.
Brother San.
It’s him.
Crystal Bloody Dragon Ginseng is gone.
I can only convince Yang Wu Di,
the strongest chief of the Four Tribes,
with my own strength.
Come.
Old Goat.
Let me introduce to you a young friend.
Old Gorilla.
When do you have such a young friend?
This young friend of mine
is not an ordinary man.
Old Goat.
Never underestimate him.
Old Gorilla.
This is a meeting of our Four Tribes.
I hope to see no outsiders here.
I have something
to discuss with you.
Old Goat.
Why are you still the same?
A man brought here by Old Gorilla
must be no outsider.
Alright.
You’re the host.
Even you don’t mind it.
Why would I mind?
Let him stay, then.
Old Goat.
Everyone’s here.
Why do you
still look so gloomy?
It’s all because of the Martial Soul Hall.
They are crossing the line.
The Elephant Armoured Tribe even came
and asked me to join their tribe.
Or else,
they would demolish my Tribe of Destruction.
Old Gorilla.
Old Rhino.
Old White Bird.
If you treat me as your brother,
let us be united
and form a clan
to fight the Martial Soul Hall.
We shall let them know
that the four single attribute tribes
are not so easy to bully.
Why?
Are you afraid?
If our Four Tribes join hands,
we will have almost 1,000 soul masters.
We won’t be weaker
than any of the Lower Four.
Old Goat.
Were you humiliated?
You’re not so impulsive normally.
Humiliated?
I was not only humiliated...
If we don’t take action,
you won’t see me next year.
Old Goat.
Seems like we are
having the same idea.
Now, the Martial Soul Hall is
getting more powerful.
I’m afraid that it will be hard
for a single tribe to survive.
So, in this meeting,
I wanted to discuss
the matter of forming a clan.
That is just right.
I’ve planned it all.
If we want to form a clan,
we shall move to the capital of Xing Luo Empire.
Martial Soul Hall’s power there is not so strong.
The Tribe of Destruction has some savings.
In a short period of time,
we have no problem supporting our livings.
Old Goat.
I don’t think Xing Luo Empire
is a good choice.
Why?
We are not familiar
with the capital of Xing Luo Empire.
None of us have stayed there for a long time.
Old Rhino, Old White Bird and I have discussed it.
We are planning to move to Tian Dou City.
It’s not a problem
to move to your place.
But,
our Tribe of Destruction’s business is
in Xing Luo Empire.
If we move to Tian Dou Empire,
we will have to start over again.
Don’t worry.
It’s not a problem in supporting everyone.
With your Tribe of Strength’s
financial ability alone,
it might be hard to support everyone.
The clan we’ve planned to form
is called Tang Clan.
I just wanted
to introduce to you the Chief.
But you were ignoring him.
He’s the Chief?
This immature guy?
Why is that impossible?
Old Gorilla.
It’s extremely urgent for me now.
Stop joking with me.
Old Goat.
Who joked with you?
Tang San is not only the chief of Tang Clan,
he’s also the son of our master.
What?
[Soul Land]
He is Tang Hao’s son?
Yes.
Old Goat.
What are you doing?
You’ve all yielded to Hao Tian Tribe.
What can I say?
I don’t belong here.
I’ll leave.
Treat it as if I didn’t come here today.
Don’t be reckless.
Don’t you believe us,
your old brothers?
I can stay.
Kick Tang San out first.
And,
don’t mention Tang Clan in front of me.
This...
Senior Yang Wu Di.
Can I say something?
I swore
Hao Tian Tribe would be my enemy forever.
Get out when I can still hold my temper.
Or else,
don’t blame me for killing you.
Granduncle.
Excuse me.
I would like to see how Senior Yang Wu Di
can kill me.
Even an immature kid
dares to yell in front of me!
Old White Bird.
Don’t blame me for offending you.
I won’t kill him outright.
Just fight.
It’s better to fight it out.
Senior Yang Wu Di.
Why don’t we make a bet?
Do you even deserve to make a bet with me?
We bet on how many rounds you can
survive under my attack?
No.
I’m betting on the victory
of the fight between us.
If I defeat you,
please promise me one thing.
If I lose,
you may do whatever you want.
How is it?
An overconfident kid.
I will see
how you can compete with me.
If you win,
I’ll not only promise you one thing.
Even if it’s ten or a hundred things,
or my life.
They all belong to you.
Brother San’s trick works.
I’m here to learn from you, Senior.
Yang Wu Di.
Level 82 Storm Attack Branch’s
Great Soul Land Master.
Tang San.
Level 66 Controlling Branch’s Soul Emperor.
He even has the Century Millennium Soul Ring.
No wonder he was arrogant.
Your martial soul isn’t Hao Tian Hammer?
You will see my Hao Tian Hammer.
This is...
This is my attached soul bone.
Eight Spider Bone.
Little San.
How much power are you still hiding?
He’s so concentrated.
I must
do my best in this battle.
Are you ready?
Please.
Fourth Soul Skill, Blue Silver Cage!
The Tribe of Destruction is good at attacking,
but bad at defending.
The key to victory
is to stop his attack
with restrictions.
First Soul Skill!
Shock!
What a scary momentum.
- Third Soul Skill!
- I almost can’t move.
Burst!
Blue Silver Emperor is not working at all.
It’s Teleport.
I can’t waste my time.
Cluster Soul Chasing Life Taking Balls!
Little tricks.
They’re useless!
Kid.
You finally made me serious.
Seventh Soul Skill, Martial Soul Form!
Old Goat is really serious.
Is he going to destroy my living room?
Blue Silver Emperor Tyrant Spear!
He even fended off my strongest single attack.
Will I lose?
I can only bet on it.
God Killer Attack!
Invincible Golden Shield!
Invincible Golden Shield
can only last for three seconds.
I must...
I can’t dodge it.
He used Invincible Golden Shield
to nullify the attack,
and instantly found the opponent’s weak spot.
Brother San was risking his life to survive.
Chief!
Brother San!
Xiao Wu again?
Brother San has used too much of his spirit power.
He can’t contain Xiao Wu’s soul anymore.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 145 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1396 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2191]
[Total scene: 54633]
[Total CGI: 26855]
[Total plan of action scene: 11852]
[Total scene model: nearly 533]
[Total character model: nearly 990]
[Total props model: 13368]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
You two go to check on Old Goat first.
Leave the Chief to me.
Xiao Wu.
It’s a dream again.
What is this?
I’ve been looking for it my whole life.
I’m finally home.
It’s already noon.
Everyone must be done with his class.
Why are there few people?
[Soul Land]
[Available at 10 AM every Saturday]