♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped by wind♪
♪ Missed the farewell to my lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
We shall depart
to Long Xing Town in Xing Luo Empire
to visit the Tribe of Defense next morning.
Hao Tian Tribe!
Tang Hao!
Have you ever considered us?
Dad.
Are we really going to be an affiliated tribe
to the Martial Soul Hall?
Stop right there!
We’ve been looking for you for a long time.
Now you come to us instead.
Brother San.
I don’t need your help.
I can settle it by myself.
Fatty.
You overestimate yourself.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 141]
Fatty.
You overestimate yourself.
Second Soul Skill, Firing Bathing Phoenix!
Third Soul Skill,
Fiery Palm of Destruction!
This again?
Phoenix Firing Line!
Did you forget?
Your martial soul is restrained by me.
Kneel down and surrender to me now.
I might spare your life.
My martial soul has evolved.
Wanna see my new trick?
How is that possible?
Sixth Soul Skill,
Dragon Killer Sword!
He’s using
the sixth soul skill,
Dragon Killer Sword, right away.
This should be the most powerful attack
of Tian Ya so far.
With the Sensitivity Soul Master,
E Kao’s coordination,
I’m not sure if Fatty can handle it.
You, stupid
man!
Stay steady!
Fifth Soul Skill, Formless Attack!
It’s the Soul Skill Lockdown.
How about...
I can’t see anything.
You! Bu Le!
We’re in the dark fog too!
Bring it on!
You cunning fatty!
Damn it!
Take this hit!
Flaming right arm soul bone skill!
Bursting Phoenix!
Fatty!
No!
Hey!
Bu Le!
Do you still want to fight?
Not anymore.
Alright.
I won’t kill you.
You beat me.
But I did the same to you.
You and I,
we are even now.
Then, may I
go now?
No.
We’ve settled
our grudge.
But...
what about the things you did to them?
Fatty.
I need to talk to you.
Actually,
I don’t really hate you.
Come on!
Just go!
Fatty!
I can’t defeat you
but I can disgust you!
You’re still immature.
The problem is
that you’ve not only disgusted him,
but also me.
How much is this?
This one?
It’s cheap.
Fatty.
You’ve changed
a lot in the past few years.
You bet.
My soul power has improved,
so has my appearance.
Don’t get too carried away.
But now
you don’t just
aim at winning in a fight.
You know the meaning of protection.
I’m impressed.
I’m overwhelmed.
In the championship,
you risked your life to fight against the Martial Soul Hall
to protect Sister Wu.
I feel ashamed
after thinking about that.
Ashamed?
Ashamed.
I had chased so many people
but I was never serious about anyone.
Alright.
Fatty,
it’s good that you understand now.
Later,
I’ll write a letter to Boss Dai
and ask him
to send the gang of Bu Le
to Xing Luo Empire for a trial.
Look at this.
So peaceful.
I’m not sure how long this can last.
Hello.
Greetings, Leader Tai Tan.
Tribe of Strength, welcome to my tribe.
You’re welcome.
Is Old Rhino here?
Our tribe chief is here.
Wait a minute.
I’ve sent someone to inform him.
Old Gorilla!
I could hear your loud voice
even when I was inside.
How dare you call me by my nickname?
You’re unhappy about it?
Shall we have a fight
if you think you can do it?
If you win,
I won’t call you Old Rhino anymore.
How is that?
This is
the Chief from the Tribe of Defense.
Not bad. Old Gorilla.
You have had greater strength.
Well...
I’m not as strong as you are,
but you can forget about
breaking these old bones of mine.
I know you’re tough.
Tai Long.
Come here.
Greet Grandpa Niu Gao.
Nice meeting you.
Grandpa Niu.
Tai Long.
You’re firm.
You do look like your grandfather
when he was young.
I think
you’ll have greater achievement
than your father.
Tai Nuo
is slightly thinner.
You call that...
thin?!
Let’s go.
Why aren’t you bringing us in yet?
We’ve waited here for so long.
I forgot as I was so excited to see you.
Let’s go!
Get in!
I’ve prepared
your favorite liquor.
Tonight,
we shall all get drunk.
[Soul Land]
Master San.
Why is Tai Long
being so polite to this guy?
Old Gorilla.
You haven’t introduced these two young men to me.
They don’t look like people from your tribe.
They are good friends of my grandson.
They studied at the same school.
I’m bringing them with me
to gain more experience.
Old Gorilla.
Why bother to hide from me?
Who exactly is this guy?
Why are you bringing him to our gathering?
Senior Niu Gao.
Hello.
I’m Tang San.
My father is Tang Hao.
What?
Old Gorilla.
What’s this about?
Hao Tian Tribe has brought us
enough suffering.
If it wasn’t for Tang Hao,
we wouldn’t end up like this.
Old Rhino.
Calm down.
Do you think the Martial Soul Hall
would leave Hao Tian Tribe in peace
without that matter of our master?
We hate Hao Tian Tribe, too.
They abandoned us, their subordinates.
But, what does that have to do with Tang San?
Old Gorilla!
If he wasn’t brought in here by you,
I would chase him out right away!
Ask him to leave!
Or else,
don’t blame me for being rude.
You...
Alright.
We’ll leave together.
We, Tribe of Strength,
won’t attend this gathering!
Senior!
Wait a minute.
Senior Niu Gao.
I would like to apologize for
what my father and Hao Tian Tribe did to
the four single attribute tribes.
I know.
My apology can’t change anything.
I’m here
to look for a way
to compensate these Four Tribes.
Has Hao Tian Tribe stopped being secluded?
The tribe is still closed,
I’m representing only me and my father,
not Hao Tian Tribe.
The status of Hao Tian Tribe
is none of our business.
We are doing well now.
We don’t need your compensation.
Moreover, what a brat like you can do
to compensate us?
Senior Niu Gao,
I hope you will give me a chance
to stay here
and attend this gathering.
A chance?
When Hao Tian Tribe announced their closure,
did they give us, the Four Tribes, a chance?
When your father
fought against the Martial Soul Hall,
did he ever consider our well-being?
Why shall I give you a chance? Huh?
Get lost!
Or else,
I’ll kick you out!
What a strong force!
It only affects my body
but I can’t move.
Old Rhino!
Senior Tai Tan.
I’ll settle it by myself.
God Killer Domain!
He can resist my force?
He’s indeed the son of Tang Hao.
Alright.
It’s okay if you want to stay.
You and I compete here.
As long as you can withstand my power
for half an hour,
you can not only stay,
our grudge
will also be wiped off the board.
Do you mean it?
I am the chief of a tribe.
Do you think I’ll break my promise?
Very good.
Seems like
we won’t have to leave today.
Old Gorilla.
Are you so confident about him?
My soul power
has reached Level 84 in the past two years.
How old is he?
As I said,
he has to withstand my attack for half an hour.
Old Rhino.
Don’t say that I didn’t remind you.
Tang San’s talent
surpasses
his father’s.
Old Gorilla speaks so highly of him.
He must be good.
Senior Niu Gao,
you’re the elder.
Why don’t we make it simple?
What do you mean?
Fatty.
Draw a circle on the ground with your fire.
A slightly bigger one.
What does this mean?
Senior.
This circle is the battle field.
We shall only use our soul power.
No martial soul skills are allowed.
If I manage to stay
in this circle for half an hour,
you’ll let me stay.
How is it?
Master San.
Grandpa Niu’s skill of defense
is the best on this continent.
And his soul power is much powerful than yours.
You’re in a unfavorable situation.
Young man.
You’re so arrogant.
How do I dare to be arrogant
in front of you two seniors?
I just hope that we can finish this nicely.
Alright.
Let’s do as you said.
Senior.
Please.
The battle begins!
Boy!
You first.
Alright then.
Senior, watch out!
Boy!
Are you kidding me?
Master San, be careful!
Boy.
Game ends.
Accumulate the energy into a single spot
and let it explode.
This is the enhanced skill of
the God Killer Domain.
God Killer Attack!
Not bad.
I won’t be nice to you anymore.
He’s doomed.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 141 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1368 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2129]
[Total scene: 53323]
[Total CGI: 26475]
[Total plan of action scene: 11466]
[Total scene model: nearly 530]
[Total character model: nearly 979]
[Total props model: 13366]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
Are you going to let us
experience another catastrophe?
What’s wrong?
I’m afraid
that the whole soul master world
will be totally renewed very soon.
The Martial Soul Hall has issued a decree.
One year later,
they will re-select the Seven Great Tribes.
As long as you agree, Big Brother,
your tribe and mine will co-operate.
The title of the Deputy Chief of
the Elephant Armoured Tribe
will be yours.
You guys!
How could you not wait for me
to enjoy such good wine?
[Soul Land]
[Available at 10 AM every Saturday]