♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Emperor Xue Ye is about to die.
Hurry and come with me to the palace.
It turns out Tang Yin is Tang San.
Stay in the palace and help me.
Gold, beautiful women, nobility,
and even soul rings and soul bones,
I can give you everything.
Xue Qing He.
Do you think that I would follow
a traitor who killed his own father and ruler?
But don’t you understand？
You’ve revealed all my plans.
I definitely won’t let you go.
[Episode 153]
A poisonous thorn.
Potent poison!
Grand Venom Master.
Don’t try to resist.
Your poison is useless
against them.
This stupid suppression on my soul power.
I need to wait for a better chance.
Dugu Bo!
Come become my nourishment!
It’s useless.
I will absorb all the poison.
Die!
Is that so?
Old Freak!
Dugu Bo.
The more you struggle,
the faster I absorb your soul power.
Another one here volunteer to die.
Do you still not understand?
Poison will only increase my power.
Then let’s see if you have
that big of an appetite!
Old Freak!
Use poison!
Useless resistance!
Damn it!
Yang Wudi.
You’re a Great Soul Land Master after all.
I underestimated you.
A Great Soul Land Master
is that powerful and domineering?
Third Soul Skill, Broken Shadows!
Seventh Soul Skill, Martial Soul Form!
Blue Silver Domain.
God Killer Domain.
A double domain
to weaken your opponent
and boost your teammates.
With the support of these domains,
Grand Bloody Thorn Master’s power
is completely restricted.
Fifth Soul Skill,
Break!
Now’s the time.
Fourth Soul Skill, Blue Silver Cage!
Seventh Soul Skill, Martial Soul Form!
Again!
In your dreams!
Fifth Soul Skill,
Exploding Thunder Kill!
Can’t avoid it.
Break!
Invincible Golden Shield!
Tang San.
You always manage to create miracles.
But...
do you think you’ll get lucky again today?
Charge!
Even if you use the signal flare,
no one will come to rescue you
because the Qibao Amber Tribe and the Shrek
have been surrounded.
They won’t even be able to save themselves.
What?
Why don’t we...
have a negotiation?
About what?
Tang San.
Very soon, I will inherit the throne
and become the new ruler of Tian Dou Empire.
As long as you submit to me,
you can ask for whatever you want.
I can even make you more powerful
than anyone else in the Tian Dou Empire,
second only to one.
I admit.
Your conditions are very tempting.
But
I don’t think you will agree
to the conditions I suggest.
You’re still underestimating
how much I can take.
Maybe
I will agree with you.
I have two conditions.
First,
kill everyone
that attacked me and Xiao Wu in the Star Forest
in front of me.
Including the Grand Chrysanthemum Master
and the Grand Ghost Master.
Can you do that?
I can take
this one
but only after you become a Grand Soul Land Master.
When you can bring me
more benefits than those two elders do,
I will live up to my promise.
As for everyone else,
I remember Hu Liena didn’t attack you.
Besides her,
I’ll have the rest all killed.
[Tian Dou Empire] [Lima Plain] [Silves Kingdom]
[Barak Kingdom] [Fassnor Province]
[Soul Land]
Xue Qing He can make decisions
on behalf of the Martial Soul Hall just like that?
The two Grand Soul Land Masters
not only didn’t object at all,
but they’re also afraid to offend him.
Could it be...?
Tang San.
This is enough to prove my sincerity, right?
How can I believe you will keep your promise?
I’m not afraid to tell you
my real name is not Xue Qing He,
and I’m not the actual son of Xue Ye.
As a matter of fact,
your father is the one that killed my father.
I can even leave that kind of hatred behind.
Can this prove it?
Do you mean
you are the son
of the Martial Soul Hall’s former pope?
Tang San.
I’ve already answered your question.
Tell me your second condition.
I think
either my authority
in the Martial Soul Hall or the Tian Dou Empire,
is enough to fulfill any wish of yours.
My parents
were hunted down by the Martial Soul Hall.
In the end, my mother died a terrible death
and my father was kicked out of his clan
losing everything.
As long as you avenge them for me
and destroy the entire Martial Soul Hall,
submitting to you
is not a big deal.
Are you fooling me?
I’d rather die for justice
than submit to evil.
How could I compromise with you?
The Martial Soul Hall
is my enemy for life!
Tang San.
I will give you one last chance.
To submit
or to be destroyed?
I will also answer you one more time.
Go!
Seventh Soul Skill, Martial Soul Form!
Alright.
I will let you die as you wish.
Seventh Soul Skill, Martial Soul Form!
The tool soul form has turned into a soul beast.
Teacher said before
that these unique martial soul forms
are mutated from martial souls.
They have both a beast soul’s
increase in power
and the tenacity of a tool soul,
which are top of the top.
Seventh Soul Skill, Martial Soul Form!
This is the Six-winged Angel Martial Soul.
Such an overwhelming sense of holiness.
Innate Domain.
If we fight above ground,
Xue Qing He’s domain
might affect Old Freak
and Senior Yang Wudi.
When did he learn how to fly?
First Soul Skill, Angel Attack!
Xuan Yu Hand.
God Killer Domain!
We have to win
or else the Tian Dou Empire
will be controlled by the Martial Soul Hall.
The only way to stay alive against him
is to outwit him.
God Killer Domain, nice.
Even though your God Killer Domain
happens to counterbalance
my Angel Domain,
it’s a pity
that an Innate Domain only truly awakens
after the master of the Seventh Soul Skill.
Only through your martial soul form
can the domain truly release its effect.
What?
Let me show you
the true power of an Innate Domain.
Seventh Soul Skill, Martial Soul Form!
This is the real Angel Domain.
I can feel my soul power
being cleansed and weakened again.
If we can’t break this domain,
I will die once my soul power is depleted.
Do you see the difference between us now?
Tang San.
This is my domain.
I am the ruler.
Is this...
what you truly are?
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 153 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1452 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2311]
[Total scene: 56989]
[Total CGI: 27350]
[Total plan of action scene: 12219]
[Total scene model: nearly 552]
[Total character model: nearly 995]
[Total props model: 13376]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I’m faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven’t told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
I didn’t expect you
to have a bright side as well.
Everyone has their own judgment
about righteousness and evil.
The winner
is always upright
and the one brings light.
I have no soul power left.
I will always remember you.
Tang San.
Goodbye.
[Soul Land]
[10 AM every Saturday]