CLASS A VS CLASS B
Class A and Class B of U.A. High School
are having joint battle training.
In the fourth battle, Class A displayed
great teamwork with Kacchan as their main force,
and secured an overwhelming victory.
Now we proceed with the fifth battle!
This is the last battle of the day.
Are you ready?
Do not let your guard down until the very end!
Start!
♪When we are stranded on the same spot,
make our heart beat♪
MY HERO ACADEMIA
♪Rather than searching for an answer
in this world full of uncertainties♪
♪I want to live even though
my constant doubts are a waste of time♪
♪Take off the unseeable armor and feel the wind♪
♪I make my effort sound worthless
as a way to hide myself♪
♪The No.1 who came out of nowhere
is pointing at the endless sky♪
♪It's our desire to see the view
from greater height and distance♪
♪Ignite the heart of unquenchable desire♪
♪Ignite the path to our future,
burn the illusions to ashes♪
It's No. 1541.
He's on the move again.
It's happened so many times since yesterday.
I hope the verdict and execution
can be done as soon as possible.
At this rate, we won't be able to keep up.
Do you think taking one life make you a murderer
but taking millions of lives makes you a hero?
Is that a line from Chaplin's movie?
It just happened recently.
Gigantomachia.
He served All For One directly.
It's not just Shigaraki's League of Villains.
Who knows how many are sharing
the same ideal with this guy?
It's best not to provoke them for now.
Oh my, I'm sorry for the trouble I caused.
The nostalgia is giving me an itch.
I can hear my little brother's voice.
THAT WHICH IS INHERITED
You have a phone call...
"ALL MIGHT, QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL"
Excuse me.
"MIDNIGHT, QUIRK: SOMNAMBULIST"
Just hang up the phone.
GRAND TORINO
Sorry, but I have to answer this call.
I appreciate you calling me so soon.
But I'm in the middle of a lesson.
It's about Izuku Midoriya's dream.
Have you started talking just now?
"GRAN TORINO: QUIRK: JET"
You asked me whether Shimura said
anything about One For All's visage.
Since you asked, it actually jogged my memory.
But it's from a time so long ago.
So don't expect too much from me.
It happened soon after
Shimura inherited One For All.
Listen to me, Gran Torino.
I had a weird dream last night.
A dream?
Yeah. A dark and misty guy appeared
right before me.
That guy looked at me and said,
"It's not the right time yet."
Well, that's about it.
Thank you, sir.
Excuse me, but I'm still in the middle
of a class. I must hang up now.
"It's not the right time yet."
That means, the time will come sooner or later.
Has One For All's heir
"IZUKU MIDORIYA, QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL"
inherited something else?
Class B has Shinso on their team.
I mustn't talk to him when we meet.
I'm still wary about One For All's secrets.
I can't afford to be brainwashed by Shinso.
Ever since I was a kid,
people have been telling me
I could never become a superhero with my Quirk.
"HITOSHI SHINSO, QUIRK: BRAINWASH"
Why are you telling us now?
I mean, I know I can't do it by myself.
I won't last long if their Quirks
aren't compatible.
I do admire you.
We share quite the similarities.
I don't like that.
But that's a fact.
How did you manage to brainwash Midoriya?
How did you make him talk to you?
I didn't know what kind of person he was,
so I mocked his classmates.
In order to become a hero,
we have to act the other way around.
Otherwise,
we won't be able to overcome
the power that can do anything.
Our goal will become unclear.
Have you felt this before?
Your childhood dream and hope
slowly became your burden as you grow older.
It's like a curse.
The formation of Midoriya's team
"TENYA IDA, QUIRK: ENGINE"
is similar to Bakugo's team.
"HANTA SERO, QUIRK: TAPE"
They share the same team balance.
But Jiro's role...
I was the scout of my team.
They don't have a scout.
They must be more cautious
so the enemies don't decimate them.
"KYOKA JIRO, QUIRK: EARPHONE JACK"
You have a point.
If they want to bait the enemies
to locate them,
"KATSUKI BAKUGO, QUIRK: EXPLOSION"
Midoriya has to take more risk than Bakugo did.
I need to draw their attention
and act as a decoy.
I doubt Class B can overlook my speed.
I will draw their attacks.
That should help me locate them.
Then our team can proceed with the capturing.
They are here!
It's Yanagi's Quirk, Poltergeist!
Monoma's here!
Oh my, you found me.
After seeing Bakugo's coordination,
we're going to just ignore you.
Being wary of a strong and agile opponent
is what normally the smart would think.
But anyone smart enough
would also think otherwise.
Bakugo did so well because
of their excellent teamwork.
This is why we should take down
the other three first.
I bet you drew our attention to locate us.
But on the other hand, my teammates
are almost in range to attack yours.
He is provoking me.
Perhaps he already copied Shinso's Quirk.
It's three against four.
Are you sure they can hold up?
We also have Shinso on our team.
You can get into contact unnoticed.
Perhaps you should go to your teammates now.
Wait.
What if the screaming was Shinso's voice?
Then you had already exposed the location
of your team.
This must be troubling for you.
That was cold. You didn't bother
to look at your teammates' direction!
He is trying to locate them
with my line of sight. I won't fall for it!
Such a nuisance.
Class B, Neito Monoma.
Hero name: Phantom Thief.
Quirk: Copy.
Once he touches the target,
he can use their Quirk freely for five minutes.
But he can't use two Quirks at the same time.
He is using Yanagi's Quirk!
Release.
"MINORU MINETA, QUIRK: POP OFF"
The noises just now...
"OCHACOO URARAKA, QUIRK: ZERO GRAVITY"
It wasn't me.
Was it Shinso? He's closing in.
"MINA ASHIDO, QUIRK: ACID"
I'd love to see his dull face
when he starts yelling for help!
Please look at us when you talk.
I got something.
Acid Veil!
It's gone.
Did they block it? Or was it a trap?
It's Yanagi's poltergeist!
She is attacking blindly!
Class B, Reiko Yanagi.
Hero name: Emily.
Quirk: Poltergeist.
She can control objects around her,
but the maximum load is about
the weight of a person.
Class B, Yui Kodai.
Hero name: Rule.
Quirk: Size.
It's the ability to manipulate
the sizes of objects.
But she can't use the Quirk on creatures.
Release.
Twin Impact!
Fire!
I can roughly tell where they are heading.
Class B, Nirengeki Shoda.
Hero name: Mines.
Quirk: Twin Impact.
His Quirk allows him to strike a target and
inflict a second impact on the point of contact.
The second impact is several times
stronger than the initial blow.
Split up. Don't let them spot you.
I am reloading the second batch.
That was scary.
Where is Midoriya?
He's supposed to be our decoy.
They might have caught our location
from the attack just now.
Where is Deku?
I talked to Shinso.
The privileged will bring the world to ruins.
Since you're his friend, then tell me.
How can Bakugo
laugh as if nothing is happening?
He was captured by the villains.
Wasn't he the one who destroyed
our symbol of peace?
That guy looked at me and said,
"It's not the right time yet."
The right time. But when is it?
What's going on?
He has more abilities I didn't know.
This is getting annoying.
Why? What is this?
Everything was normal up until just now.
Run!
Shinso!
Shinso...
Run!
I can't...
control this power!
I can't hold it anymore!
What is that?
Deku!
What is going on? Stop it!
What is this? Stop it!
It hurts!
Why?
Midoriya has a new attack.
Aizawa, Vlad!
We should stop him now.
"SHOTA AIZAWA, QUIRK: ERASURE"
Something is not right.
Why?!
Ever since I inherited the Quirk from All Might,
There are too many things I don't understand
while I was badly injured.
Stop it now!
Even so...
I finally learned to control this power!
Stop it now! One For All!
I don't want to make anyone worry again!
Deku! Calm down!
NEITO MONOMA, QUIRK: COPY
HE CAN COPY THE QUIRK OF THE TARGET HE TOUCHES
FOR FIVE MINUTES
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH SCHOOL CLASS 1-B,
BIRTHDAY: MAY 13
HEIGHT: 170 CM, BLOOD TYPE: A,
FAVORITE THINGS: FRENCH FOOD AND COMICS
OCHACCO URARAKA, QUIRK: ZERO GRAVITY,
THE ABILITY TO REMOVE THE GRAVITY
ON ANYTHING OR PERSON SHE TOUCHES.
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH SCHOOL,
BIRTHDAY: DECEMBER 27
HEIGHT: 156 CM, BLOOD TYPE: B,
FAVORITE FOOD: JAPANESE CUISINES
My parents always looked so exhausted.
It pains me to see them so tired.
When I first witnessed the mission
of a pro hero...
Compared to the hero that saved the day,
I'm more attracted to the cheers of the crowd.
I like to see the happiness on their faces.
In my eyes, helping those in need is my duty.
And that duty...
could come with great risks and challenges.
Even if I try my best,
he never stops helping those in danger.
And that inspires me.
Deku!
Who is there to protect the heroes
when they are in need?
I can't control it at all!
This isn't Deku's doing.
Shinso!
Brainwash him now!
Help me stop Deku's rampage!
She wants me to brainwash Midoriya...
But what should I say?
You defeated me on the sports day.
I've been excited since then.
I want you to see how much I've grown.
I've looked forward to meeting you
in a battle.
I want to become a true hero
that saves lives with my Quirk!
Midoriya!
Fight me!
Very well!
I'm here again.
Hey, you!
Are you kidding me?
No!
Didn't I tell you?
I told you you weren't alone!
I told you the time had come.
Haven't you noticed?
However,
this power...
is not something you can control
while your mind is full of distractions.
He was one of the heirs...
You need to work harder!
If you work hard enough,
you can figure out most of the problems!
Can't you talk?
Don't mind!
I can see him so clearly...
This is more than just a blurry visage.
It's not a dream either.
This man...
These people...
Are they all living inside One For All?
It seems like we're running out of time.
Hey, young man.
The power you wield right now is my Quirk.
Our Quirk factors are mixed up
inside the core of this power.
They have existed inside
One For All's tiny core.
It's like a flickering flame.
Or you could say it's like a dot
on the glittering water.
It's been buried under the power you've
cultivated so far. This is its primal state.
That core is now expanding.
It's begun to move.
Like a flickering image in the crevice,
the power of One For All...
is growing.
What is going on?
Hey.
Were you trying to capture or grab that target?
I bet that was your plan.
I wanted to capture Monoma.
The best Quirk that responds to that thought
is my Quirk, Blackwhip.
You should be grateful I'm the first one
you've ever met.
This is a wonderful Quirk.
However,
due to the accumulated power of One For All,
this Quirk is much stronger
than when I wielded it.
Well, I'm disappearing now.
I used to float around like a specter.
That's because my consciousness
is what's left of me.
Listen closely. If you use the power with rage,
it answers your call.
So your priority...
is to control your mind.
Having rage is a good thing.
It's the source of power.
That's all the more reason
to focus on controlling your rage.
After being held by eight users,
One For All is powerful beyond imagination.
Listen closely, young man.
Another six Quirks will manifest in your
in the future.
Learn to master your mind,
use these abilities as yours.
All the best, young man!
We're watching over you!
The only one who can make One For All whole...
is you!
Deku!
Did that hurt?
Uraraka...
Stay away from me!
It's too dangerous!
Don't worry.
Shinso's brainwash calmed you down.
Shinso...
Are you all right?
Uraraka, you're hurt!
My goodness, what have I done?
Gunhead Martial Arts!
The match is not over yet!
Release.
Fire!
Those rampaging black tentacles
ruined our attack plan.
Nice timing!
Are you all right?
What was that just now?
I found you! Eat this!
Midoriya! Uraraka! Are you all right?
Everyone is here!
Let's get ready to rumble!
Eat this!
If you use the power with rage,
it answers your call.
So your priority is to control your mind.
I can't let anyone else get hurt.
What should I do now?
I feel like my mind is going to explode!
Eraser Head, how should we proceed?
All Might.
Let's observe for a little while.
Aizawa, what do you mean?
The fifth battle...
should proceed.
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪I hope my destination♪
♪Is where we shall meet again♪
♪I'm always seeing the world through your eyes♪
♪Tears are somehow falling down my cheeks♪
♪I hate it when you say it's all right♪
♪Your gentle whisper turned
into an unsettling silence♪
♪I want to believe the clouded sky before us♪
♪Our longing is the very thing that breaks us♪
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪But why? I'm already covered in wounds♪
♪Why must I search for the answer♪
♪Goodbye, we will meet again♪
♪I hope you would still be the same♪
♪I hope that the memories we share♪
♪Would once again bank up♪
♪So I could see you again♪
Next episode!
One For All went on a rampage.
It's too risky to use the Quirk again.
But I'm not giving up on the battle.
Shinso and Monoma aren't going to
give up either.
I must give it my all,
for my team, and to secure our victory!
Next episode, Our Brawl!
Remember why you took on this path!
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!