Why?
What is this?
Aizawa! Vlad!
We should stop him now.
It's not looking good.
Deku, calm down!
Shinso!
Brainwash him now!
Help me stop Deku!
Midoriya!
Fight me!
Yes!
Release.
Fire!
Nice timing!
Are you two all right?
Eat this!
Midoriya! Uraraka! Are you all right?
Everyone is here.
Let's get ready to rumble!
Eat this!
I can't let my teammates get hurt again.
What should I do?
My mind is overloading!
♪When we are stranded on the same spot,
make our hearts beat♪
MY HERO ACADEMIA
♪Rather than searching for an answer
in this world full of uncertainties♪
♪I want to live even though my constant doubts
are a waste of time♪
♪Take off the unseeable armor and feel the wind♪
♪I make my effort sound worthless
as a way to hide myself♪
♪The No.1 who came out of nowhere
is pointing at the endless sky♪
♪It's our desire to see the view
from greater height and distance♪
♪Ignite the heart of unquenchable desire♪
♪Ignite the path to our future,
burn the illusions to ashes♪
Eraser Head, what should we do?
SHOTA AIZAWA, QUIRK: ERASURE"
ALL MIGHT, QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL
All Might.
We should observe for now.
Aizawa, what are you saying?
The fifth battle
should continue as usual.
"VLAD KING, QUIRK: BLOOD CONTROL"
Continue?
No matter how you see it,
Midoriya was acting very strange.
If it happens again, I will put a stop to him.
Shinso managed to stop him
with brainwashing.
If it's still part of Midoriya's Quirk,
I can stop it.
Aizawa, why?
They want to continue the battle.
Both Midoriya...
and Shinso.
No, not just the two of them.
All of them desire...
to win this battle.
You are surprisingly optimistic.
You're right.
"OCHACCO URARAKA, QUIRK: ZERO GRAVITY"
Deku's strength
was outmatched!
IZUKU MIDORIYA, QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL
I can't use my Quirk right now.
I might put everyone else in danger.
We should retreat and regroup.
If we fall back, we lose.
Shinso is right before us.
"HITOSHI SHINSO, QUIRK: BRAINWASH"
This is our chance to win!
But...
Wouldn't that mean you have to fight
without using your Quirk?
No.
Uraraka, I need a favor from you.
OUR BRAWL!
Acid Shot!
Enlarge!
We can't keep taking damages.
Twin Impact!
Fire!
"MINORU MINETA, QUIRK: POP OFF"
Grape Buckler!
Mineta!
The ball can stick to any surface,
but only I can bounce them off!
The balls I laid down are
traps for everyone else,
but they are platforms for me!
I calculated everything.
I knew I couldn't withstand Twin Impact's power.
I knew this would happen too!
Stop messing around!
Give me a break! Acid Layback!
Grape-Pinky Combo!
Mineta Bounce!
"REIKO YANAGI, QUIRK: POLTERGEIST"
This is bad!
Stop dodging!
"NIRENGEKI SHODA, QUIRK: TWIN IMPACT"
We have to retreat.
"YUI KODAI, QUIRK: SIZE"
But he is moving too quickly!
We have no chance to devise a counter-attack!
That's right.
Mineta and the others are doing well!
Ashido can be in range if they close in!
She is amazing!
"KOSEI TSUBURABA, QUIRK: SOLID AIR"
Shoda alone must protect
"SHISHIDA JUROTA, QUIRK: BEAST"
the other two who can handle close combat.
The number advantage became their disadvantage.
"KYOKA JIRO, QUIRK: EARPHONE JACK"
Should the teachers stop them?
Midoriya and Uraraka are...
"NEITO MONOMA, QUIRK: COPY"
You can't become stronger on your own.
I can only copy others' Quirks.
I don't have the qualities
to be in the spotlight.
But I never hated my Quirk.
Every masterpiece has a side character
that can outshine the main protagonist!
Your power...
Could it be...
I'm taking it!
Is he copying One For All?
A weak body can't handle the sheer might.
The body will explode into a million pieces.
No, Monoma! Don't do it!
You're too late!
Gunhead Martial Art!
It's not your Quirk! He was tricking you!
Run!
I couldn't activate it.
Curse it, it was a bluff!
Monoma!
Release.
This is my first fight with
you after the sports day!
Isn't that right, Midoriya?
If Shinso gets away, the enemy
will have the upper hand later on.
You're a great threat, Shinso!
Eraser Head, Midoriya is on the move.
I'm watching him.
That hurts...
If Eraser Head used six years to master it,
can I really use it at will?
I had to learn from scratch on my own.
Having the tips makes a huge difference.
People like you and me,
if we can't defend ourselves during
critical moments, we'll die for sure.
Practice as I say.
I am not...
going to waste my time on useless matters.
I'm different now.
I should use the binding cloth sooner.
Sorry...
I must become a real hero with my own strength.
Midoriya!
He is different from earlier.
My doubts and insecurities are gone.
What's important is to control your heart.
His aura and voice...
He shared so many resemblances with All Might.
Control your heart.
Use our power as your own extension!
IZUKU MIDORIYA, QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL
THE INHERITED POWER CAN CRUSH HIS ENEMIES
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH SCHOOL CLASS 1-A
BIRTHDAY: JULY 15, HEIGHT: 166CM
BLOOD TYPE: O, FAVORITE THINGS: PORK BOWL RICE
HITOSHI SHINSO, QUIRK: BRAINWASH
HE CAN CONTROL PEOPLE WHO REPLY HIS SPEECH
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH SCHOOL GENERAL EDUCATION
BIRTHDAY: JULY 1, HEIGHT: 177CM
BLOOD TYPE: AB, FAVORITE THINGS: CATS
My doubts and insecurities
for the power are gone.
This new power is my comrade.
I must control my heart.
You can become a hero.
All Might said that to me.
My training with him at the bay park...
My starting line...
Just remembering these...Whenever it is,
I feel invincible.
Wait.
Why?
He seems different now.
He relies on Young Uraraka's Quirk
to focus on his own power.
What happened in the last few minutes?
Young Midoriya...
Come on, what was it just now?
Was your rampage just an act?
You've disrespected my spirit!
It's gone.
That power...
It disappeared in an instant.
It's a pain that comes from within.
Due to the accumulated power by One For All,
this Quirk has become much stronger
than when I wielded it.
The new power is too much
for my body to withstand.
This isn't the power I can control
with 20% of my max output.
I can feel it deeply.
This power exists before One For All.
It's a power I can only master after
having total control over One For All.
But even so, using inaccurate air blasts
might trigger another rampage.
If I use One For All at 8%...
Under these circumstances,
Midoriya won't be brainwashed.
Sorry, Monoma.
Don't you resent Midoriya?
If we show the slightest mistake,
we'll fall like the last team
after he breaks through our formation.
So we should deal with Midoriya first.
Either the way, we have no chance
unless we can take him out.
We're counting on you, Shinso.
I wasted the opening you created for me.
But I won't let this be game over for us!
It seems like the Poltergeist missed.
It's been around five minutes
since the battle started.
Monoma can only copy a Quirk for five minutes.
Maybe my Quirk can last for ten minutes.
If I attack now, can you beat me on your own?
Oh my, you thought of everything.
She is wary of Shinso's Quirk.
Do you know how many Quirks
I can copy at a time?
I can confirm he copied Yanagi's Poltergeist
and Kodai's Size.
Finally, he will need Shinso's Brainwash
to execute their plan.
Three Quirks at a time?
Is it because I have three timers on me?
If I pretended to only copy three Quirks,
what would you do if I started using
a fourth Quirk?
I can copy different Quirks.
I can't activate them all at once,
but there are residue power I can use.
Except for power that affects the body,
most Quirk effects can last.
Such as Kodai's Size.
Even after activating other Quirks
after I enlarged the bolt, its size remains.
Do you not get what I mean?
This is the "fire".
This is the last struggle of a side character.
What did Monoma do to Deku?
But...
Uraraka, I need a favor from you.
I need you to make me weightless.
I'll close in on Shinso.
I leave Monoma to you.
Afterward, regroup with Ashido and Mineta.
Don't worry about me.
I can't win him in direct combat.
Then I must lure him into my field!
He's too fast! He's catching up!
Fire.
Twin Impact.
It creates a second impact on
the point of impact.
Shinso, I apologize for getting caught so soon.
Did I manage to create an opening?
Monoma...
Could it be...
He used Shoda's Quirk at that instant!
And they say I have a dexterous physique.
Things should be easier after we took
one of them down!
"EIJIRO KIRISHIMA, QUIRK: HARDENING"
It's not looking good for Ashido.
"TOGARU KAMAKIRI, QUIRK: RAZOR SHARP"
Good job, Shoda!
You can turn the battle around!
Remember...
Remember the starting line...
at all time!
Reiko!
Kodai! Yanagi!
Don't worry about me.
Don't worry.
We can win!
Curse it.
I've been looking forward to this fight.
I want to show you how strong I've become.
But everyone has moved forward.
They never stop moving forward.
They go beyond!
Plus Ultra?
Curse it.
The Hero Course is amazing.
WELCOME
There was come close calls during the battle.
But the fifth battle is over.
The match is over.
"MIDNIGHT, QUIRK: SOMNAMBULIST"
All of you managed to anticipate enemy attacks.
"THE BIAS BROADCAST IS STILL VERY APPARENT"
You performed well.
"WE WANT VLAD KING REMOVED FROM BROADCASTING"
We'll announce the result now.
Class A won the first battle.
Class B won the second battle.
The third battle ended in a tie.
Class A won the fourth battle.
Class A also won the fifth battle.
The victor of this joint training...
is Class 1-A!
I wasn't really that competitive.
"KINOKO KOMORI, QUIRK: MUSHROOM"
I know, but this feels bad.
"IBARA SHIOZAKI, QUIRK: VINES"
Almost everyone was very tactful in battles.
Sir.
I can't achieve anything on my own.
I still have a long way to go.
This joint training also serves
as my entrance test, right?
You knew all along?
Did you tell him?
No.
But I could tell based on
the timing and form of this training.
The lack of communication devices
makes it easier to test my skill.
Not to mention only I joined both teams.
Either the way, we still have a post mortem.
You should get ready.
The post mortem starts now.
First of all, Midoriya,
what happened to you just now?
FUMIKAGE TOKOYAMI, QUIRK: DARK SHADOW
You showed some dark manifestation.
"SHIHAI KUROIRO, QUIRK: DARK"
You lost control, but the manoeuvre was...
Was it a new move?
That was way beyond the limit of raw strength.
Honestly,
I still don't quite understand what it was.
The power was surging,
and I couldn't control it.
It was as though the very thing I trusted
had backfired at me.
I was terrified too.
But Uraraka and Shinso stopped my rampage.
That helped me realize it wasn't as I thought.
If Shinso hadn't brainwashed me,
things would have become worse.
Shinso, you asked whether it was a trick or not.
But at that moment, I had no idea either.
Thank you, both of you.
I only said that because
I wanted to brainwash him.
But he's still concerned about it.
It was clear to everyone you weren't acting.
Indeed!
Shinso was amazing when Midoriya lost control.
Uraraka deserves praise for her quick
reflexes and reaction!
She risked her life to calm down her friend!
Yes, that's the way to do it! I like it!
Uraraka, you flew to him a swoosh!
You were so fast!
You hugged him with your arms.
I charged out without thinking too much.
I should have reacted with more cautions.
But it's better than doing nothing
and end up with regrets afterward.
I want to...
save the people.
You are showing great improvement, Uraraka.
I didn't use my Quirk for Midoriya alone.
I merely followed Uraraka's instruction.
More precisely speaking,
I saw those black whips
attacking Monoma and the others.
In any case, our chances of winning would
dwindle unless we could subdue the rampage.
I only stopped Midoriya because
I wanted to fight and beat him.
What happened back then was
merely a coincidence.
I could barely handle all that was going on...
No one asked you to go out
of your way to do such a thing.
Everyone here
is training hard to become a hero
that saves lives from danger.
Only a genius like All Might can
catch up so quickly to all of them.
You can't save anyone if you're obsessed
with what people think of you.
If you can't save yourself,
you don't have the strength to save others.
On this point alone, your performance just now
was enough to pass the test.
But I still have much to learn.
One thing I've learned after real combat...
is how amazing the Hero Course can be.
I will not be satisfied
with just passing the test.
I will work even harder
to achieve greater heights!
That's good to know.
Fight on with your Plus Ultra spirit.
Yes!
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪I hope my destination♪
♪Is where we shall meet again♪
♪I'm always seeing the world through your eyes♪
♪Tears are somehow falling down my cheeks♪
♪I hate it when you say it's all right♪
♪Your gentle whisper turned into
an unsettling silence♪
♪I want to believe the clouded sky before us♪
♪Our longing is the very thing that breaks us♪
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪But why? I'm already covered in wounds♪
♪Why must I search for the answer♪
♪Goodbye, we will meet again♪
♪I hope you would still be the same♪
♪I hope that the memories we share♪
♪Would once again bank up♪
♪So I could see you again♪
Next episode!
One For All's new power has awakened.
That power is the Quirk of the previous wielder.
That mysterious man told me
there would be six other Quirks
manifesting inside of me.
Wouldn't be similar to All For One's power?
Next episode, The New Power And All For One.
Control your heart,
wield One For All like your own extension!
Go Beyond!
Plus Ultra!