You don't seem to be taking this seriously.
Are we not worthy enough to fight you?
Bring it on, Class A!
Let's settle the score today!
CLASS A VS CLASS B
1ST BATTLE
Hero Course of U.A. High.
Class A and Class B
are having the first round of
joint training battles.
Shinso's Quirk successfully disrupted
Class B's coordination,
securing victory for Class A.
2ND BATTLE
All right!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Proceed as we planned.
Please scout ahead,
Tokoyami.
Roger.
Dark Shadow!
Understood!
Report back to me when you found our enemies.
Leave it to me!
The second battle has begun.
I'll be right back.
Everyone, scatter!
The surprise attack from Kuroiro of Class B
caught Class A off guard.
Help!
But Tokoyami countered with his new move,
"Dark Fallen Angel".
The battle...
is now seesawing between the two teams.
Naval Buffet!
♪When we are stranded on the same spot,
make our heart beat♪
MY HERO ACADEMIA
♪Rather than searching for an answer
in this world full of uncertainties♪
♪I want to live even though
my constant doubts are a waste of time♪
♪Take off the unseeable armor and feel the wind♪
♪I make my effort sound worthless
as a way to hide myself♪
♪The No.1 who came out of nowhere
is pointing at the endless sky♪
♪It's our desire to see the view
from greater height and distance♪
♪Ignite the heart of unquenchable desire♪
♪Ignite the path to our future,
burn the illusions to ashes♪
I found him, Hagakure!
Yes! We can catch him!
That's as far as you get!
There is nowhere to run!
"TORU HAGAKURE, QUIRK: INVISIBILITY"
I never expected you to strike alone.
"MOMO YAOYOROZU, QUIRK: CREATION"
But everything that is unexpected
is already within my anticipation!
"SHIHAI KUROIRO"
Within your anticipation?
Stop right there!
Give it up now!
Mushrooms?
I knew it.
Kendo anticipated your expectations!
Just as Kendo foresaw.
If I see the light,
that means Kuroiro's plan A failed.
Plan B commences.
You'll all be covered in mushrooms.
FORESIGHT!
No!
People can see me with these mushrooms!
This is embarrassing!
MUSHROOMS
The reproductive power is incredible!
"FUMIKAGE TOKOYAMI, QUIRK: DARK SHADOW"
Mushrooms have covered the whole field.
"YUGA AOYAMA, QUIRK: NAVAL LASER"
I can't see Kuroiro.
This is...
It must be Class B's tactic.
Pezizales!
Yellow knight!
Velvet shank.
Inky cap!
Grow!
Mesmerize the world with your charm!
Kinoko Komori, Hero Name: Shemage.
Quirk: Mushroom.
She can spread fungus spores from her body.
The spores spread better in humid environments!
The mushrooms can even grow on people?
"MINORU MINETA, QUIRK: POP OFF"
This is like a horror movie!
"YOSETSU AWASE, QUIRK: WELD"
Her mushrooms will disappear
after two to three hours.
There won't be any side effects.
This is also why she has a bad habit of
spreading the spores everywhere.
"OCHACCO URARAKA, QUIRK: ZERO GRAVITY"
The mushrooms are growing on the cameras!
"KYOKA JIRO, QUIRK: EARPHONE JACK"
This is so gross.
Our Plan A is to take control of Dark Shadow
to launch a surprise attack.
Our opponents will definitely
send Dark Shadow after us.
The is a low-risk yet highly efficient tactic.
They would never expect Kuroiro's
improved Quirk can take control of Dark Shadow.
That will be our chance to capture one of them.
Help!
It's easier said than done.
Nice speech.
What if I failed?
Wouldn't that put us at risk?
The opponent must use
light to counter your Quirk.
We can locate them with the light they emit.
When they unleash the light,
Dark Shadow can't attack as violently.
Even if Kuroiro failed,
we would be able to surround and take them out.
Plan A failed.
It's time to retreat for now.
Let's put Plan B into motion.
I'm counting on you, Kinoko!
The mushrooms keep popping up!
This is driving me crazy!
Judging by their two-phase combo,
they anticipated our tactic to counter Kuroiro.
Impressive, Kendo.
Everyone, calm down.
Let's regroup for now.
Dong! Clang! Bang!
Bam!
What?
This is...
Something is coming out!
I'm so amazing.
The impact of that effect manifested perfectly!
My spirit is all fired up!
Burp!
Class B, Manga Fukidashi.
Hero Name: Comicman.
Quirk: Comic.
He can materialize words
used in speech bubbles in midair...
simply by speaking them.
He can even manipulate the
effect by using different onomatopoeia.
Pop! Da da da!
What is going on?
Yaomomo! Where are you?
My laser has no effect on it.
Drippydy drip drip...
DRIPPYDY DRIP DRIP
What is this?
Drippydy drip drip?
No! It's a humidifier!
More mushrooms are growing on me!
They are everywhere!
Invisible Girl!
This is disgusting.
Komori and Fukidashi
saved Kuroiro from his predicament.
Their continuous long-range attack
is putting Class A in a tight spot!
"VLAD KING, QUIRK: BLOOD CONTROL"
This is Class B's true potential!
Stop your bias broadcast!
"WE ARE AGAINST BIAS BROADCAST"
Stop it!
"RIKIDO SATOU, QUIRK: SUGAR RUSH"
They must deal with two opponents
"HANTA SERO, QUIRK: TAPE"
with long-range attacks.
Not to mention...
Can Fukidashi use his Quirk
with foreign language?
Who knows?
"IZUKU MIDORIYA, QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL"
Deku, look!
That wall isolated Yaoyorozu from her teammates.
Could it be...
This is what they've been after!
I'm isolated.
Their true target is...
We cornered the master strategist.
Now is the time to fight with all we've got!
She crushed the tungsten shield so easily.
Class B, Ichika Kendo.
Hero Name: Battle Fist.
Quirk: Big Fist.
She can change the size of her fists,
the bigger they become,
the more powerful they are!
You won't even have time to react!
I can do this all day!
You can only create with matter
inside your body.
So you'll be the first to fall!
I can't stop.
It was the same during the sports day.
I mustn't give her the opening to think.
I'll overwhelm her with my raw might!
She gained the upper hand in a blink of an eye!
"TETSUTETSU TETSUTETSU, QUIRK: STEEL"
She has the perfect strategy!
I told you! She is brilliant
and she makes calm judgment!
That's our beloved Kendo!
"SHOTO TODOROKI, QUIRK: HALF COLD HALF HOT"
We don't know that yet.
If they are restraining Yaoyorozu
by isolating her from the team,
it might be a miscalculation.
Huh?
Yaoyorozu, you have a plan, right?
But even your plan didn't work.
There is no way I could...
Stop hesitating!
You're a better strategist than me!
You got two votes when we were
selecting our class rep.
I voted for you!
That was because I knew you're
capable of brilliant tactics!
I have a plan, Todoroki.
I have a solution.
I have a way to secure our victory!
I've had that plan in mind all along.
If they want to restrain Yaoyorozu,
they should have taken her out
with an all-out attack.
Maybe she had foreseen...
the situation she is facing right now.
Yaoyorozu has the better Quirk and grades.
But people are comparing me with her.
That really gets on my nerve.
That is not true, Kendo.
That's far from being true.
Even now, I'm still inexperienced.
But since you think so highly of me,
I can't show you the vulnerable side of me.
Since she anticipated the situation,
she will have a way to turn the battle around.
That's what she specialize in.
Momo.
Show them the result of your training.
I'll show them how strong I've become!
Are you kidding me?
She has a canon!
It takes quite a while to
build a weapon this massive!
MOMO YAOYOROZU, QUIRK: CREATION
SHE CAN CREATE ANY OBJECT FROM HER BODY
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH CLASS A,
BIRTHDAY: SEPTEMBER 23TH
HEIGHT: 173CM, BLOOD TYPE: A
HOBBY: READING
ITSUKA KENDO, QUIRK: BIG FIST
SHE CAN WRAP A PERSON WITH BOTH HER HANDS.
AFFILIATION: U.A HIGH CLASS B,
BIRTHDAY: SEPTEMBER 9TH
HEIGHT: 166CM, BLOOD TYPE: O
FAVORITE THINGS: BIKE AND BLACK COFFEE
I don't see Kuroiro anywhere.
I lost visual on Hagakure too.
Should we regroup with Yaoyorozu
on the other side?
Or should we...
Can't Stop Twinkling!
Help!
Mushrooms...
What?
Cursed fungi!
They got me!
Go!
My throat is starting to hurt.
Invisible Girl!
Not only did they isolate Yaoyorozu,
they can even hide themselves...
while using large-scale attacks
to surround us.
They are strong.
Strong and annoying.
Komori.
Fukidashi.
Kuroiro.
If we don't find out where they are hiding,
the battle is basically over.
I must find a way to break through this.
Are you kidding me?
She has a canon!
It takes quite a while to
build a weapon this massive!
"SEN KAIBARA, QUIRK: GYRATE"
She could kill someone with that thing!
She seems to like canons a lot.
Is she really going to fire that thing?
No...
Is she bluffing?
Will she tear down Fukidashi's wall?
Sorry if I startled you.
That was too close!
I have to expand my fists
before she fires the canon.
Double Jumbo Fist!
She didn't use it on the wall.
What did she fire?
From the moment you closed in
for close-range combat,
perhaps I was already losing.
However...
to secure our victory...
That sound...
It wasn't from Fukidashi.
It's from the other side of this wall.
That was...
Yaoyorozu!
Dark Shadow!
Roger!
YAOYOROZU'S LUCKY BAG
This is...
Hi, Komori.
What was that? I didn't catch that.
I caught him.
I caught Aoyama.
Nicely done, Kuroiro!
I'm counting on you to capture the rest of them.
Yes.
Well done, Kuroiro.
Our enemies have no idea where we are.
We'll keep pushing with my mushrooms.
OK.
Hey, Komori.
Mushroom?
Class A shouldn't know where we are, right?
Night-vision goggles.
I can see how they are spying on us.
When you stare into the abyss,
it's staring right back at you!
Lucky Bag?
Like a gift bag?
I can hold this.
This is...
Goggles and ethanol?
And disinfectant spray?
Judging by the design of these goggles,
I think they are meant for you.
She sent a message without using a single word.
Everyone, calm down!
Let's regroup!
Yaoyorozu,
did you foresee this...
all the way back then?
"THIS IS BAD"
Oh no...
Tokoyami is coming this way!
I'm right here for you.
I was curious why the mushrooms
don't grow on your team.
So you had already disinfected yourselves.
"I CAN'T SEE HER!)
Where is she?
I'm not going to tell you!
"WHERE IS SHE?"
STOP IT!
There will be an opening
as long as I can locate them.
He is headed this way!
You will not escape...
the gust of wrath!
Just as Hawks taught me,
speed will outshine raw power!
Abyssal Dark Body!
Sabbath!
Mushroom!
Komori!
He's fast...
No, I must hide in the shadow!
Are you looking for darkness?
Why don't you use my cloak?
Hey...
You're not a threat if you can't move.
Fumikage, I got the girl!
Incredible, he captured two of them at once.
This is a comeback!
This is all thanks to Yaomomo's items.
Yeah!
Hagakure has the upper hand as well.
They can win by outnumbering Kendo!
Dark Shadow, put them into jail.
Fumikage.
Sorry.
I don't like this move so I've kept it a secret.
But seeing our victory is at stake,
I have no choice but to use it.
My throat...
This is...
Schizophyllaceae that attacks your lungs.
Komori is not a powerful combatant,
"NEITO MONOMA, QUIRK: COPY"
but she is a force to be reckoned with.
You got sloppy thinking
this is merely training, Tokoyami.
You should have knocked her out first.
"CUT IT OUT!"
Eat this!
I can't see anything!
This is so confusing!
I must defeat Fukidashi so I can aid my friends!
"THAT HURTS"
Tokoyami and Yaomomo...
might be in danger!
Invisible Girl,
you're invincible!
I'm sorry for being late.
Kendo, you saved me.
What's with that?
Don't worry, I knocked her out.
But she got the better of me.
She tied herself on me along with the canon.
That makes it hard for me to move.
Everything she creates
is based on her foresight.
I just can't defeat her.
You saved us both, Komori.
It's only natural to help a friend, mushroom.
Kendo, Fukidashi, are you all right?
I think so.
Fumikage!
Komori, you used that spore?
We would have lost had I not used it.
Indeed.
Class A is formidable indeed.
They are very strong.
You bring honor to Class B, Kendo!
Great!
Yaoyorozu, I hope you don't
get depressed over this.
"MIDNIGHT, QUIRK: SOMNAMBULIST"
Yaoyorozu could make a great leader.
I feel so satisfied with their display
of Plus Ultra spirit.
They lost the battle,
but with Tokoyami's new move...
and Yaoyorozu's foresight for battle,
I can see you've grown much over time.
"ALL MIGHT, QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL"
You've taken another step forward.
One step closer to your dream.
One step closer...
to become a hero!
WELCOME
Second battle,
Class B won with a score of 4:0!
Well done, Class B! Congratulations!
Stop your bias broadcast!
"WE ARE AGAINST BIAS BROADCAST"
Stop it!
Congratulations!
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪I hope my destination♪
♪Is where we shall meet again♪
♪I'm always seeing the world through your eyes♪
♪Tears are somehow falling down my cheeks♪
♪I hate it when you say it's all right♪
♪Your gentle whisper turned into
an unsettling silence♪
♪I want to believe the clouded sky before us♪
♪Our longing is the very thing that breaks us♪
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪But why? I'm already covered in wounds♪
♪Why must I search for the answer♪
♪Goodbye, we will meet again♪
♪I hope you would still be the same♪
♪I hope that the memories we share♪
♪Would once again bank up♪
♪So I could see you again♪
Next episode!
It's the battle between Class A and Class B.
With both teams winning one battle,
the third battle is about to begin.
With Ida's speed...
and Todoroki's powerful Quirk,
they should have the advantage in this battle.
Fight on, Class A.
Next episode, The Third Match!
Class B will shine even brighter
with Honenuki's flexibility.
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!