Hey...
You don't seem to be taking this seriously.
Bring it on, Class A!
Let's settle the score today!
CLASS A VS CLASS B
1ST BATTLE
Hero Course of U.A. High.
Class A and Class B are having
the first round of
joint training battles.
Shinso's participation secured
a victory for Class A.
2ND BATTLE
In the second battle,
Kendo's tactic
even the field as Yaoyorozu employed
her sharp analysis of the battle.
But after a fierce battle, Class B won.
The score is now 1:1.
♪When we are stranded on the same spot,
make our heart beat♪
MY HERO ACADEMIA
♪Rather than searching for an answer
in this world full of uncertainties♪
♪I want to live even though my constant doubts
are a waste of time♪
♪Take off the unseeable armor and feel the wind♪
♪I make my effort sound worthless
as a way to hide myself♪
♪The No.1 who came out of nowhere
is pointing at the endless sky♪
♪It's our desire to see the view
from greater height and distance♪
♪Ignite the heart of unquenchable desire♪
♪Ignite the path to our future,
burn the illusions to ashes♪
KINOKO KOMORI, QUIRK: MUSHROOMS
FUMIKAGE TOKOYAMI, QUIRK: DARK SHADOW
I'm sorry, Tokoyami.
Do you need some cough drops?
You shouldn't show me sympathy.
I have an idea.
I'll get some medicines from Recovery Girl.
ITSUKA KENDO, QUIRK: BIG FISTS
MOMO YAOYOROZU, QUIRK: CREATION
You can't improve without training.
Humans are so pathetic.
Why should we carry the wounded?
Just ask for your school nurse.
This damage caused quite some damage.
It's on a different level compared
to the first battle.
This is normal for Hero Course training.
But the destruction they caused
is a little too much.
"VLAD KING, QUIRK: BLOOD CONTROL"
Fukidashi and Kendo!
You should know better!
Reduce the damage to minimum!
"MANGA FUKIDASHI, QUIRK: COMIC"
Yes!
Sorry.
Vlad.
How long will it takes for the mushrooms
to disappear?
It should take another two hours or so.
"SHOTA AIZAWA, QUIRK: ERASURE"
Then we should use the other arena.
Let's take a break.
THE THIRD BATTLE
It's a total victory for Class B!
I bet we are going to win just as we did
during the school festival!
"NEITO MONOMA, QUIRK: COPY"
But Class A, don't feel disheartened.
The difference in our strength
is simply too obvious!
Sorry about that.
That guy is always so full of himself.
Why would he provoke us if he knew
Kendo would knock him out?
"DENKI KAMINARI, QUIRK: ELECTRIFICATION"
By the way, don't you think Class B
"TORU HAGAKURE, QUIRK: INVISIBILITY"
has quite some unique characters?
Not at all. Your class is much cooler.
Fukidashi, I can't believe you can make
something so huge!
But my throat will become dry and itchy.
I'll just have to put up with it.
I know this is expected,
but aside from their improvements in Quirks,
their mental development makes
their Quirks even stronger.
There he goes again.
Deku, you've become much stronger too.
I wish that were true.
You have a long way to catch up to me.
No way.
I'm not talking about my height!
"ALL MIGHT, QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL"
I managed to sneak in.
Al Might?
Young Midoriya, may I have a word?
Sure.
A honeymoon?
Midoriya seems to have grown closer
with All Might lately.
He's been asking All Might to supervise
his training since the school festival.
Nice job, Uraraka.
You know Deku like the back of your hand.
I've only heard rumors about it, that's all!
Sorry!
Don't use your Quirk before the battle!
Save your strength for later!
I feel like I'm breakdancing!
Young Midoriya.
Has there been any anomaly
with your Quirks since then?
No, nothing in particular.
I see.
My mentor never told me anything
about the Quirks going berserk.
I'm going to find out more from Gran Torino.
OK, thank you very much.
You must be cautious.
The fifth battle is...
You saw One For All's real appearance
when you first fought Shinso.
HITOSHI SHINSO, QUIRK: BRAINWASH
Very well, I'll be careful.
KATSUKI BAKUGO, QUIRK: EXPLOSION
Kacchan, I didn't hear you coming.
If you want me to keep your secret,
then stop whispering behind me!
It'll only draw suspicion!
Oh...
Don't "oh"!
What's wrong with One For All?
The truth is...
Quirk trigger?
I'm not sure if you've improved
or the other way around!
I'm not sure either.
When will the Quirk truly become yours?
I'm much stronger now than we last fought.
I see...I can't wait to see.
Is Young Bakugo showing his concerns
in his own way?
What's with the smirk?
You're getting on my nerve!
Cut it out, you fool!
Or maybe I'm mistaken.
Young Midoriya saw the true face of One For All.
His fight with Shinso was the trigger.
I still think the two incidents are linked.
Mentor, and the previous holders,
what are you trying to convey?
"RECOVERY GIRL, QUIRK: HEAL"
Your injury
should heal in 30 minutes or so.
Be grateful that your body
is still young and strong.
You have really soft and delicate skin.
For the third battle,
the arena will be changed to
the east side of 2nd Street.
Let's proceed to the next battle!
Third battle, get ready!
3RD BATTLE
It's finally Ida's turn.
Todoroki has fire and ice
for a wide-range attack.
Ida has overwhelming speed.
Shoji has his sharp senses.
Ojiro is skilled in close-quarter combat.
This team is well-balanced in all aspects.
Todoroki is in this team.
That should make the fight a lot easier.
Underestimating your foe
will bring you to defeat.
I know that!
SHOTO TODOROKI, QUIRK: HALF COLD HALF HOT
Todoroki.
Tokoyami, how is your throat?
I took some medicine.
I'm feeling well.
I see.
I'm sorry you had to see my humiliating defeat.
I'm counting on you next.
Why me?
Hawks and Endeavor
were both in that fierce battle with Nomu,
and they are both our mentors.
We must live up to the expectation
of the No.1 and No.2 Heroes.
I see...
That last battle...
Plus Ultra!
Prominence Burn!
Shoto.
You must master this move.
Do not run away from me or yourself!
Stand up! Don't show any weakness!
It's a shame Toya didn't cut it.
His flame surpasses even mine.
But his body couldn't handle the cold.
It's such a shame.
You're my last hope, Shoto!
It's finally your turn!
Only you can master this move!
Only you can realize my ambition!
Todoroki...
Are you all right?
You seem odd just now.
Really?
Is something bothering you?
It's nothing. Thank you for asking.
You barely show any expression,
so it was hard to tell.
I'm impressed you actually noticed.
As the class rep, I must pay attention
to everyone and offer them my help!
He seems hyped somehow.
But he's always excited about something.
My brother is recovering well.
I'm glad to hear that.
I think Pro Hero Ingenium...
might have to retire from now on.
No!
People still need your leadership and guidance!
If you are willing,
could you please take on my hero name?
I must live up to the name
of my brother, the previous Ingenium!
As I'm watching everyone,
they are watching me as well.
I was in third place during the sports day.
I'll show everyone
my determination as the heir of his name!
Determination of an heir...
I know people see me as an oaf.
But at least I made it into U.A. High.
I'm not living on an empty brain!
Why are you bringing this up now?
It's about our team!
We don't know how to utilize
the element of surprise to our advantage!
That is true enough.
What should we do then?
Everyone!
We talked about this just now.
That's for sure!
Huh?
We'll raze this place to the ground!
That's what a fool would do!
Vlad King just told us to minimize the damage!
What? He wasn't even listening just now.
What is that?
I can hear the constant hitting of metals.
That is likely...
Tetsutetsu's doing.
Class B, Tetsutetsu Tetsutetsu.
Hero name: Real Steel.
Quirk: Steel.
He can turn his entire body into metal.
He can be the strongest weapon
and the toughest shield.
No more petty tricks.
Come on and face me head-on!
Tetsutetsu, they have Todoroki on their team!
I don't care!
You really are living on an empty brain.
Forget it. This is not entirely a bad thing.
Juzo, how you can you be so calm?
Geez! Don't keep us in the dark like that!
See? Pony is speaking in her mother tongue!
She is really upset!
Tetsutetsu doesn't mean any harm.
In fact, his approach plays to our strength.
Juzo, your approach is too gentle!
Bring it on!
The sound of metals is not stopping.
Judging by the noises, he is destroying
the surrounding.
They are planning a frontal assault.
Are they serious?
In that case, we must retaliate.
Agreed.
Great.
Let's go, Class A.
Team Three!
TENYA IDA, QUIRK: ENGINE
ENGINES ON HIS LEGS ALLOW HIM
TO MOVE AROUND SWIFTLY
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH
BIRTHDAY: AUGUST 22, HEIGHT: 179CM
BLOOD TYPE: A, FAVORITE FOOD: BEEF STEW
MASHIRAO OJIRO, QUIRK: TAIL
HE CAN USE HIS TAIL FOR ATTACKS
OR MOBILITY
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH, BIRTHDAY MAY 28,
HEIGHT 169CM
BLOOD TYPE: O, FAVORITE: MARTIAL ARTS
The villain is headed toward Line No.5.
The villain is headed to the port as expected.
I have to escape them.
Huh? Endeavor!
You're not getting away.
I'll use them as my hostage.
Run! Now!
Curse you! Let me go!
"ENDEAVOR, QUIRK: HELLFLAME"
That is not possible.
Fine, I get it! Let me go!
I'll do as you say!
Thank you, Endeavor.
How is the damage to the street?
There is barely any damage.
It was right to isolate him from the crowd.
Indeed.
So...
What is it?
Thank you!
You saved us!
Are you hurt?
No!
Stay safe on your way home.
OK!
Endeavor, there is another request to team-up.
Should we do the usual?
Yes. Make a list of the requests.
Thanks to Fuyumi,
I can finally...
add Shoto's number to my contact list!
Shoto, I have a message for you.
ARE YOU AVAILABLE? WAITING FOR YOUR REPLY
HOW ARE YOU? I NEED TO SPEAK WITH YOU.
Start replying my messages, Shoto!
I'm not the same guy
who used to ignore your feelings.
Do not run away from me or yourself!
Stand up!
Don't' show any weakness!
I've moved toward my own goal.
I believe I can teach you that move
as your father.
Which is why...
Which is why you should
start replying my messages.
Shoto!
I think he is in class right now.
His obsession with Shoto
is getting worse every day.
Are you all right?
Did you catch a cold?
It's nothing, I'll be fine.
We're almost there.
Follow the plan. Let's split up.
Understood.
We're counting on you, Todoroki.
Tetsutetsu!
Our opponents won't be stupid enough
to charge right at us!
This must be their trap!
No, I would come here if I were them.
After Shoji read the situation,
Todoroki will be their main force.
If they are all in this open area...
He always starts with his ice attack!
That is too sneaky!
But the ice won't block their view,
he's made some improvements.
Todoroki is behind the ice!
Where are the rest of them?
I can't see them.
Even if Honenuki makes the ground soft,
it won't matter as long as there is ice!
As soon as they slow down,
we'll take them all out.
Recipro Burst!
Bring it on!
What?
Using large-scale ice attack is too predictable.
We would be doomed
had you used your flame instead.
Class B, Juzo Honenuki.
Hero name: Mudman.
Quirk: Softening.
He can turn any object he touches soft.
But it doesn't work on creatures.
A second touch will undo the effect.
Thank you, Juzo!
Your reaction was flexible indeed!
He got in through official recommendations too!
He activated his Quirk before
the ice pinned them down.
His response was incredible.
We should retreat and regroup...
I found you.
I softened random objects in the area,
don't let your guard down.
Class B countered
Todoroki's ice attack flawlessly!
Now, retaliate!
Honenuki foresaw the ice attack?
Even so, he merely improvised.
"RIKIDO SATOU, QUIRK: SUGAR RUSH"
Honenuki is very intelligent.
"HANTA SERO, QUIRK: TAPE"
His flexibility is formidable.
Nice job, Juzo!
Leave Ojiro to me!
That hurts!
I can't guard against this attack!
Class B, Sen Kaibara.
Hero name: Spiral.
Quirk: Gyrate.
His body can spin like a drill!
Ojiro!
Not again!
Your legs can only run on hard surfaces.
The ice you stepped on was soft.
I knew you would be a threat.
I'll sink you and trap you in there.
You plan to stop our coordinated attack.
Cursed villain! How treacherous!
He's really into his role-playing.
They dealt with Ida's mobility.
Class B has no scouting member,
but they won't be at a disadvantage
as long as all combatants are in the vicinity.
If it turns into a battle royale,
Todoroki's efficiency will be greatly reduced.
Indeed. Now they simply have to
see it through the end.
Under these circumstances,
I can't use my flame or ice freely.
Should I go to the front-line?
But then I wouldn't be able to guard Shoji.
Shoji!
They thought Shoji would be hiding
in a safe spot and act as a scout.
I bet it's safe to hide behind Todoroki!
Class B, Pony Tsunotori.
Quirk: Horn Canon.
She can shoot her horns as projectiles.
She can currently control four horns at once.
She always makes sure
to keep her horns polished!
This is surprisingly powerful!
Tetsutetsu!
Here I come!
Horn Dash Hammer!
You sure are freezing cold, you jerk!
I can barely feel my metal, Todoroki!
But can you win a fight
if you have to fight me with bare hands?
Eat this!
"EIJIRO KIRISHIMA, QUIRK: HARDENING"
Tetsutetsu,
he learned from my mistake so quickly.
No, I don't think that was his intention.
Honenuki created this advantage for them.
Can you do nothing except dodging?
Stay there and stay still.
Curse it.
Sorry.
There is a time limit to your Recipro Burst.
Using it at the start wasn't a great idea.
I have to aid Tetsutetsu.
A time limit?
That was a long time ago, Mudman.
Ingenium will never be absent from a fight.
My legs exist for that sole purpose!
Right now,
I'm always going full-throttle!
New Style: Recipro Turbo!
Are you kidding me?
Tenya, congratulations on getting
your provisional license.
Thank you, Brother.
Aren't you working your engines too hard?
By the way, Mom,
he's grown a lot.
I know, but I think it's still too soon.
Tuning my engines?
Yes, you must start
training without your mufflers.
Then you'll be able to grow mufflers
with greater tolerance.
It's a technique passed down by our grandfather
so we can make it in time
to anyone that needs our help.
Removing the mufflers
will bring you great pain.
But to obtain greater speed...
This increases the base horsepower of Recipro.
The fuel depletion is minimized.
Ten minutes.
Within the next ten minutes
I am unstoppable!
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪I hope my destination♪
♪Is where we shall meet again♪
♪I'm always seeing the world through your eyes♪
♪Tears are somehow falling down my cheeks♪
♪I hate it when you say it's all right♪
♪Your gentle whisper turned into
an unsettling silence♪
♪I want to believe the clouded sky before us♪
♪Our longing is the very thing that breaks us♪
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪But why? I'm already covered in wounds♪
♪Why must I search for the answer♪
♪Goodbye, we will meet again♪
♪I hope you would still be the same♪
♪I hope that the memories we share♪
♪Would once again bank up♪
♪So I could see you again♪
Next episode!
Honenuki's flexible reaction
put Class A in a disadvantage.
Ida's Recipro Turbo is now the deciding factor
of this battle.
That and Todoroki's left side.
Ignite your flame, Todoroki!
Unleash your true potential
and become what you strive to become!
Next Episode, The Third Battle's Conclusion.
The battle ends heroically.
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!