♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(Meet our new recruit, Luo Feng.)
(Go get it.)
(Xu Xin, why is she...)
(She's also on the rescue list.)
(Get ready to fight.)
(There's a big monster coming!)
(There are many monsters in the county.)
(It'd be hard for
them to survive the siege.)
It's time to hunt.
Let's go, let's hide in the building.
=Episode 9=
Captain.
Go. I'll cover you.
We should believe in him.
Our priority is to keep her safe.
Primary beast officer,
two-tailed ocelot.
I'll be your opponent!
(Found you.
Captain of Fire Hammer Team, Gao Feng)
(Li Xiao, Zhang Zehu,
Pan Ya, Tietou, Dong, One-eye)
Gao Feng is strong.
He's got good strength,
which is as good as
an intermediate senior warrior.
He is a bit slow, but he's still
as fast as primary senior warriors.
Gao Feng's here, meaning the rest of
the team members are nearby.
I think they're hiding in that building.
Captain, Gao Feng is something.
That rookie, Luo Feng,
is better than I thought.
If we let him grow,
he'll bring us trouble.
Hump. Why don't we seize
this opportunity and kill Gao Feng?
His team will descend into
chaos following his death,
and that will be the time we
take them down.
I'm afraid that might expose us.
Captain, this is a rare opportunity.
The Fire Hammer Team
rescued the survivor.
If we let them go, there's a good
chance it'll lead back to us.
We'd better finish them off now.
I know your grudge
against Luo Feng. Don't worry.
I won't let him go.
But we can't act recklessly right now.
Xu Xin, stay close.
All these are low-level monsters.
Let's go up, it'd be safer
as there's no sign there.
The battle begins.
(There are 32 of them left now.)
(Tiger mastiff is not dangerous alone,
but works well as a team.)
(We must kill them as soon as possible,
or they might hurt Xu Xin.)
Luo Feng!
(I didn't see him
take out his sabre at all.)
(It's his first fight,
yet he's improved a lot.)
(Damn, it's 33 of them.)
Xu Xin, are you all right?
I'm good, you...
Luo Feng, I didn't know you could use fly-cutters.
I'm still practicing.
I dare not use it in combats.
(I'd better keep it a secret for now
that I'm a Spirit Master.)
Let's go.
(It's a trap.)
(The fiercer the attack is, the less
attention they will pay to the defense.)
(I'm stronger than a two-tailed ocelot.)
(But my speed is slower.)
(Looks like I need
more training on that.)
Gao Feng wins. He is something.
Captain, we could use him as the bait.
Right. If Gao Feng
fights that old monster,
he will surely die,
but that old monster
will be badly injured.
Then we can
take advantage of it.
=Swallowed Star=
No monsters are coming.
Should we go help the Captain?
No. Two-tailed ocelot is just
a primary beast officer.
It won't hurt the Captain.
You had been trapped in the wilderness
without water for so long,
thank god you survived.
Xu Xin, how come you
joined the volunteer team?
We're working on RR Virus Blocker.
RR Virus Blocker?
My college tutor is a bioengineer.
He recently developed
the RR Virus Blocker.
The tests were successful.
But we had to come here
to get the data to see
if it works on monsters.
It's too dangerous. You could have
trusted the warriors to do it.
A team of warriors
was with us to keep us safe.
The thing is we
have to collect the data on site.
My tutor, my classmates,
and the warriors...
They didn't die in vain.
Someone uses the volunteer team and
injured warriors as a bait
to drain the power of
the advanced monsters
and finally kill them.
It's dirty!
Whoever it is, we'll come after them.
They have yet to give it up.
I'm sure the beast they are after
didn't show up yet.
Why do they have to go through
so much trouble to set
a trap to hunt a monster?
It's got to be a strong and smart one.
It must be a beast officer
or even above that.
Prearranged ambush site
and the ultrasonic devices.
Looks like they've used this dirty trick
to their advantage many times.
Probably, they are also
a warrior's team.
A corrupt and depraved one.
(Huya Squad)
(returns to the warrior supply base)
(from 0201, too)
(Maybe...)
Captain, you can have whoever you want
but I'll deal with Luo Feng.
You're so angry with him?
Just a rookie who doesn't
know what he's doing.
But he embarrassed me many times.
He won't know what I'm capable of
if I don't teach him a lesson.
What's your plan, bro?
I'll cut his limbs and
leave him stranded.
And then I'll have the tiger mastiffs
eat him up piece by piece.
I'll make him regret messing with me.
Alright, just don't forget our business.
I won't.
Advanced beast officer,
the hunter, moon wolf.
It's worth a lot more than
the Fire Hammer Team.
We still don't know
who injured that old monster.
Li Xiao, save the last bullet for me.
I'm not a bad shooter.
You do hate Luo Feng a lot.
No problem. The rocket projectile is
self-navigated.
You won't miss him.
How's it going?
It's all set.
Let's wait for them to take the bait.
They're out.
Captain.
Other monsters will be here soon.
We need to leave as soon as possible.
(Captain is safe and sound after
a fight with a beast officer.)
Should we continue the investigation
into who's after all this?
We must do, but let's focus on
the mission right now.
We can't afford any
more unnecessary casualties.
All casualties are necessary.
Your death will bring us money.
Target locked. Ready to fire.
I'm good to go, too.
I'll blow his leg in one shot.
Very good.
(What's that noise?)
Captain.
Luo Feng!
(Dry cleaning)
Zhang Ke.
Get inside the building.
You have nowhere to hide!
Xu Xin.
I'm... I'm here.
The route of retreat has been cut off.
Huya Squad.
They found us. Go!
Don't worry.
The black snake, wild bull
and the iron scorpion!
All of them are beast officers.
(So many beast officers.)
(We're doomed.)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Next episode)
(Run!)
(Follow me.)
(We'll make it out.)
(Luo Feng is a Spirit Master?)
(My life as a warrior)
(is over.)
(I'll have no peace once it's exposed.)
(Boss, where is it now?)
(Don't regret messing with my people.)
(Fine, I'll see)
(what I'm capable of through you.)
(Luo Feng's fly-cutter doesn't work?)
(Damn!)
(Be safe.)
(That is fast.)