(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
=Episode 1=
(The end of the world is coming!
Where should the human go?)
(Wu)
File No. TJ210324.
Name: Great Nirvana.
Welcome to consult. Please follow me.
(It all started in the summer at the end
of the old century,)
(more than 2 billion people worldwide
died of RR virus.)
(Fire exit)
(First case of viral mutation was found
in animals infected in the Middle East.)
(Unknown species invaded America.)
(North America Coalition announced
abandonment of 13 East Coast states.)
(RR virus brought a new
intelligent species, the Monster.)
(Then, mankind has entered the era of
Great Nirvana.)
(Proposal No. 62:)
("Comprehensive Nuclear Program".)
(Scientists believed that)
(if all the nuclear bombs were launched,)
(the earth would be totally destroyed
three times.)
(However, that is not the case.)
(65 million years ago,
the earth was hit by an asteroid)
(whose energy equalled to
hundreds of thousands of nuclear bombs.)
(But the earth was not destroyed.)
(Einstein once said)
("I don't know what weapons we will
use in the Third World War,)
(but I'm sure
we will use stones in the Fourth.")
(It's us that will be destroyed,)
(along with human civilization.)
(We always use nuclear weapon)
(as the trump and value it)
(thinking that the huge mushroom cloud)
(could solve all the problems.)
(But we all see that)
(plants grew one year after
the bombing in)
(Hiroshima and Nagasaki.)
(Even in the nuclear test site
in Novaya Zemlya,)
(vegetation and wildlife have fully restored.)
(The power of nuclear weapons)
(is far less powerful than we thought.)
(A thousand bombs failed
to stop the Monsters.)
(The United Nations declared
a state of emergency.)
(Please take refuge
in the underground base immediately.)
(If there is a global nuclear war,)
(it is human civilization
that is most likely)
(to be destroyed.)
(Survived or destroyed?
The last homes for mankind)
(Human beings survived
in the Great Nirvana.)
(Although many countries were occupied,)
(with military strength, technology and
our indomitable willpower,)
(five major countries survived.)
(We formed the Earth Alliance)
(and established bases in 23 regions.)
(Human beings are always here.)
(The most important reason)
(is the warrior, of course.)
(Five years ago)
Feng.
Luo Feng.
In any case,
the old world is just spectacular.
I still can't believe
that human beings survived
in the Great Nirvana.
Indeed, human civilization was almost
destroyed that time.
Unexpectedly,
the Earth Alliance formed by
the five major countries survived.
A whole new civilization started.
All thanks to them.
The heroes known as warriors.
Only the strong warriors
can explore the old world.
I'll be one of them in the future!
Feng, your skill is outstanding and
you're diligent.
It's just a matter of time
before you become the warrior.
After all,
there is still a long way to go.
My first goal is next month's
college entrance examination.
I plan to go to the Military Academy.
After all,
for poor students like us,
getting subsidies and free education
is the best we can do for our family.
Studying in the Military Academy
helps to improve yourself and
become a warrior.
Don't forget me, brother.
Wei Wen.
Did you see something
flying through just now?
It's like a flying Monster.
Impossible.
After the Great Nirvana,
no Mutant Monster could
get close to the shield.
Was I wrong?
Forget it. Let's go back.
(Warning)
(Highest alert)
Sir! The Mutant Monster has
crossed No Man's Land.
Intercept now!
What is our target?
Black Crowned Golden Eagle.
It ranks third in the Eagle Monsters.
Flying at 3.9 times the speed of sound.
Its feather is harder than the diamond,
as hard as third-level chrome.
From the image,
the wingspan is 36 meters,
the body length reaches 21 meters.
Adult. Grade S.
Grade S. How far is it?
A thousand km away.
According to the speed of
Black Stork Golden Eagle of Mach 3.9,
it will reach in 15 minutes.
What about the fighters?
Attack in five minutes.
The target's in sight. Request to fire.
Request approved.
(Lost)
Shall we call out the warrior?
Yes. Hope it's not too late.
(38th anniversary of Long March hero,
Dong Nanbiao's sacrifice is being held.)
(Wreaths are laid in all martial clubs
across the country.)
(National Research Institute has made
a breakthrough in RR virus research.)
(It can reduce its survival time
in the air by 30 minutes.)
Is the breakthrough in RR virus research
meaningful?
(Tencent Video)
The Great Nirvana is over.
Of course. Humans are infected with
the RR virus and produce antibodies.
That's why we gained
unprecedented power.
In some way,
it made the powerful warriors.
When we talk about warriors,
your eyes shine.
Forget it. Let's live in the moment.
Goals are good,
but it's too far away from us now.
I went to the wrong classroom,
and they were all staring at me.
We're going to graduate.
It doesn't feel real.
Oh, do you hate to leave someone?
I'm not.
Oh, here he is.
We are leaving now.
See you after the exam. Bye.
Seize the chance!
Xu Xin, I'll take you home.
(Zhang Haobai.)
Are you blind? Don't you see my car?
(Sparkly Studio)
Damn! Take cover!
The warrior killed the Mutant Monster.
The crisis is over,
and radar is being repaired.
(Only one shot.)
(This is the power of the warrior.)
(So incomparable.)
(I've decided)
(to be)
(a warrior!)
=Swallowed Star=
♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Everyone, tomorrow is the day for
college entrance examination.)
(I hope you can work hard.)
(Next episode)
You want to be a warrior, too?
Let's compete.
(Next episode)
(Why hasn't Feng come yet?)
(Yes, Young Master.
We found Luo Feng's residence.)
(They are not here to fight.)
(Next episode)
(What's going on? It's late.)
(The exam discipline)
You have 30 minutes left.
Luo Feng, wait for it!
(Next episode)
Check on him later.
(=Swallowed Star Time to Shine=
Every Sunday at 10 a.m.)