♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(I am a disabled person.)
(Why do I want a girlfriend or
marriage?)
(What are you talking about?)
(My parents sent the message behind
my back.)
(I didn't know until now.)
(But I am...)
(I have a way.)
(Oh,)
(what my buyer wants most is
living embryos of the beast generals'.)
(Buyer?)
(It'd be bad if it was the bait
Li Wei's parents secretly left behind.)
(Fist power test)
(The power of your fist is 28 tons!)
(God of War is not out of my reach.)
=Episode 20=
Yang.
Zhou. Last time we met
when you just became president.
Commissioner Yang.
Yeah.
It's not easy to be a leader.
I've been worrying about the things
in the martial club.
Eight years passed in the blink
of an eye.
I have been a teacher for several years.
It's hard to recruit people every year.
Headquarters sent you here
to check Luo Feng's ability, right?
Thank you.
Well, we need to recruit the best students
around the world.
Of course, we must take it seriously.
Where are we going this time?
It's under discussion.
Luo Feng.
I heard your fist power reached 28 tons.
Yeah.
You can attend the special
training, I think.
Special training?
Every year, our martial club chooses
two to three
talented warriors from the base city
for special training.
I think you are qualified.
If Luo Feng goes to the training,
there will be only four people
in Fire Hammer Team.
It was Luo Feng who helped to
solve the problems
when our team was in danger.
Especially after Zhang Ke's accident.
He has greatly eased the pressure of
the downsizing.
If Luo Feng leaves...
Don't put pressure on Luo Feng.
I've been in the wilderness for
more than a decade.
I can't make any more progress.
If Luo Feng is to join a better
organization,
I'm going to retire.
We, too.
(Special training.)
(It's a good opportunity for me.)
(But if I leave the team,)
(it'll be bad for Fire Hammer Team.)
Emergency rescue signal!
It's in city 023, set off immediately!
Oh?
At the age of 19, he reached the level
of primary senior warrior
and mastered Nine Thundering Sabre
Level 3?
Yes.
I saw with my own eyes
that he used the Nine Thundering Sabre
and hit 28 tons.
It seems that Luo Feng is not suitable
for special training.
He should be qualified
for the highest standard of training.
Where is Luo Feng now?
Commissioner.
Luo Feng and Fire Hammer Team
are in a rescue operation in City 023.
Commissioner. President.
Just got word from headquarters
that the Wang family of HR Alliance
went there by a private plane
and wanted to buy a quota for
50 billion.
There are limited quotas, and they
want to buy one.
Get your things done first.
Yes.
What will the headquarters do?
Headquarters don't want to make it bad.
They are hanging it up.
The Wang family is impatient now.
They said
unless the extreme martial club could
immediately give a qualified candidate,
or they will tell the media
that we reserved places for
the well-connected.
The world's major powers and consortia
all want those quotas every year,
It's not easy to choose a person
by his strength.
Zhou, help me prepare a warplane.
And find where Luo Feng is.
You mean...
Give me an hour and I'll bring
Luo Feng here.
The besieged Beihe Team is not
far away from us.
(Locked)
(Satellite Map Dangerous area Mark)
Unable to contact Luo Feng.
Just get his location.
Luo Feng, I hope you really are
strong enough
to shut the losers in HR Alliance up.
=Swallowed Star=
(It's Wan Dong and one more.)
(I think I met him before.)
We can't keep up with Luo Feng anymore.
Captain, you go save people.
I'll deal with these monsters.
(Luo Feng's body method
almost reaches the highest.)
(Giant rock bear is a beast general.)
(Luo Feng can actually fight it.)
(He's been a warrior for a short time,)
(yet he has grown to this level.)
Look out!
Nine Thundering Sabre Level 3.
Luo Feng has got something.
Commissioner. It's almost 20 minutes.
It takes time to return and report.
It probably takes more than an hour.
Open the hatch and I'll finish it
as fast as I can.
There are other monsters
coming to Luo Feng.
Let's settle the Beihe Team
and go to support Luo Feng.
OK.
(He must come to the rescue.)
(Each sword light seems
to contain more than ten shots.)
(It's incredibly fast.)
(Is he a God of War?)
Thank you very much, senior.
Luo Feng.
Thank you for saving us.
Director, this is...
Let me introduce you.
He is
Mr. Yang Hui
the special commissioner from
headquarters of Extreme Martial Club.
He is a God of War.
-It's him.
-He's really famous.
I've heard of him for a long time ago.
You are Luo Feng?
Yes.
Luo Feng.
Commissioner Yang came to
Jiangnan base city
mainly because of you.
He spent a lot of effort on you
this time.
The martial club has a better
arrangement for you.
Time is running out. Luo Feng.
Go back with us now.
(If it's for the special training,
it means)
(the Fire Hammer Team will be
dismissed.)
I didn't expect this day to
come so soon.
What nonsense.
It means you've made great progress.
Do you remember why you wanted to
be a warrior?
You can't stay in
Fire Hammer Team forever.
Just go ahead, there are more
important things waiting for you.
I will always remember
I was part of the Fire Hammer Team.
I became a warrior a few years earlier
than Luo Feng.
Instead,
he went to the special training!
Don't be jealous, OK?
Besides,
the commissioner came in person.
It's more than just a special training.
Ah?
Could it be...
President Zhou,
I'm not going for the special training?
There are two training camps
in our headquarters.
The so-called special training
is the basic training camp.
Another camp is even rarer.
One is selected from the base city
in every five years.
The teachers there are
at least Gods of War.
Even Hong and Thunder, the world's
top warriors, will guide them.
There are training equipment
and treasures from the relics
of ancient civilization.
Hong.
Relics of ancient civilization?
There are the most talented students
in the world.
The best teachers, the best equipment.
It's known as the world's
first training camp.
It's called
Elite Training Camp.
(Yang Hui, intermediate God of War, special commissioner
from the global headquarters of Extreme Martial Club.)
(Teacher in the Elite Training Camp.)
(Responsible for searching potential talents
for Elite Training Camp around the world.)
(Therefore, he values
Luo Feng's talent a lot.)
(Zhou Zhengyong, primary God of War.
President of Extreme Martial Club in Jiangnan.)
(Head of the local
Extreme Martial Club.)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪Never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star")
(Next episode)
(Received a remittance of one million)
(Oh, it's you.)
(We are really predestined.)
(We met each other two days in a row!)
(I have only one word to say to you.)
(I advise you to leave Xu Xin.)