♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(Rat surge!)
(You're Lu Gang, God of War!)
(The future of the base city
depends on you.)
(Go!)
(Mr. Lu Gang!)
(The kid's got Nine Thundering Sabre!)
(No worry, I'll find someone strong
enough to make them die miserably.)
=Episode 13=
Mr. Lu Gang's funeral
(Obituary: Loss of God of War.)
will be held at the Heroes Hall
at 10:00 a.m. this morning.
It's 9:45 in the morning.
Warriors and dignitaries have begun
to pay their respects.
(Obituary: Loss of God of War.)
National TV is here.
God of War's funeral is broadcast live
across the country.
We don't have many Gods of War
in our country.
Every God of War will be mourned
by the whole nation.
(Mr. Lu Gang)
(died for the country and mankind.)
Xin.
Yes. Grandpa.
(Xu Xin's grandfather?)
(He must be the master of the Xu Clan.)
(He's also here.)
Gang.
Guo Hai,
I didn't expect to see you here.
I thought you were in the wilderness.
Mr. Lu Gang's Funeral is a big deal.
I have to come even if
I was on a mission.
Mr. Lu Gang guided me back then.
I can't believe
a strong man like him would...
It was the rat surge.
He was strong but...
The kid was in county 0201 at that time,
but he managed to escape!
Kid?
There, Luo Feng.
He's still got a thing for Xin.
Last time, I warned him
to stay away from my sister.
Looks like he hasn't given up yet.
He's just a soldier.
Far worse than you.
You're 21 years old, and you're
an intermediate senior warrior.
Soldier?
That's delayed information.
I know Luo Feng.
He's killed over 10,000 monsters
in two months.
Almost all were advanced beast soldiers,
hence the name "Psycho".
He's probably as strong
as a primary senior warrior.
Primary senior warrior? He's only 18.
Captain,
the Fire Hammer Team is also here.
Let's take this opportunity
to get rid of them.
Captain, you're saying...
This time,
we'll be working with the Thunder Team.
We can play some tricks
and pit them against
the Fire Hammer Team.
The Thunder Team is strong,
they can easily kill
the whole Fire Hammer Team.
That's a good plan.
They should be here by now.
We'll go in now, Young Master.
You guys go ahead.
I'll go to the hotel to get some rest.
Foreigners?
It's the Paulinus Clan.
Paulinus Clan,
one of the nine clans of HR Alliance?
The white man's name is Charon,
the old man's surname is Liu.
(What a sharp look!)
It seems the old man
has rich combat experience.
They're all advanced senior warriors,
especially the old Liu.
He's almost a God of War.
God of War!
They're bodyguards of the Paulinus Clan.
Two advanced senior warriors are here.
It means they're
on an important mission.
Uh? Huya Squad.
They are the Fire Hammer Team?
Yes, Mr. Liu.
I don't care about
your personal grudges.
I want you to keep an eye out
for the mission in City 003.
I don't want to be held back.
We must protect the Young Master.
Yes, it's all set.
I can't believe
the warplane could land right here!
It’s the superior
of Extreme Martial Club.
Even the dignitaries come to greet him.
(It's him.)
You know Senator Zhu Xi?
I met him once in test of warrior-to-be.
Who is he?
Senator Zhu Xi, one of
Extreme Martial Club's core powers.
His power is second to
the funder of the club,
the most powerful man in the world,
Hong.
He's also one of the 5 major inspectors
of the club.
Rumor has it that
he's outgunned God of War.
Outgunned God of War?
(We didn't find his body,
maybe he is...)
He was buying time for reinforcements.
He was strong enough
to escape unscathed.
Mr. Lu Gang was so good,
but he sacrificed in the rat surge...
The war between the warriors
and the beasts will continue.
We need to be more vigilant
about the internal strife.
You mean Huya Squad.
They seem to have made contact
with the Paulinus Clan.
It's a powerful family
with many Gods of War.
Huya Squad could only
do some legwork for the Paulinus Clan.
How could Gods of War
possibly help them?
Captain,
if the Paulinus has nothing but wealth,
they wouldn't have attracted
so many Gods of War, they...
No, for such a big clan,
it isn't hard to raise Gods of War.
Just like the three children
of Mr. Lu Gang's,
two of them are senior warriors.
The gene can be inherited.
-Inherited?
-The cell in the warrior's body
absorbs genetic energy
which perfects the genes, and it
can be passed on to future generations.
Let's say the most powerful man, Hong.
The second best, Thunder.
And Senator Zhu Xi we met today.
Their children
are usually Gods of War.
So a big clan like the Paulinus,
can always strengthen
the bloodline.
It's an advantage
we ordinary warriors don't have.
If the strong gene is passed on,
then in the future...
Maybe we'd defeat the monsters for good.
But it's a very long way to go.
What we can do now
is to defeat as many monsters as we can.
I have a bold idea.
Mr. Lu Gang had been guarding City 003.
And now that he's gone,
there will be many more monsters there.
The nation has called in
a team of senior warriors.
Why don't we go to City 003, too?
City 003.
It's one of the most dangerous areas
in Eurasia,
with Asia's most prolific buildings.
There are large numbers
of beast generals there.
Some are even stronger than that.
And it's near the ocean.
Many ocean beasts emerge in rivers.
They are far worse than land beasts.
Have you forgotten?
Why did we take the genetic agentia?
Not to be somebody
or to show off,
but to kill more monsters
and take back what is rightfully ours.
Right. We can't let Mr. Lu Gang
die for nothing.
Captain and Luo Feng are right.
We can't back down!
We're going to City 003!
=Swallowed Star=
There are a lot of troops
and high-ranking warriors.
It is very close to City 003.
To deal with any sudden attack,
the military configuration is way better
than that of other military commands.
There are a lot of
flying beasts in City 003.
So this military district
has to take on more air defense.
There are ocean beasts in rivers too.
This city's got ocean beasts,
land beasts
and flying beasts, all of them!
The Fire Hammer Team came!
They're seeking their death.
Don't worry.
Mr. Liu can defeat them easily.
But
the 2 martial clubs and 5 great powers
forbid warriors from killing each other.
We...
Don't worry.
Mr. Liu can kill them
without everyone knowing.
Even if the two martial clubs
and the five great powers find it out,
the Paulinus could deal with it easily
as they are so powerful.
The captain's right. This time,
I'll kill Luo Feng myself!
(The UN has declared
a state of emergency.)
That's City 003,
it used to be the economic center,
Shanghai.
Now there are good
and evil people mixed up.
There are many beast generals
and Gods of War there.
There are many powerhouses
from home and abroad.
It's also a place
where Mr. Lu Gang fought.
We can't just go into the city,
let's go slowly from the suburbs.
Hurry. Spread out!
It's an armored car
before the Great Nirvana.
Black Crowned Golden Eagle.
Prepare for the battle.
A Black Crowned Golden Eagle,
primary beast officer.
Two black snakes,
advanced beast soldiers.
Over 30 Lion Mastiffs.
So many monsters in half an hour.
It has never happened before.
That's the City 003.
Cunning beasts are everywhere.
You'll barely have time to take a break.
Captain, we got a big one.
Two-headed black snake,
and it's about to have a horn.
At least an advanced beast officer.
-Foreigners.
-They don't seem to be a match.
Right.
Though they are foreigners,
we are all warriors protecting mankind.
We can't just sit and watch them die.
Good, join hands.
OK.
(It's after me.)
Hit its vital part!
(So hard).
(Nine Thundering Sabre.)
(Second stage, hidden power!)
Good.
Gao Feng.
That's good.
-It's them.
-Advanced senior warriors, this is bad.
It's Thunder Team's prey.
(Thunder Team?)
You'll have to spit it out
even if you have it.
This one's mine.
(Two-headed black snake,
advanced beast officer)
(One of the best of the snake beasts.
Mutant ones are close to beast general.)
(The poison teeth are deadly.
Whoever gets bitten will be dead.)
(Indian Team. Senior warriors.
A team of Indian senior warriors.)
(It's led by a bald man
who's good at using long sticks.)
(It's strong. Two team members
are good at shield knives.)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Next episode)
(This is ours!)
(Please release the Indian team.)
(Who are you to make demands?)
(Two advanced senior warriors,
if they attack,)
(we may not even have a chance
to react.)
(Instead of waiting and defending,)
(we'd better...)
(Call me when your team finds out
where Fire Hammer Team is.)