♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(Don't forget)
(my teammate's got a sniper rifle
pointing at you, too.)
(It's day 10 and I can't wait anymore.)
(Zhang Zehu and Li Xiao should be
at the hotel today.)
(I'll beat them
while they're scattered.)
(How dare you hurt my family.
I'll make you pay!)
(-There's no regular call!
-It's too late now.)
=Episode 15=
(I can't go further, this kid's so strong!)
Xiao!
You are so good!
I can only beat you with some tricks.
His right lung was shot.
This kid's not gonna make it.
But don't you worry.
Your family will be with you soon.
This thing.
I'm sure you're familiar with it.
A small ultrasonic device.
It can attract monsters
by mimicking their sonic frequencies.
They must really like you.
You! You're pretending!
You missed.
You're... A Spirit Master!
Did you break Zhang Ke's right hand?
Kill me.
I'm not like you guys from Huya Squad
who hurt other warriors,
but the monsters will.
Young Master, that was a clean cut.
Quick and deadly. Cut the throat.
Yeah, that was a hunting wolf,
a beast officer.
Smell of blood.
Hu, Xiao, reply. What's going on?
Oh, no.
Hu! Xiao!
Captain.
There's a bullet hole in the wall.
Monsters attacked suddenly.
They were so careless!
They stayed at the hotel
and relaxed their vigilance.
But that's strange. Master Liu.
Hu and Xiao are alert.
If they couldn't make it,
they would tell us with their watches.
Maybe other warriors attacked them.
(Master Liu is very prudent.)
(I don't know if
I can hide it from them.)
Of course, there's another possibility.
A beast officer attacked them.
They are extremely intelligent.
Especially those
in the hell of city 003.
They've mastered a lot of
human assassination techniques.
If a beast officer found them
and attacked them suddenly...
Then they would not
have a chance to tell us.
(Salty)
Master Liu, what about...
The master's training is still on.
The mission continues.
But if it was a warrior...
Even if it was a warrior who attacked,
it was an elaborately planned assassination
of these two losers.
It means he's just average.
No need to worry.
But if he was after Young Master...
Young Master is noble,
no one dares to kill him.
You've got nothing to worry about.
We'll work together.
No one's gonna lay a hand
on Thunder Team.
Alright. We'll follow you.
What's up?
Ultrasonic device. No.
This device has never stopped!
Lion mastiff, 5 meters tall.
A beast general.
What's going on?
They could do nothing right.
Go upstairs, now!
=Swallowed Star=
(So strong. They are indeed
the advanced senior warriors.)
Captain! Captain! Ah!
(Lion mastiff, 5 meters tall
and over six meters long.)
(An advanced beast officer.)
(He's getting a horn.
Almost a beast general.)
Protect Young Master.
Look behind you.
There's another advanced beast officer!
(What's going on?)
Uncle Li.
Uncle Wang.
Look at you. You're all messed up.
Li Wei, your dad got your distress call,
and found there were only two
Gods of War near you.
He called us as soon as he could.
Luckily, we weren't too far away
and we came in time.
(God of War. Two!)
What on earth happened, Liu?
You shouldn't mess with the herd
with two advanced beast officers!
Here's the thing, Mr. Wang.
We went for field training with
Young Master this morning
and two teammates that stayed here
were attacked by monsters.
They were dead. When we got back,
the monsters were hiding in the shadows
around the compound
and attacked us.
We were caught unprepared.
Strange! Warriors usually
hide in covert places
where monsters can't find.
How did you find the stronghold?
And who stayed here?
His squad, Huya Squad,
was in charge of finding stronghold and guarding.
Master Wang, Master Li.
My name is Pan Ya.
Huya Squad.
It's a team of senior warriors
hired by our Thunder Team.
We protect Young Master together.
Someone plots against you.
It probably holds grudges against you.
You're saying someone
got back at Huya Squad.
Li Wei's father has some enemies,
but they are all Gods of War.
They won't plot against a child.
Now the dead were
members of Huya Squad.
So it can only be retaliation
against your squad.
Uncle Wang, I'm not a child.
I'm almost an intermediate senior warrior.
I can handle most of the
primary beast officers.
Primary beast officers? Very average.
Or I should say bad.
A true warrior master can handle a beast
of his own rank.
Some can even go kill
monsters of higher ranks.
You're physically
as strong as an intermediate senior warrior.
But you can only deal with primary beast officers.
You need more training.
Your body condition is good.
With your talent
and the support of your parents,
you still might
be a God of War in 10 years.
When you become a God of war
and join the Palace of Gods,
then people will respect you
instead of treating you
like some stuck up young master.
(Palace of Gods.)
Got it.
Thanks, Uncle Wang and Uncle Li .
Master, what is Palace of Gods?
You'll be told
when you're an advanced senior warrior.
It's possible that
you will make it someday.
It's okay if I give you a heads up.
Palace of Gods is a group of
Gods of War or
even stronger warriors
from all base cities of
the five great powers.
All Gods of War in the world
are members of the Palace of Gods.
The world's most powerful warrior, Hong,
and the second most powerful one,
Thunder, are the creators.
(Hong and Thunder.)
(So the world's first and second best
aren't just competitors.)
Palace of Gods is
the temple of the warriors.
Its purpose is to pursue
the limits of the human body,
and to wipe out
all the monsters on earth.
All right, Li Wei,
you'd better get out of here now.
Soon this place will be at war.
War?
Wang and I are gonna fight an iron dragon,
an advanced beast general.
Advanced beast general.
This operation is dangerous.
Miles around would be involved.
(Two Gods of War hunt
an advanced beast general together.)
Three months ago,
the iron dragon led monsters
to raid the Southeast Army Supply Depot,
resulting in massive casualties.
Over a thousand men were eaten
by the iron dragon in battle.
We think it was preparing for spawning.
Spawning? Then its offspring...
Will grow into another beast general.
It's estimated that the iron dragon
laid its eggs earlier.
This weakens it.
Now is the perfect time to kill it.
And that egg
must be destroyed before it hatches.
Otherwise, it's an imminent threat
to the base city.
All right, you guys get out of here.
We're about to make a night raid.
Understand.
(Two Gods of War fight
an advanced beast general together.)
(It's a rare opportunity
to watch and learn.)
(I need to watch it
even if it's dangerous.)
(The silver lion mastiff,
advanced beast officer,)
(whole body is silver,
five meters tall,)
(huge and athletic.)
(The pounce reaches over 20 meters,
like a silver flash.)
(Wang Tong, advanced God of War.
Known as Shadow Blade.)
(Friend with Li Yao
and his wife until death.)
(Quick and elegant.
His moves are great.)
(Li Kan, intermediate God of War.
Known as Strong Bear.)
(Friend with Li Yao
and his wife until death.)
(Armed with Mace,
as powerful as an advanced God of War.)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Next episode)
(Don't waste time with the herd.)
(Go straight to its lair!)
(Understood.)
(Master Li is quick when dodging.)
(He's perfected with
the Micro Bodily Movement.)
(Two warriors and monsters
have been at each other's throats.)
(Right!)
(If the egg is destroyed,
and the iron dragon will be sad.)
(They'll have a better chance.)
(Iron dragon's egg.)
(Oh, no, the iron dragon's gone mad.)