♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(Run!)
(Luo Feng is a Spirit Master?)
(Follow me. We'll make it out.)
(My career as a warrior is over.)
(The moon wolf!)
(Seeing from its size,
it should be an advanced beast officer.)
(I got you!)
(Ah!)
(Someone should have
taught you about karma.)
(Leave your arm here!)
(Ah!)
=Episode 11=
(Zhang Zehu, it's okay you come at me.)
(But I won't let you set my team up!)
Drop your weapons,
or we will fire.
Hump!
Let's go.
Captain, do we just
let them go like this?
Pan Ya's a snake.
We can report it to the Security Bureau.
But without proof, we'll get nowhere.
Zhang Ke's injuries are worrisome.
We've had someone sent
the girl back to the city.
For your team member here,
he may need a new plan for life.
Huya Squad!
It's fine. Captain. I've been thinking
about retirement for a long time.
I've been busy with missions
since my daughter was born.
I am not a good father.
Maybe this is the time.
Captain, I still want to be a warrior...
Alas.
It's not easy being a warrior.
Dead bodies of warriors are sent to
my tiny infirmary every day.
There's always a way.
Let's check with the HR Alliance Mall
and see if there's a robotic arm
for warriors.
Captain, thank you for your kindness.
How can a robotic arm be
as strong and fast as a warrior's?
(Robotic arm, then Hua...)
Hello, she's back? That's good to know.
Yes. Yes. It won't happen again.
Okay, thanks. Bye.
Miss Xu is home. Thank you so much.
(Why does Mr. Wang
care so much about her safety?)
We've made payment to you, Captain Gao.
Please check it.
OK.
There's something I'd like
to ask, Mr. Wang.
The robotic arm?
One of my team members was seriously
injured in this mission.
If we can't get him a good robotic arm,
I'm afraid...
I'm sorry to hear that.
But our best robotic arm can only
help him get daily life back.
It's not for warriors.
But...
But what?
For all I know, there is the treasure
that can regenerate broken arm.
What is it?
(Regenerate? Then Hua...)
(SAT 29/06 25° SUN 30/06 22°
MON 01/07 24°)
It's called the water of life.
It's made from the spirit of Earth King,
the King Beast.
It costs as much as 30 billion each.
Thirty billion!
But there is nowhere you can buy it.
Alas.
Let's not get carried away.
It's good to retire
and be an instructor.
At least, I have more
time for my family.
Mr. Wang, this time,
apart from rescuing your people,
we have taken down some monsters
that pose a threat to the city.
Ah?
The moon wolf! You killed a moon wolf?
Oh.
We were being lucky.
The moon wolves are hunters.
It's far more dangerous than
any other beast at the same level.
It was an advanced beast officer.
It's as dangerous as a general beast.
I could not beat it
if it was as strong as usual.
And we have paid a great price.
We will pay a good price to you
as you killed a moon wolf.
Taking all the other monsters
you've killed into account,
how about a billion dollar as reward?
That would do.
Zhang Ke. This is to celebrate
your retirement.
From now on, you'll be Instructor Zhang
of the Extreme Martial Club.
We've been set up by Huya Squad.
I'm lucky I only lost one arm.
Thank you, Captain
and Luo Feng. You saved
the day and my life.
Don't say that, Zhang.
As a Spirit Master,
I didn't notice what
Huya Squad was up to,
so you have to retire early.
You saved my life.
You can't blame yourself!
The future of the Fire
Hammer Team depends on you!
Yes. Luo Feng is a Spirit Master
who grows much faster than others.
We're going to kick
Huya Squad's ass in no time!
Speaking of which,
Huya Squad and we are at odds now.
They are stronger than us.
Pan Ya and Zhang Zehu are scheming.
I'm afraid they're going to retaliate.
I wouldn't worry about it.
The state and the club will
protect the veterans and their families.
But you guys...
It's true that the threat of Huya Squad
must be taken seriously.
I have a proposal for you to consider.
Class A genetic agentia?
Yeah.
Genetic agentia optimizes human genes.
Class A genetic agentia
can increase the warrior's
strength greatly in a short time.
I'm confident that in two months,
you'll reach senior warriors level.
Of course, the downside is that
once the agentia takes effect,
it's nearly impossible for
you to further improve yourself.
Luo Feng. You're young
and you're a Spirit Master.
You have a big future.
You don't need this.
But this agentia...
It's available at Extreme Mall
and very expensive.
I have a friend who's a senior warrior.
He can buy it at a lower price.
I'll take it.
Count us in. We're not young anymore.
Primary senior warriors
are the best thing for us.
Okay, I'll reach to my friend later.
All of us would be senior warriors!
Mom, Dad.
Honey, what happened to your arm?
It's all right. I'm home safe and sound.
My girl. Daddy will play with you
every day from now on, OK?
(Zhang, I'll make Zhang
Zehu and his team pay!)
=Swallowed Star=
(Since the first battle
in the wilderness,)
(I've improved a lot in Genetic Energy
Practices. I gotta practice more.)
(I've mastered the first
stage of Nine thundering sabre.)
(I'm a Spirit Master. So I'm as good
as an intermediate senior warrior.)
(I can't rely too much on that.
My priority is physical fitness.)
(I immediately started practice when
I come home. I haven't taken a shower.)
Captain.
Luo Feng. There's a nice item for you
at the HR Alliance Mall. Come.
S9 flycutter?
I contacted my friend who just
came back from the wilderness.
These are part of the collection
from the beast generals they killed.
Beast generals!
They are smart and
hate warriors very much.
When they kill a warrior,
they will collect the
warrior's weapons as trophies.
For them, these trophies
are their badges.
I see.
Your flycutters were destroyed
in battle with the moon wolf.
It's not about your skill,
but the quality of the weapon.
Luo Feng, you're a Spirit Master.
The quality of your flycutters
determines your power.
These six flycutters are my gift to you.
I can't accept it. I will pay.
Zhang Ke's retirement
did make our team weaker.
But we wouldn't be afraid of Huya Squad
if you could improve fast.
All right, I'll take that.
Thank you, Captain.
I'll work hard to catch
up with the team.
You haven't got changed
since you got back from the wilderness.
Ha ha!
I was busy practicing and forgot.
(Xu Xin)
You just came back yesterday.
Why not take some rest?
I'd rather work here
as there is too much going on at home.
Work?
Oh.
In addition to her lab job,
Miss Xu is also a part-time
manager at our mall.
Luo Feng, thank you
for bringing me back.
I'll catch up with you
when I'm done with my work.
Where's Xin?
Oh.
Mr. Xu, there you are.
Miss. Xu just went up.
You are?
(HR)
I'm Luo Feng.
Luo Feng, from the Fire Hammer Team?
Thank you for bringing my sister
back from the wilderness. I'm Xu Gang.
Hello.
(So he's Xu Xin's brother.)
Xin went to the data room?
I'll go find her.
Hump.
Who is this Xu Gang, Mr. Wang?
Oh, you don't know?
The Xu Family is a big family
in the HR Alliance.
The HR Alliance is an alliance of
nine super clans around the world.
These clans are supported by
over a dozen secondary clans
among the five states.
His clan is one of
the 12 clans in our state.
(Xu Xin comes from a powerful family.
I've never heard of it.)
(Emergency!)
(The beast general, giant rock bear
is approaching Jiangnan city fast.)
(It has breached
the military's first defense.)
(The beast general, giant rock bear
is approaching Jiangnan city fast.)
Calm down, we can't deal with it.
Captain.
(Ah, here come the warriors!)
(It's Lu Gang, the God of War.)
(He saved the pilot from the fighter
destroyed by the giant rock bear.)
God of War.
-It's the Fluxay.
-Fluxay from the Nine Thundering Sabre.
(He won! Defeated the giant rock bear!)
(God of War also practiced
Nine Thundering Sabre.)
That's the God of War.
Much better than the ordinary ones.
Even our clan wants him badly.
Although a 21-year-old young,
intermediate senior warrior
and a young man from a leading family
in capital are after Xin,
I still think Xin deserves better.
Don't you agree, Luo Feng?
Mr. Xu, you don't seem to
be fond of a warrior like me.
Of course I'd respect God of War, but...
You're saying this
to get me to back off
and give up your sis. Don't worry.
I'll be the best warrior,
a true champion.
Then you'll be ashamed of
how little you thought of me today.
Coming from the same family,
Xu Xin has never been arrogant
because of her background.
Mark my words, pride and prejudice
often blindfold many.
(Giant rock bear)
(Lu Gang, an intermediate God of War)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Next episode)
(There are many monsters in 0201 again.)
(Alone.)
(Try to get back before dark.)
(How many monsters did you kill?)
(Hi, Luo Feng.)
(Something's wrong.)
(Chen. There's an incident in 0201.)
(Here's how you use
Nine Thundering Sabre.)
(There are still 20,000
people left in the city.)
(I'm not strong enough,
far from enough.)
(I'll find a strong hand)
(and make them die miserably.)
(Explode!)
Every Sunday at 10:00 a.m.
every Sunday morning