♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(I'm William Addison)
Would you like to compete with me?
(OK.)
(You didn't get overwhelmed
by a senior.)
(There are not many new students
with such courage and insight.)
(We need to know every detail
of this fight.)
(Remember this. There is no shortcut
to becoming stronger.)
(Just accept your weakness)
(and do your best.)
(Once he's suppressed,)
(the emotions of excitement
and chagrin will come.)
(He will be impulsive)
(and show his real ability.)
(Damn.)
=Episode 25=
(I can beat William
as long as I use spirit energy.)
(Luo Feng.)
Remember this.
There is no shortcut
to becoming stronger.
But talking is not enough.
You have to practice hard.
(No.)
(I didn't go to Elite Training Camp
to beat them)
(or to win 5 billion,)
(but to be stronger.)
(There's no shortcut)
(to becoming stronger.)
(Calm down.)
(I can't fall into disarray now.)
(He's really patient.)
(His swordsmanship
is totally flawless and natural.)
(To turn the table on, I can only...)
(Let's see how you avoid this.)
It's the Bodily Movement
of Nine Thundering Sabre, Fluxay.
Luo Feng has found his way.
(So fast.)
(Luo Feng's speed)
(is 50% faster than William.)
You are too slow!
Luo Feng is taking advantage
of his speed
to try to counterattack from the side.
Luo Feng!
If you dare,
fight me head on!
As you wish.
(So strong!)
(Luo Feng)
(wins the challenge.)
Good. Great. Great. Nice!
(His power is terrifying.)
(This guy's strength grows rapidly
in battle.)
(Did he really...)
Luo Feng.
You are really strong.
You grow so fast.
You're not keeping any trumps, are you?
William.
Your swordsmanship is much better
than mine.
But my combat power is stronger
than yours.
I'm faster and stronger than you.
I beat you with my comprehensive
strength.
Luo Feng is very strong.
But he doesn't seem to be a
Spirit Master.
It's not that simple.
There are 120 frames per second.
Only in this frame did he behave
abnormally.
He's vigilant.
I suspect that he is the murderer!
Since he's hiding it,
I should go and force him
to show his real strength.
(Ninth Tower)
Candice.
You're from the Paulinus clan.
You will make Luo Feng suspect you.
I suggest you spy on him before you
take action.
That's the only way left.
Bro, you just entered the camp,
and you made 5 billion!
You should buy us lunch today.
No problem.
Senior, just help yourself.
Luo Feng.
After dinner, I'll take you to someone.
He's coming.
(Feels so fierce.)
(But she is controlling her breaths.)
(If senior didn't tell me,)
(I didn't even notice her approach.)
Luo Feng.
This is Ms. Jiang.
Ms. Jiang.
(Teachers in the camp are at least
God of War.)
(And she...)
My name is Jiang Fang.
Luo Feng.
I'll be guiding and teaching you
in the camp
in the next five years.
Luo Feng.
Learn with Ms. Jiang.
I'll go back now.
OK.
I heard you beat William at noon today.
Yes.
The levels of the technique of using
sabre and sword are divided into basic,
mastery,
perfect
and artistic, four levels.
William's swordsmanship
has reached the second level.
You beat him.
Good.
Luo Feng.
Use your sabre to fight me.
I will use no more strength and speed
than you.
OK.
Teacher.
Come on.
Come again!
(Her sabre technique is good.)
(No matter how fast I am,)
(I can't break the barrier formed
by her sabre technique.)
Your sabre technique is so weak.
How did you beat William?
Teacher.
I won William with my speed.
And I'm much stronger.
So I beat him.
Yeah.
You're really fast.
Judging from the attack just now,
your strength is not weak.
What's your fist power now?
2.8 times.
2.8 times?
No wonder they took you in.
But do you know
what the fist power means
to the warriors?
The level of fist power is the multiple
of the skill the warrior uses
compared to the normal brute force
without skill.
It means the warrior's ability
to control power.
You are a primary senior warrior.
Under normal circumstances,
your strength is about ten tons.
With the unique way
of Nine Thundering Sabre,
your fist power is 2.8 times.
A punch can reach up to 28 tons,
which is far above William.
But your sabre technique
is much weaker than William.
Do you know why?
Because you are not using the power
method wisely.
You mean...
The same method can be used on the legs.
This is the key to improve
Bodily Movement.
The strength points of Nine Thundering
Sabre are in the whole body.
If your legs are weak,
the sabre technique will be much
inferior.
(No wonder my swordsmanship
can't suppress William's.)
(Theoretically, the power of Nine
Thundering Sabre is far more than that.)
Take your sabre and follow me.
=Swallowed Star=
The most important place
in Ninth Tower is the challenge room,
trial room and gravity room.
From the 1st to the 30th of every month,
there are students
in the trial room and gravity room.
Today is March 31.
So they are both empty.
This gravity room is excavated
from the relics
of ancient civilization.
(Relics of ancient civilization.)
(Commissioner Yang also said about it)
The structure of this gravity room
is beyond the current level
of human science and technology.
Look at the alloys
that make up this room.
Even someone stronger than God of War
can't leave a mark on the wall.
This is...
This is fist of the strongest man
in the world,
Hong.
Except for him,
no one else can do it.
Your physical strength is
as good as a primary senior warrior.
Nine times gravity
should be close to your limit.
(My body is getting heavier.)
(Too hard to breathe.)
How do you feel?
I feel terrible everywhere.
Under nine times gravity,
your Blood Shadow Sabre
has reached about one thousand
kilograms.
(The Blood Shadow Sabre is very heavy,)
(but the pain in my blood vessels)
(and the viscera are much worse.)
Luo Feng.
Do you know the importance
of gravity room to warriors?
Gravity range of the ancient
gravity room
is up to a thousand times.
If you train here
in extreme gravity for two hours a day,
you will grow ten times faster
than normal practices.
(Ten times.)
But
there is only one ancient gravity room.
All 183 students share it.
How much time can you get?
(Instructions for use of gravity room)
(101st-183rd students for 1 hour)
Only an hour?
There's no other way
to use the gravity room?
There are ten other gravity rooms
in the camp,
built according to the ancient
civilization and technology.
Although the gravity inside
is only three times,
the advantage is that you can use it
for two hours a day.
It's more suitable for new students
like you.
Luo Feng.
The competition in the training camp
is very fierce.
You are new here, you should seize the
opportunity to strengthen yourself.
I'll keep guiding you.
Yes, teacher.
(Most suspicious)
Except Luo Feng,
all the others have been dealt with.
Send more people to check
Luo Feng's background.
Yes, all information!
Wei.
If Luo Feng really killed you,
I will tear him to pieces!
(Jiangnan Pavilion)
(I've met a lot of guides.)
(They gave me advice,)
(praise and encouragement.)
(And)
(I keep going to a higher position.)
(But I'm getting further away
from them.)
(Now,)
(is it time for me
to protect them instead?)
(Jiang Fang, intermediate God of War.
Known as Moon Witch.)
(Luo Feng's teacher.
Good at using two-handed machetes.)
(She plays a very important role
in Luo Feng's breakthrough.)
(Elite Training Camp, gravity room.
Ancient gravity room.)
(The inner wall is made of yellow
and black alloy, extremely hard.)
(Only Hong can leave fist marks on it.)
(The gravity room can strengthen
the gravity up to 1,000 times.)
(It is important equipment
for training and upgrading.)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪Never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star")
(Next episode)
(Need material backup.)
(Please come in if you receive it.)
(90% of those who are lower
than advanced level)
(are dead.)
(Luo Feng.)
(If you see a King Beast,)
(you wouldn't even have a chance.)
(Jiangnan base city may fall.)
(Be prepared to give up.)
(Head of the monsters.)
(Where on earth is it!)
(It's really him!)
(Luo Feng.)
(We can't gamble on people's lives.)
(I don't approve of this plan.)
(Now I have to stand up.)
(Luo Feng!)