♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(Your bullets never hit me.)
(Ultrasonic device.)
(No need to worry.)
(We'll work together.)
(Someone plots against you.)
(He probably holds
grudges against Huya Squad.)
(Ah)
(Our mission is)
(to kill an iron dragon,
an advanced beast general.)
(And that egg)
(must be destroyed before it hatches.)
=Episode 16=
It's the sound of the iron dragon.
It has just laid eggs
but is still powerful.
The tougher part is the elite
monsters under its charge.
Two of them are fire triffids pigs,
the primary beast generals.
They are top ones among pig monsters.
Looks like it'd be a bitter fighting.
But it's a shame that
the egg of the iron dragon
will surely be destroyed.
Yeah, if we can get the egg,
we can turn it over
to some scientific institutions.
I heard there's one in Jingdu base city
that does researches on this.
(Jingdu base city.)
We'd kill the iron dragon first
and try our best to get the egg.
Let's do it.
Don't get held up by the herd.
Go straight to its lair!
Got it.
Sure enough, it gave up on the fight
in the liar to protect the egg.
I'll handle the iron dragon!
You take care of the
two fire triffids pigs.
OK.
(They're fighting.)
(Master Li is very quick when dodging.)
(He's perfect on the
Micro Bodily Movement.)
(No, it's definitely better than that.)
(They are indeed
advanced beast generals.)
(At least 20 meters in length.)
(More than any monster
I've ever fought before.)
(Master Wang is even stronger.)
Bastard! Prepare to die!
(The power of advanced
beast general's hit)
(is at least 250,000 kilos or more.
He'll lose if he keeps defending.)
(Master Wang could be in danger.)
(They can take advantages
of the environment and monsters around.)
(Their control over the fight is
better than mine.)
(The two of them and monsters
have been at each other's throats.)
(Right! If the egg is destroyed,
and the iron dragon will be sad,)
(they'll have a better chance.)
=Swallowed Star=
Hi, brother. How are you doing?
I'm fine. How about our parents?
Is everything okay in the neighborhood?
Mom and dad are fine.
But there's one thing.
Zhang Ke came by yesterday.
He said he found a guy
snooping around our neighborhood.
He and Chen Gu who just
returned to the base city
grabbed him and took him
to the Security Bureau.
When leaving, they asked us to come
to them if anything happens.
Brother. Is there something
going on over there?
The wilderness is as usual.
There's always something unsettling.
I'm just trying to make you safe.
Oh, by the way, brother.
I recently made a fortune in stocks.
Thanks to the money you gave me.
It's nothing.
I'll keep funding you. Just go ahead.
Make enough money and get married soon.
Nan's a freshman.
It's too early for that.
And I'm disabled.
Remember, Luo Hua.
Never call yourself disabled.
You may be disabled,
but you're not good-for-nothing.
I'll keep that in mind, brother.
I'm going back on mission.
OK, brother, be careful out
there in the wildness.
(This monster lair looks
like an old shopping mall.)
(There are about 70 beast officers
guarding the main gate.)
(I'm afraid only God of War can breach
from the front)
(and fight them.)
(Only elite monsters)
(can live on the third floor)
(to the fifth floor.)
(The iron dragon probably lives
on the first and second floor.)
(That's why it
didn't let other monsters in.)
(If I go in through the windows
of first and second floor)
(and get caught, I'd be doomed.)
(And there are a lot of monsters
on the third to the fifth floors.)
(How do I get in there
and find the egg?)
(Right! The elevator well
in this building)
(is a pass-through!)
(This is it.)
(There's a special patrol
unit guarding it.)
(Smells bad!)
(Iron dragon's egg.)
(The safest way to eliminate the threat)
(is to destroy the egg
immediately.)
(But if I give the egg
to a research institution,)
(it'd be more valuable.)
(I have to leave now!)
(The material must come from
an outfit of God of War.)
(Maybe the iron dragon
killed a God of War)
(and then collected
his outfit as a trophy.)
(He was killed in the wildness. I should
take his things back to the base city.)
Oh, no, the iron dragon's gone mad.
(They found me.)
(So many of them.)
(Come on!)
(Back then,)
(I've taken into account
all the 21 beast officers.)
(Is this the perfect level
that is one level higher than)
(Micro Bodily Movement?)
(Fire triffids pig,
primary beast general.)
(Top of the pig monsters.)
(There are
red flakes all over the body.)
(Big head with three crooked, pointy,
forward facing horns.)
(Vicious and dangerous.)
(Iron dragon, advanced beast general.)
(A very special race of monsters.
Covered in deep blue scales.)
(Five meters tall, ten meters long, with
a curved Black Unicorn on forehead.)
(Almost perfect in speed, force,
defense, mind and body structure.)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Next episode)
(I didn't expect)
(there's another master
hiding in the shadow.)
(Luo Feng.)
(I'll kill him myself sooner or later.)
(I'm the powerhouse.)
(A better genius than me)
(is unforgivable.)
(Do it.)