♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(The battle begins.)
(I'd better keep it a secret for now)
(that I'm a Spirit Master.)
(How dare someone use the volunteer team
and the injured warriors as a bait)
(to hunt high-ranking monsters.)
(It's so terrible!)
(Whoever it is,)
(we'll come after them.)
(Maybe...)
(Ah!)
(Zhang Ke!)
(Right.)
(If Gao Feng fights that old monster,)
(he will surely die,)
(and that old monster
will be badly injured.)
(Then we can)
(take advantage of it.)
=Episode 10=
Run!
Let's fan out.
At least some of us would survive.
(Why did Huya Squad do this?)
(Is it because of me?)
Luo Feng is a Spirit Master?
Follow me. We'll all survive.
Listen to Luo Feng.
The Spirit Master is awesome!
The skull is the hardest part
of a Bloodthirsty Tank.
Aim at its eyes, ears or leg joints.
We didn't kill anyone of them!
We didn't miss them.
But they blocked it.
Luo Feng is damn lucky!
Don't worry.
They are injured
and being chased by the herd.
No way they'll survive.
Let's go.
The old monster is on the move.
We need to catch it now.
Bleeding has stopped.
Huya Squad, these bastards!
It must be them
who attacked the volunteer team.
Looks like them.
How is it?
I won't die.
Ahem.
My career as a warrior is over.
Alas.
You took the shot for me.
No.
It's my fault.
I think Huya Squad attacked us
because I offended Zhang Zehu before.
Don't blame yourselves.
Compared with those killed
by monsters in the Great Nirvana,
I'm lucky that I'm still alive.
As a child, I swore that
I would kill these monsters
when I grew up.
Then I passed the warrior test,
and became a hero.
A few years later, I started a family.
Zhang, you could have gone further.
Alas.
Not exactly.
I've killed many monsters
and I'm getting tired of this.
Every time I went to the wilderness,
my wife and children would worry
about my safety.
I'm also worried
that I won't see them again.
But I didn't have the courage to quit.
The injury gives me a reason to quit.
Brother, enjoy a peaceful life then.
You can be an instructor
in the Extreme Martial Club.
And then you would have more time
for your wife and kids.
By the way, Luo Feng.
Why didn't you tell us
you're a Spirit Master?
I don't want to get into trouble.
Once it is disclosed, I have to
say goodbye to my peaceful life.
Yeah.
He's right.
The army, the martial clubs
and the clans
are trying all they can to
get Spirit Masters.
I hope you can keep it a secret for me.
Don't tell anyone.
Of course we won't.
Ha-ha.
The Fire Hammer Team
has a Spirit Master now.
If Huya Squad knew it,
they wouldn't dare to play tricks with us.
=Swallowed Star=
Boss, where is it now?
It's about 4 miles from us.
It has been staying there for a while.
That's good.
We're almost there. Hurry up.
The moon wolf!
Seeing from its size,
it should be an advanced beast officer.
But it seems to be seriously injured.
It seems to be very manic.
It's not safe here.
We need to evacuate right now.
Captain, since it's seriously injured,
let's kill it now,
in case it would hurt others.
Even if it's seriously injured,
we can't beat it.
Captain, I'll try.
Are you sure you would win?
No, but I can escape unscathed.
It will be OK.
All right, be careful.
Don't force yourself.
Be careful!
OK.
Don't worry.
Zhang Ke.
Do you think Luo Feng
can kill that moon wolf?
According to his previous performance,
Luo Feng has reached the level of
an advanced soldier in strength.
And Spirit Master is two levels higher.
That is, the intermediate
senior warrior.
Right.
But it's not easy for
an intermediate senior warrior
to win the moon wolf,
an advanced beast officer.
Fortunately, it was seriously injured.
Luo Feng still has chance.
(Its target is actually the fly-cutters!)
(It reacts like this,)
(maybe because it was hurt
by fly-cutters of other Spirit Master?)
(Ha.)
(Fine, be my touchstone.)
(I'll see what I'm capable of.)
(So fast.)
Luo Feng's fly-cutters didn't work?
(I should focus all my strength )
(on one point as I once did.)
(I have to lead it into the air)
(and then use the fly-cutters
to slow it down.)
Got you!
Is it serious?
No, I'm lucky this time.
It's not about luck.
You adjusted your tactics in time
and focused on one fly-cutter
which made it six times
stronger and faster.
So that you could kill it
in the last blow.
Look!
What is it?
Go.
What?
Fur, teeth and claws.
These high-valued stuffs
have been robbed.
How dare they rob our stuff!
They're so dead!
They just dissected its body.
For security reasons, they'd rush to
the supply base immediately.
So
let's go to the supply base now
and try to stop the poachers on the way.
So
Huya Squad ambushed
the warriors and volunteers
just to hunt the moon wolf?
Yeah.
Their locator is in its body.
It's probably them.
Alas.
They must be mad as their prey was gone.
Hump!
They're lucky enough.
When we get back, let's report this to
the Security Bureau and make them pay.
Can't find them.
Where are they?
We won't find them.
Look. Is it the Fire Hammer Team?
(The things in his hand...)
Captain, Huya Squad is over there.
OK.
Chen, what are you yelling about?
You took our prey and now
are showing off your arrogance here !
No one seems to have
taught you about karma.
Let's start with you.
Leave your arm here!
Ah!
Don't regret messing with my people.
(Moon wolf. Advanced beast officer.
The royal family of wolf monsters. )
(Cruel, eccentric and murderous.
They love to attack humans as well as other monsters.)
(So it is called the "Hunter".)
(Bloodthirsty tank intermediate officer.
Ranking second among the pig monsters. )
(Huge, covered with scales, amazing defense.
It is as strong as a red galloping tank.)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Next episode)
(The treasure that can make a broken arm regenerate.)
(I have completely mastered the
first stage of Nine thundering sabre.)
(I'm a Spirit Master.)
(So I'm almost as strong as
an intermediate senior warrior.)
(Emergency!)
(The beast general, giant rock bear)
(is approaching Jiangnan city fast.)
(Warriors are the
ultimate power in the world.)
(The so-called consortia)
(is nothing compared to)
(the most powerful warrior.)