♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(I want you all to work hard!)
(We all want to be warriors.)
(Let's compete.)
(Don't you worry about that.)
(You know he's good.)
(Yes, Young Master.
We found Luo Feng's residence.)
(Leave your right hand here,
and we'll let you go.)
(They are not here to fight.)
(What if I testify?)
(Mr. Jiang.)
(There's still time, I...)
(-What's wrong with you, Feng?
-Luo Feng!)
(I will sign up for the test of
warrior-to-be.)
=Episode 3=
(Tencent Video)
I'm heading out.
Dad, why do you leave so early today?
I've got a big job today
and I can make few hundred bucks more.
Feng, good luck!
Thanks.
Dad, today is a big day.
Don't miss the good news from brother.
Rest assured. If I pass the test,
you'll be the first to know.
Did you hear it?
They asked you to bring your phone.
Yes, it's with me.
It's about time. I'm leaving, too.
Let me introduce you.
This is Yang Wu.
He'll also take the test today.
Instructor Jiang said that you just
finished College Entrance Examination.
Are you only 18?
He's young, but there's a good chance
he could pass the test.
Hey, kid,
you've got a big future ahead of you!
I'm overpraised. Yang, you're so strong.
I'm sure you will pass the test.
Alas.
It's not about who's stronger.
It's more about comprehensive quality
and the speed to react.
Uh, Yang. What's this test like?
Hey, you'll know it soon.
To be the warrior,
it won't be easy to pass the test.
There will be a field test after that.
You should take every test seriously.
(Looks like I need to work harder.)
Oh, Luo Feng.
Have you decided what to do
after you pass the test?
Well, I haven't thought about that.
Instructor Jiang says you're talented.
Generally, there are four choices
for the warriors.
The first is to join the army,
protecting the country and people
from monsters.
The second is to join a martial club,
taking the initiative
to attack the monsters.
The third is to join a syndicate,
helping with the recovery
of industrial economy.
The fourth is to be a mercenary,
maintaining order in
remote and volatile areas.
Take me as an example,
I'll join the Extreme Martial Club.
Instructor Jiang, then...
I know.
As long as you become a warrior
and join our club,
we will provide you
with a detached villa
and at least
20,000 Chinese dollars a month.
Ha ha. I was afraid you might forget.
(A detached villa and a base salary
of 20,000 Chinese dollars per month.)
(A detached villa is worth
at least 200 million.)
(If I got the title of the warrior,)
(mom and Hua could...)
(Alas.)
(She's got enrolled in a top college
and will become a social elite.)
(But I chose to be the warrior.)
(I'm afraid I'll never see her again.)
Guys, this is the form of
colleges you wish to go.
Now, I want you to fill it out.
(Luo Feng is absent today, too.)
What's up?
Young Master. It's done!
Okay, I'll be right back.
Zhang Haobai.
You haven't handed in your form!
Monitor. Please give Feng's form to me.
He's not coming today.
What happened to Luo Feng?
Wasn't he discharged?
Oh, it's nothing.
Feng is busy with the test of
warrior-to-be.
Wow, the test of warrior-to-be?
Ha ha.
You think Feng gave up because
he failed the exam?
He's not that kind of person.
Ah!
(Test of warrior-to-be?)
Luo Feng.
Yes.
Instructor Jiang.
We're almost there.
Yangzhou headquarters of martial clubs,
Extreme Martial Club.
(This is where the test will be held.)
(Master is also here.)
(This sword, is it...)
(him?)
I'm the chief instructor of
Yangzhou Extreme Martial Club, Wu Tong.
I'll host the test today.
Come on in. The exam's about to start.
(Test-in-process)
(This is the old world.)
(I could only see the old world
in base city from a distance.)
(These weapons...)
Pick a weapon. Here they come!
(They?)
One-horned boar. Iron-hair boar.
Shadowcat!
These are monsters!
Hum! Let's go!
(Calm down!)
(I can't be defeated here.)
Hey, buddy.
First time here?
Don't worry, it's very normal.
My name is Li...
A tiger mastiff!
(No, I'm not a coward.)
(Nice! The neck is the weakness
of the one-horned boar.)
(He can make quick adjustments
in such a condition,)
(this kid's got talent.)
Gee. The weapon is too heavy to use.
There are more monsters, over there!
Maybe the real test starts now.
=Swallowed Star=
(Transport Company of Luo's)
Oh,
Mr. Zhang's courtyard is so splendid!
Wish I could live
in a good house someday.
Stop daydreaming. Just get to work.
I want to go back to my sons soon.
Come on,
we all know you have two good sons.
One, two, three. Go!
Young Master, he's Luo Feng's father.
Ah, what's so sticky?
The danger index is 79,
it's just a monster of level G.
The test has always been difficult.
Better be careful.
The index is rising.
100, 150, 300, over 500 now!
It's coming!
Oh, no!
It's close.
Level E. The gold vulture!
What to do, Yang?
Run!
(Come on!)
(No. Bad timing!)
Instructor Jiang,
I'm sorry I didn't do well.
Luo Feng.
Yes.
I'm here to tell you
that you've passed this test.
What?
It doesn't require you
to kill all the monsters.
We are testing your fighting ability.
You get points by injuring the monsters
and avoiding their attacks.
From statistical analysis, we found that
your power reached 1,101 kilograms
when killing the tiger mastiff
and the speed was 28.6 meters per second
when you avoided attacks
from the gold vulture.
You did much better than
our base requirement.
With your extraordinary ability
to survive and kill,
you scored the highest.
(Candidates of the Warrior-to-be test.)
(Comprehensive Score)
Look.
(Luo Feng    Power:1,101 kg    Total:11 )
Sorry to keep you waiting.
(Candidates of the Warrior-to-be test.
Luo Feng.)
First of all, congratulations.
The field test
will be held on the first day
of the next month.
Please prepare yourselves.
Yes.
I have to warn you
that you might get
injured or killed
in the field test.
Got it.
Now, follow me to get your rewards
of being the warrior-to-be.
Oh, there's a reward for
those who have passed the test?
Of course.
Otherwise,
you won't be able to
attend the field test
with your current strength.
The field test is so hard.
So what's the reward?
Genetic Energy Practices.
(Dad)
(Calling)
(Can't get through.
Dad's still at work?)
I remembered he said he was going to...
You've crushed my ground.
It's from South Mountain. A piece costs
hundred thousand. Can you afford it? ‬
I told you the crack was there before.
Why did you push us?
Right!
Don't you play rough with me.
Mind where you are right now.
Young man, how could you do that?
You guys, shut them down.
(I'll show you what happens
if you mess with me.)
Stop!
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Next episode)
(I want your men to make a scene.)
(I'll take it as
I've heard nothing today.)
(We got a report of a break-in.)
(Is there a misunderstanding?)
(I'll keep you in prison forever.)
(Kid.
You're about to get your ass kicked.)
(He'll be released someday.)
(I'm afraid)
(he alone caused
the greatest number of casualties.)
(Did you)
(find someone
even stronger than the warrior-to-be?)
(Get rid of someone for me.)
(=Swallowed Star= Time to Shine
Every Sunday at 10 a.m.)