♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(No matter who killed my son,)
(I will never let him go!)
(Release the news of Wei's death.)
(Let every warrior know)
(that I, Venina Paulinus,)
(am offering a reward of 100 billion.)
(To deal with the sky-high
price reward,)
(Senior warrior Primary)
(I need to)
(plan carefully from now on.)
(I have an egg of
the iron dragon's. Do you want it?)
(Looks like I'm going on a long
journey again.)
(Sorry, Mr. Luo Hua, please understand
that it's not easy to be a parent.)
(We only have one daughter,
we want you to leave her.)
(Hello.)
(Hua...)
(Will Palace Hotel)
(Hua, something happened to him!)
=Episode 19=
What's the matter, mom?
How's Hua?
He has no life risk now.
What's the matter, mom? Tell me!
Don't worry, Feng. It's fine now.
Mom, what happened?
It's Hua's girlfriend, Zhen Nan.
Her parents
want Hua to leave their daughter.
Hua couldn't stand it, and...
Hua rowed the wheelchair into
the pool in the park.
Fortunately, Zhang Ke was doing
morning exercises in the park.
He saved Hua.
Brother Zhang Ke.
(Morning news: The only son Li Wei
was killed.)
(Mr. and Mrs. Li issued a 100 billion
reward to hunt the murderer.)
Luo Feng.
Brother Zhang Ke.
Your brother is out of danger now.
Don't worry.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
You're welcome. You saved me before.
Well, it's time for me to teach
at the Extreme Martial Club.
Be careful and come back to
see your brother soon.
OK.
(Hua committed suicide)
(because of his leg disability.)
(I must earn enough money)
(to buy the water of life and
cure his legs.)
(And Zhang Ke's arm.)
(Welcome to Will Palace Hotel)
Mr. Wei.
Wang Hou.
That's me.
(Wang Hou, professional agent)
(I don't know if I can trust him.)
(I shouldn't tell him who I am now.)
Come on, come on.
(The only son Li Wei was killed.)
(Mr. and Mrs. Li issued a 100 billion
to hunt the murderer.)
Mr. Wei. I'd go straight to the point.
I heard that you want to sell a
dragon egg.
Is it an azure dragon's egg?
The azure dragon is a King Beast,
much stronger than beast generals.
Do you think I can nail a King Beast?
Ha ha ha!
Right, if you don't mind...
Help yourself.
It's iron dragon's egg.
The embryo in it is still alive.
Oh, what my buyer wants most is
living embryos of the beast generals'.
It helps to study RR viruses.
Buyer?
(It'd be awful if it was the bait
Li Wei's parents secretly left behind.)
I can't tell you who he is,
but I can tell you
that he is a great philanthropist.
After purchasing this dragon egg,
he'll give it to the RR virus
research institute.
You know,
businessmen like to connect
with the politicians in this way.
(Normal heart rate.)
(It seems that he didn't lie.)
Mr. Wei.
I'll pay the highest price I can offer
within my jurisdiction
to buy your dragon egg.
Five billion. Is that enough?
No problem. And...
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone about you.
OK, then transfer the money to this account.
Wow.
International bank account
with the best security.
Ha ha, got it.
(Received 5 billion)
-It's a pleasant cooperation.
-Yeah.
(The price of dragon eggs is
really high.)
(If I sell it to HR Alliance,
I'd get more.)
(But I'll be targeted by Li Wei's
parents right away.)
(It seems I have to do it
step by step)
(to buy the water of life.)
Excuse me, are you Luo Feng?
You are?
I...
I'm Zhen Nan.
Zhen Nan, you are Hua's...
Please give this to Hua.
(To Luo Hua)
Feng, you're back.
Dad, where's Hua?
He's in the room, and he's all right.
But he's a little down.
Your mom's with him.
I got it!
Feng.
Mom, go get some rest.
Hua.
Luo Hua, I promise you.
You will marry Nan.
Brother, stop talking about it.
It won't work.
Nan and I have no future at all.
I've given up, too.
I'll never fall in love again in my life.
I don't deserve it.
What are you talking about?
I'll hurt whoever marries me.
Giving up marriage might be the best choice.
I am a disabled person.
How dare I want a girlfriend
or marriage?
Coward!
Nan didn't give up,
how could you give up?
What do you mean?
She wrote this for you.
See for yourself!
(Luo Hua, I was worried when I heard
that you had fallen into the water.)
(Are you OK? My parents sent the
message behind my back.)
(I didn't know until now that they
didn't want us to be together.)
(But I won't give up.
I hope you won't give up, either.)
(Love you forever, Zhen Nan.)
Brother.
Come up.
Be with her and that's good for
both of you.
But I am...
I have a way.
I heard that
there is a magic potion called
the water of life in this world.
It is made from the spirit of
the Earth King.
It can regenerate the broken arms
and the broken legs.
As long as you're alive,
all serious traumas can be cured.
Earth King.
That's a King Beast.
The water of life must be expensive.
What's this?
My bank balance.
I want to tell you that your brother
can afford the water of life.
And you will stand on your feet.
Brother!
=Swallowed Star=
Mr. and Mrs. Li.
How is it?
After the investigation,
we find that there are 26 out of
the 506 targets
are with motives.
Some of them were oppressed
by the HR Alliance.
Some had a grudge
against the young master's bodyguards.
Some are Huya Squad's enemies.
Huya Squad.
The enemy of this damn team
dared to kill my son!
Yao, I think it's possible.
Do you remember
they were in danger once before
Wei was killed?
I informed Wang Tong and Li Kan
to save them.
The whole team died that time,
except for the team leader Pan Ya.
And Wei, Liu and Ka Long escaped.
You mean Wei wasn't the target?
Right.
Of course, the murderer might be
aiming at Wei.
But he started with others
to confuse us.
There is another possibility.
What's it?
The murderer has been plotting
for a long time.
He probably didn't wear a communication
watch when he committed the murder.
So, he's not among the 506
targets at all!
Keep checking these 506 people.
One by one!
And expand the search.
Anyone with a motive has to be
investigated.
I'd rather kill a thousand than
let one go.
Yes.
Yao, who on earth do you think did it?
There are more than 10 Gods of War
in the world
who hold grudges against me.
In order to make you the CEO
of Hanxia District of the HR Alliance,
we both offended a lot of people.
Fortunately, you came out from the ruins
of ancient civilization successfully
and your strength greatly improved.
That's why those bastards dared not
to hurt us.
Ruins of the ancient civilization. Hump!
I'll find out who killed Wei.
And...
Hua, come to eat.
Where's brother?
Feng went to the Extreme Martial Club
to practice again.
If he doesn't come back soon,
he will miss the New Year.
(I can't slack off as brother
is working so hard.)
(Nan, believe me.)
(Fist power 28081kg)
28 tons.
The power of your fist is 28 tons!
Thank you, Uncle Wu.
After these days' training,
I can finally control
the Nine Thundering Sabre Level 3 a bit.
You're making terrible progress!
Half a year ago,
you were just a primary soldier.
Now, as an intermediate senior warrior,
I can't win over you!
Uncle Wu, you flattered me.
(Now I can fight intermediate senior
warriors, not using the Spirit Energy.)
(If I use the Spirit Energy,
I might fight)
(against the primary Gods of War.)
I can't teach you anything anymore.
What's your plan next?
After the New Year, our Fire Hammer
Team is going to the wilderness again.
After all, actual combat is the most
effective way to enhance strength.
Well, you're right. Let's call it a day.
It's New Year's Eve. Go back early.
OK.
Director Zhu Ge, this is Wu Tong.
I would like to recommend a person
for special training.
With his talent,
it's a pity if there is no expert
teaching him.
Yes, it's Luo Feng.
(God of War)
(is not out of my reach.)
(During the great nirvana of mankind,)
(all countries launched the Ark Program)
(and escaped from the earth.)
(They looked for a new home
in the vast universe.)
(The ark was destroyed
by monsters during its construction,)
(the Ark Program failed.)
(The site is left in the wilderness.)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪Never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star")
(Next episode)
(Special training?)
(If Luo Feng goes to the training, there will be
only four people in Fire Hammer Team.)
(Emergency rescue signal!)
(It's in city 023, set off immediately!)
(Each sword light seems
to contain more than ten shots.)
(Is he a God of War?)
(Luo Feng, the martial club
will have a better arrangement for you.)
(So it means...)
(Sigh.)
(The Fire Hammer Team will be
dismissed.)