♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(It had just laid egg)
(and is still powerful.)
(Looks like it'd be a bitter fighting.)
(Brother. Anything going on over there?)
(I'm just trying to
make sure you're safe.)
(It gave up the fight in the liar)
(to protect the egg.)
(We'd kill the iron dragon first.)
(But giving the egg to
a research institution)
(would be more valuable.)
(The advanced beast general
is really something.)
(It is stronger than any monster
I've ever fought before.)
=Episode 17=
Oh, no. The iron dragon's gone mad.
Hum. Try to escape?
Get out of here!
Go.
I don't think they will just let us go.
Something must have
happened to its lair.
That's why it's in such
a hurry to get back.
The only thing that
would make it so anxious
is the egg.
Let's take care of the enemies here.
(The iron dragon!)
(Right in time.)
(Its tail is 11 meters long.
It can't hit me from there.)
(56 centimeters short.)
(Damn it.)
(It has reached its maximum height.)
(It hasn't given up yet! Advanced beast
generals have good eyesight.)
(Even if I fly to two to three
kilometers above the sea level,)
(it can still see me as long as
there are no obstacles.)
(I have to break through the clouds.)
(I'm such an idiot!)
(The sky above city 003)
(is full of flying monsters.)
(I'd die if I have to deal with
the flying monsters)
(up here.)
(Damn it.)
(If I go down fast,
I'll hit iron dragon for sure.)
(If I slow down, the flying
monsters will catch me.)
(It's now or never!)
(The injury is getting worse.)
(The residential building
could cover me up.)
(I can hide in the underground garage.)
(I don't think the iron
dragon would find me.)
(The iron dragon is commanding
the herds around to hunt me down.)
(It's impossible to stay
here until I recover from the wound.)
(But it's okay.)
(I forgot when I was
escaping the hunting)
(that there are many
subway tunnels in this city.)
(The tunnel is small.)
(The iron dragon can't get in.)
(I sought far
and neglected what lied close at hand.)
(That almost killed me.)
(Lucky me.)
(There's a tunnel not far from here.)
I didn't expect there's another
master hiding in the shadow.
He stole the egg
while we were fighting the iron dragon.
No wonder it was so
desperate and ran away.
Now there's nothing left in its lair.
Two fire triffids pigs were killed.
All the other monsters have fled.
If the mystic master
joined forces with us,
we would kill that iron
dragon more easily.
Everyone has his own ambition.
He's been able to escape
from so many beast officers,
and he stole the egg.
He must be
as strong as an intermediate God of War.
Wang, then we...
We hurt the iron dragon.
It ran like hell for the egg.
Its injury will definitely get worse.
Let's follow the trail and investigate.
It won't escape.
OK.
Young Master's training is
not yet fulfilled.
But his strength has improved a lot.
Still far from what my dad wants to see.
My parents are both Gods of War.
Of course I'm good.
By the way, Pan Ya.
You said Luo Feng is 19 years old,
but he's a primary senior warrior?
How could he compare with you?
Our Huya Squad won't
get peace of mind until he's dead!
Now I'm the only one left in the team.
I'll kill him myself sooner or later.
(Thunder Team!)
=Swallowed Star=
Luo Feng!
I've been looking for you everywhere.
Good that I find you here.
Ah, it's Luo Feng. I've seen you before.
(Captain of Huya Squad.)
(Pan Ya wants to kill me.
If these three weren't here,)
(he'd be a piece of cake.
But those three...)
(The old man and the big white guy
are both advanced senior warriors.)
(Li Wei isn't strong enough,)
(but his background is terrifying.)
Sir, this captain has a grudge
against Fire Hammer Team.
And you can see what he's about to do.
Our state has laws
that forbid warriors to kill each other.
I'm not asking you to stop him.
But please stay out of this.
(As long as the three stay out of it,
I should be able to...)
Now you are begging for mercy.
Oh dear.
When you grabbed the two-headed
black snake from us with the Indians,
you never expected this, did you?
I was holding a grudge
against the Huya Squad,
and didn't pay attention to the
interests of the whole. Can you...
The two-headed black snake
is not a rare material.
Normally, I wouldn't even be interested.
But it's unforgivable
that you humiliated me.
Wei.
Shut up. You're not qualified
to call him like that.
As the son of God of War,
I have all the materials I need.
But what I really like to collect
is the human skulls.
Especially those known
as the "gifted" juvenile warriors.
I've killed a few of
the gifted like you.
After all, I don't want to see a
genius better than me.
You have no idea how interesting it is
to see a genius
genuflecting on his knees
with no dignity.
What's in your bag?
Two Gods of War, Li Kan and Wang
Tong were fighting
the iron dragon there.
The fight was fierce.
And you came out of the subway tunnel
connecting to the battlefield.
You snuck into iron dragon's lair
when they were fighting.
You came out of that tunnel in a panic,
and forgot to observe the
environment around you.
You must want to get back
to the base city soon.
What treasure did you
steal from its lair?
So you came here to be killed by us
with a nice present for us.
(What should I do?
I'll lose if I fight them.)
(But I'll be damned if I don't resist.)
(I'll take chance.)
Yes. The iron dragon's egg
is right inside my bag.
The iron dragon's egg?
I'm sure you're aware of
the value of the egg.
It's worth at least five billion
in the market, and
more in the black market.
(The old man and the big
white man are high in the rank,)
(but after all, five billion is a lot.)
(They will want it.)
Kill him and we'll split the money.
I don't care about the
money, but the egg...
They could be my trophy in city 003.
Do it.
Then come and get it!
You want to split the money? Go to die!
There's a hidden weapon in your bag!
You plotted against an advanced
senior warrior like Cullen.
Not bad!
But the same trick won't work on me!
You're wrong about one thing.
There is no hidden weapon in my bag.
No?
More?
You're a Spirit Master!
You're quite vigilant.
I couldn't knock you out
at close range.
So I have to strike a fatal blow
when you thought you got it all.
You...
I won't kill you since
you didn't come at me.
What's that look?
Is it sympathy for the weak?
No, I'm a genius. I'm the strong one!
There's no better genius than me!
So, I must kill you!
I'm better than you!
Don't feel sorry for me!
The noise of the battle should have
alerted the surrounding monsters.
I'm going to kill you, Luo Feng!
Ah!
(003 City Mall, a shopping center
built by humans in the old world.)
(It's now the liar of the iron dragon.
There are five floors.)
(The iron dragon occupies two floors.)
(The other three are inhabited
by its elite monsters.)
(The iron dragon egg, laid by the iron
dragon living in the 003 city mall.)
(It's cyan with subtle patterns.
Great value of scientific research.)
(It's worth 5 billion in the black market.)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪Never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Next episode)
(Bastard!)
(I won't let him off!)
(Recently, nine warriors
have been killed in city 003.)
(I'm sure the murderer
has friends and family!)
(Your powers can be unleashed
beyond these walls.)
(But people here envy you.)
(That's right. Let him live in
fear of betrayal all day long!)
(You're alone in the wilderness.)
(Luo Feng, something bad happened.)
(Hua, he's in trouble.)