♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(For your team member here,)
(I still want to be a warrior...)
(Regeneration is possible in the world.)
(It's called water of life.)
(The knives are gift to you.)
(I'm Xu Gang.)
(Emergency! Beast general giant rock bear)
(is approaching Jiangnan city.)
(It's Lu Gang, the God of War.)
(He defeats the beast!)
=Episode 12=
(Mom and dad start to enjoy life
after working hard for most of their lives.)
(Hua's enjoying
his relationship.)
(Nan)
(Thanks to this city,
the last stronghold of human.)
(Warriors should fight for it.)
(In the second stage of
Nine Thundering Sabre,)
(I need to strike twice when hitting.
It's too hard.)
(We can't let monsters
ruin the city.)
(I have to master the second stage
while in the wilderness this time.)
Captain, send me to county 0201.
Alone?
Yes.
The monster is a threat to our city,
I'd like to help.
But there's a lot of monsters out there,
once they besiege you...
Spirit Master's not
afraid of a siege, though.
But are you sure?
Only you?
It's dangerous to go to the wilderness alone.
I know.
Where are you heading?
County 0201.
If you can kill monsters
and collect trophies
like ears,
you'll get reward from the army.
Try to get back before dark.
Here we go.
How many monsters
did you kill?
198.
Luo. Word is out in the base
that you killed many monsters.
They call you "Psycho."
Ah?
So handsome!
(Luo Feng No. 1)
He is Luo Feng.
-No offense. We admire you!
-Hey, Luo Feng!
(Many monsters in the wilderness
were heading to)
(0201 yesterday evening.)
(The military has raise)
(response level for the threats,)
(sending warriors to supply base.)
(Many monsters were killed
in the last 50 days.)
(My body power
has also improved.)
(But my sabre skill hasn't.)
(Something's wrong.
It's Wan Dong. After him...)
(Rat surge!)
Chen, bad things happened
to 0201. Come to Club.
Ah, Luo Feng went there!
I heard Lu Gang is also there.
I hope they're all right.
(Emergency! The military claims)
(rat monsters coming to 0201,)
(forming level 3 rat surge.)
(They can ruin a military base in minutes.)
(The military has deployed several planes
and rescue vehicles.)
(So far, no exact figures
on casualties.)
(Luo Feng.)
(Breaking News)
Are you OK?
(Damn, it's a dead end.)
(It's too late.)
You're Lu Gang,
God of War!
(It's true power of
Nine Thundering Sabre.)
Come on.
=Swallowed Star=
How's it going?
We're doing everything
we can to evacuate
and concentrate troops.
But according to their current speed,
the supply base in the Northern District
will be destroyed before the military arrives.
There are still
20,000 people there.
We're expecting heavy casualties.
When will the rat surge reach the base?
-Less than five minutes.
-What about the military?
The conveyor has arrived over the base.
But the warplanes ran into an accident.
It'll take at least ten minutes.
That means if someone holds off
the rat surge for five minutes,
The base will be safe, right?
Yes, but Mr. Lu, your safety is
very vital, please...
Let's go another way.
Now, jump!
(It's amazing he slows them down
with fire and lightning.)
Here's how you use
Nine Thundering Sabre.
Go!
When will planes arrive?
In 5 minutes at least.
I'll find ways to stall them.
It's working!
The leader seems wise.
The plan is outflanking and
these are cover.
Planes can't stay close to the ground long.
You two, jump in.
What about you?
You are future of the city.
Go.
Mr. Lu Gang!
Too many rats.
He will be exhausted at this rate.
(Finally.)
I'll ask captain
if they're back.
(Through combined efforts,)
(Jiangnan city survived
from the rate surge safely.)
However, casualties are huge.
God of War sacrificed in this case.
The military disclosed Lu Gang
used himself as bait
to attract the rats.
(In the course of evolution,)
(human are facing constant
threats of destroy.)
(warriors are the only hope.)
(But I'm not strong enough.)
(I'm not strong enough.)
(I just can't make the second strike!)
(Mr. Lu Gang was gentle
when hitting.)
(That's what this is about.)
(I was trying too hard,
which is beyond my physical fitness.)
(So there isn't enough
explosive force.)
Out!
He mastered
Nine Thundering Sabre!
You can't beat him.
We should get rid of him sooner.
Don't worry, I'll find someone strong
enough to make them die miserably.
(Rat monsters leader)
(Blood Shadow Sabre)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Next episode)
(Paulinus Clan, one of the 9 clans of HR Alliance?)
(Keep him away from my sister.)
(Rumor has it that
he's outgunned God of War.)
(Fire Hammer Team came!)
(They're seeking their death.)
(Captain, we got a big one.)
(Prepare for battle.)
(It's after me.)
(We can't just sit and watch them die.)
(What a sharp look!)
(Hurry. Spread out!)