♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(It's good. You've improved a lot)
(after a month's special training.)
(Welcome to the Extreme Martial Club.)
(You can move into
the villa for warriors today.)
(Your task)
(is to go there to
collect the supplies.)
(We will be monitoring
you all the time.)
(If the warriors-to-be
attack each other,)
(we will arrest them on the spot.)
(The air is filled with smell of blood.)
(Next goal.)
(What? Golden eagle?)
(Terminate the test now!)
=Episode 7=
Usually, only Level-H to Level-F
monsters would be out there.
How come there's
a golden eagle of Level-D?
Terminate the test now!
No, let it be.
Director Zhuge.
This golden eagle is a newly born larva.
It's probably somewhere
between Level E to F.
As long as they play their cards right,
they should be able to escape
if not defeating it.
Even so,
we should get rid of
this hidden trouble soon.
Wouldn't it be better to leave that
to the warriors-to-be?
Who is the nearest warrior-to-be
to the golden eagle?
The signal shows it's Luo Feng.
Luo Feng.
Bring it on!
(It used the body of a one-horned boar
to shield and attack.)
(So intelligent!)
(Is golden eager invincible?)
(There must be another way.)
Missed it.
(Come on!)
(Come at me at full speed.)
(I won't make the
same mistake this time.)
Luo Feng.
Well, this kid is lucky.
He eluded the deadly beak
and the flying sabre
fell right next to him.
Otherwise,
he'd have been ripped to pieces.
No.
The golden eager's flight path
is changed
by the flying sabre.
That's exactly why
he was "lucky".
It's well-planned.
He planned all that.
The golden eager's fatal attack
missed him by 1.5cm in the last minute.
Could it be...
The test is over. I'll announce
the list of qualified candidates.
Lv Fang collected
three samples and one supply.
Yang Wu collected
three samples and two supplies.
Luo Feng collected 36 samples
and five supplies.
Wan Dong collected 51 samples
and seven supplies.
So many!
Luo Feng. Chin up!
You are quite impressive!
There'll be plenty of chances for you
to beat him.
It's not on my mind at all.
That's the list of qualified candidates.
Congratulations! You are warriors now.
Yeah!
Yeah, we passed!
Bravo!
(Finally.)
Feng.
=Swallowed Star=
Dear new warrior, Luo Feng,
welcome to the House of the Extreme.
I'm your personal guide.
This is a place where
you can find information about warriors,
and buy all kinds of weapons, guidance,
special books, outfits, medicaments,
vehicles and so on.
When you become a real warrior,
you'll have the chance to learn about
Spirit Master.
Do you have information on
Spirit Master?
Based on your rank and permission,
I can show you the following:
(Warrior 101 database)
Spirit Masters are the most
gifted warriors.
There are two types of them.
(Telekinesis)
First, those who can control items.
They can control weapons
to attack from a distance.
(Psychic attack)
Second, those who master psychic attack.
They can attack opponents' spirits.
Attack on spirits.
The Spirit Master learn faster
than the average warriors
thanks to their Spirit Energy.
Usually, the Spirit Master
is about two grades
higher in the spirits
than the warrior of the same rank.
(So I'm as powerful as
an advanced senior warrior?)
That's all you're permitted to know
about the Spirit Master now.
Is there anything else
you'd like to know, Mr. Luo Feng?
No. Show me the catalog,
special books on attacking skills.
OK.
(Misty sword.
Phantom knife tactic. Destruction)
(Feature)
Well.
(Category: swordsmanship.
Level: S. Price: 3 billion)
(Category: sabre skills. Level: SS.
Price: 10 billion)
(Category: marksmanship. Level: Top.
Price: 100 billion)
Oh, my god, it's so expensive.
Don't worry. You can buy it by stages.
Take Destruction for example.
It's from Hong, the world's strongest
warrior, and comes in six stages.
The world's strongest warrior, Hong.
Hong is the most powerful man
in the world today.
He's also the founder of the
Extreme Martial Club.
He alone can destroy a big nation.
Although it's the best marksmanship,
I'm good at sabre.
Nine thundering sabre.
It belongs to the second best warrior
in the world.
Thunder's ultimate sabre skills.
It's extremely difficult to master.
I'm good at sabre.
This is the most powerful one
in the world.
A qualified warrior fights hard
to be on top.
Purchase the first three stages
of the Nine thundering sabre.
Certified and purchased.
The first three stages will be
delivered within 24 hours.
Do you want to purchase
weapons and outfits?
(Extreme Mall)
Almost forgot about them.
(A-6, 20 million. Shield. B-5, 3 million.
O5 Series, 18 million. )
(Sabre A-6, 20 million)
Oh, my god, 20 million Huaxia dollars
isn't enough for these.
Luo Feng.
You are...?
My name is Chen Gu.
An advanced senior warrior
in Extreme Martial Club in Jiangnan.
General Instructor Wu asked me
to bring you this.
Nine thundering sabre. That's fast.
It requires a warrior to
deliver it in person?
It's for the best sabre skill
in the world.
Many people are after it.
It has to be delivered by
someone reliable.
And there are a few things
I'd like to tell you in person.
In person?
According to the rule, you can only
study this skill yourself.
No copying or reselling.
Or you will be wanted by the two
major martial clubs and all governments.
I see.
And one more thing.
Luo Feng, one month ago,
you were in Yi'an detention house,
right?
They have looked into it.
I didn't pick a fight.
I know. It's been found that
a young man named Zhang Haobai
was behind it.
Assassination of a warrior-to-be
is a felony.
He might be sentenced to jail for
20 to 30 years or face death penalty.
His uncle, Zhang Zehu contacted
Extreme Martial Club
and wanted to settle out of court.
Out of court?
Zhang Zehu is a warrior of
Thunder and Lightning Martial Club.
I know him a little.
Luo Feng, don't worry.
I'll go with you.
General Instructor Wu Tong.
It was my nephew's fault.
But it didn't cause much harm.
I'm willing to pay five million Huaxia dollars
for compensation.
Five million?
You think you can bully a rookie
just like that?
You said it was a negotiation.
But you came
with three members of Huya Squad.
Aren't you throwing your weight about?
Do you think we're easy to mess with?
How much do you want?
Well, 50 million will do.
50 million?
And your nephew should apologize
to Luo Feng's father.
Get down on his knees and apologize.
Luo Feng has joined
Extreme Martial Club.
Of course, we need to get justice for
his family.
You're crossing the line!
OK, 50 million is fine.
But getting down on his knees
and apologizing is too much.
It's not up to you or me.
Only one person has the final say.
Mr. Zhang Zehu,
thank you for coming here in person.
But there's no way I'll agree
to settle out of court.
Zhang Haobai hurt me. That's fine.
But he hurt my innocent family.
I will never forgive him.
He must be brought to justice!
Does this kid know the rules?
We respect Luo Feng's decision.
Damn.
You're in Extreme Martial Club.
Behave yourselves.
You should know that I will be
a senior warrior very soon.
So what?
Alright, you're ballsy!
Let's go.
Impressive. You're neither haughty
nor humble in front of
the advanced soldiers.
Thank you, Chen, Instructor Jiang
and General Instructor Wu.
Don't mention it. We're family.
But it's a pity.
I really need that 50 million.
I spent most of my money
on the sabre skill.
Now I can't even afford my outfits.
It's nothing, I have the reward points.
I can buy them at a 50% discount.
I'll buy it for you and
you transfer the money to me later.
It works that way?
Of course, we're on the same team.
It's nothing.
Same team?
Director Zhuge asked me to put
you in a team of senior warriors.
After thorough consideration, I decided
to put you on the Fire Hammer Team.
I'm the lieutenant of the team.
I'll take care of you.
Of course, I should warn you
the missions are often
extremely dangerous.
If you're bad on your first mission
or you slow your team down,
we'll have to kick you out.
I see.
I can't believe he escaped the attacks
from the golden eager.
I will get rid of him sooner or later.
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Next episode)
(This kid is in the Fire Hammer Team!)
(Everybody, run!)
(Don't mind me.)
(Emergency, let's go now.)
(0201, oh.)
(Is that today's...)
(How dares he act like this
on our old turf?)
(Xu Xin, why?)
(Remember. Care for nothing.)
(I'm killing you right away.)
(Luo Feng's in danger, go help him!)
(So many monsters in this city.)
(It's time to hunt.)
(Swallowed Star Time to Shine
Every Sunday at 10 a.m.)