♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(You've passed B-level test.)
(Congratulations, Luo Feng)
(19 years old, primary senior warrior.)
(He's on the list of suspects
who killed Wei.)
(Jiangnan Pavilion is over there.)
(Shi Jiang, Zhao Ruo. Your junior
is here.)
(Higher points
mean rarer cultivation resources.)
(If you find that he might be
a Spirit Master.)
(William, I need you to do something.)
(Special training begins.)
=Episode 24=
(Strength 28000)
(Thanks to the resources here,)
(I've mastered the power generating
method of Nine Thundering Sabre.)
(Now my fist power is 2.8 times
stronger.)
(The power of my legs and feet,
along with my running speed)
(have been greatly improved.)
The training has been completed.
You're working too hard.
What time is it, senior?
It's almost eight o'clock.
Tonight, all the seniors from Hanxia
will come and welcome you.
(Invitation)
Don't be late!
I won't.
Cheers!
Finally.
You are the protagonist.
Of course, everyone comes to you.
And Senior Chu Qiang paid for all this.
You should drink to him later.
Senior Chu Qiang?
(No.2 Chu Qiang 540601)
He's second on the list.
There he is.
The world's major organizations
are all trying to woo him.
But a year ago,
Senior Chu Qiang has joined the
Hanxia Military.
After that, he is even busier,
but he keeps training
until late at night almost every day.
Wait for me. Let's make a toast to
Senior Chu Qiang together.
Hello.
We are partying downstairs,
but we got too much cake.
Would you like to try it?
Thank you.
What's up?
I'm William Addison from Europa.
I've been in training camp for a year.
Your name is Luo Feng, right?
Yeah.
I've always been curious
about Hanxia's martial arts.
I heard they recruited you only.
There must be something unique
about your skills.
Would you like to compete with me?
Compete?
The competition among students is
carried out in the challenge room of
Ninth Tower.
There's usually a stake.
But let's just learn from each other
with no stake.
William, Luo Feng is new here.
So you want to fight him and earn money?
Bet with me if you dare.
We're just learning from each other.
There's no stake.
William, we all know that
you're looking for new people to fight.
A student told me just now,
that he went to the challenge room
with you
and lost a billion.
Now you're looking for new people
to fight with no stake.
What do you want?
I'm keen on studying martial arts
all over the world.
I'm familiar with the senior students'
moves.
I just want to learn some new moves
from new students.
It's not about money.
So there's no stake.
Excuses.
It's a pity that the new students
from Hanxia recently
are not good.
My friend said that
Hanxia's martial arts are in name only,
but I don't believe it.
Because I believe Luo Feng's strength
will not disappoint me, right?
(There must be some purpose behind
his obvious provocative approach.)
(But he's so aggressive.)
(I have to save Hanxia's honor.)
If you want to fight, let's do it.
But it's no fun without a stake.
A little bit more, five billion.
How can you bet with him?
What's in your mind!
All right, I'll bet you.
OK.
I'll apply to use the challenge room
when I get back.
See you later.
Luo Feng.
Senior Chu Qiang.
So there's no need to introduce myself.
Senior, Luo Feng is new here.
And he's gambling 5 billion
with a senior.
Help me persuade him.
I'm sorry, sis.
He didn't get overwhelmed by a senior.
There are not many new students
with such courage and insight.
But talking is not enough.
You have to practice hard.
When you're done,
if you want to join our military,
just come to me!
Thank you, senior.
=Swallowed Star=
I'm pissed.
Even Senior Chu Qiang is helping you!
All right, all right.
Don't be angry, senior.
Those who can enter the
Elite Training Camp
are all geniuses.
No matter how talented you are,
you have to
suffer losses when fighting the seniors.
(Combat power level setting)
I've checked.
I think combat power is the indicator
that best reflects
(Medium: potential. Good: qualified.)
the strength of students.
(Excellent 8-16: excellent students.)
(Battle scene)
My combat power is 4.48, which is good.
And those students
who have been training for a year
(Gymnasium)
are at the medium level, like William.
So I dare to agree.
I won't spare you if you lose.
It's done.
It's tomorrow morning.
You're still worried, Yao.
We need to know every detail of
this fight.
I'm going to watch it myself.
Well, who do you think will win today?
I think Luo Feng will.
I think William.
Luo Feng. Remember this.
There is no shortcut to
becoming stronger.
Just accept your weakness and
do your best.
Don't worry about winning or losing.
(Ninth Tower)
(Waiting to connect)
(Connected)
(Battle scene)
Please select the battle scene.
You choose.
(Gymnasium)
Luo Feng, you could have chosen a scene
that was good for you.
But you chose a gymnasium with
no obstacles in it.
You are too confident
or you have other skills?
(The battle begins.)
Come on!
Fly-cutter.
It's a common weapon for Spirit Masters.
William's starting to take the lead.
So mean!
This is called maximizing the
utilization of equipment.
His nose is slightly open and
his breath comes in short pants.
He's taking it.
Provocative approach is not enough.
He should have a backup plan.
Anger will make him aggressive and
move more,
and there will be more flaws.
(He plays tricks. Now he's trying to
suppress me. If this goes on...)
Once he's suppressed, the emotions
of excitement and chagrin will come.
He will be impulsive and
show his real ability.
(William Addison, To-be God of War,
from Europa.)
(Medium combat power.
Senior student in the training camp.)
(He often cheats new students
to fight and gamble to earn money.)
(Candice Paulinus, To-be God of War,
from the Paulinus clan.)
(Talented warrior. The first
successor of the Paulinus clan.)
(He ranked 89 in the first month,
which broke the record.)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪Never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star")
(Next episode)
(His swordsmanship)
(is totally flawless and natural.)
(I can only...)
(It's not that simple.)
(I'll tear him to pieces.)
(No one can do it except him.)
(I go to Elite Training Camp to
be stronger.)
(There is no shortcut to
becoming stronger.)