♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
I won't make the same mistake this time.
Congratulations! You are warriors now.
Yeah, we passed!
Dear new warrior, Luo Feng,
welcome to the House of the Extreme.
Purchase the first three stages
of the Nine thundering sabre.
He must be brought to justice!
I'm the lieutenant of the team.
I'll take care of you.
I will get rid of him
sooner or later.
=Episode 8=
(School Uniform)
(Fire Hammer Team Battle Suit)
(Luo Feng.
It's your first day in our team.)
(You're lucky.
There's a pop-up mission.)
Captain, I'd like you to meet our
new recruit, Luo Feng.
This is our captain, Gao Feng.
Captain.
Go get it. I'm sure you'll fit in soon.
(Strong strength, but he seems to
be carefully controlling it.)
Yes. Captain!
These three are all members
of the Fire Hammer Team.
(Wei Tie, Zhang Ke, Chen Gu, Wei Qing)
Wei Tie, Zhang Ke, Wei Qing.
This is the manager of HR Alliance.
Please brief them.
Here's the thing.
We established a volunteer team within
our Biology Institute
and sent them to collect DNA samples
of monsters in county 0201 lately.
But we were informed that the team
was under attack.
Please bring them back safe and sound.
Doesn't the HR Alliance claim to
control half of the world's economy?
Why don't you send
a team of warriors to do it?
Alas.
Only one of their communication watches
is still working,
and the battery will be dead
in less than an hour.
Once the signal is gone,
we might not be able to rescue them.
We won't make it in an hour.
You're the only hope now.
Well, if that's the case...
Please find those volunteers.
They're very important
to the HR Alliance.
Since it's an emergency, let's go now.
If you have any questions,
let's talk on the way.
Everybody, run!
Don't mind me.
Wei Qing, Wei Tie.
Luo Feng is also a sabre user.
Teach him a little bit more.
Well, got it. Don't hold us back.
I think something's
around here.
What is it?
Well.
Shh, I heard it, too.
Get ready to fight.
Some big monsters are coming!
It's one-horned boar!
Luo Feng's in danger, go help him!
This is... Nine Thundering Sabre?
He's not skillful enough. Let's go.
Looks like Luo Feng can handle it.
Wait a minute.
Ha ha! Impressive. It's your first fight
and you killed a senior beast soldier.
Senior beast soldier?
Yes, the so-called level-F.
We warriors put the monsters
into different ranks.
There are beast soldiers,
officers and generals.
Each is subdivided into primary,
intermediate and advanced level,like us.
Bro Qing.
The unicorn is yours as you killed it.
Manager Wang, about the list of
the volunteers, how's it going?
(It's in your communication watches.)
OK.
(Xu Xin, female, Jiangnan University)
(Xu Xin, why is she...)
(She's also on the list.)
Luo Feng, you know someone on the list?
Yes.
We'll do the search and rescue together.
There will be
the best possible team plan.
Remember. Care for nothing.
Don't act recklessly.
Look what I found.
What's this, Zhang?
Ultrasonic device.
It's been transmitting at frequencies
that humans can't hear.
That's why there are
so many monsters here.
Someone's using it
to attract them to come.
Well,
this is the only way to county 0201.
They're using the warriors passing by
as bait to attract the monsters
and then kill them in one shot.
So the bastards are lurking nearby.
I didn't see anyone.
It's probably one of their traps.
Maybe they are lurking
somewhere else as we speak.
Let's speed up and get there
as soon as possible.
Boss, did you just hear anything?
What's up?
It'd be bad if any one of them
is still alive.
Let's go.
There are a lot of monsters here.
=Swallowed Star=
(LOS)
No contact yet?
No.
That's weird. It hasn't been long.
Could be another incident.
We need to hurry.
(Huya Squad, Zhang Zehu)
(This kid's with the Fire Hammer Team?)
Hey, you look awful.
How's your nephew doing?
Chen, you're taking a rookie with you.
He might hold you up
and get you all killed.
We're in a hurry to save lives,
or else,
I have to teach you guys a lesson!
(Huya Squad, One-eye)
You don't like them, why not kill them?
It can wait.
Did you hear he mentioned saving lives?
Looks like they're going to 0201.
0201. Is that today's...
Let's inform the captain
that we've got another visitor.
(Huya Squad Li Xiao)
Boss. Here comes the Fire Hammer Team.
Alright.
(Huya Squad, Pan Ya)
(Geezer, we got the perfect bait for you.)
(Look like no one's been here.
Next house.)
Did you reach them?
No.
That's impossible.
Ultrasound devices are placed here too.
We need to be very careful.
Judging from the watch
and the ultrasonic device,
they must have been attacked
by monsters.
There must be casualties.
There are many monsters in the county.
It'd be hard for them to
survive the siege.
It's time to hunt.
What's up?
Maybe we missed some of their devices.
If that comes from the devices,
then the monsters...
So many monsters here!
Run! We can't be held up.
(Huya Squad Dong. Huya Squad Tietou)
Tietou, you stay and coordinate with Zhang Zehu.
OK.
Dong. Follow the Fire Hammer Team.
Don't move.
Let me make it harder for you.
Bastards, how dare they
act like this on our old turf?
There are too many monsters,
we can't search for the survivors.
They run so fast.
Looks like I missed someone last time.
It doesn't matter.
I'm killing you right away.
Gunshot?
Over there!
Maybe the survivors are in danger?
Let's get over there.
Matched.
She's the rescue target, Xu Xin.
There are more monsters!
Take the survivor and run!
Let's go, let's hide in the building.
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Next episode)
(Probably, they are also a warrior's team.)
(A corrupt and depraved one.)
(Let's just finish it soon.)
(I'll be your opponent.)
(RR Virus Blocker).
(It's a trick!)
(Luo Feng!)
(Make him the bait.)
(It'll work!)
(There's an enemy. Now!)
(Get in the building.)
(Your death)
(will bring us a fortune.)
(It's over.)
(What's that noise? Xu Xin!)
(Swallowed Star Time to Shine
Every Sunday at 10 a.m.)