♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(RR virus brought a new
intelligent species, the Monster.)
(A thousand bombs failed
to stop the Monsters.)
(More than two billion people
died worldwide.)
(Then, mankind has entered the era of
Great Nirvana.)
(With military strength, technology and
our indomitable willpower,)
(The warriors were born.)
(The Mutant Monster has crossed
No Man's Land.)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(This is the power of the warrior.)
(I've decided)
(to be)
(a warrior!)
=Episode 2=
(Yi'an No.3 High School)
(Tomorrow is college entrance exam.)
(I hope you can work hard)
(to live up to your 12 years' efforts.)
(Thought without learning is perilous)
(Dismiss.)
Stand up!
Goodbye, teacher.
Zhang Haobai.
Luo Feng,
I heard you want to be a warrior?
To be honest, me, too.
It's just that I'm much closer to
this goal than you are.
What do you mean?
It's easy. I also want to be a warrior.
Let's compete.
Good,I happen to
need someone to be my sparring.
Tell you what, I am a senior student
of a martial club.
So are they.
Well, Zhang Haobai?
Those two are also our senior students?
What about that kid?
It seems that we don't have his data.
They want to be a warrior, too.
You can have a friendly competition.
Ah!
I'd love to.
That's fast.
It should be 25 meters per second.
Puff! My teeth!
Luo Feng, wait for it!
(Yi'an No.3 High School)
(School ahead, slow down)
Instructor Jiang, well...
Knock down three of our senior students
in such a short time.
The boy's hitting power
is at least 800 kg.
Check on him later.
Yes.
(School ahead, slow down)
(There are 200 million people living
in Jiangnan City.)
(Densely-populated.)
(I can't afford
a neighborhood like this.)
(Unless,
I get into the Military Academy!)
(Memory of Hua Xia)
(Certificate Handling)
Brother, it took you 20 seconds more
to climb up today.
The dishes mom cooked are getting cold.
No, I was held up.
There's no elevator in civilian areas.
(If we can live in a fancy building
with elevator,)
(Hua doesn't have to stay home)
(when we are all out.)
You promised to
take me for a walk after supper.
Hey, I do that every day.
I always keep my words.
(Twenty Financial Theories by Price)
Hua, what are you reading?
Twenty Financial Theories by Price.
I want to do a good research on
Investment Principles.
Nice! If it wasn't for the car accident,
your grades must be better than mine.
Brother!
Come and eat.
Braised pork? Why...
Tomorrow is the day for
college entrance exam.
You deserve something good.
So, are you confident?
Don't worry, mom.
You know he's good.
Feng, which college you want to apply?
Dad, with my grades, I think
I can apply for
Jiangnan No.1 Military Academy.
If I become the key person to be trained
by the country,
we can get a house.
That's good. Mom and dad don't
have to sleep on the couch every night.
Feng, we know you are thoughtful.
But it's your wish to be a warrior.
The rich go to martial clubs,
and we can't afford it.
Dad, don't say that.
Although we are not rich,
you always give Hua and me
whatever you have.
I never feel I'm worse than anyone.
Besides, I can be a warrior on my own.
You are right!
(Unlocking. Dredge the sewer)
Haha.
Yes, Young Master.
We found Luo Feng's residence.
Luo,
get down to work after finishing eating.
Double pay
for working overtime at night!
Luo?
Mom, dad, I'm leaving.
Take care.
What's going on?
Road construction. Detour, please.
Why didn't you inform us yesterday?
Construction for Zhang's Tower.
The road's closed.
I have to run then.
I'm running out of time.
I can't be late.
Boy, we have no grudge against you.
But you have offended the wrong people.
We don't want to give you a hard time.
Leave your right hand here,
and we'll let you go.
My right hand is used for writing,
as well as beating dogs.
Come on!
Boy, you're doomed.
You can't beat me. Get lost!
If they are the normal gangsters,
they would have left in
this kind of situation.
They are not here to fight.
Why hasn't Feng come yet?
The exam will start soon.
Hard nut to crack. It's about time...
It's getting late!
=Swallowed Star=
(Yi'an No.3 High School)
(Slow down)
What's going on? It's late.
Looks like they made it.
Alright, you may start.
Teacher, I'm also an examinee.
(Thought without learning is perilous)
No, according to the rules,
you are not allowed to enter 15 minutes
after we start.
But, I'm not too late.
You are not allowed to
enter no matter what.
What if I testify?
Mr. Jiang.
I witnessed everything.
He's late for a reason.
Besides, it wasn't past 15 minutes
when he reached.
I saw it clearly.
Of course.
You are in charge of the safety of
the college entrance examination,
as well as the instructor of
Extreme Martial Club in Yi'an district.
I would never doubt your words.
Extreme Martial Club.
Senior student of Extreme Martial Club.
Please, come in.
Go ahead, kid.
Thank you.
He made it?
But do you think
you are totally safe now?
There are 30 minutes left. Hurry up.
Why do you peek at my paper?
I didn't.
Quiet!
Teacher, it's true.
-He peeked at my paper.
-Bullshit.
Go back to your seat.
Nonsense!
You two, stop!
What are you doing?
Ah!
(Thought without learning is perilous)
Oh, I'm so sorry, Mr. Luo Feng.
I didn't mean it.
You!
All of you go back to your seats.
But teacher, my test paper...
What happened has happened.
Hurry and finish your paper.
But...
(There's still time for me.)
There are 10 minutes left.
Remember to check your paper.
Two more questions, I still have time.
Five minutes left.
There's still time, I...
-What's wrong with you, Feng?
-Luo Feng!
Haobai, you did well
in the exam this time.
One more step further to
become a warrior.
Dad, my goal is to be
an elite warrior like uncle.
Good. Ambitious!
Bro, if he passes the test for
warrior-to-be during college,
I will get him into our Huya team.
Thank you, uncle.
I'm sure I'll pass the test.
Haobai, I heard that a good student with
good grades in your school
fainted during the exam?
It's Luo Feng.
He thinks he has good skills and grades,
and never respects me.
He deserved it.
Luo Feng, you're awake.
Xu Xin, you...
You fainted
during the exam the other day,
I'm here to visit you on behalf of
the student union.
Thank you for
what happened earlier.
Never mind.
By the way, your parents have stayed for
three days, and they went back just now.
Really? I've been in a coma for so long?
Luo Feng, you've been in a coma long.
Come and have food.
What about an apple for you?
You!
Luo Feng.
Calm down.
Failing in the examination is nothing.
Your health is the most important thing.
You can take it again next year.
Yes, your health is the most important.
Have some.
I didn't know you are quite close.
Of course.
Besides,
schoolmates should help each other.
Humph.
Thank you so much, President Zhang.
Oh, Xu Xin. We need to deal with
handover procedures of student union.
I think it's about time.
Now that Luo Feng is awake,
let's visit him another day.
Okay then. Luo Feng, I'm leaving.
Take care.
(Yi'an No.3 High School)
(Today, the exam result comes out.)
(I missed two questions, but...)
Feng, here!
Don't be nervous. You'll be fine.
I'm there. What about you?
Did you see?
Am I there?
(Jiangnan No.2 Military Academy)
(Jiangnan No.1 Military Academy)
I made it!
(Jiangnan University)
No...
Your griping power is at least 300 kg.
And hitting power might be over 900 kg.
You are... Instructor Jiang.
Sorry. You helped me so much.
But I still failed.
Don't be discouraged.
You'll have a better opportunity.
The other day,
I saw you fight those
three senior martial club students,
your hitting power was about 800 kg.
In just a few days,
it actually exceeded 900 kg.
It's unbelievable!
In other words,
you are now as good as a warrior-to-be.
Warrior-to-be?
It's the first step towards
becoming a warrior.
Unlike the college entrance examination,
there is no threshold for the test.
It's held
at the beginning of each month.
As long as you pass
the test and the Field Test,
you will be awarded the title of warrior
and become a real warrior.
However,
there are other requirements, too.
Only after actual testing
can we find out about it.
But you should have a good chance.
Really?
(If I can become a warrior,)
(the welfare provided by the country)
(will let parents and Hua
live a good life.)
(Dad doesn't have to work hard
every day)
(and Hua could study Finance.)
(I will sign up for)
(the test for warrior-to-be.)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪to be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
We're almost there.
Work hard today.
Sorry, captain, for making you wait.
Young Master, it's done.
Here...
Stop!
Choose your weapon, they are here!
This sword, could it be...
(Calm down!)
The index is rising.
Yang, what to do?
I'll show you
the consequences of offending me.
It might be my last chance.
What's wrong with Luo Feng?
(=Swallowed Star Time to Shine=
Every Sunday at 10 a.m.)