♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(War of God Preparatory Camp, then...)
(Yes, 90% warriors in Elite
Training Camp)
(will be the Gods of War.)
(But on one condition,)
(you have to pass the B-level test.)
(Heng Xia is a young warrior selected)
(by the Extreme Martial Club
for basic training camp this year.)
(I can help you with the money problem.)
(Xu Xin went out with a boy
I don't know.)
(It's a rare opportunity!
You should study for five years.)
(I'll be waiting for you.)
(You are Luo Feng?)
(My name is Wang Xingping,
from the Wang family in Jingdu.)
(I advise you to leave Xu Xin.)
=Episode 22=
Brother Wang, you are also here.
Senior Luo Feng!
Senior?
You know each other?
We just met.
Brother Wang, don't you like
to meet some talented warriors?
Senior Luo Feng is going to enter
the world's top Elite Training Camp.
(Elite Training Camp?)
Much better than me.
(My family tried to spend 50 billion
to buy a place but failed.)
Brother Wang, you know that.
Senior Luo Feng's
performance evaluation
is a primary senior warrior,
but his real strength...
It's said that he can even fight against
a giant rock bear, a beast general.
Giant rock bear?
Huh?
It's a shame that I didn't win
in the end.
Commissioner Yang dealt with it.
(Luo Feng is much stronger than
I expected.)
(He'd become a God of War
in two or three years.)
(I'm such a fool.)
(What should I do now?)
Brother Wang.
Luo Feng.
I was wrong.
Please don't take it to heart.
What's going on?
It's OK. It's just a misunderstanding.
Guys. I have to go now.
Brother Wang.
You wanted to fight with
Senior Luo Feng just now?
Feng, take good care of yourself there.
Stay safe.
OK.
I got it!
Hua, take good care of parents.
(Domestic departure)
Brother, don't worry.
Ha ha ha, little boy.
Luo Feng.
It's time to go.
OK.
(Cordon Do not cross)
I'm going.
Goodbye, mom and dad.
(Domestic departure 03)
Goodbye, brother.
(Yi'an No.3 High School)
(Life Science)
(The flight will arrive
in Hongning base city in 10 minutes.)
(Please take your belongings with you.)
The owner of the martial club manages
the whole base city by himself.
Hongning base city is located
in the west of Asia.
He built it with a group of followers
during the Great Nirvana.
So that the refugees could live there.
As time goes by, the base city
has become bigger and bigger.
He is the strongest in the world today,
Hong?
Yes, thanks to him,
no King Beast dares
to harass Hongning base city yet.
It is the safest of the 23 base cities
in the world.
All right, we're ready.
We'll arrive soon.
(Domestic arrival 03)
(Exit 4)
(Slow down Exit 1)
(I... can't move.)
(The black dragon's eyes
look more horrible)
(than being stared at
by an iron dragon.)
This is actually a pair of
real dragon eyes.
From a King Beast.
The black dragon bred from the volcano
caused great losses to human beings.
After the owner killed it,
he got these eyes and put it
in the black dragon sculpture
to guard Elite Training Camp.
He wanted to remind the students
that they will be responsible
for destroying these monsters
and protecting human civilization
in the future.
These are...
This is the ranking of fighting
capacity for each student.
The higher they rank,
the more resources they have.
The one who ranks in the last three
for three times will be eliminated.
Eliminated?
Don't think you can relax
after entering Elite Training Camp.
The intensity of competition is
much higher here.
All right, come with me.
They are the students of
Elite Training Camp.
Yes.
The Elite Training Camp
recruits 30 to 40 students a year.
Two thirds are recruited from the basic
training camp of Extreme Martial Club.
The rest are recruited from
all over the world.
Good! Come on!
Heng Xia,
I'm going to take Luo Feng to test.
You are free to visit or return to
the entrance.
The teacher will take you
to the basic training camp.
It's a three-year course.
And the number of students is far
more than the Elite Training Camp.
It's a fierce competition.
You have to work hard.
I will.
Got it.
Well done.
Here we are.
This is the Ninth Tower.
A place for all trainees to
learn and train.
We will take your B-level test here.
=Swallowed Star=
You are Luo Feng?
Inspector Wang, this is Luo Feng,
the probationary student for the test.
(Inspector? A senior position
in the Extreme Martial Club?)
I'm the examiner of this B-level test.
I'll take you to the examination room.
OK.
Inspector Wang,
please allow me to watch the test.
Wait in the hall.
Luo Feng, follow me.
Go.
OK.
(Testing)
(Elite Training Camp)
Wear it, your mind will enter a virtual
space which is just like the real.
We'll put you in the test tower
for the B-level test.
(Virtual space?)
Follow me.
This is the test tower,
an important place for students and teachers
of Elite Training Camp to improve themselves.
There are seven floors.
The level is based on the progress
you've made.
I can only get to the fifth floor.
The owner can get to the sixth floor.
(That is to say, none of them
got into the seventh floor.)
When you enter the test tower,
the system will teach you what to do.
I'll leave the virtual space and
check outside.
Luo Feng, wish you success!
(Please choose battle suit and weapon.)
(The B-level test will start
in 120 seconds.)
(Please kill all the monsters
within 30 minutes.)
The content of this test is
to kill all the 100 wild bulls)
(within 30 minutes.
(There are a lot of them.)
(But I've dealt with
the wild bulls before.)
(Ninth Tower)
(No.)
(In this virtual space,
my physical fitness is weakened.)
He finally noticed it.
(Spirit energy is not working.)
In virtual space, everyone's physical
strength will be reset to primary level
to test the students' ability to bring
the limited conditions into full play.
Didn't you tell him?
The elite students should quickly
understand the status quo
and make response. It's essential.
(I see. It's a test of ability
under limited conditions.)
(I'll have to fight!)
Ah!
(This body can only use a part of
my strength, but now...)
Nice! He instantly launched
a counterattack while moving.
Nine Thundering Sabre Level 3.
This is the Micro Bodily Movement.
But it is not enough for
the B-level test.
(Damn, they noticed that I wanted)
(to launch a more powerful attack.)
To deal with the siege of nearly 100
wild bull, the primary beast officers.
There is only one way to win.
The Perfect Bodily Movement.
Perfect level, that is to master
the surrounding environment completely,
use everything around,
even the smallest stone,
to dodge perfectly.
He and the environment should be
like a whole.
(Luo Feng, can you do it?)
(Nine Thundering Sabre, Fluxay!)
(Let's use technology to make up
for the bodily movement.)
(My physical strength is declining,
but more than half wild bulls are left.)
(Using Nine Thundering Sabre)
(has made me exhausted.)
(And disturbance of consciousness.)
(Black Dragon Square of Elite Training Camp
is located at the gate of Elite Training Camp)
(There is a 50-meter giant black dragon
in the center)
(The dragon eyes are from
an SS-level King Beast)
(The black dragon ranking list is
located in the Black Dragon Square)
(The ranking of all students is updating
all the time)
(Inspector His position is second only
to the founder Hong in the Extreme Martial Club)
(Only those who are stronger than
God of War can get this position)
(There are five inspectors now who are
in charge of the round table meeting,)
(the highest standard meeting
of the Extreme Martial Club)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪Never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star")
(Next episode)
(19 years old, primary senior warrior)
(is a Spirit Master.)
(The top 30 students in the training
camp are all as strong as a God of War.)
(It's just they didn't apply for
the title.)
(Be close to him.)
(What could possibly be difficult
for you,)
(the first successor of Paulinus Clan?)
(He is very strong.
I'm not sure I can beat him.)
(The clan is thinking to draw him over
to our side.)
(What?)
(William, I need you to do something.)