♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel
"Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(Mr. Lu Gang's funeral)
(will be held at the Heroes Hall
at 10:00 a.m. this morning.)
(The war between warriors)
(and beasts will continue.)
(It is said)
(that he's beyond
God of War.)
(We can't let
Mr. Lu Gang die for nothing.)
(That's City 003,)
(which used to be
the economic center,)
(Shanghai.)
(This one's mine.)
=Episode 14=
(They are the...)
This one's mine.
You can leave now.
(Looks like the mixed-race man
being protected)
(is the most important person
in the team.)
This is ours!
(Sniper!)
Back off if you want to stay alive!
Those three from the Paulinus Clan
are not to be trifled with.
Once you intervene in this,
you can't get out.
Have you decided?
Don't forget
my teammate's got a sniper rifle
pointing at you, too.
Why get in the way?
Warriors should never rob others.
You shouldn't have flaunted.
(They've parted. It's time!)
Captain, Chen, I have an idea.
Done?
Please spare the Indian team.
Who are you to make demands?
Because
I will save your Young Master's life.
(Blank ammunition).
If you don't spare them,
I won't help you anymore.
Bastard!
You're just a primary senior warrior!
Wait, we will let them go.
Do we just let it go?
Sniper rifles won't threat us much.
But Young Master
is only an intermediate senior warrior.
If he's shot, he might be dead
or seriously injured.
Young Master. You're here to practice.
Just deal with the monsters yourself.
All right, let's go.
You're lucky this time. Luo Feng.
A valuable prey was right
in front of us!
Your safety comes first
in this operation.
Please understand.
Pan Ya.
Master Liu.
The two-headed black snake is
indeed a treasure.
But not nearly as important as
Young Master's safety.
Huya Squad should know that
when taking this task.
If anything happens to him,
you know what would happen next.
Got it.
It seems that Fire Hammer Team
has grown a lot in strength.
I see.
Captain, we can't hesitate anymore
especially for Luo Feng.
They say Luo Feng is
a primary senior warrior now.
This kid's got a lot of potential.
We can't just let it be.
I'll see what I can do. At the worst,
we'd pay Mr. Liu and others
for help.
Hang in there.
Can you still see Huya Squad?
Yes,
they're heading north down the street.
I want to shoot them all!
Their previous secret plot
is found by us.
So they don't want us to be stronger.
They might strike again
if they get an opportunity.
They got backing. There are 9 of them.
It's harder to get avenge for Zhang.
Our safety is also a problem.
Captain, Chen.
Why don't you fall back
with the Indian team?
Luo Feng, you mean...
This time, they held back because
of their Young Master.
They're far more powerful than us,
but they gave in.
Once their Young Master is settled,
there's a good chance
they will retaliate madly.
It would be safer to go
with the Indian team at this point.
You're not coming with us?
If two advanced senior warriors
launch attack,
we may not even have a chance to react.
So instead of waiting and defending,
I'd better track them down
and know their movements.
Then I'll go with you.
Chen, I can do it. I have spirit energy.
I can get away even if it's dangerous.
Luo Feng has a point.
You're just a liability.
Trust Luo Feng.
This is a much more dangerous situation.
An advanced senior warrior can kill
a primary senior warrior easily.
And there are two, be very careful!
Don't take any chances.
If you're discovered, escape first!
=Swallowed Star=
(It should be here.)
Pan Ya, the information you gave me on
the Fire Hammer Team is reliable, right?
Absolutely. We have accurate information
on them.
The only problem is Luo Feng. I think
he's as good as
a primary senior warrior.
In that case,
call me when your team finds out
where Fire Hammer Team is.
Yes.
(I can defeat
the Huya Squad all by myself now.)
(When they're separated
from the two advanced senior warriors,)
(I'm going to take them down.)
(If Huya Squad
has lost fighting capacity,)
(they won't attack Fire Hammer Team.)
Hump.
It's cool to have a rich dad.
He can hire 2 advanced senior warriors
as bodyguards,
and let our entire team protect him.
Don't compare yourself with him.
Time to go.
What about the hotel, boss?
One-eye and Li Xiao will stay.
Let's go now.
(The other two should still
be at the hotel, shall I attack?)
(If I do, the other 7 would be on alert.
I'll wait.)
(Patience.
I'm sure the chance will come.)
(Too organized.)
(Two of Huya Squad's men are staying.
There's no chance at all.)
(It's day 10 and I can't wait anymore.)
(Zhang Zehu and Li Xiao should be
at the hotel today.)
(I'll beat them
while they're scattered.)
(The person who stays
should be on a lower floor.)
How's the injury?
It's no big deal. Fire Hammer Team's got
a vendetta against us.
They're dead!
Hu, I heard you went straight to
Luo Feng's house.
Ha ha, I can't deal with him,
but his family is a piece of cake.
Assaulting warriors' family members
is a felony.
And there are many monitors
at his place.
Yes, but outside that area is fine.
Oh, I see.
Remember Cobra?
Those desperadoes can do that well.
Cobra's been investigating
Luo Feng's family for some time.
His dad sometimes goes back to
Nan'an Residence to meet his mates.
There's a pretty covert road
on his mom's way to grocery store.
These are ideal places
with less surveillance.
And the families of Zhang Ke and Chen Gu
in his neighborhood.
I'll find a way to take them all down.
Shh.
How dare you hurt my family.
I'll make you pay!
This is Cobra's regular call.
If I don't answer,
he'll know I'm in danger. I don't know
what will happen to your family then.
Let go now!
There's no regular call!
It's too late now.
(Charon, advanced senior warrior.)
(Lieutenant of Thunder Team.
Li Wei's bodyguard.)
(A strong and tall white man,
armed with Huge Two-Handed Sword.)
(Elder Liu, advanced senior warrior.)
(Captain of Thunder Team.
Li Wei's bodyguard.)
(Calm, sophisticated, responsible
and good at analyzing the situation.)
(Li Wei, intermediate senior warrior,
from the Paulinus Clan of HR Alliance.)
(His parents are Gods of War.
His family is rich.)
(Selfish and domineering. He was spoiled
since childhood, and wasted talents.)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Next episode)
(This operation is dangerous.)
(Miles around would be
involved in the fighting.)
(Even if it's dangerous,
I've got to try.)
(A man who's done nothing but fail.)
(Ha ha, they must really like you.)
(I need to use a good deal
of tact to deal with you.)
(So strong!)
(But don't you worry.)
(Your family will be with you soon.)
(Swallowed Star Time to Shine
Every Sunday at 10 a.m.)