♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(Feng)
(take good care of yourself there.)
(The higher they rank,
the more resources they have.)
(I'm the examiner of this B-level test.)
(Next, I'll take you to the
examination room.)
(Please choose battle suit and weapon.)
(B-level test will start in
120 seconds.)
(In this virtual space,
my physical fitness is weakened.)
(To deal with the siege of nearly 100
wild bulls, the primary beast officers.)
(There is only one way to win.)
=Episode 23=
(Using Nine Thundering Sabre
continuously)
(has made me exhausted.)
(And disturbance of consciousness.)
(This is...)
(The breath.)
(The breath of wild bull.)
(The breath of grass.)
(Even the breath of earth and stones.)
This is...
Perfect Bodily Movement!
(Perfect Bodily Movement)
(is about mastering the surrounding
environment completely,)
(use everything around,)
(even the smallest stone,)
(to dodge perfectly.)
(He and the environment)
(should be like a whole.)
(The test is over.)
(Completed)
(It took 21 minutes and 18 seconds.)
(All 100 wild bulls are killed.)
(You've passed B-level test.)
(Why does it end now?)
Give me more wild bulls!
If I keep fighting,
my Bodily Movement will improve more.
(Testing)
Congratulations, Luo Feng.
Commissioner Yang.
Inspector Wang.
Don't call me commissioner.
You should call me teacher now.
Teacher?
I am also a teacher at
Elite Training Camp.
I kept that from you
to avoid arousing suspicion.
Now you can choose two numbers as the
last two digits of your student number.
Today is March 29th, 2057.
And you will enter Elite Training Camp
on the 1st of next month.
(Elite Training Student registration)
So your first four numbers are 5704.
You can choose the last two.
I can choose?
That's city 003.
It's called water of life.
The price is as high as 30 billion.
(Xu Xin: Luo Feng, it's my birthday.
Would you like to have dinner with me?)
(February 3)
I'll go with 03.
(No. 183 Luo Feng 570403)
(City 003)
(Luo Feng Elite Training Camp student)
Luo Feng.
HR Alliance just got the news
that Luo Feng has passed the
entrance test of Elite Training Camp.
The clan is thinking to draw him over
to our side.
If I remember correctly...
Yes.
He's on the list of suspects
who killed Wei.
19 years old,
primary senior warrior,
a Spirit Master?
Not sure yet.
He's definitely stronger than Wei
as he can enter Elite Training Camp.
He is highly suspicious.
(Jiangnan base city)
Do you know anyone in
Elite Training Camp?
Yes.
Come on.
Well done!
Another round. Good! Come on!
Luo Feng.
Jiangnan Pavilion is over there.
It will be your home in
Elite Training Camp.
Jiangnan Pavilion.
It has the same name as
Jiangnan base city.
It's based on the name of the base city.
All the students there
are from Jiangnan base city.
There are
two more students living there with you.
Among them,
one is called Shi Jiang.
He is very strong.
I'm not sure I can beat him.
Get close to him.
It's good for you.
You are not sure if you can beat him?
No.
Shi Jiang is in the top five
in the Elite Training Camp.
The top 30 students in the training camp
are all as strong as a God of War.
Are all as strong as a God of War?
It's just they didn't apply for
the title.
If they do,
they have to graduate.
Shi Jiang, Zhao Ruo.
Your junior is here.
New student!
Yeah.
Mr. Yang.
(He is Shi Jiang.)
His name is Luo Feng.
From this day onwards,
he will live in Jiangnan Pavilion
with you.
Shi Jiang. Zhao Ruo.
You are seniors.
Luo Feng is new here.
You have to take care of him.
Don't worry, leave it to me.
As long as I'm here,
he won't suffer.
Good.
I'll leave now.
If you have any questions,
just ask them.
OK.
=Swallowed Star=
(Jiangnan Pavilion)
(Furniture control Music Soul music)
Cheers.
Welcome the new member in
Jiangnan Pavilion.
Cheers!
Luo Feng.
When you get back to your room,
turn on the computer you've got at camp.
There is an e-manual for students.
Read it through.
Yes, yes, yes.
Especially the points.
In training camp,
ranking is the most important.
You have seen the black dragon list
at the door, right?
(No.1 Renatus Breech (530321))
Yes.
There seems to be one Chinese in
the top three.
The black dragon list
is our ranking.
From the 1st to the 28th of every month,
we can earn points.
They will calculate on the 29th
and make the final ranking of the month.
The next month,
all points go to zero.
We will rank again.
Seniors.
How to get the points?
Boy, you got the point!
I am very satisfied.
Listen up.
Score system is calculated by
multiplying the battle points
and combat power.
Battle Points are the points you get
by hunting monsters every month.
Combat Power, in simple words,
is your current strength.
Brother Shi Jiang.
It's my extracurricular tutoring time.
Please be quiet.
Brother Shi Jiang has told you.
But combat power
is calculated by
multiplying the power level
of fist power and
the level of test tower.
Huh?
The power level of fist power means
how strong your fist is.
Test tower level...
It should be the number of floors
I break through in the virtual space.
Exactly.
You're smart.
Luo Feng.
Don't worry
about those inexplicable numbers.
You just need to remember one thing.
The more you hunt in the wilderness
the higher the test tower level is,
and the stronger you are,
the higher the ranking will be.
Why is ranking so important?
The students in the camp are likely to
be comrades in arms in the future.
Don't take it for granted.
Higher points mean rarer cultivation
resources.
That's why a lot of students
who have reached the level of God of War
still stay here.
Take our brother Shi Jiang for
an example.
Got it.
Thank you for your advice.
To you two.
(Aunt)
Aunt.
Is the investigation going well?
The only valuable thing
(Luo Feng)
is Luo Feng who is admitted this year.
Luo Feng?
Aunt, you don't want to woo him
just like the old folks
in the family, do you?
No.
When Wei died,
he was also in city 003.
And he was not far away.
What? Unless
he's a Spirit Master.
Probably.
Since he became a warrior-to-be
last July,
he became a primary senior warrior
very soon.
And he was admitted to Elite Training
Camp.
There are many young talents.
But he who grows this fast
is not an ordinary warrior.
Once we confirm it,
we will know the murderer
who killed Wei.
Keep an eye on Luo Feng
in the camp.
If you find that he might be a
Spirit Master,
tell me as soon as possible.
OK. Aunt.
I got it!
(Candice)
You must help me catch the real him!
OK.
What's the matter, Candice?
What could possibly be difficult
for you,
the first successor of Paulinus Clan?
William.
I need you to do something.
(Start matching courses.)
(Fist power Primary course
Test tower tactics guide Level 1)
(Bodily Movement Advanced.
Sidestep Slide Dodging.)
Special training begins.
(Strength 10000)
(Strength 28000)
(Shi Jiang, advanced senior warrior.
From urban area of Jiangnan base city)
(Entered the Elite Training Camp from
Basic Training Camp. Top 5 in the camp.)
(As strong as a God of War,
but not willing to get the title.)
(Zhao Ruo, advanced senior warrior.
From Sucheng, Jiangnan base city.)
(Former elite of the army, warm and
cheerful, willing to fight the bullies.)
(Adores Hong, the world's most
powerful man.)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪Never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star")
(Next episode)
(Play tricks.)
(Now he's trying to suppress me.)
(If this goes on...)
(William's starting to take the lead.)
(No matter how talented you are,)
(you have to suffer losses)
(when fighting the seniors.)
(I won't spare you if you lose.)
(Luo Feng, you could have chosen
a scene that was good for you.)
(Luo Feng.)
(Remember this.)
(There is no shortcut to
become stronger.)
(So mean!)
(His nose is slightly open, his breath
comes in short pants. He's taking it.)