♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(Be good, we will only break
one arm and leg of you.)
(Come on, all of you. And you.)
(Good, that makes you a perfect prey.)
(How could my fly-cutter miss him?)
(Is this the extremely rare
Spirit Energy the instructor mentioned?)
(Mr. Luo Feng, you can go home today.)
(If he dares to mess with me,
I'll make sure he suffers.)
(Your goal is not within the fence.)
(You want to protect the world.
I'll help you with it.)
=Episode 6=
Mr. Zhu?
(You have new mail, open or close)
Director, here's a document for you.
(Processing. Please be careful.)
It's good. You've improved a lot
after a month's special training.
There's a good chance that you would
pass the field test tomorrow.
Yeah, but I'm not good enough.
Instructor Jiang,
your speed is amazing.
You avoided all my attacks,
barely moving your feet.
It's not about speed.
It's Micro-Level Body Movement.
Micro-Level Body Movement?
There are four levels of
body movements in warriors' world.
Basic level, micro level, perfect level
and superb level.
Micro body movement means
you predict rivals' moves
by observing their movement,
and avoid their attacks with
minimal movements.
It's a skill built
on numerous combat experience.
What? This brilliant skill
is only on the second level?
It's not a complicated skill.
Most senior warriors have mastered it.
Senior warriors?
Oh, you don't know, right?
There are also
hierarchies among warriors.
According to the grading system,
there are soldiers, senior warriors,
and the rare God of War.
Each level is subdivided into 3 levels:
primary, intermediate and advanced.
Generally, warrior becomes junior
soldier once passing the test.
Usually,
you can defeat them with hot weapons.
Senior warriors are not afraid of
hot weapons.
Their mental speed
is far faster than
the fastest guns we have.
Their body movements are perfect.
Next is the God of War.
They are as fast as lightning,
and they can smash buildings.
They're the real God of War.
Instructor Jiang, is there
any level higher than that in the world?
Yes, it does exist.
They are powerful enough to destroy
the universe.
But such a warrior is really rare.
There are only
two or three of them in Huaxia.
Ah.
Huaxia, one of the 5 greatest powers,
has only 2 or 3 warriors
beyond the God of War level?
Um.
General Instructor Wu.
(Jiang Nian, Director Zhuge arrives.
Come down with Luo Feng.)
On my way.
Luo Feng, follow me.
Luo Feng, I heard from Jiang Nian
that you have mastered
the Five Acupoints Skywards?
Yes, not long ago.
(Who on earth is Director Zhuge?)
(It seems that he is senior to
General Instructor Wu Tong.)
How's your fist power and speed now?
I just tested them today.
My fist power is 3,110 kg.
My speed is 58 meters per second.
Good. I'm here today,
on behalf of the Extreme Martial Club,
to invite you to join us in advance.
Ah, join the
Extreme Martial Club in advance?
But I haven't passed the field test yet.
I've confirmed your ability.
You're a talent worthy of our attention.
This is our offer.
Take a look at it, please.
A villa and 20 million Huaxia dollars
Guidance on guiding technique,
sabre skill and body skill,
with a total price of
100 million Huaxia dollars.
One hundred million!
The best offer we ever gave
was guidance on guiding technique
and skills worth 50 million.
But I have faith in you
that I raised it.
Would you accept it?
OK, I'll sign it.
Welcome to the Extreme Martial Club.
You can move into the
villa for warriors today.
Jiang Nian, you'll be in charge.
OK. Director Zhuge.
My name is Zhuge Tao.
I'll see you around.
Instructor Jiang, who is Director Zhuge?
He is one of the three directors
of the Jiangnan
Extreme Martial Club headquarter.
Among the Extreme Martial Clubs
of Jiangnan city,
he is only below the president.
And his strength has reached the level
of advanced senior warrior.
Advanced senior warrior!
Alright, let's get moving now.
(Huaxia memory.)
(Tencent Video)
I'm not dreaming, am I?
Of course not. I've signed a contract
with the Extreme Martial Club.
But you haven't
passed the field test yet.
Luo Feng, let's go.
(Liquor)
I didn't expect to move to the upscale
neighborhood in the downtown area
from the slum district
outside the city.
Here we are.
It's the exclusive villa area
of Extreme Martial Club
of Jiangnan city. Moonlight Villa.
Villa?
Mom, dad, I didn't mention it's a villa
because
I was afraid you'd be overexcited.
Kiddo.
Oh, my god, is it true?
This is really...
Yes, from today on,
here's our home.
I learned about it before I came.
The first floor is the living room
and the dining room.
The second floor is for bedrooms
and video rooms.
There's an elevator, too.
Hua, you can move freely in this villa.
(It's all worth it)
(since they are all happy.)
(But now,)
(I have to deal with something else.)
=Swallowed Star=
I guess you must be Zhou Huayang, right?
Yes, it's me.
Looks like you're well-informed.
You actually found me.
I've been waiting in Nan'an Residence
for a long time.
I followed your car all the way here.
Come on, what do you want me to do?
Bro, I'm sorry.
Why apologize?
I did arrange the fight
in the detention house, but Cobra...
I really didn't know Cobra.
It must be Zhang Haobai.
Zhang Haobai?
He has an uncle who's a warrior.
Cobra is a disqualified warrior.
Well, he contacted his uncle.
Warrior? Uncle?
Brother, please forgive me.
I won't take it.
Bro.
I know what was going on,
and I'll let you go.
I'll get it over with Zhang Haobai.
But I...
This cup of tea is on you. I'll take it.
Now we are even.
I'll deal with Zhang Haobai later.
Tomorrow is the field test
of the warrior.
(Feng, you signed a contract
with the club already.)
(Do you have to take the field test?)
(Yes, I heard that many people
get injured during the test.)
(I did sign the contract,
but if I don't get to be a warrior,)
(I wouldn't be able to use the account.)
(Besides, I want to know what I've got.)
It's a great outfit.
It's all made of first-class gold.
It can resist the attacks from
Level-H monsters.
But it's a pity that
it is just lent to us.
As long as we become a warrior,
we will get better outfits.
You are Luo Feng?
You are?
Wan Dong from Thunder
and Lightning Martial Club.
What can I do for you?
I'm a warrior-to-be,
and I just signed the contract with
Thunder and Lightning Martial Club.
Since we both have signed in advance,
do you dare to compete with me?
See who will get a high grade.
Not interested.
You!
You want to fight before
the field test starts,
you'll be disqualified right away.
Hey, this kid is so funny.
He's probably too confident.
But you already signed?
I didn't know yet.
Well, I...
Good boy!
Try you best in the field test.
Let me see what you've got.
I'm with Huya Squad.
We're going into the wilderness from
the north military area. This is permit.
(Temporary pass for Huya Squad)
But this is the place blocked
for the field test.
I have the permit. Are you blind?
Have you got all your fight
suits and outfits?
Now I'll announce the contents
and precautions of the field test.
Last week,
we were attacked by the monsters
when sending
important supplies to Hongning.
The convoy was destroyed.
It was in the wilderness area known as
the monster town
outside the city of Jiangnan.
Your task
is to go there to collect the supplies
and get DNA samples of the monsters
to develop vaccines.
DNA samples?
A boor like me is not
good at such things.
You don't have to do the research work.
All you have to do
is cut off their ears.
To avoid repeated sampling,
the ears must come from
different monsters.
The number of ears will
determine your grade.
Cutting ears? Simple yet rude.
The passing rate of field test is 20%.
In other words, 80 out of 100
candidates will be eliminated.
Now get in the car.
We will be monitoring you all the time.
If the warriors-to-be attack each other,
we will arrest them on the spot
and permanently disqualify them.
20% pass rate?
It is more difficult than before.
Alright, the field test starts now.
(Different from the virtual combat
of the warrior-to-be,)
(this is a real combat.)
Luo Feng.
I can't believe you survived
the assassination of Cobra.
You were so close to get me in trouble.
I'll show you the consequences of
offending a senior warrior.
(The air is filled with smell of blood.)
(Looking at the monster closely makes
me feel a strong homicidal intent.)
(The field test is indeed different
from the test of warrior-to-be.)
(Come on!)
(Micro body movement means you
predict rivals' moves by observing,)
(and avoid their attacks
with minimal movements.)
(I understand a bit now.)
(Next goal.)
Ah?
(Attacked by other warriors-to-be?)
(Warning)
What? Golden eagle?
There are only Level-H to
Level-F monsters there.
How come there's a golden eagle
of Level-D?
Terminate the test now.
No, let it be.
Director Zhuge!
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Next episode)
(As the world's top skill, there are 6 layers.)
(How much do you want?)
(50 million Huaxia dollars.)
(50 million!)
(You're pushing it too far.)
(There are only Level-H to
Level-F monsters there.)
(How come there's a golden eagle?)
(Who is the nearest warrior-to-be?)
(It's Candidate No.93, Luo Feng.)
(Is golden eager invincible?)
(You know assassinating a warrior-to-be
is a very serious crime.)
(You might be dead.)
(I will get rid of him sooner or later.)
(Terminate the test now.)
(Swallowed Star Time to Shine
Every Sunday at 10 a.m.)