♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(Help me prepare a warplane.)
(And find where Luo Feng is.)
(Give me an hour and I'll bring
Luo Feng here.)
(I'll always remember
I was part of the Fire Hammer Team.)
(There are the most talented students
in the world.)
(The best teachers, the best equipment.)
(It's known as the world's
top one training camp.)
(It's called)
(Elite Training Camp.)
=Episode 21=
Elite Training Camp is the top
warriors training camp in the world.
It has a more widely known name
among the warriors,
War of God Preparatory Camp.
Ah.
War of God Preparatory Camp, then...
Yes, 90% warriors in Elite Training Camp
will be the Gods of War.
90%!
Another 10% were disabled or died.
It is not a place for fun.
It offers the best teaching.
Students also have to endure
the hardest training.
OK.
Even so,
There are still countless people
trying to get in.
You know,
every quota
in the Elite Training Camp is priceless.
Even the consortium can't buy a quota
with their connections and money.
Luo Feng, you have the chance
to enter the world's top training camp.
But on one condition,
you have to pass the B-level test.
B-level, that means...
Actually, A-level test would do.
But just now,
Hanxia military asked for one quota from
Extreme Martial Club.
That's why you have to take the
B-level test, which is harder.
Luo Feng, are you willing to take it
to join Elite Training Camp?
Yes.
OK.
Good, but don't stress out.
Even if you fail the B-level test,
you will enter the basic training camp.
All right, let's go. The test will be
conducted directly at headquarters.
Before that, go home and say goodbye
to your relatives and friends.
Within five years in Elite Training Camp,
you only get a 2-month holiday each year.
Director Zhuge.
He is Heng Xia?
Yes.
A young warrior from the Extreme Martial
Club for basic training camp this year.
He's a genius, too.
Heng Xia, this is your senior, Luo Feng.
He will go to the global headquarters of
Extreme Martial Club with you this time.
Your senior's goal is
Elite Training Camp.
Ah!
Hello, senior. My name is Heng Xia.
Hello.
On March 28th,
you and I will fly to the global
headquarters of Extreme Martial Club.
You all have to
get to the airport before 2 p.m.
Yes.
(I've been here for so many years.)
(I'm leaving soon.)
(I'll leave the country
for the global headquarters.)
(Sigh, five years is long.)
(Dad, Mom)
(Hua.)
(I can't live with them
for five years.)
(And Wen, he should be
studying hard now.)
(The final exam is coming.)
(Xu Xin.)
We arrived, Mr. Luo Feng.
OK.
Ah.
Mom, Dad, I'm going out.
Hello.
No. No.
Take a look, please.
No.
No, thanks.
Wen.
Feng.
We meet once every half a year.
You're leaving again.
I have no choice.
The time of departure is nailed,
no change can be done.
Well, it's like you're not happy.
Elite Training Camp is the dream of
all warriors.
I have been in the Military Academy
for a semester.
I'm not as good as the senior students
in the martial club.
But you're heading towards
the God of War!
You want to be a warrior, too?
I knew that I was not talented enough,
so I went to the military academy first.
The resources there would
help me improve.
Ah, but even in school,
we still need to pay for
the expensive training facilities.
I have to work part-time to
earn extra money.
But there's less time for me to train.
Huh?
(Received a remittance of one million)
This... This money...
Wen, since you want to be a warrior,
you can't waste your time
on part-time jobs.
I can help you with the money problem.
Don't forget to pay me back
when you become a warrior.
Feng.
Well, I have another date
with Xu Xin. Goodbye.
I hope you will become a warrior soon!
Xu Xin... Oh, got it.
Come on, Feng!
=Swallowed Star=
Luo Feng!
Xu Xin.
Young Master, Xu Xin went out
with a boy I don't know.
His name seems to be Luo Feng.
How dare he!
You know what to do.
Young Master,
what about the things I want...
This year's latest limited-edition
branded bag.
It'll be on your desk when it's done.
OK. Young Master, I'll finish the task!
So... You're leaving at the end of
the month.
Yeah.
The world's top Elite Training Camp.
I heard about it from my grandfather.
You'll for sure be a God of War
since you get in.
Congratulates, future God of War.
You know, my new boyfriend
is handsome and rich,
and he's also a warrior.
A warrior! Impressive.
Oh, it's you.
We run into each other for 2 days.
It's fate calling!
Ah?
You got the wrong person, right?
How can it be? Didn't you say you
want to go shopping with me?
Eh.
Who is it?
The guy I just mentioned.
I think you have the wrong person.
My boyfriend just came back
from the wilderness yesterday.
How can you meet him two days in a row?
(Boyfriend!)
Well...
Oh, yes, yes.
I'm sorry. I got the wrong person.
You said boyfriend...
You...
Sorry.
Six months ago,
we were high school seniors,
standing on the border of the base city,
staring at the old world
that ordinary people can't set foot in
and discussing the future with
each other.
And you,
you have already taken the first step.
Now you will take the second step.
Is Elite Training Camp the second step?
I'm not in it yet.
I need to study for five years.
Except for the holidays
in January and February every year,
I can't leave the camp any other time.
OK.
I see.
But as long as they rate me
as good as the God of War,
I can apply to finish it earlier.
No.
This is not good.
There are the top teaching resources
in the world.
Even Hong and Thunder
sometimes teach there.
It's a rare opportunity!
You should study for 5 years.
But...
I'll be waiting for you.
(Extreme Martial Club)
(I was living there half a year ago)
(and training in the dim corridor,)
(living in a crowded room.)
You are Luo Feng?
Who are you?
My name is Wang Xingping,
from the Wang family in Jingdu.
I am here to warn you.
Stay away from Xu Xin.
Wang family in Jingdu.
Wang family, one of the nine
core families of HR Alliance.
Good. You are a smart guy.
A wise man should know the rules.
Rules?
You should know
that people are different in this world.
Some people can only abide by
the law and rules.
Even so,
disasters may come from the sky.
Some people can break the law,
murder and burn. And they'd be alright.
You should know
what kind of person I am,
and what kind of person you are.
That's right. We're different.
You swagger around with
your power.
I heard that you've only been a warrior
for more than half a year,
and you're a primary senior warrior now.
Well, my useless bodyguards
are also warriors.
You guys tell him your levels.
Intermediate senior warrior.
(Ah.)
(Intermediate senior warrior,
same as Uncle Wu.)
Intermediate senior warrior.
(Three intermediate senior warriors
as bodyguards.)
Advanced senior warrior.
(Almost as strong as Thunder Team.)
(It seems that the Wang family
in Jingdu is really powerful.)
(Because of Li Wei,)
(it's very likely that I'm on
the Paulinus' investigation list.)
(If the Wang family...)
So? Why don't you have a fight?
Huh?
Fight friendly.
(Three intermediate senior warriors
and one advanced senior warrior.)
(Without Spirit Energy,)
(I'm not sure I can win.)
(But if I use Spirit Energy,)
(I'll be a target
of Li Wei's parents in no time.)
(What to do?)
(No, I can't throw in the towel.)
Come on!
Brother Wang, you are here, too.
(Wang Xingping, one of the nine
core families of HR Alliance.)
(Young master of the Wang family
in Jingdu city.)
(He transferred from Jingdu
to Jiangnan University for Xu Xin.)
(Heng Xia, freshman of
Jiangnan University. A talented warrior)
(sent to the basic training camp
by Extreme Martial Club. Handsome.)
(Good temper, excellent family
background, father is a God of War.)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪Never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star")
(Domestic departure 03)
(Bye, mom and dad!)
(Goodbye, brother.)
(Please choose battle suit and weapon.)
(B-level test will start
in 120 seconds.)