♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(Luo Feng has been put in the detention.)
(I want your men to
mess with him there.)
(He is a warrior-to-be,)
(and already in detention for fighting.)
(If he causes trouble in there,)
(he will be disqualified.)
(I'll transfer you
to the Yi'an detention house first.)
(Get rid of someone for me.)
(Well,
is this the energy from the universe?)
=Episode 5=
(The scent of shadow last night
was strange.)
(I feel like there is
the malice approaching.)
Bah, these dishes are unsavory!
(Is it an illusion?)
Go, go.
I thought it was someone tough.
Just this brat?
Be good, we will only break
one arm and leg of you.
You won't suffer much.
Come on, all of you. And you.
I have to make sure
you're qualified enough. Go!
(Keep quiet)
(For new life)
Good, that makes you a perfect prey.
Come on now.
Well, disappointing!
I wanted to take it slowly
and have fun,
but now, I have to make it quick.
Good. You're getting me
more and more excited.
(Turn over a new leaf)
Five Acupoints Skywards
is not a big deal to him.
(His spirituality surprised me.)
(How is it possible?)
(How could my fly-cutter miss him?)
Get down, all of you!
Stay down. Don't move!
Get him to the infirmary now.
(In addiction to Zhang Haobai,)
(I also saw Luo Feng's family members
were injured.)
I thought there was something fishy.
So I checked the monitor.
Oh.
I heard that the security guard was
about to delete the surveillance video.
Thank you for bringing it here.
Director, we got something from Cobra.
He said he was ordered by Zhou Huayang.
I see. Make the arrangement.
Yes.
(Oh,
thank you for providing the evidence.)
(We will deal with the case
according to law.)
(Where is this place?)
(Looks like a military sanitarium.)
(I think my eyes and ears
are sharper now.)
(I can control objects
without touching?)
(Go!)
(Is this the rare Spirit Energy
the instructor mentioned?)
(Whether it's Spirit Energy or not,
I'll check it out later.)
(I should practice
Genetic Energy Practices now.)
=Swallowed Star=
(My head!)
(Where is this now?)
(Did I get into my subconsciousness?)
(The fog)
(is Spirit Energy.)
(This dark golden ball)
(is probably
the source of Spirit Energy.)
(Does it have something to do
with my headaches?)
(Maybe my current condition)
(does not allow me
to stand that much of energy.)
(I need to try harder
to make good use of this energy.)
Ah, Mr. Luo Feng. Feeling better?
Yes, much better.
Sit, please.
I'm Dong An from Yi'an detention house.
This is the
military sanitarium in the district.
Mr. Luo Feng, you can go home today.
I can go home?
What about my qualification
as a warrior-to-be?
Don't worry about it.
We got witness's testimony
and checked the surveillance.
We've also ascertained what happened.
(Who is the witness?)
(I should say thank you in person.)
As for prisoners
who tried to attack you,
according to our investigation,
they were ordered to
break one arm and leg of you.
Who ordered them?
A local villain named Zhou Huayang.
I don't know him.
(We've already interrogated him.
Maybe there is someone behind him,)
(but I'm not sure.)
(Maybe the guy
has powerful connections.)
You can ask Jiangnan Security Bureau
to investigate it.
As an organ in charge of
military affairs, they can help you.
OK, thank you.
(Powerful connections?)
(I haven't offended anyone
except Zhang Haobai.)
Oh, and one more thing,
someone asked me to give you this.
(Application
of College Entrance Examination)
He failed? How come?
Alas,
I didn't expect Cobra was so unreliable.
It seems that we have to find
a real warrior next time.
Next time?
What?
Cobra sold me out.
I pulled a lot of strings, but couldn't
delete the surveillance video.
If Luo Feng submits a request to
Security Bureau for investigation,
this video will be a valid clue.
How can this happen? How come?
Zhou, did you sell me out?
Even if I zip my lips, if Luo Feng
turns to the Security Bureau,
they will find you sooner or later.
Even your uncle could not
cover you on this.
We have been friends for years.
That's why I'm telling you this.
Otherwise,
you won't even know what's going on.
Go to your uncle and discuss it.
He's much better than you.
No, no, I don't want to
be caught by the Security Bureau!
Uncle, I'm going to find my uncle!
OK, here you are.
Director Dong, could you tell me
who was the witness
that testified for me?
Does this application form
remind you of someone?
Enough?
Hu.
This is a big deal.
Do you have any idea?
Don't worry, brother.
Haobai, you are grounded from now on.
Don't go out and make troubles.
Yes, uncle.
Alas.
We could have had
a winner last time! Damn it!
And you.
You're lucky you can get out of there.
Don't make any trouble again!
Don't do anything else.
Even if the Security Bureau comes,
don't act rashly. I'll deal with it.
Only the powerful ones
get a say in this world.
Luo Feng is just a warrior-to-be.
A brat who hasn't fought a real monster.
If he dares to mess with me,
I'll make sure he suffers.
(She went through all the troubles
to send me this form,)
(I'll take good care of it.)
Luo Feng.
I'm here to get some fresh air.
You like the scenery here, too?
Yes.
Xu Xin, thank you for testifying for me.
You're welcome.
I've always believed you.
By the way, congratulations on passing
the test of warrior-to-be.
Thank you,
but I haven't passed the field test yet.
Compared with the predecessors
who have fought with
real monsters, I have a long way to go.
I remember the way you looked at
the warrior when
the Black Crowned Golden Eagle attacked.
It was so dangerous,
there was no fear in your eyes,
but yearning.
I've learned one thing since then.
Your goal is not within the fence.
Not within the fence?
You want to protect the world.
I'll help you with it.
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Next episode)
(Am I dreaming?)
(The convoy was destroyed.)
(The extreme martial clubs
of Jiangnan city.)
(He is only below the president.)
(I'll show you)
(the consequences of
offending senior warriors.)
(You are Luo Feng?)
(You want to fight
before the field test starts,)
(you'll be disqualified right away.)
(If the warriors-to-be
attack each other,)
(we will arrest them on the spot
and permanently disqualify them.)
(The air is filled with smell of blood.)
(Looking at the monster closely)
(makes me feel
a strong homicidal intent.)