♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(Luo Feng)
(wins the challenge.)
(I suspect that he is the murderer!)
(This is Ms. Jiang.)
(I'll be guiding and teaching you
in the camp)
(in the next five years.)
(This gravity room is excavated
from the relics)
(of ancient civilization.)
(You are new here, you should seize
the opportunity to strengthen yourself.)
(I've met a lot of guides.)
(Now,)
(is it time for me)
(to protect them instead?)
=Episode 26=
(That monster...)
Wait for me!
(Jiangnan Pavilion)
What happened?
Jiangnan base city is in danger!
No information about the
head of the herd yet.
Chief! There's something wrong with the
frontline team's digital equipment.
They can't detect the head's movements.
What about the casualties?
90% of the Southeast Military Region
who are lower than advanced level
are dead.
Assemble our warriors immediately
to search and intercept in units.
Use military satellites
to secure the communication system.
Are there Gods of War from
the local two martial clubs
and HR Alliance coming to help?
Zhou Zhengyong from Extreme Martial Club
is out with Supervisor Liu.
Two Gods of War in Thunder and
Lightning Martial Club are injured.
HR Alliance has ordered to
restrict the warriors.
Now, only the world headquarters
of Extreme Martial Club can help.
Why can't we fight?
We are also from the Jiangnan base city.
It's our duty to fight.
The military speculates that the head of
the herd is as strong as a King Beast.
Luo Feng.
If you meet a King Beast,
you wouldn't even have a chance.
I...
Zhao Ruo.
You just got into the top 100
on the black dragon list.
This operation is too dangerous for you.
You two should train hard.
Why don't you stand up for us?
I've got a bad feeling.
Senior, go back.
I need to go to the city.
(Their levels are not high.)
(Where on earth is their head?)
(Domestic departure)
I'm sorry,
but the airport has been requisitioned.
Only people who perform important tasks
in Jiangnan base city can use it.
Is he also going to Jiangnan base city?
Yes.
He's with the HR Alliance,
responsible for the transport of
medical supplies for Jiangnan base city.
Hey, sir!
Huh?
Connecting to the real-time monitoring
of camera 3.
(Warning)
Where does this
powerful electromagnetic wave come from?
Damn!
The city's protective energy shield
and weapon system
will be temporarily malfunctioned.
Ready for the crash.
(The shock wave comes from
the north of the city.)
(There are stronger mutant
monsters there.)
(Judging from the power of
the shock waves,)
(it's stronger than normal
beast generals.)
(It's an advanced beast general.)
(Or a King Beast!)
(The front line is in urgent need of
ammunition. Need material backup!)
Please come in if you receive it.
(Warning)
Defenses in the southeast
aren't working!
Contact the Commander
of the Southeast Military Region.
Defend the southeast pass at all costs!
Yes!
How is the distribution of supplies?
Non-digital equipment is sent
to the front.
But we're still in urgent need
of medical supplies.
Contact the President of
HR Alliance now!
I'll talk to him in person.
Rest assured.
I'll send someone to take stock
and send it to the front.
You're welcome.
It is our duty to provide medical
assistance to the soldiers.
Call the person in charge of
the HR Alliance in Jiangnan Base City.
Listen up.
Be prepared to give up
Jiangnan base city.
HR Alliance has to preserve strength.
Stop sending the medical supplies
to the front.
Bring them all back to headquarters.
I'll talk to
Extreme Martial Club about you.
Emergency notice.
HR Alliance has decided to suspend
(HR Alliance Notice)
all one-way flights
to Jiangnan Base City.
(Do you return to the Departure Point?)
The manned vehicles heading for the city
should return immediately.
Ah.
Please.
Run! Faster!
Go, go!
Hurry! Get into the basement right now!
Hurry, don't get separated.
The soldiers have to die for it.
This is too...
-Commander!
-Yes.
-More monsters are coming!
-Ah!
They are about 3,000 meters away
from the Southeast Military Region.
Contact the North Military Region
and ask them to send 80% military forces
to support us.
Hurry! Support the
Southeast Military Region.
Go, go, go. Ready to go!
Ah?
In this way,
there will be no one guarding here.
Don't worry. As long as the war
in the southeast is over...
The monster!
The enemy!
Laser cannon. Target!
Attack!
Ah!
(What's going on?)
=Swallowed Star=
The head of the monster was found
in the Northern Military Region?
OK, I'm heading there.
We need people in the north pass.
Thank you for supporting.
It's our duty.
They look one way and row another.
No wonder we couldn't find their head
in the Southeast Military Region.
Their head has got into the city.
We must stop them!
To cooperate with the military,
the martial club has mobilized
special forces to intercept.
But if we confront them in the city,
the power of the Gods of War
might hurt many people.
So, it's best
we draw it out and
encircle and suppress.
OK.
Our target is to draw the head
out of the city.
What's that?
(Thank god I landed safely.)
(I need to contact the military
to get the medical supplies.)
What?
Hijacked HR Alliance's airfreighter!
So bold!
I just heard from the pilot.
The warrior is called Luo Feng.
Luo Feng! Again?
Luo Feng?
Connecting to the real-time monitoring
of the base city.
Locate Luo Feng.
(Those two look weird.)
(It's like their minds are
being controlled.)
Run! Run! Help!
Run! Hurry!
(That... It's him!)
Mom.
Great.
Ah, over there!
Everybody,
go to the underground shelter.
I'll take care of it.
Spirit Master!
It's him!
Let's go there and kill him!
Hump!
No.
He is a hero, defending base city now.
Everyone's watching.
If we just kill him,
you and the whole Paulinus clan
will fall into disgrace.
But he's the one who killed our son!
I'll make sure he dies.
And no one will find out.
(The place has been evacuated.)
(That's... me in the monster's eye.)
Go.
Fire!
Instructor Jiang, everyone's here.
So, Senator Zhu was right.
You're a Spirit Master.
How did you come?
I flew with HR Alliance's airfreighter.
There are medical supplies
for the military to be received.
The one just crashed?
Yes.
Leave it to us.
Cheer up.
Freezing weapons can only
buy us some time.
It won't last long.
This is just the beginning.
That monster...
It has spirit energy,
which is very rare in monsters.
It has a snake head and nine bodies.
It's called Nine-headed Snake Dragon.
Looks like the freeze gun
can't restrain it for long.
Shi Jiang, Chu Qiang.
Go and help evacuate the residents.
We'll take care of it here.
Make sure people are safe.
OK!
We need to draw it to a place
where there are fewer people,
so we can evacuate the residents.
Let's go to the manufacturing district.
But the infrastructure along the way
would be severely damaged.
We can draw it out of the city.
That's the best.
But it's the hardest.
If we fail,
residential areas along the way
will be affected.
It'll cause casualties.
(This plan is risky,)
(but it's a way to minimize the
casualties)
(and protect most of the citizens.)
(Besides...)
I suggest we play it safe
and draw it to the manufacturing
district.
I'm a Spirit Master.
I won't be affected by the monster.
If I try,
I think I can get it out of the city.
But the monster's spirit energy
is better than yours.
You're good,
but not good enough to defeat it.
Even so,
I might break through.
As long as we draw it out of the city,
we can protect the
infrastructure and people.
Increase the power of the freeze gun!
Now I have to stand up.
We can't gamble on people's lives.
I don't approve of this plan.
The monster is about
to break free from the freeze!
As long as it's in the city,
it will be a threat to the citizens.
The only discipline
is to make decisions
that I won't regret.
Please forgive me.
Luo Feng!
(Chu Qiang, primary God of War.
Senior in Elite Training Camp.)
(He trains hard and ranks the top three
on the black dragon list.)
(He has joined the military and
is determined to defend the base city.)
(Nine-headed Snake Dragon, advanced
beast general. It has spirit energy.)
(As strong as King Beast. Its electrical
superpulse can ruin equipment.)
(It's a great threat to the base city.)
(Its mental attack can disable warriors
lower than God of War.)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪Never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star")
Swallowed Star Soaring aspirations
Please stay tuned