♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asleep with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(Maybe the real test starts now.)
(Level E. The gold vulture!)
(I can't be defeated here.)
(Luo Feng.)
(I'm here to tell you that
you've passed this test.)
(You guys, keep them quiet.)
(Stop!)
=Episode 4=
Feng.
Zhang Haobai,
how dare you hit my father!
You losers. What am I afraid of?
(Luo Feng.
There are cameras everywhere.)
(If you dare to hit me.
I'll keep you in prison forever.)
Try it.
(What a strength!)
Go!
We got a call about a break-in.
Please come with us
to the police station for questioning.
Mr. Luo, we need to further investigate
the confrontation
in Garden Villa.
During our investigation,
you will be in detention.
Please try to understand.
I'll cooperate as long as
you deal with it fairly.
Good.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Is my father in detention, too?
When will you release Feng?
Mr. Luo Hongguo, we have confirmed
that your colleagues and you
didn't get involved in the fight.
You may leave now.
But your son is still
under investigation.
Impossible. Feng won't fight others
unless it's necessary.
Is there a misunderstanding?
Ms. Gong, please try to understand.
Mom, dad, don't worry.
We know brother well and we believe him.
As long as they deal with it fairly,
brother will be alright.
Feng took part in the test of
warrior-to-be today.
Will this detention affect him?
Ah, warrior-to-be?
Newbie, come over! Massage me.
I'm sorry but I won't.
Brat, you never heard about me?
Looks like you need a good lesson.
(What? He's strong!)
Brat, forgot to mention
that I've past the test of
warrior-to-be before.
Warrior-to-be?
Hump.
So? Scared?
Warrior-to-be?
Looks like
you didn't pass the field test.
What? Are you also...
Ah! Hero! Please show some mercy.
Lad, stop!
If a warrior-to-be causes trouble,
he will be disqualified.
(Hump!)
(That's what Zhang Haobai wants.)
(Tomorrow Bank)
Mr. Zhang, what do you mean?
Zhou,
I know there's nothing you can't do
in Yi'an district in Yangzhou.
Actually, I need a favor from you.
Oh? You are rich and powerful,
what's troubling you?
A boy named Luo Feng, he pissed me off.
Luo Feng? Never heard of him.
He's my classmate.
He bit my bodyguard a while back
and dared to hit me.
High school student? If I'm not wrong,
you are a senior student
in the martial club.
How could
a high school student defeat you?
He... is a warrior-to-be.
Well, Mr. Zhang.
We didn't actually meet today.
Adios.
Zhou. A warrior-to-be would
scare the hell out of you?
Don't worry.
You don't have to do it yourself.
Mr. Zhang. What does that mean?
Luo Feng is
in the detention house in Yi'an.
I want your men to mess with him there.
Stop kidding. He's a warrior-to-be.
Hump.
Yes, a warrior-to-be.
He's already in detention for fighting.
If he causes trouble there,
he will be disqualified.
So what? Even if he's disqualified,
I can't afford to mess with him.
Your men only need to make a mess,
I'll arrange someone
to do the main part.
Someone? Did you
find someone even stronger
than the warrior-to-be?
Cobra, you've got a visitor.
Em?
=Swallowed Star=
OK. Got it.
Haobai. I'll help you.
Sorry, but I have to bail you out
few days later.
I'll transfer you
to the Yi'an detention house first.
Get rid of someone for me.
You know I don't like to take risks.
Here's one million.
I'll recommend you to
join the Huya Squad once it's done.
I'll try to delete the record
of your killing on the field test.
Cobra?
Huya Squad was trying to reach him.
Huya Squad is a senior warrior squad.
Why do they take Cobra so seriously?
Though he was disqualified,
he's so much stronger
than the junior warriors.
In the field test last month,
he himself caused
the greatest number of casualties ever,
though he's in jail.
But the field test
allows casualties.
It's only a matter of time
before he's released.
(If Luo Feng meets
this kind of opponent)
(in the field test, I'm afraid...)
What? Warrior-to-be?
Chief. I learned that from his family.
He isn't in the official records yet.
(Today is the day of the test.)
(The list of eligible candidates
didn't come out yet, but if...)
Hello, Yi'an detention center.
Hello, are you Chief Dong?
Yes.
(How does she know me?)
I witnessed the fighting
in Garden Villa yesterday.
My surname is Xu.
Xu? Could it be...
(Personal Data File System, Luo Feng.)
The kid's good but inexperienced.
It won't be easy for him
to pass the field test.
If he comes across
an opponent like Cobra,
he might be in danger.
We will see if he can grasp
Five Acupoints Skywards.
It's the first step to
be a warrior.
He can.
Senator Zhu.
Luo Feng showed great spirituality
in the test earlier.
Five Acupoints Skywards
won't be a problem for him.
Great spirituality?
His spirituality surprised me.
Surprised you? You're the Spirit Master.
I've heard of an extremely rare group
of warriors with great spirituality.
They are called the Spirit Master.
But I can't find
any information about it.
It's normal.
Because there are only few of them.
A Spirit Master is also
an excellent warrior.
They learn the Genetic Energy Practices.
But the difference is they learn
another energy at the same time.
(Another energy?)
The Spirit Energy.
(It means
under any circumstances)
(a Spirit Master is more powerful
than a normal warrior)
Then, can we practice that, too?
Yes.
Unfortunately, as far as I know,
spirituality is a gift.
When you become a real warrior,
you'll have the chance
to learn about it.
For now, just prepare for the field test
next month.
Yes.
Palm, sole, head.
Five acupoints are towards the sky.
Is this Five Acupoints Skywards?
What's he doing?
Genetic Energy Practices?
As you know, the warriors
are more powerful and faster,
with better physical strength,
defense and mentality.
And these abilities
are from Genetic Energy.
During the Great Nirvana,
humans were infected with R.R. virus.
The antibodies optimize our genes.
When it reaches a certain point,
we can take energy from the universe.
Energy will come into cells, causing an
explosive increase in strength.
That's the genetic energy.
Now the warriors have
a rudimentary knowledge to practice it.
That is
Five Acupoints Skywards Practices.
It's highly classified.
I will only show you once
on the monitor.
There's no copy or file.
You need to remember
in the shortest time possible.
(Five acupoints,
they're in palms, soles)
(and the head.)
(Make them skywards and be calm.
So you can feel energy from the universe.)
(Anyway,
what is energy from the universe?)
(Can I feel it this way? Or...)
(No. I have to calm myself down.)
(Calm down, if I'm easily distracted,)
(how would I defeat
the strong opponents?)
(Well,
is this the energy from the universe?)
(That's it!)
(I can feel the energy
flowing into my body)
(and all my cells are getting bigger.)
(No. It's evolving.)
(That's genetic optimization.)
(The awakening of genetic energy?)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪To be never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Next episode)
(You want to protect the world.)
(I'll help you with it.)
(Where is it now?)
(This fog. Is it...)
(This video will be a useful clue.)
(Come on, all of you.)
(And you.)
(Only the powerful ones
got a say in this world.)
(I, Zhang Zehu,
will teach him a good lesson!)
(You're making me more excited now.)
(Squat down, all of you.)
(Ah!)
(Swallowed Star Time to Shine
Every Sunday at 10 a.m.)