♪It's time to say goodbye♪
♪Carry some happiness in your bag♪
♪It is covered with dark clouds ahead♪
♪The entanglement,
the trapped beast is growling♪
♪The silence♪
♪Feels bitter♪
♪May you never be hurt♪
♪Don't fall asLip with tears♪
♪The tortuous world♪
♪Lies numerous answers♪
♪The wound is heroic because of love♪
♪Let's move forward together♪
♪The power of rebirth comes within me♪
♪Defeat respectable opponents♪
♪Faith is all I have♪
♪Reach the vastness in my heart♪
♪Lost, go ahead♪
♪Regretful, go ahead♪
♪Reluctant, go ahead♪
♪The glory♪
♪Leads the way♪
♪After the catastrophe♪
♪There will be hope♪
(Based on the novel "Swallowed Star".)
(Previously on Swallowed Star)
(Oh, no. The iron dragon's gone mad.)
(I didn't expect there's another
master hiding in the shadows.)
(He must be)
(as strong as an
intermediate God of War.)
(I'll kill him myself sooner or later.)
(What's in your bag?)
(Now you are begging for mercy.)
(Do it.)
(But the same trick won't work on me!)
(You're a Spirit Master!)
(Luo Feng, I must kill you!)
(Ah!)
=Episode 18=
(X251 02 user is dead)
(Wei.)
Connecting two bodyguards of Wei's.
(X251 02 user is dead)
Open. Search the warriors.
Mr. Li Yao.
Find the coordinate of my son, Li Wei.
And search for the location
of the God of War nearby.
OK.
There is no God of War near Li Wei.
Search for the advanced
senior warriors then.
(Searching for God of War)
Mr. Li Yao, we can search for
God of War via the sharing
system of the Palace of Gods.
But for lower level warriors,
S-level authorization from
the alliance is required.
Damn!
Yao.
I give S-level authorization on behalf
of the Paulinus Clan of the HR alliance.
Search now!
Yes.
Maybe something is wrong with
the signal. Wei might be alright.
Do you remember Wang Tong and Li Kan
who teamed up with us?
They're in city 003.
I'll ask them for a favor
and let them check the scene.
When the search results come,
let's meet there.
OK.
(Though I was in self-defense,)
(I can't prove myself innocent.)
(Once Li Wei's family uses
satellite to probe,)
(I'd be in trouble.)
(I have to stay as far away
from the scene as possible.)
(They are flying towards city 003.)
(Could it be...)
(WARNING LINE DO NOT CROSS)
I'm sorry for the gaffe.
We used to a team.
Never mind.
Did you find anything?
When we arrived,
your son was bitten up by the monsters.
But
someone killed the other three.
Looks like the murderer
is a Spirit Master.
And the murderer
might have set all this up.
I have people search for
the warriors nearby.
There are four advanced senior warriors,
21 intermediate senior warriors,
58 primary senior warriors,
and 426 soldiers.
But I don't think any of them can kill
four senior warriors.
Mr. Li Yao, we got the conclusion.
The one from Huya Squad
might get killed
by the giant sword in the scene.
There may be internal
strife among them.
The two bodyguards
were killed by a single blow.
And master Li Wei
might have been killed by monsters
as no one was there to protect him.
The murderer may be the one
who plotted against Huya Squad.
Unfortunately, the dead
cannot give witness.
But why did they have internal strife?
According to forensic experts,
they didn't take hallucinogenic drugs
before they died.
So it wasn't internal factors.
For external factors,
maybe the murderer incited.
Or they were fighting
for some resources.
Let's put this aside. The point is
how the murderer killed tow
advanced senior warriors.
First,
the murderer is as strong as a God
of War, but hid his strength.
So his rating is low.
Second, the murderer is a Spirit Master,
and lower than an intermediate
senior warrior.
No matter who killed my son,
I will never let him go!
Release the news of Wei's death.
Let every warrior know
that I, Venina Paulinus,
am offering a reward of 100 billion.
100 billion.
Anyone who finds out the murderer
will have the money.
I'm sure the murderer
has friends and family!
As long as he tells people about it,
his relatives and friends might tell us
just to get a big sum of money.
Right.
Let him live in fear of
betrayal all day long!
(Recently, nine warriors have
been killed in city 003.)
(According to the HR Alliance,)
(one of the dead was an important member
of the Paulinus Clan.)
(Members of Jiangnan base city under
HR Alliance have investigated the scene.)
(Initial findings suggest
that it was a homicide.)
(It is speculated that the killer might
be a God of War or a Spirit Master.)
(Li Yao and his wife of
the Paulinus Clan offered)
(Breaking news)
(a reward of 100 billion for clues.)
(The amount is close to the total revenue
of the whole HR Alliance.)
(It is the highest reward
since the Great Nirvana.)
We just got back, and they have
already issued the high rewards.
She is the sister of the
head of the Paulinus Clan.
Warriors below God of War
can't make a tenth of it
in their lifetime,
let alone ordinary people.
Even I want to have a try.
You organize offline meetings
for the reward?
Yeah, the murderer must be something.
That's why we need more people.
I'm leaving.
Wan Dong, 100 billion!
Do you have to be hard on money?
When did you become a Huya Squad?
The young master saw talented
warriors as enemy.
He had killed many of them.
He deserved it. Go by yourself.
You!
(100 billion! HR Alliance is
really influential.)
(They made it broadcast on Hanxia TV.)
Enter the House of the Extreme,
War of God's Forum.
=Swallowed Star=
I must kill you!
(War of God's Forum)
(New posts.)
(High reward, 100 billion)
(They spend so much money to find me.)
(Even I want to report myself.)
(Though I didn't kill Li Wei myself.)
(I'm afraid Mr. and Mrs. Li will still
blame me for his death.)
(They don't have enough clues now,)
(but)
(the reward points out that
the killer might be a Spirit Master.)
(If Captain and others see it,)
(they will think of me.)
(Gao Feng)
(Why does Captain call me at this time?)
What's up, Captain?
Luo Feng, when will you
return to the base city?
Everybody's back.
We will report on the
results of this operation.
We are waiting for you.
I'm good. I'll be back soon.
You're not in any danger when you
acted alone, are you?
No. Captain, you forgot
I... I can get out of danger quickly.
I do remember. I'm just worried.
(100 billion high reward, who will team up with me?)
(Your powers can be unleashed beyond walls.)
(Is the killer a God of War or a Spirit Master?)
(But people here envy you.)
Captain, you...
Take care! If you're in trouble,
don't forget about your brothers
in Fire Hammer Team.
Thank you, Captain.
(Maybe I shouldn't doubt them.)
(But in my heart, I just can't get rid
of the pressure brought by the reward.)
(I can't think about it any more.)
(Xu Xin)
(Luo Feng)
Luo Feng, have you returned
to Jiangnan base city?
I'm on a mission myself today,
so depressed.
So...
You're alone in the wilderness?
There are no monsters
near me. It's safe.
Forget about me. How are
you at school recently?
At present, I am
doing researches in the laboratory.
Thanks to the virus samples collected
in the wilderness last time,
we made many breakthroughs.
(If I'm accused of
murdering in the future,)
(maybe I can't talk to her anymore.)
(But now, I feel more
peaceful than ever.)
(Now I can practice sabre
without any distractions.)
(Nine Thundering Sabre Level 3, done!)
(The third level gives me 2.8 times
of explosive power.)
(Now, you will enjoy it.)
(I'll go back to the base
city tomorrow morning.)
(To deal with the reward,)
(I need to plan carefully from now on.)
(Firstly, about Li Wei, Spirit Master,)
(and everything that
happened in city 003,)
(I won't tell anyone,)
(including parents and Hua.)
(Second, go to the Extreme
Martial Club headquarters.)
(Hand over the weapons and outfits
gathering from the iron dragon's lair,)
(so their families can
claim them.)
(Then I'll report the results
of Fire Hammer Team's operation,)
(update my personal data,)
(upgrade my official level
to primary senior warrior)
(Senior warrior Primary)
(and get my bonus.)
(If I don't update my
personal information,)
(as time goes by,
it may look suspicious.)
(Third,)
(use the bonus
to buy Nine Thundering Sabre Level 4.)
(If I improve my personal strength,)
(the threat of the reward
will be smaller to me.)
(Finally, I'll make
a decision on the egg.)
(Based on the information I got,)
(I found an institution in Jingdu
base city that fits the description.)
(But the dragon egg is
too ostentatious,)
(I might expose myself
if I give it to them directly.)
(I'll give the egg to them
through the black market.)
(Dragon egg of the iron dragon. Do you want it?)
(The thing is how to negotiate in the black market.)
(Looks like another long
journey is waiting for me.)
(Mr. Luo Hua, I'm sorry, but please
understand we are parents.)
(We only have one daughter,
we want you to leave her.)
(This is the political center of
the whole Hanxia state,)
(which occupies the largest land)
(with the most population,)
(sure enough, is extraordinary.)
(Will Palace Hotel)
(Mom)
Hello.
Feng, something happened!
Hua, Hua, something happened to him!
(Li Yao, advanced God of War,
member of the HR Alliance.)
(Known as "vulture". He and his wife Venina
are known as "Vulture Scorpion")
(Suspicious and headstrong,
he makes people palpitate with his evil spirits .)
(Venina Paulinus, advanced God of War,
comes from one of the nine core clans of the HR Alliance.)
(She is the younger sister of the head
of the Paulinus Clan,)
and the chief executive officer
of the HR Alliance in Hanxia District.)
(Known as "poisonous scorpion",
insidious and vicious,)
(she would seek revenge
for the smallest grievance.)
♪When the city is shadowed in grey♪
♪Blood is running like blazing sunray♪
♪Law of the jungle is for the old days♪
♪Watch who is more qualified♪
♪To stop explosion by the last sight♪
♪To welcome the outer space with flame♪
♪While meteorite
tugging with atmosphere♪
♪Nirvana comes right away♪
♪War machine built with flesh and bone♪
♪Faith turned into powerful pulse♪
♪Let the heart and the planet♪
♪Never fall♪
♪To shuttle through smoke and ash♪
♪To rise from the ruins♪
♪Knocked down but never back out♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with fire♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
♪Breaking through the heavens♪
♪Roaring heard by the universe♪
♪Roaring♪
♪Struggling♪
♪Light up the night sky with blood♪
♪Watch the stars getting swallowed♪
♪Fire it up!♪
(Next episode)
(Could it be an azure dragon's egg?)
(It'd be bad if it was the bait
Li Wei's parents secretly left behind.)
(I'd rather kill a thousand mistakenly
than let one go!)
(Are you Luo Feng?)
(I'll never fall in love in my life.
I don't deserve it.)
(The enemy of this damn team
dared kill my son!)
(Yes, Luo Feng.)
(Hua can't stand it, and...)