It's my first high-school life.
The second semester was about to end.
I'm all fired-up!
Hagakure, don't you feel cold?
It's freezing out here!
Everyone's costume has changed a lot
since we first came to U.A. High.
Ida, that suit looks toasty.
I can't believe you survived the summer in it.
Kacchan's suit looks different too.
Say it to my face!
Hey...
You seem to be slacking off.
Bring it on, Class A!
Let's settle the score today!
CLASS A VS CLASS B
The Hero Course of U.A. High.
Class A and Class B...
will soon have their joint training.
Shinso who wants to transfer to Hero Course
has joined this battle.
With that, the first battle began.
Class A soon ran into a predicament.
♪When we are stranded on the same spot,
make our heart beat♪
MY HERO ACADEMIA
♪Rather than searching for an answer
in this world full of uncertainties♪
♪I want to live even though
my constant doubts are a waste of time♪
♪Take off the unseeable armor and feel the wind♪
♪I make my effort sound worthless
as a way to hide myself♪
♪The No.1 who came out of nowhere
is pointing at the endless sky♪
♪It's our desire to see the view
from greater height and distance♪
♪Ignite the heart of unquenchable desire♪
♪Ignite the path to our future,
burn the illusions to ashes♪
BEFORE THE FIRST BATTLE
In case some of you didn't know,
I'll explain to you how my Quirk,
"Brainwashing" works.
First of all, I must focus on one single target.
I must have the thought
of controlling the target.
With that as a foundation,
as soon as the target talks to me,
I can seize control of them.
They will move as I order.
There are different degrees of brainwashing.
But the target can break free
after taking damage.
I haven't tried this before,
but brainwashing multiple targets is impossible.
I'll get distracted.
Even so, your Quirk is still very potent.
"HITOSHI SHINSO, QUIRK: BRAINWASHING"
However,
I can't target under my control speak.
Orders that require thinking won't work either.
I can show my target the name "Tsuyu Asui".
I order the target to copy that name.
"WHAT IS THE FROG GIRL'S NAME?"
But I can't ask my target...
"PLEASE WRITE DOWN HER NAME."
to use that name as an answer.
"DENKI KAMINARI, QUIRK: ELECTRIFICATION"
This is common for heroes,
but we are doomed if the weakness
of our Quirks are known.
They can just ignore your voice.
Which is why I need this device.
It works like a vocal cord.
This mask can mimic different voices.
The Persona Chord.
My Quirk won't work through
microphones or speakers.
So it must be your own voice.
Yes.
The countless plates in this mask
can shift and resonate...
to change my voice and send it out
as a different voice.
TSUYU ASUI, QUIRK: FROG
Which means...
That means...
it's a voice changer.
"EIJIRO KIRISHIMA, QUIRK: HARDENING"
That is awesome! You have the strongest Quirk!
The first battle begins!
The battle has begun.
We don't have a strategy yet.
I guess we'll have to improvise.
How strong can this device be?
"JUROTA SHISHIDA"
That's up to me!
Nice!
Send him flying, Shishida!
You can count on me!
"KOSEI TSUBURABA, QUIRK: SOLID AIR"
That was my voice...
Thank you for saving me!
He copied my voice and took control of Shishida!
That guy...
MAKE IT HAPPEN, SHINSO!
Before he wakes up...
You're too slow!
Air Prison!
Wake up, Shishida.
Wake up!
Shinso from General Education.
Damage and impact can break his brainwashing.
Shiozaki told me about this Quirk.
I didn't know he could change his voice.
You fool! Stop!
If you touch me,
you get shocked!
That hurts...
I electrocuted him
how is he still standing?
Shishida!
I got you!
Nice!
Take him to the prison, Tsuyu!
Seriously?
You should have passed out!
Shishida from Class B.
"RIKIDO SATO, QUIRK: SUGAR RUSH"
Such incredible strength.
"OCHACCO URARAKA, QUIRK: ZERO GRAVITY"
Tsuyu...
Don't worry.
"IZUKU MIDORIYA, QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL"
Class A...
can count on him!
Koda!
That air wall can't be very durable.
It's surprisingly tough!
Well...
I'll strike again!
"KOJI KODA, QUIRK: ANIVOICE"
Kirishima...
I'll send him to the prison.
OK!
You shall not pass!
My tiny friends,
lend me your strength!
Red Gauntlet!
I'm in human form again!
Jurota Shishida, Quirk: Beast.
Activating this Quirk will
make him increase in size.
When deactivated,
his body goes back to normal size.
Beast form once again!
The only who can match my strength
is probably Kirishima.
In that case...
That direction...
Hey, wait!
"IBARA SHIOZAKI, QUIRK: VINES"
A lost lamb descends from the heavens.
"TENYA IDA, QUIRK: ENGINE"
They got Kirishima!
Even so,
Asui got Tsuburaba as well.
"SHOTO TODOROKI, QUIRK: HALF-COLD HALF-HOT"
The score is now even.
KATSUKI BAKUGO, QUIRK: EXPLOSION
It's far from even.
I can't speak.
He's too strong!
I knew it!
But Koda is still quite a handful to deal with.
Carrying him during a battle
puts me at a disadvantage.
It's time to retreat.
I'll finish this match with life advantage!
HIRYU RIN
That 2:1 for us.
Sorry, Koda.
They got me, however...
She wrapped me with her tongue!
This barrier is much harder than
what we saw on the sports day!
Class B is really strong.
This must be the fruition of
their intensive Quirk training!
Is that right?
Both teams have already started undermining
their opponents' combat strength!
Shishida and Tsuburaba did a great job!
Both teams have equal number of combatants.
But Class B seems to be holding up
much better with their morale!
"PRO HERO VLAD KING, QUIRK: BLOOD CONTROL"
My students' ferocious attacks...
might finally bring Class A to its knees!
"NEITO MONOMA, QUIRK: COPY"
That's our teacher Vlad King!
"WE'RE AGAINST BIAS BROADCAST"
Vlad King,
"VLAD KING, WE WANT A FAIR BROADCAST"
don't be so biased!
"HANTA SERO, QUIRK: TAPE"
Shishida is too strong. He's a threat.
His nose can sense anything.
"PRO HERO SHOTA AIZAWA, QUIRK: ERASURE"
Shinso...
It's undeniable that he lacks experience.
Judging by the way he used the binding,
he only had them made
after knowing the situation.
It seems like he still lacks
the speed for real combat.
To utilize Shinso's strong point...
What now, Tsuyu?
We'll lose at this rate.
It took us some time to
understand Shinso's Quirk.
They caught us off-guard.
I should have acted faster...
with my binding.
Sorry...
We should apologize.
We let you fight them head-on.
It's my fault for coming up with that strategy.
Speaking of which,
injury is very common in combat training.
Thankfully, you acted fast.
I was saved thanks to you.
Thank you for saving my neck.
I know you're not interested
in becoming our friend,
but I like you a lot.
You really do want to become a hero.
It's nothing.
We should figure out our next plan.
I have an idea.
Kaminari, look at the navigator.
Navigator?
You used me as a decoy to initiate the attack.
Such sinful action.
You deserve flogging.
Flogging?
But I pulled off a great feat.
We only need to catch three from Class A
to win this battle.
We know about Shinso's voice changer.
If we can catch him,
we can still secure the victory
by ignoring Kaminari.
Shinso...
Losing Tsuburaba took a toll on our ranks.
This is...
What is it, Shishida?
I don't know how this is happening.
But there is no doubt about it.
I can sense three Asui coming this way.
Three Asui?
Is this their strategy
against your sense of smell?
In that case,
I should teach them a lesson.
Your plan...
will only lead to foulness.
HITOSHI SHINSO, QUIRK: BRAINWASHING
TAKING CONTROL OF ANYONE WHO REPLIES HIM
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH
BIRTHDAY: JULY 1ST, HEIGHT: 177CM
BLOOD TYPE: AB
FAVOURITE ANIMAL: CAT
DENKI KAMINARI, QUIRK: ELECTRIFICATION
RELEASING ELECTRICAL CURRENT
FOR ATTACK OR RECON
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH CLASS 1-A
BIRTHDAY: 29TH JUNE, HEIGHT: 168CM
BLOOD TYPE: O
FAVOURITE FOOD: BURGER
I can sense three Asui coming this way.
What is Shishida talking about?
Tsuyu is not like Ectoplasm.
They can't be her clones.
"MINORU MINETA, QUIRK: POP OFF"
Midoriya, that's...
Yes, it is.
Tsuyu told us about it,
but we've never seen her use it before.
I'll tell you more about my Quirk.
I can jump far and stick to walls.
I can also stretch my tongue.
It can reach over 20 meters away.
I can take out my stomach to wash it,
I can also secret venomous slime.
But the slime will only paralyze the enemies.
Venomous slime!
She covered both of them with her slime
to mask their scents!
We almost forgot her ability.
I bet Class B didn't see this coming.
Kaminari, check your navigator.
Navigator?
I put a tracker on Shishida when I attacked.
"MY ADORABLE BABY ACADEMIA"
You can stick the tracker to any surfaces.
You can also use the visor
to locate your target.
You actually prepared for everything, Tsuyu.
You're awesome.
You're amazing for not noticing it.
Shishida can pinpoint our location.
My nose can sense anything!
It's best to assume
he has our location at all times.
We'll use that to our advantage.
We all smell like Tsuyu.
He can't tell who we are unless
he sees it in person!
He hasn't noticed the tracker yet.
There is no sudden movement either.
We need to deal with his other teammates.
We don't know where they are.
Rather than searching for them,
we should take down Shishida while we can.
His nose and strength are too powerful.
Tsuyu, how are you holding up?
He sent your flying just now.
I managed to avoid any serious injury.
But I won't hold up for long
if we face him head-on.
In the name of Vine,
punish the treacherous evildoers!
Via Dolorosa!
Beast of Revelation, reveal their locations!
Ten o'clock! Twelve o'clock! And two o'clock!
They are splitting up and closing in!
And stop calling me the Beast of Revelation!
I am Gevaudan!
They are closing in.
So they know where we are.
Do they have a scouting Quirk we don't know?
Hey, Beast of Revelation,
there's something stuck on you.
This came from Kaminari.
I got one.
I'll drag you out!
We don't know who that is.
Find cover, Shishida!
If it's Kaminari...
Yes, you got it right!
But you chose the wrong target!
All of you are here,
start holding hands and get electrocuted!
Crucifixion.
What?
Faith's Shield!
I sealed off his electricity
with layers of vines.
I can even use this as a shield.
It's a flawless execution.
I tricked you.
As long as the navigator is within 10 meters,
my electricity...
can form a straight beam!
Give me a break!
That was so close!
Hiryu Rin.
Quirk: Scales.
He can form hard scales with his body.
He can shoot them as projectiles
or wear them as armor.
Reset the vines now!
Yes. Shishida, give me their location.
That wasn't my voice!
It's Shinso's voice changer!
Come on, look at those vines!
Is Shiozaki still with them?
It's over if she catches us. Let's fall back.
No, I have an idea.
Let her catch me.
Let her catch you?
They are wary of me.
That means, I'm a real pain in their necks.
On the sports day,
she put up a huge pile of vines
to stop my current.
If I annoy her enough,
the vines will thin out.
Then, Shinso and Tsuyu, it's your opening.
Come on.
I never underestimated Kaminari,
but his experience in combat
makes a difference.
So this is the Hero Course's strength.
We have no idea where the voice came from.
He used the environment for reflection of sound.
Shishida, where are they?
Is someone there?
Hey, talk to me!
Just look at my mouth and you'll be safe!
I need to wake up Shiozaki.
Your scale shots won't hit her!
Asui!
She is really agile.
Shishida, it's Asui!
He is not listening...
Judging by the scent, I can tell
Tsuyu is right over there.
That means,
this scent here came from Shinso!
Shinso!
You said you were falling behind.
But you're a terrifying foe.
You're a real threat!
Not bad.
I won't fall for the same trick!
Eraser Head's Binding Cloth!
Capturing Cloth!
I see...
However...
Villains won't be defeated so easily...
with your puny trick!
I'm right behind you!
Enough!
I'm behind you, Beast!
You can't brainwash me again!
Beast?
Get out of the way!
Sorry for that.
Yeah!
A stunning performance!
Shinso, that was too close.
How is this match balanced?
No, Asui and Kaminari figured out a plan...
and put Shinso's Quirk to good use.
This is so cool.
Asui's slime masked their scents.
That confused Shishida's nose.
Then he used the voice changer
to bait their opponents,
stopping them from communicating.
Under the right circumstances,
his very presence can dominate the field!
Brainwashing...
This Quirk is far more
formidable than I thought.
With his new support device and capturing cloth,
he's totally different from the person
I met on the sports day.
I guess he had been secretly training.
It can't be helped, I want to be a hero.
To realize our dream...
To become a true hero...
WELCOME
Shiozaki! Shiozaki!
Why am I inside the prison?
I was brainwashed?
Lord!
Please forgive my foolishness!
Shiozaki! Shiozaki!
I'm already falling too far behind.
Sorry, but I'll give it my best.
Forget it. You can't catch up to us.
Shinso, you're already too strong.
I have a long way to go.
I will need guidance.
I will become a pro hero with my own strength.
CLASS A WON!
The victory of the first battle...
goes to Class A and Shinso!
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪I hope my destination♪
♪Is where we shall meet again♪
♪I'm always seeing the world through your eyes♪
♪Tears are somehow falling down my cheeks♪
♪I hate it when you say it's all right♪
"♪Your gentle whisper turned into
an unsettling silence♪"
♪I want to believe the clouded sky before us♪
♪Our longing is the very thing that breaks us♪
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪But why? I'm already covered in wounds♪
♪Why must I search for the answer♪
♪Goodbye, we will meet again♪
♪I hope you would still be the same♪
♪I hope that the memories we share♪
♪Would once again bank up♪
♪So I could see you again♪
NEXT EPISODE
The second battle between Class A and Class B
is about to begin.
Class B learns from their mistake
in the first battle.
They came up with a more refined tactic
with Kendo as their focus.
Tokoyami's Dark Shadow is at a disadvantage,
can Class A overcome their predicament?
Operation New Improved Moves!
We'll finally see Tokoyami's new move!
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!