1ST BATTLE
Hero Course of U.A. High.
Class A and Class B...
are in a joint training battle.
In the first battle,
Shinso's Quirk successfully disrupted
the coordination of Class B.
The battle ended with Class A victorious.
♪When we are stranded on the same spot,
make our heart beat♪
MY HERO ACADEMIA
♪Rather than searching for an answer
in this world full of uncertainties♪
♪I want to live even though
my constant doubts are a waste of time♪
♪Take off the unseeable armor and feel the wind♪
♪I make my effort sound worthless
as a way to hide myself♪
♪The No.1 who came out of nowhere
is pointing at the endless sky♪
♪It's our desire to see the view
from greater height and distance♪
♪Ignite the heart of unquenchable desire♪
♪Ignite the path to our future,
burn the illusions to ashes♪
"SHOTA AIZAWA, QUIRK: ERASURE"
What have you learned from the first battle?
If the opponents are avoiding a fight with me,
my Quirk is basically useless in the battle.
If that were a real battle with villains,
Shiozaki would have
"EIJIRO KIRISHIMA, QUIRK: HARDENING"
finished me off instantly.
"KOJI KODA, QUIRK: ANIVOICE"
I must learn how to order the insects
with greater precision.
"DENKI KAMINARI, QUIRK: ELECTRIFICATION"
I did a great job, didn't I?
I bet you are all awestruck, but that's OK!
I know it's hard to control the urge
to fall in love with me.
No sweat!
"TSUYU ASUI, QUIRK: FROG"
I lost Koda and Kirishima...
when the battle began.
I wanted to win without losing any teammates.
But I messed up so badly.
The binding cloth.
Kero?
I failed to put the tool Mr. Aizawa gave me
to good use.
"HITOSHI SHINSO, QUIRK: BRAINWASH"
That was unacceptable.
It wouldn't be so challenging
if it were easy to use.
It took me six years to
finally master this tool.
Don't be sorry, just be better.
Yes.
"YUGA AOYAMA, QUIRK: NAVAL LASER"
The two who went to internship...
is very strict with themselves.
"HANTA SERO, QUIRK: TAPE"
That is only natural.
Shie Hasaikai, wasn't it?
I heard it was an impossible battle to win.
They actually pulled through that fight.
Even if this is only a training battle,
their attitude and motivation
are undoubtedly different.
Compared to that...
Jammingway's outstanding performance
was a genuine surprise.
Listen up!
Kirishima, you must learn how to bait
your opponent into battling you head-on.
Yes.
Koda, it's as you said earlier,
you need more precision
in controlling the animals.
Aside from a direct attack,
you must learn to take them by surprise.
Kaminari, you got too complacent at first!
Does this mean you can't do well
unless you lose your teammates?
Oh...
Asui.
Remember not to dwell on mistakes.
Instead, learn to recover from it quickly.
Kero!
Reflect on your mistake and utilize the lesson
for future training.
That's all!
Yes!
They won, but came to realize
their lack of experience.
But they are not disheartened.
They are already
figuring out ways to improve for
the upcoming battles.
"MIDNIGHT, QUIRK: SOMNAMBULIST"
This is inspiring!
Shinso's freshness is awesome!
"ALL MIGHT, QUIRK: ONE FOR ALL"
Hey, you...
VLAD KING, QUIRK: BLOOD CONTROL
I'm pretty sure you are well aware of...
why you failed.
"JUROTA SHISHIDA, QUIRK: BEAST"
Whether you played to Shishida's strength,
"IBARA SHIOZAKI, QUIRK: VINES"
or played to Shiozaki's strength,
had you coordinated better,
you would have won easily!
Your glare is scaring us, Vlad King.
"NEITO MONOMA, QUIRK: COPY"
Shiozaki is too honest,
Shishida, expecting her to lie was you failed.
Monoma...
It's true we allowed the opponents
too much time to get ready.
Sorry, Shiozaki.
May the inferno incinerate you.
However,
that was a great battle you put on.
I couldn't wait to fight by his side.
Hey, Shinso!
Let's compose a strategy that will
annihilate Class A and their pride!
We'll make them shut up for good!
"MINORU MINETA, QUIRK: POP OFF"
We'll instill despair into all of their hearts!
-He is so excited by himself.
-They will kneel before Class B and surrender!
We should come up with a strategy too.
Let's list out the ideas and tactics we have.
OK.
Let's design a combo, like an ultimate move!
We should brainstorm together.
Todoroki should be our main offensive strength.
Me?
That's a sound plan.
Bakugo, we should discuss our strategy as well.
"KATSUKI BAKUGO, QUIRK: EXPLOSION"
You! Don't you dare slow me down!
He's loud as ever.
"OCHACCO URARAKA, QUIRK: ZERO GRAVITY"
We'll face Shinso in the fifth battle.
"MINA ASHIDO, QUIRK: ACID"
His voice is a threat to us all.
Sticky Acid Flying Kick!
What kind of ultimate move is that?
The field is full of obstacles,
making it easy to hide.
Which means I can search more easily.
You can count on me.
I'll come up with the plan!
I'll come up with a plan for my fight!
"MASHIRAO OJIRO, QUIRK: TAIL"
Ida can be our trump card during an emergency.
"TENYA IDA, QUIRK: ENGINE"
But before that,
I must tell you about my Recipro moves.
Instant Kill Swimming Orb!
What kind of an attack is that?
-I'll inject my acid into your grape!
-Injured combatants, proceed to the infirmary.
-Then we'll toss it at them!
-Puny humans can't change their damaged parts.
As if!
This is it!
The younglings' spring of freshness!
But it's winter right now.
It's already the end of the year.
Everyone is doing their best to develop
their Quirks and ultimate moves.
Young Midoriya has learned the ways
to use One For All.
He can use Shoot Style and Air Force
for his attacks.
He's earned his provisional license,
he's battled the villains of Shie Hasaikai.
And the school festival as well.
With every event and obstacle
that came to pass, he grows stronger.
This is his chance to test
his strength against others'.
He will learn what his place is
as of now.
This training will serve as a lesson
that cover all aspects.
All Might.
How as Shinso's performance?
Not bad.
He doesn't falter at all.
The fact it's hard for him
to accept his defeat deserves a compliment.
This is the entrance exam for him
to transfer to Hero Course.
I believe he will give his best
for the next battle.
Vlad, commence the next battle.
Well...
Second battle,
get ready!
2ND BATTLE
OPERATION NEW IMPROVED MOVES!
Yaoyorozu.
What is it, Kendo?
Why didn't you join the pageant contest
during the school festival?
I thought you would join for sure.
"MOMO YAOYOROZU, QUIRK: CREATION"
That was because Mr. Aizawa...
didn't tell me about the contest.
We were too busy practicing
our band performance too.
Perhaps Mr. Aizawa didn't
think I needed to participate.
ITSUKA KENDO, QUIRK: BIG FIST
After we filmed the advertisement
during that workplace training,
we've always been seen as a pair.
This must be the "pair pushing".
Pair pushing?
Pair pushing means
everyone likes it no matter what.
"TORU HAGAKURE, QUIRK: INVISIBILITY"
During the school festival,
people kept saying your names together.
"Yaoyorozu-Kendo!"
That did happen.
Idol worshiping.
How should I put it?
Yaoyorozu has the better Quirk and grades.
But people are comparing me with her.
That really gets on my nerve.
I've personally been looking forward
to fight you.
I humbly...
accept your challenge.
Tokoyami.
You and I...
are the same.
Shihai Kuroiro.
Your Quirk is Darkness,
you can move freely in dark objects, am I right?
Our rivalry is destined.
I see. You can read the abyss as well.
Stay in eternal darkness.
They really don't shine at all.
Both teams are ready.
Well then...
All the best, Team Kendo!
Second battle, start!
"WE'RE AGAINST THE BIAS BROADCAST!"
Please stop this bias broadcast!
Stop it!
Very well, let's go!
Yeah!
What is Kendo's role in Class B?
Kendo is amazing!
You're speaking too loud!
"TETSUTETSU TETSUTETSU, QUIRK: STEEL"
After all, she is our class rep!
Her mind works fast and she keeps calm
when she makes judgments!
She has the courage to step forward
when time calls for it!
Her cheerful demeanor brings our class together!
Without her,
the entire Class B would have
sided with Monoma!
Hey, don't say that so loudly.
The Big Sis of Class B!
That's right, it's Itsuka Kendo!
Can Yaoyorozu's operation...
"SHOTO TODOROKI, QUIRK: HALF COLD HALF HOT"
be executed successfully in this battle?
What operation?
Please scout ahead for us,
Tokoyami.
Roger.
Dark Shadow.
Yeah!
Report back as soon as you spot the enemies.
Leave it to me!
I basically know all about their Quirks.
But I have no idea what new moves
they have come up with.
That might lead to our defeat.
Which is why...
we'll have to see how it goes first.
Dark Shadow seems to have found our enemies.
It's right under that chimney.
Let's head over there.
You're going to see anything!
I'll deal with the weak ones first!
I'm counting on you,
Kuroiro!
I'll be right back.
Dark Shadow went really far.
Did you level up during your internship?
That's hard to tell.
The further Dark Shadow goes,
the harder it is to maintain its form.
He's back.
Everyone, scatter!
Tokoyami!
What is going on?
Fumikage!
We fell for their trap!
What's going on with Dark Shadow?
Did it go berserk?
No.
The field is bright enough for Tokoyami
to keep Dark Shadow under control.
Is something else controlling Dark Shadow?
It's must the Quirk's of someone from Class B!
Wait!
Hagakure, release your beam!
Yes!
Warp Refraction!
Say "Cheese!"
Return, Dark Shadow!
Kuroiro came out from Dark Shadow!
He disappeared!
He merged with the shadow.
That's Kuroiro's Quirk.
Class B, Shihai Kuroiro.
Quirk: Darkness.
He can merge with darkness,
and even move the object upon possession,
but only if the object is movable.
Fumikage Tokoyami.
I will take you out.
You and I are destined to be rivals.
I see, my rival.
Very well!
I will use the move I invented
when I worked with Hawks,
Dark Fallen Angel.
Dark Fallen Angel?
Yes.
Dark Fallen Angel.
FUMIKAGE TOKOYAMI, QUIRK: DARK SHADOW
HE MANIFESTS A SHADOW INSIDE HIS BODY
THAT IS FLEXIBLE AND FIGHT HIS ENEMIES
AFFILIATION: U.A. HIGH SCHOOL CLASS 1-A,
BIRTHDAY: OCTOBER 30TH
HEIGHT: 158CM, BLOOD TYPE: AB
FAVORITE FOOD: APPLE
HAWKS, QUIRK: FIERCE WINGS
ABLE TO MANIPULATE HIS FEATHERS
SHOOT THEM AS PROJECTILES
PRO HERO, BIRTHDAY: DECEMBER 28TH
HEIGHT 172CM
FAVORITE FOOD: CHICKEN
A FEW MONTHS AGO IN KYUSHU
He always settles everything on his own.
These are the real deal, real diamonds!
These should fetch me at least 300 million!
"HAWKS, QUIRK: FIERCE WINGS"
I got you.
Hawks!
You are too slow for me.
There is a brawl fight in the bar at Kante.
I have to go there next.
I'll leave the cleaning up to you.
Tsukuyomi.
I have to deal with this criminal.
Hawks is simply too fast.
This is the most efficient way to operate.
I'll go after him.
Tsukuyomi!
He sure is full of spirit.
It was the first time Hawks took part in
nominating a student.
I was always running after him during
the workplace training,
constantly cleaning up after
he had completed the job.
That raised a question for me.
If the damages spread
while my sidekicks were catching up,
wouldn't that be unacceptable?
But...
why did you nominate me?
Because we're both birds.
You're joking, right?
No, there's a little truth in that.
I need some information from those
in Class 1-A.
It's about the thugs from League of Villains
that attacked your class.
Since I've been looking for information,
I should get it from an outstanding student
who can catch up to me.
So I chose the bird guy who has...
a fairly high ranking
during the sports festival.
I need to know more about the USJ incident.
What can you tell me?
When I was about to tell him
the details about the USJ attack,
the unwillingness almost took over me.
I'm not a pigeon.
The workplace training ended
with me learning nothing at all.
How was your time in Kyushu?
Nothing special.
Nothing at all.
For my internship,
he accepted me once again.
Much had happened between the time...
of my workplace training and internship.
He must be after more information,
Hawks.
Don't look down on me, the No.3 Hero..
No.
He's the No.2 Hero now.
Tsukuyomi is so determined.
He has a bright future ahead.
Great work today.
Tokoyami, may I have a word with you?
What is it you want this time?
I'm not going to ask questions.
Hawks!
We are flying like the wind!
You've never learned how to fly?
I'd say 20% of my reason for choosing you
was because we're both birds,
50% because I wanted to know more
about the League of Villains,
and the rest was because
you're wasting your time.
The sky is great.
You can see everything from above.
What do you mean I was wasting my time?
It's a sound plan to strengthen your skill
in close-quarter combat.
But never forget to develop
what you're already good at.
You can move more freely.
I never wanted to be a mentor.
But since we're both birds,
I guess it must be fate.
You belong in the sky if you can fly.
Don't limit yourself to the ground.
I will use the move I invented
when I worked with Hawks,
Dark Fallen Angel.
Dark Fallen Angel?
That sounds fun,
let's see what you got!
He is moving in the shadows!
I'd never expected them
to launch a solo assault.
It's the same situation as the first battle.
It's time to improvise.
But the place is full of pipelines.
There is no way to tell his location.
Tokoyami, are you all right?
Yeah.
Fumikage Tokoyami.
I'll take you out.
I'm his target.
I bet that's what you think, Class A.
Our rivalry is destined.
I started psychological warfare
before the battle even began.
I made them think Tokoyami was my target.
They are certain of it, but they are wrong.
Scheming Hero,Vantadark,
that's how I roll!
Aoyama!
Help!
His scheme...
This is despicable.
Repent with the purest intent.
With my speed...
and the complex layout of this arena,
Dark Shadow and its master
are connected, which makes it hard
to navigate this place.
In that case,
they will never catch up to me!
Is that so?
Dark Shadow!
Dark Fallen Angel!
He is flying!
Tokoyami...
That is his new move!
How can he fly?
The principle is simple.
Dark Shadow is always floating in the air.
It can carry Tokoyami as it moves around!
Thanks to the mantle,
sunlight is blocked out, allowing it
stay active even longer!
The way Dark Shadow carries him
also allows for the use of his hands!
Dark Shadow is floating!
Everyone takes that feature for granted
and overlooks its potential!
It's simple yet hard to imagine!
Awesome! You're awesome, Tokoyami!
But never forget to develop
what you're already good at.
Hawks, you have my thanks.
I'll take it up a notch!
Twinkling Laser Date!
Plan A failed.
Aoyama, use your naval laser!
Tokoyami, keep flying.
Dark Shadow, grab the jacket!
All right!
I just need to disrupt the shadows!
Naval Buffet!
I found him Hagakure!
Yes, I'll get him this time!
That's as far as you can get.
There is nowhere to run.
We didn't expect you to operate solo.
But every unexpected outcome...
is already within my expectation!
You saw this coming.
Stop right there!
Surrender!
Mushrooms!
I knew it.
Kendo anticipated your expectations!
Just as Kendo foresaw.
If I see the light,
that means Kuroiro's plan A failed.
Plan B commences.
You'll all be covered in mushrooms.
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪I hope my destination♪
♪Is where we shall meet again♪
♪I'm always seeing the world through your eyes♪
♪Tears are somehow falling down my cheeks♪
♪I hate it when you say it's all right♪
"♪Your gentle whisper turned into
an unsettling silence♪"
♪I want to believe the clouded sky before us♪
♪Our longing is the very thing that breaks us♪
♪Farewell, it's time for me to go♪
♪Hear my outcry, I must become who I am♪
♪But why? I'm already covered in wounds♪
♪Why must I search for the answer♪
♪Goodbye, we will meet again♪
♪I hope you would still be the same♪
♪I hope that the memories we share♪
♪Would once again bank up♪
♪So I could see you again♪
NEXT EPISODE
Class A launches their counter-attack.
But the wide-range attacks
from Fukidashi and Komori...
has turned the battle into their advantage.
Not only that, Yaoyorozu is isolated.
What should Class A do now?
Next episode, Foresight!
Yaoyorozu predicted the battle,
she will start creating to secure their victory!
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!